<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>national debt on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/national-debt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in national debt on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 22:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/national-debt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Interest Rates Hid True Cost of Increasing Debt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/12/low-interest-rates-hid-true-cost-of-increasing-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/12/low-interest-rates-hid-true-cost-of-increasing-debt/</guid>
      <description>House mortgage-type instrument suggested as means to pay off national debt
Guest Post By Lee A. Presser
Interest rates have been held artificially low by the Federal Reserve since 2008. This has had the effect of hiding the true cost of increasing debt. As interest rates rise back toward 4%, the U.S. Treasury will have less money to spend on discretionary governmental functions.
The FY 2015 budget is approximately $3,900,000,000,000.00. Another way to look at that number is about $12,187.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Last, Obama’s Ready to Borrow More Money from China</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/22/at-last-obamas-ready-to-borrow-more-money-from-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/22/at-last-obamas-ready-to-borrow-more-money-from-china/</guid>
      <description>The headline on July 15 was knee-slapping funny:
 Obama says he’s “ready to move**” on debt ceiling. **
 Really? The man who dug a deeper debt hole in two years than anyone else did in 8—or 15—is willing to borrow more?
Say it ain’t so.
For those who believe Obama’s some sort of deficit hawk, let’s take a quick stroll down memory.
 Obama wanted to increase the debt limit by $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simply Staggering</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/07/simply-staggering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 22:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/07/simply-staggering/</guid>
      <description>The federal budget deficit in the month of February 2011 exceeds the deficit for all of 2007 by 40 percent.
Simply staggering.
Yet Senate Democrats refuse to cut more than a paltry $6 billion. They refuse because they seem bent on collapsing the American system – the economy, the government, and the people themselves.
But at least the Obama administration stands by with its arms folded as gasoline prices skyrocket at the their fastest pace in history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2/3 Think Worst Is Yet to Come for USA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/11/23-think-worst-is-yet-to-come-for-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 03:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/11/23-think-worst-is-yet-to-come-for-usa/</guid>
      <description>The Wall Street Journal headline is grim:
   Grim Voter Mood Turns Grimmer  Underpinning the gloom: Nearly two-thirds of Americans believe the economy has yet to hit bottom, a sharply higher percentage than the 53% who felt that way in January.
Wow. I think thebarrage of terrible economic news this week has people realizing that you can’t borrow your way out of a debt problem.
So far this fiscal year, the US has paid more in interest on its rapidly rising debt than it’s taken in from all corporate taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evil of Debt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/18/the-evil-of-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 15:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/18/the-evil-of-debt/</guid>
      <description>_The debtor is a slave to his lender. _
Americans hold hundreds of billions of dollars in credit card debt alone. To this add automobiles, student loans, mortgages, medical, and myriad personal loans and you arrive at the staggering figure of$2.55 trillion with a &amp;lsquo;t&amp;rsquo;. 
This massive debt&amp;ndash;encouraged and backed by the US Government&amp;ndash;makes us miserable. Seriously. Are you happy? If the debtor is slave to his lender, then the US Government is slave to China and Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>