<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>April 2 Election on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/april-2-election/</link>
    <description>Recent content in April 2 Election on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 14:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/april-2-election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockwood School District Wants More Money But State Audit Found It Mismanages The Money It Has</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/rockwood-school-district-wants-more-money-but-state-audit-found-it-mismanages-the-money-it-has/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/rockwood-school-district-wants-more-money-but-state-audit-found-it-mismanages-the-money-it-has/</guid>
      <description>Were Rockwood School District to shut down, the entire bond-issue-campaign-financing industry would slump into depression.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12113&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;284&amp;rdquo;] Rockwood School District wants another $38 million bond issue on the heals of scathing audit of its financial management practices.I’ve lived in this district since 1996, and I honestly don’t remember an April in which the board wasn’t asking for more money to carpet the football fields or remodel 12-year-old theatres or build an observatory or whatever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote No on Proposition P on April 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/19/vote-no-on-proposition-p-on-april-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/19/vote-no-on-proposition-p-on-april-2/</guid>
      <description>Every penny taken from your in taxes is a penny someone else decides how to spend. It’s a penny you earned but forfeited to someone else’s arbitrary discretion.

Don’t surrender your economic freedom any more.
Proposition P is an easy No vote.
Proposition P is a sales tax increase that would drive up the cost of everything you buy in St. Louis City and County. St. Charles County already opted out of the tax, because they knew the money would be frittered away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Vote in Kirkwood School District, Listen Up</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/if-you-vote-in-kirkwood-school-district-listen-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/if-you-vote-in-kirkwood-school-district-listen-up/</guid>
      <description>In the past 15 years, Kirkwood School Districts operation costs have skyrocketed almost 100 percent. But the people paying the taxes for that district have seen a cost of living increase of only 44 percent.

Obviously, at some point, the system will crash. Unless you do something now.
On April 2, you can elect two fiscally responsible members to the board of education.
Eric Peterson and Amy Russell
Here’s what you should do:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>