<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>foreign policy on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/foreign-policy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in foreign policy on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 03:18:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/foreign-policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Russian Empire</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</guid>
      <description>The last two years of Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s presidency will see the rise of a new Russian empire.
This new empire will resemble the Soviet Union in shape, the Czars in style.
We looked at this subject over the summer (here and here). To summarize those blogs:
 The US-led coup of Ukraine convinced Putin to reassert safer borders Russia wants to build a buffer between itself and NATO Putin wants to re-establish a Russian Empire to revitalize Russian pride and influence Western debt and war-weariness make NATO impotent Putin knows the next US president might be more of a man than Obama, even if its Hillary Putin will want to complete his expansion by January 20, 2017 Ukraine is as good as done and Poland will fall under Russian influence  I still believe all of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Abdullah Kicks Obama Out of Saudia Arabia ? **Video Added**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 00:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think American foreign policy couldn&amp;rsquo;t sink any lower than standing by while Vladimir Putin re-conquers the Warsaw Pact nations. Then you&amp;rsquo;ve underestimated Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s incompetence.
Apparently, Obama didn&amp;rsquo;t bow low enough to King Abdullah of Saudi Arabia. Whatever happened, an &amp;ldquo;intimate&amp;rdquo; evening planned for Obama and Abdullah was abruptly cancelled after a two-hour meeting between the two leaders. A meeting intended to &amp;ldquo;mend fences&amp;rdquo; between the two men.
UPDATE: Here&amp;rsquo;s the video from Lou Dobbs on Fox Business</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Incompetence Leaves Americans At Risk</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/obamas-incompetence-leaves-americans-at-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 08:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/obamas-incompetence-leaves-americans-at-risk/</guid>
      <description>It took almost three years of Jimmy Carter’s dangerously naive worldview before the world rushed in. By “rushed in,” I mean the Soviet Union rushed into Afghanistan, Iranian radicals rushed into the US Embassy in Tehran, and Cuban-backed communists rushed into every Central and South American country they could.
These aggressions resulted from a world perception that Jimmy Carter was unwilling to use America’s arsenal for good. Additionally, following Vietnam and observing American culture, the world surmised that:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>