<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economy on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economy on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 21:33:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If Donald Trump Scares You, You Should See a Depression</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/09/if-donald-trump-scares-you-you-should-see-a-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 21:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/09/if-donald-trump-scares-you-you-should-see-a-depression/</guid>
      <description>Guest post by Lee Presser.
America’s fiscal year is October 1 to September 30. With two month left in FY16, the U.S. Treasury has already paid creditors $380,925,428,211.67 in interest costs. (That’s $381 Billion) https://www.treasurydirect.gov/govt/reports/ir/ir_expense.htm
The average interest rate was just over 2%. https://www.treasurydirect.gov/govt/rates/pd/avg/2016/2016_07.htm
 It is expected that the last two month’s of this fiscal year, interest costs will increase another $45 to $66 Billion. The total FY16 interest cost may be between $426 and $447 Billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservatism Is The New Black</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/15/conservatism-is-the-new-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 02:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/15/conservatism-is-the-new-black/</guid>
      <description>What has 50 years of loyalty to Democrats won for African-Americans?
If you answered &amp;ldquo;civil rights legislation,&amp;rdquo; you better look at who voted for the laws and who opposed. (Hint: Republicans yea, Democrats nay.)
Welfare? In 1967 the poverty rate was 14 percent. In 2014, the poverty rate was 14 percent. In the interim, we pissed away $22 trillion on bureaucratic sex junkets to Costa Rica and massive government office buildings in every major city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Welfare Reform Must Continue</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/09/why-welfare-reform-must-continue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 22:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/09/why-welfare-reform-must-continue/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I missed this.
It&amp;rsquo;s the story of Marienthal Austria.
Marienthal was a town in Austria that thrived thanks to a single employer. When the flax mill went out of business in 1932, Marienthal&amp;rsquo;s population became mostly unemployed.
Thanks to Austria&amp;rsquo;s liberal unemployment programs that replaced up to 90 percent of income, no one in Marienthal plunged into economic poverty as a result of the mill&amp;rsquo;s closing. But spiritual poverty was another story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why poverty is a conservative issue</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/08/why-poverty-is-a-conservative-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/08/why-poverty-is-a-conservative-issue/</guid>
      <description>Oh but now old friends they&amp;rsquo;re acting strange, They shake their heads, they say I&amp;rsquo;ve changed Well something&amp;rsquo;s lost, but something&amp;rsquo;s gained In living every day. &amp;ndash;Joni Mitchell, Both Sides Now
 I&amp;rsquo;ve looked at poor from both sides now.
I get a lot of grief for pushing poverty solutions. And service. Many conservatives believe Mitt Romney was right when he uttered his infamous 47 percent line.
In case you forgot:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Note on Market</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/24/quick-note-on-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/24/quick-note-on-market/</guid>
      <description>I was up early this morning sifting through the market stories.
** Asia: crash ** Middle East: crash ** Europe: crash ** USA: set to open
There&amp;rsquo;s good news in all this loss. First, stocks were overpriced. At some point, they will bottom out and it will be time to start buying. Second, the Golden Age of the Central Banker seems to be over. And that is very good news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Compassionate Alternative to Raising the Minimum Wage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/we-can-do-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 10:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/we-can-do-better/</guid>
      <description>The headline is depressing, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to write it anyway:
America&amp;rsquo;s Slums Are Exploding
The story is in the Atlantic, a progressive publication. But they admit what so many Americans know: the welfare state has failed those who needed it most. And it&amp;rsquo;s failing those never needed it but were sucked into it nonetheless.
 Half a century after President Lyndon B. Johnson declared a war on poverty, the number of Americans living in slums is rising at an extraordinary pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Ferguson and Dellwood This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 04:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I&amp;rsquo;m so late on this. This sounds whiny, I know, but I have a really involved week at work this week. Sorry. Crap always seems to work out this way, though. When there&amp;rsquo;s a great need for Tea Party services, I&amp;rsquo;m tied up with work obligations. Something has to give, and it&amp;rsquo;s usually the thing that doesn&amp;rsquo;t generate revenue.
But we all have work to do. Ferguson businesses and families are still struggling with the effects of the riots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bureaucratizing Street Gangs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/26/bureaucratizing-street-gangs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/26/bureaucratizing-street-gangs/</guid>
      <description>Did you ever wonder why do-gooders and social planners never pay for their crimes?
Yesterday, I wrote about Jesse Jackson dressing down at the hands of activists in a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s parking lot in Ferguson. I pointed out that Martin Luther King and Dick Gregory were similarly dismissed by rioters in the 1960s. Some things never change.
One thing that has changed is the economic gap between whites and blacks. That&amp;rsquo;s gotten worse despite trillions in federal poverty programs that went mostly to &amp;ldquo;community organizing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exposing the Race Hustlers in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/25/exposing-race-hustlers-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 21:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/25/exposing-race-hustlers-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s an awesome YouTube video of Jesse Jackson getting skewered in Ferguson.
First, though, a little history.
One of the greatest books ever on race-based poverty and jobs programs is Tom Wolfe&amp;rsquo;s Mau-Mauing the Flak-Catchers. You won&amp;rsquo;t understand race politics in America without reading it. Twice. Four times, maybe.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve read it, you know why Jesse Jackson and Capt. Ron Johnson and all the other &amp;ldquo;black leaders&amp;rdquo; are impotent to stop riots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why St. Louis Tea Party Went to Ferguson To Shop</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/why-st-louis-tea-party-went-to-ferguson-to-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 04:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/why-st-louis-tea-party-went-to-ferguson-to-shop/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;rsquo;t change the world in your living room.
That&amp;rsquo;s why a small band of (mostly) white people from (mostly) West County drove to Ferguson (and Dellwood) to shop tonight.
We targeted the small businesses that were hit hard by violence&amp;ndash;violence committed (mostly) by out of town agitators, criminals, vandals, and hooligans.
We drove to Ferguson to make two statements with our actons: 1) Ferguson is OUR community, and 2) Ferguson is open for business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferguson is the Canary in the Coal Mine&#34; for St. Louis County</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/18/ferguson-canary-coal-mine-st-louis-county/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 21:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/18/ferguson-canary-coal-mine-st-louis-county/</guid>
      <description>The next St. Louis County Executive better brace himself for this: poverty is exploding in the county.
I&amp;rsquo;m not saying poor people do bad things. I&amp;rsquo;m saying that, at some point, eliminating jobs and hope will drive people to take things. And they will take things by force. And they will show no mercy to anyone who tries to get in their way.
Right or wrong, it happens. And no militarized police force will stop it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insane: Stocks Markets Rally On Economic Disasters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/14/insane-stocks-markets-rally-economic-disasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 11:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/14/insane-stocks-markets-rally-economic-disasters/</guid>
      <description>Eurozone&amp;rsquo;s economy is basically in recession.
Walmart lowered expectations. Again.
The world is teetering on the edge of World War.
The US is launching Iraq War 3.0: Mission Accomplished Accomplished.
Germany&amp;rsquo;s economy is flat, and Italy and France are getting worse.
Risk is high.
Corporate debt is staggering.
The Fed&amp;rsquo;s balance sheet is a sea of monetized debt.
The central banks have nothing left to fix another crash.
And the stock markets are rocketing to record highs because of all this news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conscious Capitalism:The One Book Every Conservative Must Read</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/26/heres-the-one-book-every-conservative-must-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/26/heres-the-one-book-every-conservative-must-read/</guid>
      <description>The motivating force behind the first tea party protests of February 27, 2009, was , in part, crony capitalism. Across the country and on the steps of the Arch in St. Louis, signs and speakers denounced bailouts for failed businesses.
Rasmussen found that 68 percent of Americans believe Big Business and Big Government work together against the rest of us.
I think they’re right.
Since then, crony capitalism has only grown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Florida Has the Relationship Between Home Ownership and Growth All Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/25/richard-florida-has-the-relationship-between-home-ownership-and-growth-all-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/25/richard-florida-has-the-relationship-between-home-ownership-and-growth-all-wrong/</guid>
      <description>In a column intended to attract readers, not to promote hard economics, Rotman University economist Richard Florida declares that home ownership is terrible for the US Economy.

The problem is, like many economists,** Florida’s understanding of home ownership is 180 degrees ass-backwards**. Florida thinks that home ownership is supposed to _cause_ economic growth.
 Instead of leading to economic development, higher rates of homeownership today are associated with lower levels of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday (Infographic)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</guid>
      <description>The world&amp;rsquo;s economy&amp;ndash;including BRICs&amp;ndash;is collapsing. The problem is debt, and the youth will set us free. Even if that&amp;rsquo;s a very painful liberation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYT Describes Mayhem of “Taxmageddon”, And It Will Scare You Sick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</guid>
      <description>What the hell’s going on at NYT? First, they do a piece on Andrew Breitbart. Then they warn the world that Taxmageddon will crush the world in 2013, beginning with the USA.

Here&amp;rsquo;s how Business Insider summarized the David Leohardt article:
 Basically, with no changes to current law, taxes will rise for everyone, and after tax, inflation-adjusted income for the average American will drop to 1998 levels.
 Read more: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Killed the American Job Machine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/who-killed-the-american-job-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/who-killed-the-american-job-machine/</guid>
      <description>Maureen Dowd’s having trouble slathering make-up on her favorite pigs these days. Her President—the man for whom she surrendered all pretense of intelligence, wisdom, and self-control—is flailing.
And Maureen Dowd is going all wobbly. Wobbly on Obama. Wobbly on America. Wobbly on life. Here’s an exceprt:
 On the razor’s edge of another recession; blocked at every turn by Republicans determined to slice him up at any cost; starting an unexpectedly daunting re-election bid; and puzzling over how to make a prime-time speech about infrastructure and payroll taxes soar, maybe President Obama is wishing that he had thrown the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Makes It Worse</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/06/03/obama-makes-it-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 14:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/06/03/obama-makes-it-worse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rdquo; could refer to anything. Anything at all.
In this case, though, I&amp;rsquo;m referring to unemployment. Well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;m referring to the economy overall.
Unemployment rate rises to 9.1%, 54K jobs added « Hot Air
Obama has increased regulation, seized entire industries (auto, student loans, commercial banking, medicine), and borrowed more money faster than all previous presidents combined.
Obama is a one-dictator disaster. And an incompetent one at that.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a job, Obama made it worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin Talks to Lee Presser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/31/ed-martin-talks-to-lee-presser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 10:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/31/ed-martin-talks-to-lee-presser/</guid>
      <description>This is an important conversation in an important race. Please watch.
Ed talks about regulation, taxes, debt, Race to the Top, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Fit?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/23/whos-fit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/23/whos-fit/</guid>
      <description>Take a look at Drudge.
I’ll wait. The day doesn’t really matter. It’s always full of stuff that makes you think rivets are flying out of the planet like a jalopy in a cartoon.
** Two girls beat another girl into convulsions over the course of eight minutes while cowardly young men quiver in fear. (But an old lady steps in and protects the victim.) ** Syrian security opens fire on demonstrators killing 90.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYTimes: Cubans Find Freedom Fun</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/nytimes-cubans-find-freedom-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 11:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/nytimes-cubans-find-freedom-fun/</guid>
      <description>Since mass murderer Fidel Castro fired thousands of Cuban government workers due to the economic unviability of Obamanomics, those set free are enjoying their independence. To the shock of the New York Times:
 “I feel useful; I’m independent,” said Ms. Álvarez, who opened a small cafe in November at her home in this scruffy town 25 miles from the capital, Havana. “When you sit down at the end of the day and look at how much you have made, you feel satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Learned from Milton Friedman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/26/what-we-learned-from-milton-friedman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/26/what-we-learned-from-milton-friedman/</guid>
      <description>I am a big fan of Milton Friedman. I’m also becoming a big fan of Creating Shared Value. Some believe the two values are inconsistent, but I disagree.
In 2005, Reason Magazine posted an online debate between Friedman and Whole Foods Market CEO John Mackey. The debate coincided with the 35th anniversary of Friedmans’ famous The New York Times Magazine article entitled: : &amp;ldquo;The Social Responsibility of Business Is to Increase Its Profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas Have Consequences—Even Stupid Ones</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/ideas-have-consequenceseven-stupid-ones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/ideas-have-consequenceseven-stupid-ones/</guid>
      <description>When Barack Obama became president in January 2009, he began a campaign to weaken America. I’m not talking about military cuts; I’m speaking of America’s stature. Barack Obama famously refused to acknowledge American Exceptionalism in 2009. He bowed to kings and princes, then denied doing so, then bowed again and again. His White House has driven down the dollar. Timothy Geithner, Obama’s Secretary of the Treasury, warns that the world economy must “rebalance” with less reliance on America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Signs of Economic Disaster</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/3-signs-of-economic-disaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/3-signs-of-economic-disaster/</guid>
      <description>Each day, more economists jump onto the Double-Dip bandwagon. Signs abound that the natural economic recovery that would normally follow a deep recession won’t happen. Instead, the economy is now saddled with so much debt, so many regulations, and such onerous new taxes that the Obama Administration tells us to be happy with 9.5 percent unemployment.

Barack Obama is an economic disaster of the first order.
So why all the pessimism?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2/3 Think Worst Is Yet to Come for USA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/11/23-think-worst-is-yet-to-come-for-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 03:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/11/23-think-worst-is-yet-to-come-for-usa/</guid>
      <description>The Wall Street Journal headline is grim:
   Grim Voter Mood Turns Grimmer  Underpinning the gloom: Nearly two-thirds of Americans believe the economy has yet to hit bottom, a sharply higher percentage than the 53% who felt that way in January.
Wow. I think thebarrage of terrible economic news this week has people realizing that you can’t borrow your way out of a debt problem.
So far this fiscal year, the US has paid more in interest on its rapidly rising debt than it’s taken in from all corporate taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed: Other Shoe About to Drop</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/fed-other-shoe-about-to-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 03:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/fed-other-shoe-about-to-drop/</guid>
      <description>The only two people in the world who believe the economy is healthy and vibrant are Barack Obama and Joe Biden.

Now, the Federal Reserve Board’s Open Market Committee (FOMC) is getting ready to announce that the economy is sicker than we thought.
 Although Fed policymakers still believe the basic trajectory of the economy remains one of moderate expansion, there may be more attention given to heightened dangers of a sharp slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Blink (you’ll miss the recovery)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/22/dont-blink-youll-miss-the-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/22/dont-blink-youll-miss-the-recovery/</guid>
      <description>The stock market reacted mildly to some devastating economic news today. In fact, the stock market appears to be in denial about the state of America’s economy.
Existing home sales fell in May. As of this morning, economists expected a six percent increase.
Economists expect new home sales to be worse than existing home sales.
And economists expected home sales to fall off the table in July and for the remainder of 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8,000 Dow? *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/8000-dow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/8000-dow/</guid>
      <description>So says Yale economist Nouriel Roubini in an interview today on CNBC.
 &amp;ldquo;There are some parts of the global economy that are now at the risk of a double-dip recession,&amp;rdquo; said Roubini, head of Roubini Global Economics. &amp;ldquo;From here on I see things getting worse.&amp;rdquo;
 
Roubini’s comments came in response to a 376 point drop in the Dow Industrials. Nasdaq and S&amp;amp;P 500 were off significantly as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Crisis: Greece, Portugal, Spain . . . ?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/28/debt-crisis-greece-portugal-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 15:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/28/debt-crisis-greece-portugal-spain/</guid>
      <description>WSJ.com Alert:
 S&amp;amp;P downgrades Spain to &amp;lsquo;AA&amp;rsquo; with a negative outlook, saying the country is likely to have an extended period of subdued economic growth.
 Markets react: DJIA plummets from +23 to –22 in seconds after S&amp;amp;P drops Spain’s debt rating. And the sovereign debt nightmare is only beginning. The UK is next. But the USA borrows more money faster than anyone, and Socio-History blog ain’t happy:
  As I pointed out yesterday, US debt threatens to end the economic stabilization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greece: America’s Future</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/27/greece-americas-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/27/greece-americas-future/</guid>
      <description>As I waited to appear on Larry Kudlow’s show last Friday, I heard Larry announce over and over again that he’s sick of hearing about Greece’s problems. Greece isn’t America. The U.S. economy is booming, and Greece can’t hurt it.
I didn’t tell Larry, but I think he was wrong.
Greece’s problems will hurt the American economy because Greece’s problems foreshadow a far more dangerous crash headed to America.
Markets are people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Focus on Government Spending?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/31/why-focus-on-government-spending/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 05:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/31/why-focus-on-government-spending/</guid>
      <description>The mounting government debt&amp;ndash;$2.98 trillion in recent bailouts and stimuli alone&amp;ndash;is an oppressive anchor around the neck of every American. Currently, every family of 3 is obliged to pay over $118,000 in the next 30 years. That&amp;rsquo;s a house payment with a variable-rate. In other words, the government has done exactly what helped cause the mess for individuals by borrowing beyond its means at a teaser rate of 0.8 percent. That Teaser Rate Will Skyrocket</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009 Economic Prediction *Bumped and Updated*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/14/2009-economic-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2009 07:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/14/2009-economic-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted February 15, 2009
I know this is a little late, but I was waiting for Congress to spend another trillion dollars or so before committing my prediction to the public. Here goes:
  GDP and unemployment will flatten and even improve a bit in first half of 2009 for a couple of reasons:
First, people will begin to look for excuses to spend money. This includes businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evil of Debt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/18/the-evil-of-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 15:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/18/the-evil-of-debt/</guid>
      <description>_The debtor is a slave to his lender. _
Americans hold hundreds of billions of dollars in credit card debt alone. To this add automobiles, student loans, mortgages, medical, and myriad personal loans and you arrive at the staggering figure of$2.55 trillion with a &amp;lsquo;t&amp;rsquo;. 
This massive debt&amp;ndash;encouraged and backed by the US Government&amp;ndash;makes us miserable. Seriously. Are you happy? If the debtor is slave to his lender, then the US Government is slave to China and Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Other Shoe Drops</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/08/the-other-shoe-drops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 12:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/08/the-other-shoe-drops/</guid>
      <description>For months I&amp;rsquo;ve been echoing the warnings of Peter Schiff and others: when China stops buying American debt, we&amp;rsquo;re in deep, deep trouble. The possibility for hyperflation, prices rise by double-digits on daily or weekly measures, becomes palpably high.
Even though this article from IHT failed to suprised me, I have a sick, frightened gnawing in my stomach:
 China has bought more than $1 trillion in American debt, but as the global downturn has intensified, Beijing is starting to keep more of its money at home - a shift that could pose some challenges to the U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>