<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>abortion on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/abortion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in abortion on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 17:55:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/abortion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very Bad Week for Planned Parenthood</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-18-a-very-bad-week-for-planned-parenthood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 17:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-18-a-very-bad-week-for-planned-parenthood/</guid>
      <description>The abortion company fires its CEOs as sloppily as it delivers &amp;ldquo;healthcare.&amp;rdquo;
Before that, the Trump Administration successfully cut some of Planned Parenthood&amp;rsquo;s federal funding, which may have precipitated the decapitation of its management team.
And, today, Planned Parenthood&amp;rsquo;s hand-picked judge tentatively ruled in complete favor with the journalist the company is suing.
Aborting Dr. Wen On Wednesday, Planned Parenthood clumsily fired Dr. Leana Wen as its chief executive. I guess you could call it a late-term firing, since Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Catholic Priest Eviscerates Childish NeverTrumpers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/19/a-catholic-priest-eviscerates-childish-nevertrumpers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 12:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/19/a-catholic-priest-eviscerates-childish-nevertrumpers/</guid>
      <description>Outcomes.
NeverTrumpers seem to believe that the act of voting is a sort of magic spell that can right all past wrongs. Psychologists call this &amp;ldquo;magical thinking.&amp;rdquo; Children do it. Magical thinking is the belief that we can change the outside world with our thoughts. Think of rain dances and crossed fingers. Or, as Dr. Ben Hunt explains, Fed policy.
Father Christopher J. Pollard, writing in Catholic News Agency, destroys the NeverTrump argument in his essay &amp;ldquo;On Voting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Is the Only Viable Pro-Life Choice</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/09/trump-is-the-only-viable-pro-life-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 21:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/09/trump-is-the-only-viable-pro-life-choice/</guid>
      <description>Some pro-life activists like Erick Erickson are plotting ways to sabotage Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy for president. They probably haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped to think. If they succeed in defeating Trump, they will be culpable in many, many abortions. That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of guilt for a guy like Erickson to carry around, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Chances are Congress won&amp;rsquo;t introduce any major abortion laws in the next four years. That means the abortion battle will remain in the courts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Wrong--Evil</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/not-just-wrong-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/not-just-wrong-evil/</guid>
      <description>Today was a particularly busy day for me.
I had a series of meetings. Like every hour, another meeting. From 9:00 on.
I saw the text from my wife. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to click on a video. I was in a room full of people. Important business. Major client and all that. And I completely misunderstood the &amp;ldquo;H/T Gina L.&amp;rdquo; thing. For some reason, I thought Angela was mad at Gina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Want Fewer Abortions, Stop Talking About How Many There Are</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/19/if-you-want-fewer-abortions-stop-talking-about-how-many-there-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/19/if-you-want-fewer-abortions-stop-talking-about-how-many-there-are/</guid>
      <description>I’m using abortion as an example, but this bit of science applies to all political messaging.
What’s wrong with this headline?

I’ll tell you what’s wrong with it. It shouts: “Everybody’s getting an abortion!” Even if connected with messages that say abortion is wrong.
In numerous studies, messages intended to discourage a behavior by promoting the number of people engaged in the behavior (called negative social proof) actually caused the behavior to increase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why Turning People Off Is A Terrible Idea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a cause’s worst enemies are its best friends.

In 1995, 56 percent of American described themselves as “pro-choice.” At the time, Michael Kinsley on CNN’s Crossfire declared the debate over.
Then something strange happened. Americans started changing their minds. The pro-life movement whittled away at public opinion.
By May of this year, Gallup found “pro-choice” to be at an all-time low:
 The 41% of Americans who now identify themselves as &amp;ldquo;pro-choice&amp;rdquo; is down from 47% last July and is one percentage point below the previous record low in Gallup trends, recorded in May 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Cancelled Religious Freedom, But Some People Aren&#39;t Listening to Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/obama-cancelled-religious-freedom-but-some-people-arent-listening-to-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 10:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/obama-cancelled-religious-freedom-but-some-people-arent-listening-to-obama/</guid>
      <description>When Obama decreed that Catholics shall support and provide chemical abortions,he wasn&amp;rsquo;t promoting women. He was shackling religion.
Totalitarian autocrats don&amp;rsquo;t cotton freedom, unless they personally granted it. Obama doesn&amp;rsquo;t believe in individual liberty, but that all power and rights emanate from government. Timothy Cardinal Dolan agrees.
So it&amp;rsquo;s exciting to report that some St. Louisans are fighting back. Here&amp;rsquo;s the details:
Protest for Religious Freedom
Location: Old Courthouse (Directions) Date: Saturday, April 28, 2012 Time: 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: White House Chief of Staff Says Obama Has Complete Power to Decree Healthcare Rules</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/16/video-white-house-chief-of-staff-says-obama-has-complete-power-to-decree-healthcare-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 00:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/16/video-white-house-chief-of-staff-says-obama-has-complete-power-to-decree-healthcare-rules/</guid>
      <description>Jack Lew, Obama’s Chief of Staff, says Obamacare law gives the President the power make rules regarding your health. Period.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NhCxGdTJrxs]
Lee Presser’s comment nails it:
 Chris Wallace states this is precisely the reason why so many people oppose Obamacare.
 Share this frightening power grab with your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 Days of Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/40-days-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 20:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/40-days-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Forty Days of Life is a peaceful, prayerful response the poverty of abortion.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x-AfLO6Oevo]
The Coalition for Life is a community based Christian pro-life organization made up of over 90 churches and thousands of individuals who are working to end abortion in St. Louis, peacefully and prayerfully. ____
 The 40 Days for Life St. Louis Adopt-A-Day program is for Churches and/or Organizations that feel God is calling them to a day of prayer at our vigil location near Planned Parenthood on Forest Park Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abortion and ObamaCare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/abortion-and-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 16:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/abortion-and-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>In Tennessee and Arizona, insurance exchanges created under ObamaCare are barred from covering abortions. Pro-life groups claim this trend will continue as more states realize that the bill passed earlier this year allows states to block abortion coverage by private exchanges. (Missouri’s legislature sent a similar measure to Gov. Jay Nixon.)

Pro-abortion members of Congress are incensed, according to the Associated Press and Fox News:
 &amp;ldquo;Implementation of this reform should be about increasing access to health care and increasing choices, not taking them away,&amp;rdquo; said Sen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Government Doesn&#39;t Kill Babies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/20/good-government-doesnt-kill-babies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 12:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/20/good-government-doesnt-kill-babies/</guid>
      <description>One of Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s first actions as president will likely involve a series of executive orders ensuring that as many abortions as possible happen. Good government protects its most vulnerable citizens; bad government kills them. Nazi Germany killed the weak, the halt, the improvident. Of course, the Nazis trained specialist to carry out these grim and evil tasks. In America, we rely on ordinary citizens to do the killing for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Question for Obama on Abortion</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/11/one-question-for-obama-on-abortion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 03:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/11/one-question-for-obama-on-abortion/</guid>
      <description>Everytime I&amp;rsquo;ve debated the death penalty with a bleeding-heart, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard this question: &amp;ldquo;Would you pull the switch&amp;rdquo; or its equal. It&amp;rsquo;s only fair to turn the question on them.
Barack Obama, if you read this blog, please answer this question: Would you kill child who survived an abortion with your own hands? (Thanks to Jill Stanek via Michelle Malkin)
 Barack Obama, as chairman of an IL state Senate committee, voted down a bill to protect live-born survivors of abortion - even after the panel had amended the bill to contain verbatim language, copied from a federal bill passed by Congress without objection in 2002, explicitly foreclosing any impact on abortion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>