<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>amazon on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/amazon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in amazon on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 11:41:27 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/amazon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Print Edition of Fight to Evolve Now Available on Amazon. Rush!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/23/print-edition-of-fight-to-evolve-now-available-on-amazon-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 21:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/23/print-edition-of-fight-to-evolve-now-available-on-amazon-rush/</guid>
      <description>Most of my readers asked for a print edition of my new book, Fight to Evolve: The Government&amp;rsquo;s Secret War on NTX.
Great news! Your book is waiting for you on Amazon. It&amp;rsquo;s just $17.99, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be happy to know that I don&amp;rsquo;t get a penny from the sales. All proceeds go to the Coalition for Safer Drinking and its fight to reduce alcohol&amp;rsquo;s negative effects on health.
If you, like me, prefer electronic books, you can get the Kindle version of Fight to Evolve for just $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Herbert Hoover Launched Cardinal Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals were the major league team farthest west and farthest south until the 1950s. But that’s not the only reason the Redbirds built a massive flock of fans from the Alleghenies to the Rockies, and from Canada to the Gulf of Mexico.
The St. Louis Cardinals owe big government statism and technological innovation a big thanks, in addition to geography and great teams. The technology was radio. The big government statist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Conservative Paperback Available Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/27/zen-conservative-paperback-available-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 20:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/27/zen-conservative-paperback-available-now/</guid>
      <description>** You Can Order My Book Online Today **Zen Conservatism is now available in paperback.
I began this book in December 2008, just after the election. My goal was to produce a book that would inspire people to restore our republic. At the time, conservatives were disheartened, dismayed, and distracted.
Then the Tea Party movement began, and I had to put my book project on hold. But thanks to your work, I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to return to my project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>