<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>g20 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/g20/</link>
    <description>Recent content in g20 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 15:46:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/g20/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas Have Consequences—Even Stupid Ones</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/ideas-have-consequenceseven-stupid-ones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/ideas-have-consequenceseven-stupid-ones/</guid>
      <description>When Barack Obama became president in January 2009, he began a campaign to weaken America. I’m not talking about military cuts; I’m speaking of America’s stature. Barack Obama famously refused to acknowledge American Exceptionalism in 2009. He bowed to kings and princes, then denied doing so, then bowed again and again. His White House has driven down the dollar. Timothy Geithner, Obama’s Secretary of the Treasury, warns that the world economy must “rebalance” with less reliance on America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Insults Americans . . . Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/obama-insults-americans-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 23:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/obama-insults-americans-again/</guid>
      <description>An arrogant and distracted Barack Obama appeared at a press conference for the G20 Summit today. His purpose: to insult, threaten, and cajole the American people from an international stage.
 I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because I said I was going to do it and I think it&amp;rsquo;s the right thing to do. People should learn that lesson about me because next year when I start presenting some very difficult choices to the country, I hope some of these folks who are hollering about deficits and debt step-up because I&amp;rsquo;m calling their bluff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>