<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics tea party on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-tea-party/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics tea party on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 23:37:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-tea-party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day of Hope, Prayer, and Clean-up in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/a-day-of-hope-prayer-and-clean-up-in-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 23:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/a-day-of-hope-prayer-and-clean-up-in-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Dellena Jones’s 911 Hair Salon was attacked at about 11:15 PM by a small band of young men. The break-in and robbery occurred close to the time of the first shooting. The hair salon is less than 100 yards from the scene of the shooting.
But that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop volunteers from St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and friends from helping.
[caption width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;quot;attachment_16631&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo;]Volunteers pose for a picture after helping clean and repair 911 Hair Salon in Ferguson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Would Like to Talk to You on Tuesday September 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/28/like-talk-talk-tuesday-september-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 03:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/28/like-talk-talk-tuesday-september-2/</guid>
      <description>Hi. Bill Hennessy here. If you can, please stop by 111 Clarkson Executive Park, Ellisville, MO 63011 on Tuesday, September 2 at 7 p.m. (RSVP Here if you&amp;rsquo;d like.)
I have something I&amp;rsquo;d like to talk to you about. It&amp;rsquo;s about the tea party movement. But it&amp;rsquo;s really about understanding two very important concepts:
*1. Living to our purpose. *2. Doing what&amp;rsquo;s important.
This is not a training session. It&amp;rsquo;s not an After Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Ferguson and Dellwood This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 04:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I&amp;rsquo;m so late on this. This sounds whiny, I know, but I have a really involved week at work this week. Sorry. Crap always seems to work out this way, though. When there&amp;rsquo;s a great need for Tea Party services, I&amp;rsquo;m tied up with work obligations. Something has to give, and it&amp;rsquo;s usually the thing that doesn&amp;rsquo;t generate revenue.
But we all have work to do. Ferguson businesses and families are still struggling with the effects of the riots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Your Calendar for June 19</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/04/mark-calendar-june-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 03:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/04/mark-calendar-june-19/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Ben Evans of Heritage Action for America and Michelle Moore of St. Louis Tea Party Coalition, you have a treat coming on June 19.

Heritage Action/St. Louis Tea Party Social: June 19 On Thursday, June 19 at 6:30pm, we will gather informally at Scarecrow in Chesterfield, 1095 Chesterfield Parkway. All are welcome. Appetizers will be provided. Come down and enjoy the company of fellow grassroots activists.
If you have friends who think Tea Partiers are &amp;ldquo;too extreme&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;racist&amp;rdquo; or whatever, bring them along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare Ruling Comes Down This Week, and We’re Having a Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/24/obamacare-ruling-comes-down-this-week-and-were-having-a-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 18:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/24/obamacare-ruling-comes-down-this-week-and-were-having-a-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Pack clothes, flags, and signs for an Obamacare Tea Party at Forest Park on Art Hill this week. The rally will begin at 7:00 PM on the day the Supreme Court rules.

We don’t know the day, but we do know the time: 7:00 pm in Forest Park on Art Hill (map below). The most likely days are Monday or Thursday, but because of the magnitude of this case, it could be any day of the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s One Way the Government&#39;s Making Medicine Worse in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 02:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</guid>
      <description>I had to go to the doctor today. The reason&amp;rsquo;s not important. Here&amp;rsquo;s what is:
It took my doctor 10 minutes to describe my symptoms into a government-mandated voice recognition system.   
In the old days, the doctor took notes. Now, he has to recite his observations into a Mad Men-era dictaphone. &amp;ldquo;Male, age 48, blood pressure one-twenty-one over seventy-three . . . &amp;quot;
The damn machine (government medical technology) couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand half the doctor&amp;rsquo;s words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd Anniversary Tea Party: Thank You!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/27/3rd-anniversary-tea-party-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/27/3rd-anniversary-tea-party-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>The 3rd Anniversary Tea Party rocked . . . because of the great patriot-activists who have decided it’s time to act and win.

Although Dr. Larry Schweikart couldn’t make it (because of the Chicago snow storm), Friday’s event was better than planned or expected. Tea Party champion Michael Patrick Leahy jumped into fill a last-minute void, and the crowd loved it.
  I had the the pleasure of reading and advanced copy of Mike Leahy&amp;rsquo;s new book, Covenant of Liberty: The Ideological Origins of the Tea Party Movement  in December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoveOnUp.org was never supposed to happen</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/14/moveonup-org-was-never-supposed-to-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/14/moveonup-org-was-never-supposed-to-happen/</guid>
      <description>This weekend, MoveOnUp.org held its first conference. The location was the Crowne Plaza Hotel at the airport. The event launched the Sherman T. Parker Scholarship for African-American Political Science students.
But that’s not the big story.
The big story is this: MoveOnUp.org has cheated history.
Why “cheated?” Because the past 50 years of American liberal history has prepared American blacks for one purpose: compliance.
Using victimhood, welfare, crime, destructive education, and programs designed to destroy families, American liberals from Ted Kennedy to Barack Obama chained African-Americans to “Uncle Sam’s Plantation,” as Star Parker so aptly puts it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollow Holiday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/06/hollow-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/06/hollow-holiday/</guid>
      <description>July 4, 2011, felt hollow, like celebrating the birthday of someone deceased.
Independence Day celebrates the birth of an idea: that people create governments and empower them, not the other way around.
Do we still believe that?

Yes, I still believe that. Morally, at least. And you probably do, too.
Does America still believe that government derives its just powers from the consent of the governed? Or do we, as a nation, believe that government has a monopoly on liberty and dispenses it at its will?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing the Pie</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/29/growing-the-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/29/growing-the-pie/</guid>
      <description>If the Tea Party brings lasting change to America, it must introduce grow-the-pie thinking on the right.
For years, the tug of war ground on. Democrats and Republicans, Liberals and Conservatives, Collectivists and Individualists all fighting for the same piece of land. The strategy was simple: if you’re behind, discredit the other side until you get the lead. If you’re in the lead, reward your friends to keep them loyal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Left Doubles Down on Threats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</guid>
      <description>What would you do?
Suppose you did something stupid. You blamed the wrong person, for instance, for a capital crime. Then supposed one of your comrades compounded your . . . error . . . by threatening to kill someone on national television?
If you’re an American leftist, you might double down by issuing even more death threats to even more people.
That’s what’ happening right now in America. Death threats are pouring into Trent Humphries, Tucson Tea Party organizer, Dana Loesch, Sarah Palin (who vows not to be silenced), Glenn Beck, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Extensive Interview with Missouri News Horizon</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/my-long-interview-with-missouri-news-horizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/my-long-interview-with-missouri-news-horizon/</guid>
      <description>When I hear all the lies, slanders, and threats against the Tea Party movement from folks on the left, I wish I could counter with a fuller examination of my beliefs. Luckily, with the help of Missouri News Horizon, I can.
The Friday before the 9/12 Tea Party, I sat down with Rebecca Townsend to talk about the Tea Party.
Rebecca and I chatted for an hour. She led me through just about every aspect of the Tea Party’s history up to that point.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>