<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>endExIm on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/endexim/</link>
    <description>Recent content in endExIm on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:53:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/endexim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: White House Shuffles Export Import Management (parody)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/28/breaking-white-house-shuffles-export-import-management-parody/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/28/breaking-white-house-shuffles-export-import-management-parody/</guid>
      <description>Washington (APP) —In a Rose Garden press conference today, President Barack Obama introduced Art Vandelay as his choice to head the troubled Export Import Bank for a five-year term, pending approval by the Senate.
The shake-up comes as Congress debates whether or not to extend the bank’s authorization amid heavy opposition from conservative and libertarian groups led by Heritage Action for America.
Mr. Vandelay brings almost 30 years of experience in the export-import business, where he traded in commodities as varied as potato chips, diapers, and matches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come to Export Import Speaking and Gathering This Saturday at Paddy O&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/27/come-to-export-import-speaking-and-gathering-this-saturday-at-paddy-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 23:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/27/come-to-export-import-speaking-and-gathering-this-saturday-at-paddy-os/</guid>
      <description>With Opportunity for All; With Favoritism Toward None Join Us Paddy O&amp;rsquo;s&amp;ndash;618 S. 7th Street, St. Louis, MO 4:15 PM Saturday, May 30 RSVP on Facebook
They say the Export Import Bank is a tiny agency that creates jobs for small business while producing a profit for the Treasury. And rescues baby rabbits from dangerous predators. And it’s gluten free.
Call us skeptics.
We saw the news that Goldman Sachs used the Export Import Bank to secure funding for a financially unstable buyer—after paying the Secretary of State’s husband $200,000 for a fifteen-minute speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Export Import Bank Matters Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/18/why-the-export-import-bank-matters-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 01:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/18/why-the-export-import-bank-matters-now/</guid>
      <description>Start small&amp;ndash;end big.
Raise your hand if you know someone who woke one morning and ran a marathon having never so much as walked around the block.
No hands?
Of course not. A few freaks of nature might be able to go from zero to 26.2 in no time, but most people would hurt themselves trying. And never do it again.
When a sane sedentary person decides to run a marathon, he starts by walking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the US House, Insider Money Buys Leadership Positions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/29/us-house-insider-money-buys-leadership-positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 20:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/29/us-house-insider-money-buys-leadership-positions/</guid>
      <description>The US House of Representatives is not a meritocracy. And that&amp;rsquo;s a shame.
House &amp;ldquo;leadership&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually have anything to do with leadership. It has everything to do with money.
In a story about the fall from power of Nancy Pelosi, Michael Barone describes how the House leadership process evolved from seniority to raw cash.
  For years, liberal Democrats had decried the seniority system, which automatically made conservative Southerners (and/or senile members) committee chairmen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Ann Wagner Is Wrong to Attack Heritage Action</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 02:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</guid>
      <description>Accountability? We don&amp;rsquo;t need no stinking accountability.
 No, Ann Wagner didn&amp;rsquo;t actually say that. But her comments to a 2nd District Republican committee meeting on Tuesday gave at least one attendee the impression that Mrs. Wagner opposes the idea of conservatives holding Congress accountable.
Ann Wagner Attacks the Conservative Heritage Action Rep. Ann Wagner accused the conservative Heritage Action for America of &amp;ldquo;pitting Republican against Republican&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;never attacking Dems&amp;rdquo; at the Republican meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>