<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 04:05:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stan Kroenke&#39;s Long Con Has Just Started</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/04/stan-kroenkes-long-con-has-just-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 04:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/04/stan-kroenkes-long-con-has-just-started/</guid>
      <description>You thought Stan Kroenke wanted a team in Los Angeles? I don&amp;rsquo;t think so. I think Stan is playing a long con. And I think it&amp;rsquo;s a brilliant strategy.
Los Angeles is a terrible market for football teams, but it&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic market for the NFL. It would be a perfect place to build a permanent home for the Super Bowl. Los Angeles has fantastic weather, great attractions, and a huge pool of football fans, fans of every team in the NFL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Don&#39;t Hear &#34;Big Data&#34; Much Anymore, And For That I&#39;m Thankful</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/04/you-dont-hear-big-data-much-anymore-and-for-that-im-thankful/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 02:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/04/you-dont-hear-big-data-much-anymore-and-for-that-im-thankful/</guid>
      <description>This is about Big Data.
You really can&amp;rsquo;t over-estimate what suckers business people are.
I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about people who create things or improve things. Guys like Steve Jobs and Donald Trump built great businesses. But they weren&amp;rsquo;t business people. They were builders. Running a business was a necessary evil that allowed them the freedom to build what they wanted to build. They were great businessmen because they cared about the work their companies did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Could Be a Very Bad Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/2016-bad-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 17:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/2016-bad-year/</guid>
      <description>People act according to what they expect.
And that, my friends, could be very bad news for the economy in 2016.
Social psychologists and usability experts both know that people&amp;rsquo;s words often conflict with their actions. This is especially true when asking people to predict their own behavior in a hypothetical.
For example, one study asked people to predict whether they would buy flowers for a charity. Eight-three percent of respondents said, &amp;ldquo;yes I would,&amp;rdquo; but only 43 percent actually did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Companies Should Adopt Conscious Capitalism Because It Pays</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/27/companies-adopt-conscious-capitalism-pays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 04:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/27/companies-adopt-conscious-capitalism-pays/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re going to hit me with the small sample size argument here, but that&amp;rsquo;s okay.
I firmly believe that the purpose of a company is to make life better, and if it does that well, it will make a profit. If, on the other hand, a company makes life worse, the market should let that company die.
Some companies try to improve life with insanely great technology products. Some make life better with fast, safe cars that are fun to drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conscious Capitalism:The One Book Every Conservative Must Read</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/26/heres-the-one-book-every-conservative-must-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/26/heres-the-one-book-every-conservative-must-read/</guid>
      <description>The motivating force behind the first tea party protests of February 27, 2009, was , in part, crony capitalism. Across the country and on the steps of the Arch in St. Louis, signs and speakers denounced bailouts for failed businesses.
Rasmussen found that 68 percent of Americans believe Big Business and Big Government work together against the rest of us.
I think they’re right.
Since then, crony capitalism has only grown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bain of Newt’s Existence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/17/the-bain-of-newts-existence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/17/the-bain-of-newts-existence/</guid>
      <description>Truth is, not all companies, not all business ideas, can make it on their own.
It’s easy to say that a good idea will automatically lead to a successful business. But it’s a lie.
Apple did not become Apple without investors. Sure, there are some examples of businesses that flourished without financial help. But not many. We’ll never know the wonderful ideas that died in their owner’s garage for lack of financing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMSL Killing American Males</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/10/umsl-killing-american-males/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 03:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/10/umsl-killing-american-males/</guid>
      <description>David Brooks—the former conservative—skewered the University of Missouri St. Louis yesterday. Brooks wasn’t aware, and UMSL administrators don’t read. But some of us caught it.
Brooks wrote of The Missing Fifth. **Did you know that 20 percent of American men in their primes don’t work? **
 Americans should be especially alert to signs that the country is becoming less vital and industrious. One of those signs comes to us from the labor market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generation Conflicted</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/generation-conflicted/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/generation-conflicted/</guid>
      <description>In the tech world, I meet a lot of brilliant, ambitious, hardworking entrepreneurs. These folks are committed to their dreams, working 100+ hour weeks, and paying themselves as little as possible. They stretch investors’ dollars to the limit and hunt for more VC to make dreams come true. They want to create jobs and better lives for many.
Over drinks, these young capitalists talk about three things:
  Easier access to capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8,000 Dow? *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/8000-dow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/8000-dow/</guid>
      <description>So says Yale economist Nouriel Roubini in an interview today on CNBC.
 &amp;ldquo;There are some parts of the global economy that are now at the risk of a double-dip recession,&amp;rdquo; said Roubini, head of Roubini Global Economics. &amp;ldquo;From here on I see things getting worse.&amp;rdquo;
 
Roubini’s comments came in response to a 376 point drop in the Dow Industrials. Nasdaq and S&amp;amp;P 500 were off significantly as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edward Whitacre Jr. Lies **Update: NYT Agrees**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/01/edward-whitacre-jr-lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 01:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/01/edward-whitacre-jr-lies/</guid>
      <description>No, General Motors did not pay back its debt to taxpayers. Edward Whitacre is a liar. Instead, Whitacre paid the Visa bill with his MasterCard. But both cards were issued by the same bank. So you, the banker, are still on the hook for the full amount.
Now we know why Obama hand-picked Ed Whitacre to “lead” GM: Whitacre will do the president’s bidding.
[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SOaS2SymjQ4&amp;amp;w;=425&amp;amp;h;=355]
UPDATE From Hotair.com: New York Times agrees that Whitacre and White House ain&amp;rsquo;t tellin&amp;rsquo; the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If The Post Office Built Cars</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/03/if-the-post-office-built-cars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 02:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/03/if-the-post-office-built-cars/</guid>
      <description>Some good people work at the Post Orifice. I know several. One of my dad&amp;rsquo;s best friends and WWII paratrooper retired from the Post Orifice. He was a great guy and good friend to my parents.
On the other hand, the United States Postal Service is among the incompetent, bureaucratic, broken down, 19th century, poorly managed excuses for an organization since the Soviet Union went out of business.
Case Study: Christmas Gift</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bunch of Hooey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/30/a-bunch-of-hooey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 18:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/30/a-bunch-of-hooey/</guid>
      <description>The silliness of companies knows no bounds.
The latest act of corporate stupidity comes from the computer maker Dell.
In its attempt to become the &amp;ldquo;greenest technology company on the planet,&amp;rdquo; Dell made much of achieving some farcically theoretical &amp;ldquo;carbon-neutral&amp;rdquo; status. But, like everything associated with AGW, there&amp;rsquo;s really no so thing. WSJ points out in a wonderful examination today:
 In fact, that&amp;rsquo;s only a small fraction of all the emissions associated with Dell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predictions for 2009</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/predictions-for-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 22:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/predictions-for-2009/</guid>
      <description>After a 2 year hiatus from annual predictions, here&amp;rsquo;s what I see happening in the precarious Year of our Lord Two-thousand nine:
The Dow: The Dow trades within a range of 1,000 points with a daily average closing of 8,500.
GDP and Economy: By July, everyone pretty much calls the situation &amp;ldquo;Great Depression II.&amp;rdquo; Unemployment, which declines in the first quarter, increases to more than 12 percent by fall. Gross Domestic Product by quarter:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Approaching Tipping Point</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/21/linux-approaching-tipping-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/21/linux-approaching-tipping-point/</guid>
      <description>Rarely does a single factor cause a paradigm shift. For one example, look at the election of Ronald Reagan. Sure, Reagan had a great message, expert delivery, and that presidential look. But without Carter&amp;rsquo;s bungling incompetence, excesses by liberals in Congress, a runaway Supreme Court, Soviet expansion, stagflation, the Iranian hostage crisis, and seventeen thousand other annoying problems, Reagan would not have upset an incumbent president in 1980.
**
Revenge of the Nerds**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America, you just bought yourself 3 car manufacturers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/09/america-you-just-bought-yourself-3-car-manufacturers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2008 02:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/09/america-you-just-bought-yourself-3-car-manufacturers/</guid>
      <description>Apparently Bush&amp;rsquo;s plan to socialize all of America before leaving the White House is alive and well. Some sort of a crappy deal has been reached.
The plan includes a car czar&amp;ndash;something that Toyata, Nissan, and Honda miraculously do not need&amp;ndash;to run the auto industry like a DMV license office. The last time a government designed, built, and sold an automobile like, it was called the Yugo. I&amp;rsquo;ll keep my SUV, thanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Auto Industry Doomed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/07/american-auto-industry-doomed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 16:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/07/american-auto-industry-doomed/</guid>
      <description>If you own US auto stock, sell.
If you work for a US auto maker, find a new job.
If you own a US-made car, start shopping.
The government is about to destroy the US auto industry, and it will cost billions of dollars.
Apparently, the White House and Congress are trying to invent an auto czar position to &amp;ldquo;oversee the restructuring of the industry [Wall Street Journal].&amp;rdquo; That means that the problems that led to the current crisis will get worse and the possible solutions to the crisis will be outlawed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homes for the Rest of Us</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/13/homes-for-the-rest-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 05:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/13/homes-for-the-rest-of-us/</guid>
      <description>Homes for the Rest of Us is my response to the mess that is the finance industry. The Harvard MBAs screwed up the whole finance thing. So how are people supposed to get houses? We&amp;rsquo;ll just have to take care of ourselves. And each other.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know exactly how this will work, but I am pretty damn sure we can make it happen.
There&amp;rsquo;s this great program called Kiva.org that allows people to make micro-loans to entrepreneurs, mostly in emerging or plain dysfunctional economies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s $26 Million Fannie Mae Be-atch</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/05/obamas-26-million-fannie-mae-be-atch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 20:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/05/obamas-26-million-fannie-mae-be-atch/</guid>
      <description>Her name is Jamie Gorelick. She was the principal architect of Al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s ability to plan and execute the 9-11 attacks under US intel&amp;rsquo;s radar. She took $26 Million in six years from Fannie Mae by ordering accountants and internal auditors to falsify records and forge documents so ensure that she, Jim Johnson, Franklin Raines, and other Democrat executives at Fannie received maximum bonuses.
FoxNews.com:
 Lehman Brothers collapse is traced back to Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, the two big mortgage banks that got a federal bailout a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hubris</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/21/hubris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 17:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/21/hubris/</guid>
      <description>From the
Mercury News:
 Barack Obama made the calamity on Wall Street the central theme of his case against John McCain on Saturday, invoking the crisis to pound his rival on Social Security, health care and government reform.
 Let me get this straight: The highest-paid Fannie Mae/Freddie Mac politician on the planet wants to blame the financial crisis on the only politician whom Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac were unable to bribe!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franklin Raines&#39; Criminal Enterprise and Barack Obama, His Accomplice **UPDATE** Top Recipients By $/Yr in Congress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/15/franklin-raines-criminal-enterprise-and-barack-obama-his-accomplice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 01:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/15/franklin-raines-criminal-enterprise-and-barack-obama-his-accomplice/</guid>
      <description>TOP OF PAGE UPDATE
This is an eye-opener. I&amp;rsquo;ve simply added Years in Congress and divided total Fraudie
Mae and Fraudie Mac donations by that number to rank the top 15 recipients by $ per Year. Obama is winner by a ton:
Download Spreadsheet FannieMaeEarningsByYearsInCongress

As an executive at Fannie Mae, Franklin Raines illegally coerced his employees to falsify accounting facts so he&amp;rsquo;d get a maximum bonus. The government-backed firm used Enron-like fraud, in part at Raines&amp;rsquo;s orders, to create the largest bail-out in US history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King of Beers Dethroned</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/19/king-of-beers-dethroned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 19:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/19/king-of-beers-dethroned/</guid>
      <description>Since A-B sold out to Belgian brewer InBev, things have changed in the St. Louis bar scene.
In a typical St. Louis County strip-mall bar during a Friday happy hour about 70 percent of the male patrons would sit behind an Anheuser-Busch product&amp;ndash;Budweiser, Bud Select, Bud Light, Michelob Ultra, even Busch.
Not anymore.
I stopped drinking Select as soon as the announcement of the buyout came last Sunday. But I was shocked last night when I walked into The Corner Pub &amp;amp; Grill in West St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deo Gratias</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/07/deo-gratias/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/07/deo-gratias/</guid>
      <description>When I first read bogus news stories about the significance of today&amp;rsquo;s date&amp;ndash;07/07/07&amp;ndash;I was dismissive, as I was of stories about the millennium bug (or &amp;ldquo;Y2K Problem&amp;rdquo;) back in the late 90s. (I made a decent amount of money fixing that bug, though.) It turns out 07/07/07 was a watershed.
Pope Benedict XVI released his long awaited motu proprio on the 1962 Missal today.
 It is, therefore, permissible to celebrate the Sacrifice of the Mass following the typical edition of the Roman Missal promulgated by Bl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move Your Company and Your Career Forward</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/03/24/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2007 12:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/03/24/12/</guid>
      <description>If you want to move your company—and your career—forward, concentrate on moving your product forward. Obvious, perhaps, but the concept gets little more than lip service in many organizations.
Most of my career in software development has involved web-based products that my companies sell or license to client businesses who, in turn, provide the applications for their clients’ use. For instance, at Abiliti Solutions (now FTS), we produced telecommunications billing and analysis software, a part of which included electronic bill (or invoice) presentment and payment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ameren: World&#39;s Worst Company?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/03/19/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 02:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/03/19/10/</guid>
      <description>After Ameren wiped out Johnson Shut-Ins State Park in southeastern Missouri, some of felt a little sorry for the company. Six months after that tragedy, a powerful thunderstorm knocked down power lines and transformers, leaving more than 100,000 Ameren customers without electricity – some for more than week. Still, Ameren had viable defenses. Among them:
·*Property owners blocked the company from trimming trees that threatened power lines
·*The storm was the strongest in 100 years</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>