<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Fourth Turning on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/the-fourth-turning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Fourth Turning on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 06:16:06 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/the-fourth-turning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fourth Turning Warning for America: Climax</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/a-fourth-turning-warning-for-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 06:16:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/a-fourth-turning-warning-for-america/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I warned, again, that the center didn&amp;rsquo;t hold. There is no center in American politics. Americans are more divided than at any time since the Civil War.
(Read We Have the War Upon Us by William J. Cooper)
Today, I have a short warning from the great book The Fourth Turning by Howe and Strauss.
What Should Have Happened after 2016 Strauss and Howe prophesied an election that changed everything sometime during the Crisis era which began with the fall of Lehman Brothers (the last time Nancy Pelosi was Speaker of the House):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 will change American culture at its core</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/26/2018-will-change-american-culture-at-its-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 18:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/26/2018-will-change-american-culture-at-its-core/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re wondering how things will change in 2018, you might think back the mid-1980s.
In the 1980s, leftist professors, leftist news media, and leftist entertainers were angry. For years, they&amp;rsquo;d preached that Ronald Reagan was a neo-Nazi buffoon whose incompetence and malice would destroy America. Maybe even wipe out the human species. &amp;ldquo;I believe Ronald Reagan can turn America back into what it once was,&amp;rdquo; said comedian Steve Martin on Saturday Night Live in 1980, &amp;ldquo;a vast wasteland covered with ice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Want You Dead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/09/people-want-you-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 23:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/09/people-want-you-dead/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself in the midst of a riot? Even if you’ve only seen riots on television, you can probably imagine how it feels to be inside one.
Imagine yourself surrounded on all sides by angry faces dressed in shabby clothes, some faces covered with bandanas or ski masks. People are chanting something you can&amp;rsquo;t quite understand, like a private joke you&amp;rsquo;re not allowed to get. Or maybe they&amp;rsquo;re chanting at you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>