<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>christianity on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/christianity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in christianity on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/christianity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Us Happy?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-makes-us-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-makes-us-happy/</guid>
      <description>Marc, at Bad Catholic, rocks.
In this post on Obama’s continuing jihad against Christianity, he answers a burning question: did human happiness exist before artificial contraception?
Put another way, is chemical birth control a natural state of humanity?
Before you answer, read the post. Think about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Romans Had Nothing on Us | *Video*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/19/the-romans-had-nothing-on-us-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/19/the-romans-had-nothing-on-us-video/</guid>
      <description>Do you know the most persecuted religious group on earth?
History speaks of the massive Roman persecution of Christians. The catacombs of Rome, housing the remains of thousands of Christian martyrs, tell us the story and give voice to the dead.
But the Romans had nothing on we moderns when it comes to persecuting Christians. Today, Christians are the most persecuted religious group on the planet. And the problem grows worse every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s War on Catholics Has Nothing To Do With Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Obama’s dictate that Catholic organizations must participate in contraception and abortion has nothing to do with healthcare or rights or contraception or anything of the sort. Not at all. Modern dictatorships don’t operate that way.
**Obama just destroyed the free practice clause of the First Amendment, and that’s exactly what he intended. **
 Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Israel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/13/go-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 23:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/13/go-israel/</guid>
      <description>No, I’m not a war monger. But peace is not the absence of war. It’s the presence of peace.

If you live in Israel, you are not at peace. You are at war. War against a massive body of people who want to destroy you before they move on to destroy Christendom. If Christendom doesn’t destroy itself first.
So let’s all thank Israel for standing tall on the front lines of this epic battle between good and evil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>