<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Military on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/military/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Military on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 04:43:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/military/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Must See Dunkirk</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/24/why-you-must-see-dunkirk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 04:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/24/why-you-must-see-dunkirk/</guid>
      <description>When Winston Churchill mouthed these eternal words, his nation&amp;rsquo;s life expectancy was about six months.
All of Western Civilization, all of Christiandom, seemed doomed.
One defiant man ended a speech to his House of Commons with this:
 I have, myself, full confidence that if all do their duty, if nothing is neglected, and if the best arrangements are made, as they are being made, we shall prove ourselves once again able to defend our Island home, to ride out the storm of war, and to outlive the menace of tyranny, if necessary for years, if necessary alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Terrible Day for the Navy Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/18/a-terrible-day-for-the-navy-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 14:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/18/a-terrible-day-for-the-navy-family/</guid>
      <description>[SEARCH CALLED OFF  US Navy ends hunt for 7 missing sailors as bodies are found in the ship](https://www.foxnews.com/world/2017/06/18/us-navy-calls-off-search-for-7-missing-sailors-several-bodies-found-inside-destroyer.html)
  I saw the FoxNews.com headline last night. My face sagged. Those tiny muscles that control our facial expressions all fell asleep at once. A long, slow breath-flood rushed from my slack lips.
I thought about those seven families. The families who haven&amp;rsquo;t heard from their USS Fitzgerald sailors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Faces of Memorial Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/30/two-faces-of-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 14:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/30/two-faces-of-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>The god of Memorial Day is Janus, looking to the future as well as the past.
Memorial Day looks back, but it also warns of something coming. The list of war dead is incomplete. It always will be.
Each generation looks at its wars and finds something final, but the end never comes. Memorials never end while man roams the earth.
When I see the Vietnam Memorial, with its rows and ranks of lost warriors, I see, too, the invisible ledger that stretches to the horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Have a New Son, America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/15/you-have-a-new-son-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/15/you-have-a-new-son-america/</guid>
      <description>My son Patrick (closest to the camera at a civilian’s idea of parade rest) listens to the instructions of the enlisting officer among 9 young men and women preparing to swear an oath to the Constitution of the United States. They were here to make their first commitment to the armed forces.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_16700&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;711&amp;rdquo;]Patrick Hennessy takes the oath of enlistment at the Federal Building in St. Louis August 14, 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Leadership?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/14/what-is-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 16:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/14/what-is-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Many of you loved Simon Sinek’s Start With Why TEDx talk.
I love the way Simon Sinek thinks. It’s no surprise, then, that his TED Talk on leadership could be the greatest definition of leadership I’ve ever heard.
Please watch and share. I have some thoughts and a poll following. [ted id=1998]
Contrasts give greater clarity. Sinek’s contrast between military leadership and business leadership says a lot about the state of American business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>