<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>obama on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/obama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in obama on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:41:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/obama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When Democrats Loved &#39;em Some Ruskies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/when-democrats-loved-em-some-ruskies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/when-democrats-loved-em-some-ruskies/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/Py8BF0hHPnc
In 2012, Barack Obama got caught telling Russian Prime Minister Medvedev that he&amp;rsquo;d have more &amp;ldquo;flexibility&amp;rdquo; after the election.
Later in 2012, during a debate, Obama accused GOP candidate Mitt Romney of stoking Cold War fears against our new friends in Moscow. Obama said, “The 1980s are now calling to ask for their foreign policy back because…the Cold War’s been over for 20 years!” In fact, in 2012, the whole pantheon of pantsuit partiersmocked warnings about Russia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do we owe Obama an apology?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/01/do-we-owe-obama-an-apology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 23:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/01/do-we-owe-obama-an-apology/</guid>
      <description>Imaginations can run wild in the affinity bubble.
I was in Washington, DC, over the weekend when it dawned on me that we on the right were probably wrong about Obama&amp;rsquo;s thirst for dictatorial power. Or maybe we were right, but seven years of near-dictatorial power have exhausted the would-be autocrat. He certain looks worn down, as this Time magazine side-by-side shows:
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_18520&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] President Obama in 2009 and again in 2016[/caption]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unbearable Lightness of Being There</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/the-unbearable-lightness-of-being-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 03:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/the-unbearable-lightness-of-being-there/</guid>
      <description>Eve: May I ask your name? Chance: Chance. Eve: Chance? Chance: Chance, the gardener. Eve: Chauncey Gardiner? Mr. Chauncey Gardiner. Are you related to Basil and Perdita Gardiner?
 &amp;ndash; Being There, 1979
 People tell us who they are, but we ignore it. Because we want them to be what we we want them to be.
 &amp;ndash;Don Draper, Mad Men
President Obama used his third Oval Office address in seven years to say &amp;ldquo;Honey, I shrunk the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Have Just One Chance for October Surprise</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 16:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</guid>
      <description>The White House and its corrupt Department of Justice has one chance to change the election&amp;rsquo;s outcome.According to Nate Silver&amp;rsquo;s FiveThirtyEight blog, the GOP has a 62.1 percent chance of a Senate majority. With nine days left until the election, and with President Obama&amp;rsquo;s approval and likability plunging, the Democrats face a huge loss.
Apathetic Democrats Many political observers blame Democrat voter apathy, particularly among African-Americans. The black vote that swelled in 2008 and 2012 with Obama on the ballot shows signs of deflating in 2014 as it did in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be President When Russia Goes Berserk Starring Ronald Reagan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 03:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</guid>
      <description>Since the scrawny punk from Chicago still hasn&amp;rsquo;t figured it out, this President 101 lesson delivered without further comment:
https://youtu.be/9VA4W1wDMAk?t=18s
Previously on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View:
We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Katrina</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/09/obamas-katrina/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 03:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/09/obamas-katrina/</guid>
      <description>Visuals: Some of the thousands of children suffering in a humanitarian disaster at the US border on the top of the split screen. On the bottom, President Obama drinking beer and shooting pool with locals 246 miles away.

Audio: President on deploying National Guard to alleviate humanitarian crisis: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to consider it,&amp;rdquo; but it would be &amp;ldquo;a temporary solution.&amp;rdquo;
Face it: the press was going to blame George Bush for Katrina no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Abdullah Kicks Obama Out of Saudia Arabia ? **Video Added**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 00:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think American foreign policy couldn&amp;rsquo;t sink any lower than standing by while Vladimir Putin re-conquers the Warsaw Pact nations. Then you&amp;rsquo;ve underestimated Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s incompetence.
Apparently, Obama didn&amp;rsquo;t bow low enough to King Abdullah of Saudi Arabia. Whatever happened, an &amp;ldquo;intimate&amp;rdquo; evening planned for Obama and Abdullah was abruptly cancelled after a two-hour meeting between the two leaders. A meeting intended to &amp;ldquo;mend fences&amp;rdquo; between the two men.
UPDATE: Here&amp;rsquo;s the video from Lou Dobbs on Fox Business</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Would You Do If You Were Putin?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 18:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</guid>
      <description>You saw Obama stand by as you threatened Georgia in 2009.
You heard Obama whisper to Medvedev that he’ll be willing to defy Congress to capitulate to you after Obama’s re-election.
You watched Obama and his bumbling Secretary of State mangle its its own strategy in Syria—if the US ever had a Syrian strategy at all.
You saw that the US was completely unprepared for your annexation of Crimea.
You see the headlines of massive NSA spying on US citizens, though that same NSA was blind to your invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Will Putin Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/will-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 01:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/will-putin/</guid>
      <description>Ask yourself this: why did the stock markets rally today after Obama announced sanctions against Russians? I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to that, but first some background.
I&amp;rsquo;ve often said that Putin plays chess while Obama fumbles with checkers. I picture our president, chin resting on fist, brows squeezed in childlike concentration, as he carefully chooses between jumping Putin&amp;rsquo;s piece to end the game or getting another of his pieces &amp;ldquo;kinged.&amp;rdquo;
Of course, Obama goes for the kingship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Conservatives: We Are Already Losing 2016</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/18/dear-conservatives-we-are-already-losing-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/18/dear-conservatives-we-are-already-losing-2016/</guid>
      <description>If you need to blame someone for our election losses, blame me.

I Let You Down I could have done more. I could have spoken up sooner. I could have been more honest with you about the mistakes we made and the opportunities we ignored. I could have worked harder on what I saw as the most important work we could do.
I let you down. I focused on petty issues of the day, too, instead of working on a different future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Petraeus Taking Obama With Him?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/what-if-petraeus-knew-exactly-what-he-was-doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/what-if-petraeus-knew-exactly-what-he-was-doing/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a flight of fantasy. If anything in this post is later shown to conform reality, it’s pure coincidence. Nor am I accusing Gen. Petraeus of any crime or of compromising of national security secrets. (Just enjoy it, will ya?) A sex scandal rocks the king of spies.
An email chain unravels the Pentagon high command.
A cover-up exposed.
It&amp;rsquo;s like the back cover of a Nelson DeMille novel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Conspire to Suppress Republican Turnout</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/media-conspire-to-suppress-republican-turnout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 23:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/media-conspire-to-suppress-republican-turnout/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s KSDK.com is doing its fair share to suppress the Republican voter turnout. They&amp;rsquo;re pumping a handful of counted votes to give the impression that Obama is walking away with the national popular vote:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the scam. Only 42 votes have been counted in a country of 150 million registered voters. In other words, it&amp;rsquo;s crap. No responsible news organization would post such misleading nonsense&amp;ndash;except in hopes of discouraging Romney voters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Shuts Down Another Small Business</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 01:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</guid>
      <description>200,000 That&amp;rsquo;s the number of** small businesses lost during the Obama Administration**.
If re-elected, Obama promises to accelerate the policies that destroyed American jobs, investments, and companies.
https://youtu.be/NlFHrLeeJIU
Voting isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. We need your help at 9966 Lin Ferry Drive, St. Louis, MO 63123.
Pick you day to work the phones and get out the vote:
 * Friday, November 2 Noon to 8 p.m. * Saturday, November 3 Noon to 5 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s How Nate Silver Determines Obama’s Chances of Winning</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/29/heres-how-nate-silver-determines-obamas-chances-of-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/29/heres-how-nate-silver-determines-obamas-chances-of-winning/</guid>
      <description>Nate Silver publishes a daily number that represents Barack Obama’s chances of being re-elected. As I write this on October 27, Silver’s magic number is 74%.
[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sKTUiwhac8Q&amp;amp;w=351&amp;amp;h=216&amp;amp;hd=1]
Nate Silver explains his scientific approach to picking winners in elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When The Three O&#39;Clock Call Came, Barack Obama Froze</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</guid>
      <description>The fog of war is lifting from Benghazi, and what lies beneath should shame Obama’s most ardent supporters. Barack Obama choked, and Americans died.

When America came under attack, Obama panicked and froze.
When Americans under his direction pleaded for their lives, he was afraid to pull the trigger.
Here’s the emerging picture.
White House Ordered Military and CIA to Stand Down and Let Al Qaeda Kill Former Navy SEALs Ty Woods and Glen Doherty, so disgusted by the White House’s refusal to help Americans under attack, defied an order to stand down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Pollsters Aren’t Telling You</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/21/what-the-pollsters-arent-telling-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 04:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/21/what-the-pollsters-arent-telling-you/</guid>
      <description>Polls do influence elections. That’s why people like Nate Silver and some of the writers at Business Insider are doing somersaults over Gallup’s Daily Presidential Tracking numbers.

For over a week, Gallup has shown a tidal wave for support for Mitt Romney. Nate Silver of FiveThirtyEight tried to discredit Gallup by blogging about outlier results it’s shown in past years. Here’s the conclusion Business Insider reached:
 Bottom line: Gallup swings wildly and it frequently has results not in line with other pollsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turns Out The Guy Dumping On The Middle Class Is Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/09/turns-out-the-guy-dumping-on-the-middle-class-is-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/09/turns-out-the-guy-dumping-on-the-middle-class-is-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, Joe Biden made the news by declaring that the middle class in America has been getting dumped on ever since he and Obama took their oaths of office. The statement marked the first time Biden got something right since that day. What Uncle Joe failed to mention was that he has been in charge of the White House’s Middle Class Task Force since January 30, 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now We Know Why Mitt Romney Has Been Wildly Successful In Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 00:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama’s performance was not nearly as bad as Romney’s performance was good.

Not good—terrific.
I’m not talking about his politics and policies; I’m talking Romney’s remarkable presence. Here are the four principles of presence that Romney knocked out of the park.
Command of the Facts When it came to facts—and to how those facts matter to the listeners—Mitt Romney seemed more prepared for the office of President than the President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barack Obama Is Having a Very Bad Week, and Even WaPo Noticed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/26/barack-obamas-having-a-very-bad-week-and-even-wapo-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/26/barack-obamas-having-a-very-bad-week-and-even-wapo-noticed/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;180&amp;rdquo;] Barack Obama (Photo credit: jamesomalley)[/caption]
The smartest man in the world can’t make a gaffe, surely. When Barack Obama says something ridiculous, mean-spirited, wrongheaded, or just plain dumb, he means it.
So we know Obama considers the murders of Ambassador Chris Stevens and three others mere “bumps in the road” to his re-election. Four bumps, to be precise.
When Obama says Israel is just “one of our strongest allies” in the Middle East, no longer our strongest, he means it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Barack Obama is Right?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/19/which-barack-obama-is-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/19/which-barack-obama-is-right/</guid>
      <description>A genius is someone who can hold contrary concepts simultaneously in mind.
What, then, do we call a person who simultaneously argues two contrary concepts?

How ‘bout “demagogue?”
A few weeks ago, Barack Obama told America’s business owners that they are not responsible for their success. “Someone else built that.”
Today, the same Obama told Mitt Romney that there not many people who consider themselves victims.
Does Mr. Obama believe that people in dire straights are not victims of circumstances?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Trust Barack Obama for 4 More Years?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/17/can-you-trust-barack-obama-for-4-more-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/17/can-you-trust-barack-obama-for-4-more-years/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama came to office promising to heal the planet (I didn’t know it was sick), lower the waters, and end war as we knew it “whilst waking on water squirting wine out his ass,” to borrow William S. Burroughs’s anti-Christian blasphemy in Naked Lunch. (Funny. I don’t recall reading about Christians blowing up embassies over that book’s publication.)

Four years later, The One might want to let the waters rise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the Romney Campaign Serious About Winning?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/11/is-the-romney-campaign-serious-about-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 10:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/11/is-the-romney-campaign-serious-about-winning/</guid>
      <description>The Romney Campaign today reminded me of the McCain Campaign of 2008.
I&amp;rsquo;m pretty good at ignoring bogus, fraudulent polls like the one CNN released tonight. In that poll, CNN announced a massive 52-46 national lead for Obama. If true, the race would be all but over.
CNN, of course, cooked the books on this one.
About one-third of voters describe themselves as independents, CNN sampled only 3% independents for its latest poll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Warning Signs That Obama’s Imploding</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/02/7-warning-signs-that-obamas-imploding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 21:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/02/7-warning-signs-that-obamas-imploding/</guid>
      <description>Hurricane Isaac smiled on the Republicans in Tampa and delivered more misery to New Orleans and its surroundings. That was just one of the ominous signs that 2012 is shaping up to be a forgettable year for Democrats, especially for Barack Obama.

Here’s seven more warning signs that Obama’s 6-year campaign is about to implode:
1. Torrential Rains Wipe the Face of Mount Obamamore
Not that weather plays favorites, but you have wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Theory and the Ryan Pick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/game-theory-and-the-ryan-pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 21:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/game-theory-and-the-ryan-pick/</guid>
      <description>If Mitt Romney applied game theory in choosing Paul Ryan, I have renewed respect for him. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain why, but first a bit of background on game theory.
Game theory is a branch of social science concerned with strategic decision-making. It is most closely associated with economics. Professor John Nash, the subject of the movie A Beautiful Mind, won a Nobel Prize in Economics for his work in game theory. (For a great primer on the subject, read Thinking Strategically: the competitive advantage in business, politics, and everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romney-Ryan Have a Vision They Can Talk About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/11/obamas-surrounded-by-really-nasty-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 02:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/11/obamas-surrounded-by-really-nasty-people/</guid>
      <description>Why did murder skyrocket in Chicago as soon as Rahm Emanuel became mayor? Why have Americans become nastier and meaner since Barack Obama became president?

As Michael Dukakis told us, a fish rots from the head down. Obama surrounds himself with people who thrive on decay and death.
After four years, Obama has nothing to say for himself. Nothing. He can only cut and attack and lie and sneer and mock like a high school bully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Economy Is Getting Worse Thanks to Liberalism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/25/the-economy-is-getting-worse-thanks-to-liberalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 10:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/25/the-economy-is-getting-worse-thanks-to-liberalism/</guid>
      <description>The horror in Aurora, Colorado, gave President Obama a little cover last Friday. That&amp;rsquo;s because the Labor Department announced that unemployment rose in 27 states.
President Obama promised to hold unemployment under eight percent if Congress passed the stimulus package in 2009. Congress did, but Obama failed. Remember all those green jobs? They&amp;rsquo;re gone.
**The problem isn&amp;rsquo;t Barack Obama; the problem is liberalism. **
Liberals believe that only experts can make intelligent decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Old Reagan Soviet Jokes Are on US</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/18/the-old-reagan-soviet-jokes-are-on-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/18/the-old-reagan-soviet-jokes-are-on-us/</guid>
      <description>Ronald Reagan loved to tell jokes about the Soviet Union.If Obama’s re-elected, though, these same jokes could be turned on the United States.

Some of them already can be.
 It&amp;rsquo;s hard to get an automobile in the United States. They are owned mainly by elite bureaucrats. It takes an average of 10 years to get a car. 1 out of 7 families owned automobiles. You have to go through a major process and put the money out in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If the election were held today, there’d be a lot of crying and gnashing of teeth</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/17/gnashing-of-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/17/gnashing-of-teeth/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a screen grab from RealClearPolitics.com’s presidential tracking poll:

RCP aggregates dozens of polls to produce its RCP average. The method has been remarkably accurate, especially at the state level.
It’s time to focus on preventing the unmitigated disaster of a second Obama term.
In 112 days, Americans will vote on whether or not to continue our experiment in self-government. If the election were held today, that experiment would be aborted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just How Bad Would a Second Obama Term Be?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/16/just-how-bad-would-a-second-obama-term-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/16/just-how-bad-would-a-second-obama-term-be/</guid>
      <description>If you believe that 92 percent of people need to have most aspect of their lives managed by experts, then a second Obama term will make you happy.

If, however, you believe in self-governance, that people are endowed by God and nature with the capacity and unalienable right to manage their own affairs, then a second Obama term will be a massive human rights violation.
Consider what the Obama administration has already brought us:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is One Sign That Your Government Is Tyrannical</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/03/here-is-one-sign-your-government-is-tyrannical/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/03/here-is-one-sign-your-government-is-tyrannical/</guid>
      <description>We throw around big scary words like “tyranny” too much. I’m guilty myself. While we get a lot of attention with hyperbole, we’ll lose credibility over time. Then when tyranny emerges, people will ignore our screams.
Like now.

For years, Congress has used the tax code to motivate behavior. Tax credits for insulated windows and electric cars are examples. The home mortgage deduction is another. And tuition tax credits, dependent tax credits, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Never Guess Who&#39;s About to Become Obama&#39;s Biggest Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>In 2008, we heard all about the youth movement for Obama. We heard that the enormous Millennial Generation, born between 1982 and 2001, would destroy the GOP and everything America once stood for&amp;ndash;like jobs, family, faith, and hard work. And when Obama won, many believed the tales of the Obama Youth.

But many were wrong. Voters under 30 have had it with vague promises and glittering bullshit from that punk from Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Differences Between Bain and Solyndra</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/23/3-differences-between-bain-and-solyndra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 09:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/23/3-differences-between-bain-and-solyndra/</guid>
      <description>As Obama and his myrmidons continue to make asses of themselves by arguing that no one should ever put their own capital at risk, it seems timely to point out that Solyndra, and the White House&amp;rsquo;s many gambles on hypothetical energy companies, is not a fair comparison to Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s work at Bain &amp;amp; Co.
   It&amp;rsquo;s legal for individuals and companies to use their own money to buy failing companies and try to save them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Holds Auditions for New Terrorist Mastermind</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/01/u-s-holds-auditions-for-new-terrorist-mastermind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 15:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/01/u-s-holds-auditions-for-new-terrorist-mastermind/</guid>
      <description>Washington, DC&amp;ndash;Reeling from the backlash over a campaign ad that paints President Barack Obama as Osama bin Laden&amp;rsquo;s sole assassin, the White House today announced open auditions for a new global terrorist mastermind.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12119&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;570&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Last year&amp;rsquo;s White House auditions for press secretary&amp;rdquo;][/caption]
White House spokesman Jay Carney told reporters &amp;ldquo;the world needs a dangerous, evil character to worry about . . . and, frankly, so does the President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Election’s Over, and America Gave Obama His Eviction Notice. Here’s What Went Down.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/the-elections-over-and-america-gave-obama-his-eviction-notice-heres-what-went-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/the-elections-over-and-america-gave-obama-his-eviction-notice-heres-what-went-down/</guid>
      <description>The look on George “Stephie” Stephanopoulos’s face was priceless. He had to say it.

“ABC News now projects that President Obama will go down to defeat.”
He couldn’t bring himself to say, “Romney won” or “Republicans won.” He just couldn’t.
The network analysis was a political cliché run amok. My favorite came from James Carville who told CNN viewers that the election result “proves that crackers and racists vote.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Cancelled Religious Freedom, But Some People Aren&#39;t Listening to Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/obama-cancelled-religious-freedom-but-some-people-arent-listening-to-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 10:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/obama-cancelled-religious-freedom-but-some-people-arent-listening-to-obama/</guid>
      <description>When Obama decreed that Catholics shall support and provide chemical abortions,he wasn&amp;rsquo;t promoting women. He was shackling religion.
Totalitarian autocrats don&amp;rsquo;t cotton freedom, unless they personally granted it. Obama doesn&amp;rsquo;t believe in individual liberty, but that all power and rights emanate from government. Timothy Cardinal Dolan agrees.
So it&amp;rsquo;s exciting to report that some St. Louisans are fighting back. Here&amp;rsquo;s the details:
Protest for Religious Freedom
Location: Old Courthouse (Directions) Date: Saturday, April 28, 2012 Time: 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Will Also Decide the Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-supreme-court-will-also-decide-the-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-supreme-court-will-also-decide-the-election/</guid>
      <description>When the Supreme Court rules on ObamaCare, it will define Barack Obama as either a winner or loser.

James Carville says overturning ObamaCare would be the best thing that could happen to Democrats. I think he’s wrong.
ObamaCare is the centerpiece of Obama’s term in office. He put all of America’s business on hold for a year to pass it. He coerced, lied, intimidated, and threatened to get the law passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Us Happy?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-makes-us-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-makes-us-happy/</guid>
      <description>Marc, at Bad Catholic, rocks.
In this post on Obama’s continuing jihad against Christianity, he answers a burning question: did human happiness exist before artificial contraception?
Put another way, is chemical birth control a natural state of humanity?
Before you answer, read the post. Think about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Surging in the Polls; Here’s Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/obamas-surging-in-the-polls-heres-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/obamas-surging-in-the-polls-heres-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</guid>
      <description>Don’t bother blaming it on poll questions designed to lead respondents. Never mind that it’s a long way until the election. And stop whining about the White House fudging the numbers on unemployment.
The fact is that Obama’s surging at just the right time. His re-election chances are now above 50 percent. His intrade.com chances of winning are near 60 percent. And he’s raising more money than al of the Republican candidates combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Save Religious Freedom in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/13/how-you-can-save-religious-freedom-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/13/how-you-can-save-religious-freedom-in-america/</guid>
      <description>When Barack Obama declared that Catholics must either violate their consciences or face government persecution, he wasn’t going after just Catholics. Nor was he promoting healthcare.
Barack Obama and his myrmidon Kathleen Sebelius tried to erase the First Amendment. They tried to erase religious freedom. They tried to take away yet another foundational liberty that made America America.
**And they will try again**
Unless you stop them.
But how are you going to stop them alone?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s War on Catholics Has Nothing To Do With Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Obama’s dictate that Catholic organizations must participate in contraception and abortion has nothing to do with healthcare or rights or contraception or anything of the sort. Not at all. Modern dictatorships don’t operate that way.
**Obama just destroyed the free practice clause of the First Amendment, and that’s exactly what he intended. **
 Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney’s Resume Cover Letter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/09/mitt-romneys-resume-cover-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/09/mitt-romneys-resume-cover-letter/</guid>
      <description>There are some things you just don’t say in a cover letter—or on the campaign trail.
A self-aggrandizing cover letter from an NYU undergrad to some Wall Street banks has the whole financial world laughing. The kid’s naïve hubris and ignorance of what employers look for in a candidate earned him public humiliation on an internet scale. Here’s just a sample of the kid’s self-promotion:
 That semester I achieved a 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Were You When Obama Nullified the Constitution?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>Most Americans know more about forensic evidence in the Casey Anthony case than they do about the Constitution. That ignorance gave Barack Obama the hubris to end constitutional government in the United States. He did it, and you probably didn’t even notice.
Over the course of a week, Barack Obama made a series of so-called recess appointments. In the process, he and his henchmen in Eric Holder’s Justice Department effectively nullified the US Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Me “Apologist”</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/13/call-me-apologist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/13/call-me-apologist/</guid>
      <description>The Washington Post’s headline writer made a common mistake on Sunday.

He confused “one who apologizes” with “apologist.”
An easy mistake, no doubt, for most of us. Professional headline writers should know better. So should Glenn Kessler, the author of the WP story.
 The claim that Obama is an apologist for the nation began to take shape shortly after he became president.
 An apologist is “one who speaks or writes in defense of someone or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas: Point of No Return</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/08/kansas-point-of-no-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/08/kansas-point-of-no-return/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday in Kansas, President Barack Obama revealed his contempt for liberty. He declared that human beings are incapable of running their own lives . . . but, somehow, other, superior human beings are capable of running their own and others’.
He said that free markets have always failed, everywhere . . . ignoring most of the last 240 years.
He all but declared himself a Marxist.
I am depressed that America let this dangerous man into our government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama the Reckless</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/08/obama-the-reckless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/08/obama-the-reckless/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, the United States suffered its highest human lost since the Afghanistan conflict began. At least 38 elite, brave American warriors died in combat.
Flasback to May 23 of this year. That’s when Barack Obama made the surprise announcement that he would begin accelerated troop withdrawals in July. That timetable meant beginning the withdrawal during the summer fighting season.
Current and former military experts advised the president against this reckless move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Things to Question About Debt Deal</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/01/5-things-to-question-about-debt-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 12:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/01/5-things-to-question-about-debt-deal/</guid>
      <description>Yes, the Tea Party movement influenced what went on in Washington.
No, the Tea Party is not the winner. (No one won.)
No, this debt deal won’t guide the government off the road toward bankruptcy. Here’s why.
  No Entitlement Fix: In fact, it appears that entitlements aren’t touched. Entitlements are the nation’s spending problem. Not roads and bridges, not the military. Entitlements. Until we arrest and reverse growth in Social Security, Medicare, and Medicaid, we’re spitting in the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Last, Obama’s Ready to Borrow More Money from China</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/22/at-last-obamas-ready-to-borrow-more-money-from-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/22/at-last-obamas-ready-to-borrow-more-money-from-china/</guid>
      <description>The headline on July 15 was knee-slapping funny:
 Obama says he’s “ready to move**” on debt ceiling. **
 Really? The man who dug a deeper debt hole in two years than anyone else did in 8—or 15—is willing to borrow more?
Say it ain’t so.
For those who believe Obama’s some sort of deficit hawk, let’s take a quick stroll down memory.
 Obama wanted to increase the debt limit by $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>80 Percent of Americans Read This Blog Every Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/16/80-percent-of-americans-read-this-blog-every-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/16/80-percent-of-americans-read-this-blog-every-day/</guid>
      <description>I’ll be honest with you: I’ve lied.
Usually out of desperation. I’ve lied to those closest to me—those most willing to forgive the thing I lied about.
I’ve also told the truth to my own detriment. In the long run, the latter works best. In fact, telling the truth works best in the short run, too.
So maybe Obama’s desperate. Maybe he knows that the debt ceiling debate is the beginning of the unraveling of Americum Sovieticum, his life-long dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimme More Money or Granny Gets It!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/12/gimme-more-money-or-granny-gets-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/12/gimme-more-money-or-granny-gets-it/</guid>
      <description>Obama showed his breaking point today. The stress got to him.
Today Obama threatened to stop Social Security payments if Congress doesn’t bend to his will on the debt ceiling.
The president told reporters that there may not be enough money to pay Social Security benefits on and after August 3rd.
But the President lies.
Revenue from taxes and other fees would cover Social Security and other payments. What won’t be covered is additional borrowing to service the country’s already outrageous debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Makes It Worse</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/06/03/obama-makes-it-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 14:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/06/03/obama-makes-it-worse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rdquo; could refer to anything. Anything at all.
In this case, though, I&amp;rsquo;m referring to unemployment. Well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;m referring to the economy overall.
Unemployment rate rises to 9.1%, 54K jobs added « Hot Air
Obama has increased regulation, seized entire industries (auto, student loans, commercial banking, medicine), and borrowed more money faster than all previous presidents combined.
Obama is a one-dictator disaster. And an incompetent one at that.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a job, Obama made it worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No “Vital National Interest”</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/29/no-vital-national-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/29/no-vital-national-interest/</guid>
      <description>ABC News is not known as President Obama’s loudest critic. More like his Amen corner. So it’s headline screams even louder:
Defense Secretary: Libya Did Not Pose Threat to U.S., Was Not &amp;lsquo;Vital National Interest&amp;rsquo; to Intervene
The rest of Jake Tapper’s story gets more disturbing.
* The President and the Defense Secretary seem to disagree on national interest** The Secretary of State cannot articulate a consistent US policy** Hillary Clinton seems to believe that the UN is a legal alternative to the US Congress  More than week into a war that lacks even the thinnest thread of Constitutionality, Barack Obama seems clueless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Disgraceful Presidency</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/23/a-disgraceful-presidency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 16:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/23/a-disgraceful-presidency/</guid>
      <description>Historians will mark March 19 as the day the Obama presidency reached its point of no return.
The image of a cowardly and selfish child-president flying to Brazil to launch a war will haunt his legacy, like Nixon’s vulgarities on tape in 1974. Obama’s war on Libya has doomed an already weak administration.
Today, Germany pulled out of NATO because of the bungled, late, and idiotic intervention. It appears, now, that the alliance that won the Cold War and help sustain two decades of peace could collapse under a lack of American leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Libya: To What End?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/20/libya-to-what-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 18:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/20/libya-to-what-end/</guid>
      <description>When the US invaded Iraq in 2003, it do so with the clear intent of bringing its enemy—Saddam’s regime—to an unconditional surrender. That was the objective. Despite what happened after that objective was achieved, we went in with a clear and measurable purpose.
The motivating reason for our foray into Iraq was also clear. We believed at the time that Saddam Hussein’s possession of &amp;ndash; and desire for more &amp;ndash; weapons of mass destruction posed an imminent threat to US interests and citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simply Staggering</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/07/simply-staggering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 22:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/07/simply-staggering/</guid>
      <description>The federal budget deficit in the month of February 2011 exceeds the deficit for all of 2007 by 40 percent.
Simply staggering.
Yet Senate Democrats refuse to cut more than a paltry $6 billion. They refuse because they seem bent on collapsing the American system – the economy, the government, and the people themselves.
But at least the Obama administration stands by with its arms folded as gasoline prices skyrocket at the their fastest pace in history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waning US Influence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/05/waning-us-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/05/waning-us-influence/</guid>
      <description>Pro-Western governments in these countries have fallen to anti-American forces or diminished their support for the US since Barack Obama became president.
* Lebanon** Jordan** Yemen** Qatar** Egypt** Turkey  Obama’s campaign promise to restore respect for America around the world is a joke. A cruel and dangerous joke. Our enemies see Obama’s weakness as American weakness. As they did during Jimmy Carter’s failed presidency, those enemies are advancing.
The next president will have more than a financial catastrophe to fix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Contempt for the Rule of Law</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/obamas-contempt-for-the-rule-of-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 10:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/obamas-contempt-for-the-rule-of-law/</guid>
      <description>When he identified the three branches of government as President, House, and Senate, Was Chuck Schumer confused, or did he accurately state the Obama administration’s intent to subjugate the Judicial Branch of government? It seems the White House no longer considers the Judicial Branch the equal of the Executive.
In two cases—the Gulf oil drilling ban and Obamacare—the White House refuses to obey ruling from federal judges. In New Orleans, federal judge Martin Feldman found the White House in contempt for its re-imposition of oil drilling bans after his previous ruling to the contrary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A President Seriously Out of Touch</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/02/a-president-seriously-out-of-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/02/a-president-seriously-out-of-touch/</guid>
      <description>Did you enjoy President Obama’s gooey nostalgia for the Happy Days of Eisenhower and Howdy Doody as much I did?

Saul Alinsky warned radicals to “never go outside the expertise of your people.” But desperate times call for desperate measures, so Obama jumped the shark to the time of Potsy and Fonzie and Joannie Loves Chachi to rekindle a flavor of Americana that died a couple of years before Obama was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forcing Functions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/01/forcing-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/01/forcing-functions/</guid>
      <description>An old boss of mine liked “forcing functions.” Forced us to meet delivery dates, while arbitrary dates tended to cause a “so what” attitude toward deadlines. Forcing functions like trade shows, magazine reviews, and client launches forced development teams to ship, no matter what.
Keep that in mind for a moment while we look at the Obama Administration.
Barack Obama campaigned on a promise to clip America’s wings. I know he didn’t use that term, but it was clear what he meant when he visited the Mediterranean and Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s 1978 All Over Again **UPDATE: Thaddeus McCotter Agrees With Me**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/28/its-1978-all-over-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 22:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/28/its-1978-all-over-again/</guid>
      <description>The news might seem unimportant to us in the USA:
 Day after day they marched, tens of thousands strong, defiant chanting demonstrators surging through the streets of Cairo, a capital unaccustomed to the shouts and echoes of dissent. The subject of their protest was the policies of Egypt’s supreme ruler, Hosni Mubarak. Some carried signs demanding his ouster. Others called for a return of long denied civil and political liberties and the enforcement of Islamic laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I went to a memorial. . . and all I got was this lousy t-shirt *UPDATE* Michelle Malkin Reminds Us of Another Massacre Memorial</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/i-went-to-a-memorial-and-all-i-got-was-this-lousy-t-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 04:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/i-went-to-a-memorial-and-all-i-got-was-this-lousy-t-shirt/</guid>
      <description>**Obama Productions Inc. ** Garish chic. No other way to describe it.
Where were the Greek columns? No official sponsors? Why not GM and Goldman Sachs?
While Obama’s speech was appropriate and well delivered—his best since taking office—the crass and tasteless setting, the shouting and cheering, the lack of dignity and solemnity, will mark this event as an embarrassment to the country and an affront to the families and victims. Step one of triangulation is admitting that your base is a bunch of wacked out hatemongers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Signs of Economic Disaster</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/3-signs-of-economic-disaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/3-signs-of-economic-disaster/</guid>
      <description>Each day, more economists jump onto the Double-Dip bandwagon. Signs abound that the natural economic recovery that would normally follow a deep recession won’t happen. Instead, the economy is now saddled with so much debt, so many regulations, and such onerous new taxes that the Obama Administration tells us to be happy with 9.5 percent unemployment.

Barack Obama is an economic disaster of the first order.
So why all the pessimism?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2/3 Think Worst Is Yet to Come for USA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/11/23-think-worst-is-yet-to-come-for-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 03:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/11/23-think-worst-is-yet-to-come-for-usa/</guid>
      <description>The Wall Street Journal headline is grim:
   Grim Voter Mood Turns Grimmer  Underpinning the gloom: Nearly two-thirds of Americans believe the economy has yet to hit bottom, a sharply higher percentage than the 53% who felt that way in January.
Wow. I think thebarrage of terrible economic news this week has people realizing that you can’t borrow your way out of a debt problem.
So far this fiscal year, the US has paid more in interest on its rapidly rising debt than it’s taken in from all corporate taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed: Other Shoe About to Drop</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/fed-other-shoe-about-to-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 03:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/fed-other-shoe-about-to-drop/</guid>
      <description>The only two people in the world who believe the economy is healthy and vibrant are Barack Obama and Joe Biden.

Now, the Federal Reserve Board’s Open Market Committee (FOMC) is getting ready to announce that the economy is sicker than we thought.
 Although Fed policymakers still believe the basic trajectory of the economy remains one of moderate expansion, there may be more attention given to heightened dangers of a sharp slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Priceless! Boy Scouts Boo Bo</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/priceless-boy-scouts-boo-bo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 16:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/priceless-boy-scouts-boo-bo/</guid>
      <description>I guess this is the Boy Scout Jamboree. It’s too wonderful to research.
On the big screen, we see The One, The Despot, Barack “Ass Kicker” Obama.
In the foreground, we see and hear Boy Scouts booing and mocking and jeering.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oAWsy7VV8oE&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]
Part of me wishes the Boy Scouts were more respectful of the President of the United States, no matter who occupies that office. But another part of me believes that Obama is such a disgraceful, un-American anomaly that to disrespect him is to honor the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/1-do-the-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 02:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/1-do-the-math/</guid>
      <description>Have you noticed few people call Barack Obama “The One” anymore? “The Golfer” or “The Vacationer” is more like it. Something less than One, by any measure.

Still, with each passing day and each new, permanent crisis, it seems like BO just ain’t up to the job of President. Nothing new. When Jimmy Carter’s incompetence became obvious, the lefty press developed a theory that the job had simply grown too complex for one man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Plan to Punish Voters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/democrats-plan-to-punish-voters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 22:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/democrats-plan-to-punish-voters/</guid>
      <description>Democrats are planning to punish the American people with draconian, destructive legislation during the lame duck session following November’s election, according the Wall Street Journal.
 That&amp;rsquo;s why there have been signs in recent weeks that party leaders are planning an ambitious, lame-duck session to muscle through bills in December they don&amp;rsquo;t want to defend before November. Retiring or defeated members of Congress would then be able to vote for sweeping legislation without any fear of voter retaliation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We&#39;ve Made a Difference</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 18:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</guid>
      <description>When you give over most of your private time to a cause, you need some feedback. We got some from former Reagan speechwriter Peggy Noonan on Friday: The Summer of the Angry Mob
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;521&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Dana&amp;rsquo;s Famous &amp;lsquo;Meet the Mob&amp;rsquo; Blog&amp;rdquo;][/caption]
Ms. Noonan reflected on the Townhall Revolt which began in St. Louis one year ago. Writes Noonan:
 When Rep. Russ Carnahan held a town hall meeting at a community college in Missouri on July 20, he tried patiently to explain that ObamaCare not only would be deficit-neutral, it would save money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Insults Americans . . . Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/obama-insults-americans-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 23:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/obama-insults-americans-again/</guid>
      <description>An arrogant and distracted Barack Obama appeared at a press conference for the G20 Summit today. His purpose: to insult, threaten, and cajole the American people from an international stage.
 I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because I said I was going to do it and I think it&amp;rsquo;s the right thing to do. People should learn that lesson about me because next year when I start presenting some very difficult choices to the country, I hope some of these folks who are hollering about deficits and debt step-up because I&amp;rsquo;m calling their bluff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Oil Leak</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/16/the-washington-oil-leak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/16/the-washington-oil-leak/</guid>
      <description>You would think that the basement of the White House was gushing 60,000 barrels of oil a day, wouldn’t you? After all, President Obama’s entire response to the greatest ecological disaster of modern times has been empower Washington, DC.
The disasters are in the Gulf of Mexico, Mr. President, and in the latest Gallup and Rasmussen polls.
Politicians who worship at the alter of omnipotent government have no answers to problems outside of government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Incompetence Leaves Americans At Risk</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/obamas-incompetence-leaves-americans-at-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 08:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/obamas-incompetence-leaves-americans-at-risk/</guid>
      <description>It took almost three years of Jimmy Carter’s dangerously naive worldview before the world rushed in. By “rushed in,” I mean the Soviet Union rushed into Afghanistan, Iranian radicals rushed into the US Embassy in Tehran, and Cuban-backed communists rushed into every Central and South American country they could.
These aggressions resulted from a world perception that Jimmy Carter was unwilling to use America’s arsenal for good. Additionally, following Vietnam and observing American culture, the world surmised that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Failure of Leadership *UPDATES*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/total-failure-of-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 17:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/total-failure-of-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama’s incompetent, confused, and contradictory handling of the Gulf oil spill reveals a man unfit for any position of authority.
As Peggy Noonan pointed out in a painfully honest Wall Street Journal column on May 28, we know now that Barack Obama is an empty suit, a child playing grown-up.
 I wonder if the president knows what a disaster this is not only for him but for his political assumptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s New Era of Secrecy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/21/obamas-new-era-of-secrecy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 14:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/21/obamas-new-era-of-secrecy/</guid>
      <description>As a candidate, Barack Obama swore he would throw open the activities of government to light of public scrutiny. In his inauguration, he swore to disclose everything. As President, he has instituted strict rules of secrecy on White House actions&amp;ndash;except those of his predecessors.
Now, Newsweek&amp;rsquo;s Michael Isikoff, no friend of the right, notices the incongruity between Obama&amp;rsquo;s promises and his actual openess.
He finds that Obama&amp;rsquo;s openess executive order contains loopholes that the media have ignored until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Skeptical</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/18/i-am-skeptical/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 13:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/18/i-am-skeptical/</guid>
      <description>You should be, too.
 The tally of continuing claims, or benefits drawn by workers for more than one week, fell 148,000 to 6,687,000, the first weekly decline since the week ended Jan. 3 and largest since Nov. 24, 2001. (wsj.com)
 That would be good news, but only if a) it&amp;rsquo;s true, and b) 148,000 more people found jobs than lost them last month.
Frankly, I think the government&amp;rsquo;s lying to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UN Security Council Ignores Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/un-security-council-ignores-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 02:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/un-security-council-ignores-obama/</guid>
      <description>Jimmy Carter was the Rodney Dangerfield of international politics: he got no respect from the people who counted. The bad guys laughed at him. The bad guys must be rolling on the floor tonight.
Rogue Leaders Respect Nothing But Strength
Almost simultaneous with North Korea&amp;rsquo;s launching an ICBM in violation of international law and in defiance of US warnings, Barack Obama stood before the world and declared his intention to disarm the arsenal for democracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama To Control Banks Permanently</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/obama-to-control-banks-permanently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 18:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/obama-to-control-banks-permanently/</guid>
      <description>The Obama administration has no intention of relinquishing dictatorial control of the banks according to financial expert Stuart Varney.  The government wants to control the banks, just as it now controls GM and Chrysler, and will surely control the health industry in the not-too-distant future. Keeping them TARP-stuffed is the key to control. And for this intensely political president, mere influence is not enough. The White House wants to tell &amp;lsquo;em what to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Message Sinking In</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/28/tea-party-message-sinking-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 22:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/28/tea-party-message-sinking-in/</guid>
      <description>Rasmussen&amp;rsquo;s weekly report shows the Tea Party message of limited government and lower taxes is hitting home with voters.
Tax Cuts: More voters than ever now say tax cuts help the economy. Over 60 percent now agree with JFK, Reagan, Bush, and the undeniable facts of economic history: cutting taxes increases GDP and personal wealth.  A separate survey released earlier today found that 66% of voters think the president is likely to raise taxes on those who make less than $250,000 per year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No, I didn&#39;t watch Obama on 60 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/22/no-i-didnt-watch-obama-on-60-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 03:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/22/no-i-didnt-watch-obama-on-60-minutes/</guid>
      <description>I did not watch America&amp;rsquo;s Toxic Asset on 60 Minutes for the same reason I&amp;rsquo;ve never read &amp;ldquo;Mein Kampf.&amp;rdquo; Some people&amp;rsquo;s words do not deserve my ear.
I find it interesting, though, that Mr. Obama&amp;rsquo;s 90 minute interview on a program called &amp;ldquo;60 Minutes&amp;rdquo; so eerily parallels his budget: he consumed 150 percent of what was available.
To those who watched our dictator-in-the-making, I ask a question, the answer to which should demonstrate that watching the propaganda piece was useles: what did you learn that you didn&amp;rsquo;t know before?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama to America:  F**k You!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/21/obama-to-america-fk-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 01:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/21/obama-to-america-fk-you/</guid>
      <description>Bill Clinton began his presidency in a recession, promising to make a middle class tax cut and more jobs his laser-beam focus. But first, he let gays into the military and sent his wife off to socialize medicine. Barack Obama began his presidency during a borderline depression, promising to save the country from economic collapse, lowering the seas, and scripting quality endings to Stephen King&amp;rsquo;s movies. But first, he symbolically flipped off everyone affected by Islamofascist terrorists,snubbed military heroes, andredifined ethics as the way one behaves when the whole world&amp;rsquo;s watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Government Doesn&#39;t Kill Babies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/20/good-government-doesnt-kill-babies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 12:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/20/good-government-doesnt-kill-babies/</guid>
      <description>One of Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s first actions as president will likely involve a series of executive orders ensuring that as many abortions as possible happen. Good government protects its most vulnerable citizens; bad government kills them. Nazi Germany killed the weak, the halt, the improvident. Of course, the Nazis trained specialist to carry out these grim and evil tasks. In America, we rely on ordinary citizens to do the killing for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Obama: Take Your Ass-Kicking Like a Man!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/17/hey-obama-take-your-ass-kicking-like-a-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 02:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/17/hey-obama-take-your-ass-kicking-like-a-man/</guid>
      <description>The day after John McCain handed Barack Obama his ass on a platter at the Saddleback Forum, Obama&amp;rsquo;s paid mouthpiece, Andrea Mitchell, accused McCain of cheating (see Newsbusters). I guess going mano-a-mano with a real man is above Obama&amp;rsquo;s paygrade, too.
How pathetically consistent. Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s childishness, immaturity, and lack of accountability grow to new legendary heights every passing day. I really don&amp;rsquo;t know how people can take this brat seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Caught Lying Like a Hansen on Climate Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/26/obama-caught-lying-like-a-hansen-on-climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 23:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/26/obama-caught-lying-like-a-hansen-on-climate-change/</guid>
      <description>TigerHawk decided to fact-check Obama&amp;rsquo;s pontifical address to his German subjects concerning the messiah&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;facts&amp;rdquo; about global warming (h/t Hackbarth). Like Hansen and Gore, Obama enjoys lying to the people. TigerHawk shows academic research that report sea levels falling, not rising, and Kansas not in a drought, but normal to exceptionally moist.
I&amp;rsquo;m not surprised to catch Obama in a lie; I am surprised that people continue to lie about global warming despite all scientific evidence (not doctored byJames Hansen) to the contrary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rare Arrogance </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/26/rare-arrogance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 22:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/26/rare-arrogance/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s most conspicuous quality, if you want to call it that, is shameless arrogance. His trip abroad was like Hitler&amp;rsquo;s tour of Italy in 1938. Before you dismiss my view as that of a party hack tearing down the opposition, read Susan Estrich&amp;rsquo;s column on FoxNews.com. (Estrich was Michael Dukakis&amp;rsquo;s campaign manager in 1988).
First, Presidential candidates rarely campaign in war zones, and for good reason. American politics traditionally sort of stopped &amp;ldquo;at the water&amp;rsquo;s edge,&amp;rdquo; as the saying went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rasmussen Poll Shows Dead Head</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/13/rasmussen-poll-shows-dead-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 16:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/13/rasmussen-poll-shows-dead-head/</guid>
      <description>Rasmussen&amp;rsquo;s presidential tracking poll shows a dead heat between Democrat Barack Obama and Republican Presidential Candidate John McCain (h/t Drudge). This poll confirms the Newsweek poll showing the two in a statistical dead heat.
Moreover, according Rasmussen, McCain enjoys higher favorability ratings than Obama.
Considering that McCain has received little media attention since the last Democrat primary in June, Obama&amp;rsquo;s 15 percentage point drop can only be blamed on Obama&amp;rsquo;s dismal performance as a candidate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsweek:  Obama Fading</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/12/newsweek-obama-fading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 00:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/12/newsweek-obama-fading/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s poll lead over John McCain has plummeted from 51-35 to a statistical dead-heat in less than a month.
Obama&amp;rsquo;s downward spiral has Newsweek&amp;rsquo;s headline writers asking if his glow is fading. The polls finds that more than half of voters consider Obama lying opportunist who will take any position for votes.
 Obama&amp;rsquo;s rapid drop comes at a strategically challenging moment for the Democratic candidate. Having vanquished Hillary Clinton in early June, Obama quickly went about repositioning himself for a general-election audience&amp;ndash;an unpleasant task for any nominee emerging from the pander-heavy primary contests and particularly for a candidate who&amp;rsquo;d slogged through a vigorous primary challenge in most every contest from January until June.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunfight At the Not-OK Corral</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/02/18/gunfight-at-the-not-ok-corral/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 05:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/02/18/gunfight-at-the-not-ok-corral/</guid>
      <description>Clinton Inc. will do whatever (it thinks) it takes to secure the Democrat nomination for president.
The news of the past two days has been Obama&amp;rsquo;s plagiarism. As if Obama is can&amp;rsquo;t produce his own pandering drivel. From WaPo:
 Yesterday, key Clinton supporters accused Obama of &amp;ldquo;lifting&amp;rdquo; a passage of the rousing speech he delivered to a party gathering in Milwaukee on Saturday night from Massachusetts Gov. Deval L. Patrick, a longtime friend and supporter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>