<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>obama on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/obama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in obama on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:41:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/obama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When Democrats Loved &#39;em Some Ruskies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/when-democrats-loved-em-some-ruskies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/when-democrats-loved-em-some-ruskies/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/Py8BF0hHPnc
In 2012, Barack Obama got caught telling Russian Prime Minister Medvedev that he&amp;rsquo;d have more &amp;ldquo;flexibility&amp;rdquo; after the election.
Later in 2012, during a debate, Obama accused GOP candidate Mitt Romney of stoking Cold War fears against our new friends in Moscow. Obama said, “The 1980s are now calling to ask for their foreign policy back because…the Cold War’s been over for 20 years!” In fact, in 2012, the whole pantheon of pantsuit partiersmocked warnings about Russia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do we owe Obama an apology?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/01/do-we-owe-obama-an-apology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 23:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/01/do-we-owe-obama-an-apology/</guid>
      <description>Imaginations can run wild in the affinity bubble.
I was in Washington, DC, over the weekend when it dawned on me that we on the right were probably wrong about Obama&amp;rsquo;s thirst for dictatorial power. Or maybe we were right, but seven years of near-dictatorial power have exhausted the would-be autocrat. He certain looks worn down, as this Time magazine side-by-side shows:
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_18520&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] President Obama in 2009 and again in 2016[/caption]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unbearable Lightness of Being There</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/the-unbearable-lightness-of-being-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 03:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/the-unbearable-lightness-of-being-there/</guid>
      <description>Eve: May I ask your name? Chance: Chance. Eve: Chance? Chance: Chance, the gardener. Eve: Chauncey Gardiner? Mr. Chauncey Gardiner. Are you related to Basil and Perdita Gardiner?
 &amp;ndash; Being There, 1979
 People tell us who they are, but we ignore it. Because we want them to be what we we want them to be.
 &amp;ndash;Don Draper, Mad Men
President Obama used his third Oval Office address in seven years to say &amp;ldquo;Honey, I shrunk the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Have Just One Chance for October Surprise</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 16:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</guid>
      <description>The White House and its corrupt Department of Justice has one chance to change the election&amp;rsquo;s outcome.According to Nate Silver&amp;rsquo;s FiveThirtyEight blog, the GOP has a 62.1 percent chance of a Senate majority. With nine days left until the election, and with President Obama&amp;rsquo;s approval and likability plunging, the Democrats face a huge loss.
Apathetic Democrats Many political observers blame Democrat voter apathy, particularly among African-Americans. The black vote that swelled in 2008 and 2012 with Obama on the ballot shows signs of deflating in 2014 as it did in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be President When Russia Goes Berserk Starring Ronald Reagan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 03:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</guid>
      <description>Since the scrawny punk from Chicago still hasn&amp;rsquo;t figured it out, this President 101 lesson delivered without further comment:
https://youtu.be/9VA4W1wDMAk?t=18s
Previously on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View:
We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>