<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Franklin Project on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/the-franklin-project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Franklin Project on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 10:55:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/the-franklin-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Wrong With The Franklin Project? – Part 3</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/22/whats-wrong-with-the-franklin-project-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 10:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/22/whats-wrong-with-the-franklin-project-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This is part three of a five-part series on national service. Part 1 introduced the controversy and corrected a major misconception. Part 2 looked at national service through the eyes of conservative giants, Milton Friedman, William F. Buckley, and Ronald Reagan.
So, what’s wrong with the Franklin Project? Plenty.
The Franklin Project promotes the idea of a renewed ethos of national service in America. It’s mission:
 The Franklin Project envisions a future in which a year of full-time national service—a service year—is a cultural expectation, a common opportunity, and a civic rite of passage for every young American.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buckley vs. Friedman on Service-Part 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 10:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</guid>
      <description>This is part 2 of a series on national service and the Franklin Project. Read part 1 here.
First, answer this for yourself: would you vote for William F. Buckley Jr?
Milton Friedman on National Service My friend Lloyd Sloan points out that Milton Friedman disagreed with Buckley’s call for national service. It seems appropriate, then, to view the idea of a service ethos through the eyes of two champions of conservatism of the 20th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fact and Fiction of the Franklin Project--Part 1</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/20/fact-and-fiction-of-the-franklin-project-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 10:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/20/fact-and-fiction-of-the-franklin-project-part-1/</guid>
      <description>You know how to tell when a political camp has nothing on an opponent?
It begins making stuff up.
That “making stuff up” has become the chief form of amusement among those who oppose Eric Greitens for Governor.
The current fiction they advance has to do with an organization called The Franklin Project. The fiction advanced by a few Facebook warriors goes something like this: “The Franklin Project wants mandatory national service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>