<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sharp Elbows on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/sharp-elbows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sharp Elbows on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 04:51:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/sharp-elbows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Ruin a Perfectly Good Joke</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/03/ruin-perfectly-good-joke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 04:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/03/ruin-perfectly-good-joke/</guid>
      <description>If you talk long enough, you can butcher the best joke in the world&amp;ndash;even the one from Monty Python that the Allies used to win WWII.
https://youtu.be/ienp4J3pW7U
Tuesday night at a Tea Party meeting, I managed to destroy a joke of my own, poor making, and insult a friend at the same time. That takes talent. Or . . . something.
So, first, let me apologize to Adam Sharp, the best indy video journalist alive, since he was the victim of my horrible comedic delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Wisconsin Police Chief Admits Illegal Harassment of Tea Party Leader, After Lying About It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/01/campbell-wisconsin-police-chief-admits-illegal-harassment-tea-party-leader-lying/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/01/campbell-wisconsin-police-chief-admits-illegal-harassment-tea-party-leader-lying/</guid>
      <description>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lbYKydZ3T0Q
The weird thing is: isn&amp;rsquo;t that Sharp Elbows questioning the Chief? When did he become a detective in Michigan?
The chief pleaded nolo contendere to identity theft charges. He presented himself as a tea party leader signing up for embarrassing, sexual email lists. From the La Crosse Tea Party:
 A shocking update to the Town of Campbell Situation this week. Detective Spencer from Monroe County Sheriff’s department called and said that Campbell Police Chief Tim Kelemen confessed to harassment/internet stalking/identity theft regarding my complaint filed to La Crosse P.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>