<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Donald Trump on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/donald-trump/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Donald Trump on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 06:45:37 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/donald-trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Along Came a Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/along-came-a-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 06:45:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/along-came-a-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>The thing that most rankled the left and crony-capitalist &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; about Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Magic Escalator Ride were his statements on illegal immigration. &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re not sending their best.&amp;rdquo;
The left sees open borders as a means of finally reducing the United States to a pauper nation, a dream long shared by socialists and communists in the US and Europe.
Crony capitalists are less prosaic in their aims. They see open borders as a source of cheap labor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thatcher Reagan Boris Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/thatcher-reagan-boris-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 22:58:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/thatcher-reagan-boris-trump/</guid>
      <description>Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s Tories will win their biggest victory since Margaret Thatcher. Maybe bigger than Thatcher&amp;rsquo;s. Praise God!
(This will be very short.)
The conservative tide continues. People around the world are fed up with the failed ideas of the 1960s and 1970s. Maybe it was nostalgia that drove world leaders to dig up all the political crap I remember from my childhood. It failed then, and it&amp;rsquo;s failing us now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, President Trump Will Win Re-election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-17-yes-president-trump-will-win-re-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-17-yes-president-trump-will-win-re-election/</guid>
      <description>New York Times columnist Thomas Friedman today asked a rhetorical question: Trump&amp;rsquo;s Going to Get Re-elected, Isn&amp;rsquo;t He?
The headline reflects the question he hears from his Democrat friends. They seem resigned to defeat. And the answer is: Yes. President Trump will win re-election in 2020.
The reasons Trump will get re-elected:
  The Hate Squad. Four radical communist freshmen Representatives are the face of the new Democrat party. They are anti-Semitic, anti-Christian, and anti-American.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea, Meet Stoicism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/chelsea-meet-stoicism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 19:29:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/chelsea-meet-stoicism/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s triumph in the 2016 election drove Chelsea Handler into a depraved descent. Weed and depression. Psychiatrists. Broken.
Not because of anything that happened to her. She didn&amp;rsquo;t lose her home. No one close to her died because of the election.
Chelsea Handler lost her mind because reality violated her expectations.
I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Ms. Handler doesn&amp;rsquo;t read Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View, but you do. So, for you, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how to avoid losing your mind when reality violates your expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Odyssey of Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/21/odyssey-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 14:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/21/odyssey-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>O Divine Poesy, goddess, daughter of Zeus, sustain for me this song of the various-minded man who, after he had plundered the innermost citadel of hallowed Troy, was made to stay grievously about the coasts of men, the sport of their customs, good and bad, while his heart, through all the sea-faring, ached with an agony to redeem himself and bring his company safe home. Vain hope – for them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>