<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Judy Ancel on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/judy-ancel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Judy Ancel on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 18:42:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/judy-ancel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy Ancel: Teacher of the Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/judy-ancel-teacher-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 18:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/judy-ancel-teacher-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Judy Ancel is the University of Kansas City instructor responsible for teaching students to use violence, sabotage and intimidation as political tools. She’s telling the Kansas City Star that she’s receiving threats from people upset that she teaches students to threaten others.
I oppose violence, sabotage, and intimidation as political tools. But Judy Ancel’s message of violence seems to have gotten through to some people.
Too bad Ancel doesn’t use her skills for goodinstead of evil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Question for Gail Hackett of UMKC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/one-question-for-gail-hackett-of-umkc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 05:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/one-question-for-gail-hackett-of-umkc/</guid>
      <description>Gail Hackett, UMKC Provost, released a deceitful, false, and irresponsible defense of UMKC instructors who encouraged students to use violence, sabotage, and intimidation to their way.
But Gail Hackett refuses to answer hard questions.
I have one question for the UMKC Provost: ****
**Do you agree with Don Giljum’s statement “I believe in a violent overthrow of Bourgeois?” **
Before you answer, remember that Giljum’s use of the personal term “Bourgois” instead of the the class “bourguoisie” indicates that Giljim believes in violence against individual members of the middle class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell UMSL to Stop Teaching Industrial Sabotage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/25/tell-umsl-to-stop-teaching-industrial-sabotage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 01:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/25/tell-umsl-to-stop-teaching-industrial-sabotage/</guid>
      <description>[ ](https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/UofMCommie.png)Contact UofM President Steve Owens and demand an immediate end to the communist-led industrial sabotage courses that he’s shoving down your kids’ throats
That’s right, UMSL and UMKC are teaching kids how to destroy business in America. They want your job to go overseas. And the guy leading the class is a proud communist.
No employer in his right might would hire a graduate of the University of Missouri-St. Louis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>