<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>political correctness on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/political-correctness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in political correctness on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:47:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/political-correctness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Up From Political Correctness</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/05/up-from-political-correctness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/05/up-from-political-correctness/</guid>
      <description>I won’t blame the neighbors, but the neighbors knew.
Syed Farook and four or five others worked long hours in Farook’s San Bernardino garage for months leading up to a deadly Islamic terror attack last week.
Neighbors knew. They knew Farook and his Pakistani wife, Tashfeen Malik, were up to no good. But the neighbors said nothing until after the massacre at a center for the developmentally disabled.
**The suspicious neighbors were afraid, not of the Muslim terrorists, but of political correctness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we need in America is more Irish</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/10/what-we-need-in-america-is-more-irish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 23:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/10/what-we-need-in-america-is-more-irish/</guid>
      <description>Disclosure: I am Irish.
I know the politically correct way to say it is Irish-American. The accurate way to say it is American of Irish descent.
But I grew up in South St. Louis where we were just Irish. And the Italians were Italian and the Germans were German. (That&amp;rsquo;s about all we had in my neighborhood, plus a few Jewish converts to Catholicism, but they caucused with the Germans.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hysterical Yale student embarrasses herself on video</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/09/hysterical-yale-student-embarrasses-herself-on-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 02:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/09/hysterical-yale-student-embarrasses-herself-on-video/</guid>
      <description>Nicholas Christakis is a giant in social psychology.
And social psychology is only part of his resume. He&amp;rsquo;s also a medical doctor.
Christakis wrote one of the most important books on social networks (the real kind, not Facebook), Connected: The Surprising Power of Our Social Networks. He holds distinguished positions at both Yale and Harvard and has appeared on Time Magazine&amp;rsquo;s list of 100 Most Influential People in the World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Rush Limbaugh Could Teach Rush Limbaugh **UPATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/04/what-rush-limbaugh-could-teach-rush-limbaugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/04/what-rush-limbaugh-could-teach-rush-limbaugh/</guid>
      <description>What made Rush Limbaugh so amazing for 24 years was his steadfast resolve. Face it, you have to believe what you believe title your books The Way Things Ought To Be and See, I Told You So.
His fans loved him because he never backed down.
Rush didn’t back down when the left went nuts over his “Obama, The Magic Negro” parody. He didn’t back down from his “hope Obama fails” statement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>