<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How 2012 Might Have Been</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/30/how-2012-might-have-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 05:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/30/how-2012-might-have-been/</guid>
      <description>Republican Presidential Primaries
The Republican Primary season was already well underway. Before a single caucus or vote, though, we pretty much knew that Mitt Romney would win the nomination. He had the entire Republican establishment behind him, including true conservatives who wanted a “safe” candidate.
We know how that worked out.

What might have been had a strong conservative emerged in 2011? What if someone without baggage had prepared years in advance for a run against the weakened, staggering Obama?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why I Feel Sorry For Millennials</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/29/this-is-why-i-feel-sorry-for-millennials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 00:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/29/this-is-why-i-feel-sorry-for-millennials/</guid>
      <description>Doctor Viktor Frankl was a neurologist and psychiatrist in Vienna, Austria. He founded the third branch of Viennese psychological therapies, logotherapy. But his life changed drastically when Austria capitulated to the National Socialists.

The Nazis interned Frankl. He spent time in four concentration camps, including Auschwitz and Dachau. For three years, his captors made him dig ditches for railroads and water pipes, and fed him a slice of bread and an ounce or two of soup a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Psychological Biases Make Good Government Unlikely</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/28/how-psychological-biases-make-good-government-unlikely/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/28/how-psychological-biases-make-good-government-unlikely/</guid>
      <description>Answer this question on paper without looking up the answer:
 Q: Which kills more people: guns or diabetes?
 Here’s what your brain is doing. It’s searching your memory for mentions of the keywords: “guns,” “diabetes,” and “kill.”
For most of us, one of the variables—guns or diabetes—carries a significantly heavier emotional weighting than the other. A paid-up-for-life member of the NRA might attach powerful positive emotions to “guns.” The parent of a child who died of complications of diabetes will attach high negative emotions to “diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Planning Is Killing the Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</guid>
      <description>Friedrich Hayek warned more than half a century ago that central planning doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. Here’s why:
 * Central Planners (government) makes a plan * The plan includes specific expectations * The expectations are never, ever, realized * A “crisis” ensues * So the planners demand more control * And create more plans * Ad hoc * Willy nilly * Capriciously * So you must wait for things to settle down to make your decision  Today’s Wall Street Journal article about the fiscal cliff demonstrates the futility of central planning:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/24/merry-christmas-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 05:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/24/merry-christmas-3/</guid>
      <description>I read today that the Christmas shopping season was off. The writer, or his sources, blamed Sandy: Hurricane Sandy and Sandy Hook. Retailers said that shoppers weren’t very jolly. They were serious or worried or distracted. Hurried, as if they didn’t want to be out too long.

I thought of my parents and others at the Christmas of 1941. Americans had endured a decade of economic depression that the planners were impotent to correct.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>