<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How 2012 Might Have Been</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/30/how-2012-might-have-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 05:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/30/how-2012-might-have-been/</guid>
      <description>Republican Presidential Primaries
The Republican Primary season was already well underway. Before a single caucus or vote, though, we pretty much knew that Mitt Romney would win the nomination. He had the entire Republican establishment behind him, including true conservatives who wanted a “safe” candidate.
We know how that worked out.

What might have been had a strong conservative emerged in 2011? What if someone without baggage had prepared years in advance for a run against the weakened, staggering Obama?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why I Feel Sorry For Millennials</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/29/this-is-why-i-feel-sorry-for-millennials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 00:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/29/this-is-why-i-feel-sorry-for-millennials/</guid>
      <description>Doctor Viktor Frankl was a neurologist and psychiatrist in Vienna, Austria. He founded the third branch of Viennese psychological therapies, logotherapy. But his life changed drastically when Austria capitulated to the National Socialists.

The Nazis interned Frankl. He spent time in four concentration camps, including Auschwitz and Dachau. For three years, his captors made him dig ditches for railroads and water pipes, and fed him a slice of bread and an ounce or two of soup a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Psychological Biases Make Good Government Unlikely</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/28/how-psychological-biases-make-good-government-unlikely/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/28/how-psychological-biases-make-good-government-unlikely/</guid>
      <description>Answer this question on paper without looking up the answer:
 Q: Which kills more people: guns or diabetes?
 Here’s what your brain is doing. It’s searching your memory for mentions of the keywords: “guns,” “diabetes,” and “kill.”
For most of us, one of the variables—guns or diabetes—carries a significantly heavier emotional weighting than the other. A paid-up-for-life member of the NRA might attach powerful positive emotions to “guns.” The parent of a child who died of complications of diabetes will attach high negative emotions to “diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Planning Is Killing the Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</guid>
      <description>Friedrich Hayek warned more than half a century ago that central planning doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. Here’s why:
 * Central Planners (government) makes a plan * The plan includes specific expectations * The expectations are never, ever, realized * A “crisis” ensues * So the planners demand more control * And create more plans * Ad hoc * Willy nilly * Capriciously * So you must wait for things to settle down to make your decision  Today’s Wall Street Journal article about the fiscal cliff demonstrates the futility of central planning:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/24/merry-christmas-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 05:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/24/merry-christmas-3/</guid>
      <description>I read today that the Christmas shopping season was off. The writer, or his sources, blamed Sandy: Hurricane Sandy and Sandy Hook. Retailers said that shoppers weren’t very jolly. They were serious or worried or distracted. Hurried, as if they didn’t want to be out too long.

I thought of my parents and others at the Christmas of 1941. Americans had endured a decade of economic depression that the planners were impotent to correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What Happens Now That Boehner’s “Plan B” Went Down In Flames</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/21/heres-what-happens-now-that-boehners-plan-b-went-down-in-flames/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 15:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/21/heres-what-happens-now-that-boehners-plan-b-went-down-in-flames/</guid>
      <description>Now that Boehner’s “Plan B” strategy has blown up like a poisoned dog, here’s what Boehner will do.
Remember this chart from last month? It shows strategic options from John Boehner’s point of view:

Yesterday, Boehner tried to land about halfway between the top and bottom quadrant on the left, shown here

Now that Plan B has been rejected, Boehner’s choices are limited to these: * Adjourn and hit the fiscal cliff * Cut a deal that will earn most Democrat votes and enough Republican votes to pass</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Fund A Terrorist Network?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/15/do-you-fund-a-terrorist-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/15/do-you-fund-a-terrorist-network/</guid>
      <description>According to the FBI:
 Domestic terrorism is the unlawful use, or threatened use, of force or violence by a group or individual based and operating entirely within the United States or Puerto Rico without foreign direction committed against persons or property to intimidate or coerce a government, the civilian population, or any segment thereof in furtherance of political or social objectives. (source)
 In Michigan, union protesters physically assaulted Steven Crowder of Fox News, then destroyed a tent belonging to Americans for Prosperity (video below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Could Be Worse?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/14/what-could-be-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 01:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/14/what-could-be-worse/</guid>
      <description>What could be worse than having no Christmas gift for a child to open?
A Christmas gift with no child to open it.

_Eternal rest grant unto them O Lord, and let perpetual light shine upon them. May their little souls, and all the souls of the faithful departed, through the mercy of God, rest in peace. _</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Schools Replace Great Fiction With Government propaganda</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</guid>
      <description>[Originally posted on Redstate.com]
English was my favorite subject in school, so much so that I can still recite from memory large passages of the books we read, like A Separate Peace:
 I went back to Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there 15 years before.
 And who doesn’t know this by heart:
 If you really want to hear about it, the first thing you’ll probably want to know is where I was born and what my lousy childhood was like and how my parents were occupied and all before they had me and all that David Copperfield kind of crap, but I don’t feel like going into it, if you want to know the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives Keep Losing Because They’re Reading The Wrong Books</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/09/conservatives-keep-losing-because-theyre-reading-the-wrong-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/09/conservatives-keep-losing-because-theyre-reading-the-wrong-books/</guid>
      <description>For the past four years. conservatives have worried more about being right while liberals worried about winning.
We all know how that worked out.
It doesn’t matter how right you are if you’re powerless.Right now we are.
Satisfied?
I didn’t think so.

After four years of 5,000 Leap and Constitution study groups, of Constitutional workshops, and rallies in the park, let’s make a vow to ourselves and to each other: We’re Done With Losing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is The Infographic That The Whole Republican Party Is Freaking Out About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</guid>
      <description>The 3 million McCain voters who didn’t vote for Romney?
They’re dead.

[Click image to view full size. Please forward, download, and print. This is important.]
To survive, the GOP needs to stop being afraid of Millennials and tell them truth: they can move out of mom and dad’s house, they can drop out of school, they can quit their dead-end job with the idiot supervisor. But they can’t get away from government and debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is Exactly How The Special Election To Replace Jo Ann Emerson Will Be Conducted. (We Think)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/05/here-is-exactly-how-the-special-election-to-replace-jo-ann-emerson-will-be-conducted-we-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/05/here-is-exactly-how-the-special-election-to-replace-jo-ann-emerson-will-be-conducted-we-think/</guid>
      <description>I’ve gotten a lot of emails and comments asking for more information on the special election process in Missouri’s 8th Congressional District. So I went to the smartest person I know about this stuff: Frieda Keough.
Here’ what I learned:
 Eddie Justice, the Chair of the 8th Congressional District will call a meeting. Anyone wanting to be appointed to run for the 8th Congressional District shows up at the meeting and will be put before the committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GOP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/05/the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/05/the-gop/</guid>
      <description>I bet ten bucks on a sentimental favorite to win. Sure, he’s old, and reports say he didn’t train as hard as he might have. But he’s been my boxing hero since childhood—when he won the gold at the Olympics. I’m sure there’s another moment of glory waiting to explode on an unsuspecting world.
He just needs to land that one magical right.
As the rounds wear on, though, I can feel it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Lloyd Smith and Jo Ann Emerson Plan This All Along?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</guid>
      <description>In an open Republican primary in Missouri’s 8th Congressional District, a solid conservative would beat an establishment &amp;ldquo;my turn&amp;rdquo; Republican, hands down. And the Missouri GOP would hate it.
That’s why I smell a rat. Would you be surprised to learn that Jo Ann Emerson and Lloyd Smith had this switcheroo planned months ago? You have to admit that the timing is suspicious:
 * Emerson wins a certain re-election * Smith announces he&#39;s stepping down as Missouri GOP Executive Director * Emerson announces she&#39;s resigning to become Queen of Lobbyists * Missouri&#39;s GOP Establishment breaks hips to tell reporters &amp;quot;Lloyd Smith&#39;s our man!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Can&#39;t Just Rage Against The Fiscal Cliff Machine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/30/republicans-cant-just-rage-against-the-fiscal-cliff-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/30/republicans-cant-just-rage-against-the-fiscal-cliff-machine/</guid>
      <description>Encouraging Boehner to shut down the government is the surest way to end conservatism as a practical political alternative.
The GOP has no leverage in budget negotiations, and conservative denial won’t change that.
Use Game Theory As I wrote on November 12, fighting Obama – voting down a budget in the House – results in the GOP’s worst possible outcome: total blame for anything that goes wrong and no credit for anything that goes right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why Turning People Off Is A Terrible Idea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a cause’s worst enemies are its best friends.

In 1995, 56 percent of American described themselves as “pro-choice.” At the time, Michael Kinsley on CNN’s Crossfire declared the debate over.
Then something strange happened. Americans started changing their minds. The pro-life movement whittled away at public opinion.
By May of this year, Gallup found “pro-choice” to be at an all-time low:
 The 41% of Americans who now identify themselves as &amp;ldquo;pro-choice&amp;rdquo; is down from 47% last July and is one percentage point below the previous record low in Gallup trends, recorded in May 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop The Crazy Talk: Vote Fraud Didn’t Cost Romney The Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</guid>
      <description>I wrote yesterday that if you need someone to blame, blame me. Don’t blame bogeymen.

Yes, vote fraud is real. Voter rolls in most states need to be cleaned up. Voter intimidation should be harshly prosecuted.
You can sign up at True the Vote or Missouri Precinct Project to take effective, useful action. These organizations do vital work, and they both need more volunteers.
Using vote fraud, however, as an excuse for secession or for blocking the Electoral College vote is neither effective nor useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Conservatives: We Are Already Losing 2016</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/18/dear-conservatives-we-are-already-losing-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/18/dear-conservatives-we-are-already-losing-2016/</guid>
      <description>If you need to blame someone for our election losses, blame me.

I Let You Down I could have done more. I could have spoken up sooner. I could have been more honest with you about the mistakes we made and the opportunities we ignored. I could have worked harder on what I saw as the most important work we could do.
I let you down. I focused on petty issues of the day, too, instead of working on a different future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Suffocate Free Speech</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 15:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</guid>
      <description>Colleges in the United States are systematically destroying free speech, free thought, and creative writing. Sixty-five percent of colleges and universities censor students, even in creative writing classes.
[youtube=https://youtu.be/Z3vgGqlZGGE] Hillsdale or nothing.
Related articles  * [GREG LUKIANOFF IN THE NEW YORK TIMES: Feigning Free Speech on Campus. &amp;quot;Colleges and universities a...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/155479/) (pjmedia.com) * [ONE WAY FREE SPEECH: The progressive vision of free speech is decidedly one-way, excluding any s...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/154514/) (pjmedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bakers Union Costs 300 St. Louisans Their Jobs  **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/bakers-union-costs-300-st-louisans-their-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 01:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/bakers-union-costs-300-st-louisans-their-jobs/</guid>
      <description>**UPDATE Union Declares Victory AsHostess Goes Out of Business. No more Ho Hos. ****
Unions destroy themselves like pathetic drunks, dragging down everyone around them.

In a fine example of anti-strategic thinking and un-game theory, the Bakers Union put 637 of its members out of work yesterday.
Hostess—makers of Twinkies—is bankrupt. Part of the bankruptcy involved rewriting union contracts to allow the company to stay in business.
Instead of taking one for the team and helping their company crawl out of its fiscal hole, the Bakers went on strike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Petraeus Taking Obama With Him?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/what-if-petraeus-knew-exactly-what-he-was-doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/what-if-petraeus-knew-exactly-what-he-was-doing/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a flight of fantasy. If anything in this post is later shown to conform reality, it’s pure coincidence. Nor am I accusing Gen. Petraeus of any crime or of compromising of national security secrets. (Just enjoy it, will ya?) A sex scandal rocks the king of spies.
An email chain unravels the Pentagon high command.
A cover-up exposed.
It&amp;rsquo;s like the back cover of a Nelson DeMille novel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Expect Boehner To Play The Black Knight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</guid>
      <description>The GOP didn’t really have a plan in place in case it lost. It certainly didn’t have a plan for getting snotclobbered. And if you try to spin Tuesday’s results as anything less than a good old-fashioned ass-kicking, you’re deluding yourself.

**Republicans Got Creamed ** I know Michelle Malkin found 20 things that went right on election night, but there about 60 million things that went wrong. Let’s take a look:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karl Rove’s Air Power Strategy Failed America And His Donors</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/10/karl-roves-airpower-strategy-failed-america-and-his-donors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2012 04:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/10/karl-roves-airpower-strategy-failed-america-and-his-donors/</guid>
      <description>We heard it repeatedly during the Iraq wars: air power alone cannot win. You must take and hold ground in war.

The same is true in political combat. For years the GOP upset Democrats at all levels through superior ground games. Typically, this process involves:
 * Identifying potential voters * Contacting the high-value targets * Registering the unregistered * Mobilizing them on election day  Karl Rove’s Crossroads PACs tried a different strategy this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody Is Telling You About The Regulatory Armageddon About To Swamp The US Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/nobody-is-telling-you-about-the-regulatory-armageddon-about-to-swamp-the-us-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 22:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/nobody-is-telling-you-about-the-regulatory-armageddon-about-to-swamp-the-us-economy/</guid>
      <description>If you think federal regulation is bad today, just wait. You ain’t seen nothin’ yet.
 By the EPA&amp;rsquo;s own reckoning, the rule if implemented annually would cost American businesses $90 billion. But a related rule due to be taken up in December similarly would declare large swaths of the U.S. &amp;ldquo;closed for new business&amp;rdquo; until emissions are reduced to meet lower caps than exist today, says Anne Kolton, spokeswoman for the American Chemistry Council.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did You Vote?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/did-you-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 20:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/did-you-vote/</guid>
      <description>Voter turnout was down in every state from 2008. In many states, turnout was lower than 2004.
[polldaddy poll=6672784]
Thanks for responding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Conservative Base Is Dying And Taking Your Freedom With It *CORRECTION*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/the-conservative-base-is-dying-and-taking-freedom-with-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 10:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/the-conservative-base-is-dying-and-taking-freedom-with-it/</guid>
      <description>Consider these numbers:
 * **9.8 million** * &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;**11.6 million **&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt;**16.8 million** * **55%** * **61%**  Between the 2008 and 2012 elections:
 * 9.8 million people died*, 55% of them were reliable Republican voters * [16.8 &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;11.6&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; million people reached voting age](https://www.civicyouth.org/you-ask-we-answer-16-8-million-new-youth-eligible-to-vote-in-2012/?%3E)--61% of them are semi-reliable Democrat voters  
Between those years, neither the GOP nor conservative leaning organizations did anything significant to deal with this **demographic cliff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Conspire to Suppress Republican Turnout</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/media-conspire-to-suppress-republican-turnout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 23:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/media-conspire-to-suppress-republican-turnout/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s KSDK.com is doing its fair share to suppress the Republican voter turnout. They&amp;rsquo;re pumping a handful of counted votes to give the impression that Obama is walking away with the national popular vote:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the scam. Only 42 votes have been counted in a country of 150 million registered voters. In other words, it&amp;rsquo;s crap. No responsible news organization would post such misleading nonsense&amp;ndash;except in hopes of discouraging Romney voters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is How To Spend Election Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/this-is-how-to-spend-election-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/this-is-how-to-spend-election-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives take great pride in working, and for good reason. Work gives shape to life. Work is the poles of a tent, the bones of a body, the beams in the ceiling.

But work isn’t why we live. We live to pursue happiness.
For some, the pursuit of happiness involves acquiring property. Land, clothes, cars, plastic surgery. All examples of the pursuit of happiness.
Voting is another pursuit. People vote for minor candidates representing strange parties who have no chance of winning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s My Electoral Map Prediction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I’m feeling a wave toward Romney.

My gut tells me this year is a lot like 1980.
1980 Was A Dead Heat
The final Gallup poll that year had a dead heat. Time Magazine’s November 3, 1980, called the race a dead heat. So did Newsweek.
The press was hoping John B. Anderson, a former Republican Congressman running for president as an independent, would siphon votes from Reagan. He did siphon votes from Reagan, but not nearly enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why You Are Underemployed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</guid>
      <description>If you can’t find full-time work, blame Obamacare.

One reason the Middle Class has shriveled and wages shrunk over the the past four years is underemployment. People want full time work, but settle for anything. And anything is usually part time.
Most of the fantastic new jobs created since the 2009 have been part-time jobs.
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, 14.6% of Americans want a full-time job but settle for part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Maximize Your Election Influence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/how-to-maximize-your-election-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/how-to-maximize-your-election-influence/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s What To Do Today And On Election Day
Tuesday is the most important election of your life, but voting is never enough. You can have a bigger impact by using social proof to increase your influence. I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how, and it won&amp;rsquo;t take you long.
First, though, make sure nothing gets in the way of exercising your duty to vote.
Studies have shown that you are more likely to vote if you answer these questions before Election Day:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandy Exposes Limits Of Government</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/sandy-exposes-limits-of-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/sandy-exposes-limits-of-government/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama ridiculed George W. Bush for Katrina.

As people starve and beg for water in Rockaways, Obama’s promises to create heaven on earth through government look foolish and born of ignorance.
Obama believes that government can solve any problem, large or small. But his FEMA can’t get water to people in New York City.
With election two days away, remember this, you Obama voters: the most activist president of all time was unable to feed, clothe, and house hurricane victims despite having a week of warning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Shuts Down Another Small Business</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 01:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</guid>
      <description>200,000 That&amp;rsquo;s the number of** small businesses lost during the Obama Administration**.
If re-elected, Obama promises to accelerate the policies that destroyed American jobs, investments, and companies.
https://youtu.be/NlFHrLeeJIU
Voting isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. We need your help at 9966 Lin Ferry Drive, St. Louis, MO 63123.
Pick you day to work the phones and get out the vote:
 * Friday, November 2 Noon to 8 p.m. * Saturday, November 3 Noon to 5 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Radles Endorses Ed Martin for Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/31/bill-radles-endorses-ed-martin-for-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 04:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/31/bill-radles-endorses-ed-martin-for-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>I Endorse Ed Martin Dear Friends,
This is an email to encourage you to remember to do all you can to get Ed Martin elected Attorney General of Missouri. I know there are a lot of races and it is easy sometimes to overlook some of the down-ticket offices. But the Attorney General is an extremely important office. He is the chief law enforcement official of the state. He is responsible for seeing to it that our laws are faithfully enforced and our constitutional rights protected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Rights In Missouri Are Unprotected. Vote For Ed Martin For Your Own Security</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/31/your-rights-in-missouri-are-unprotected-vote-for-ed-martin-for-your-own-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 23:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/31/your-rights-in-missouri-are-unprotected-vote-for-ed-martin-for-your-own-security/</guid>
      <description>Please forward this post to everyone in your email address book. Use the buttons below to share on Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, StumbleUpon, Reddit. Tell your family that their vote for Ed Martin for Attorney General is your best defense against a Washington power machine run amok.
https://youtu.be/kRy2XWvGe38
Ed Martin&amp;rsquo;s opponent doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to realize that the job of Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Attorney General is to represent our state. The AG isn&amp;rsquo;t just some high-ranking prosecutor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney’s Cleaning Up in Early Voting, but It’s Confused the Hell Out of Politico</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/30/mitt-romneys-cleaning-up-in-early-voting-but-its-confused-the-hell-out-of-politico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/30/mitt-romneys-cleaning-up-in-early-voting-but-its-confused-the-hell-out-of-politico/</guid>
      <description>Gallup released its early voting poll today, and it shows Mitt Romney winning 52% to 45%—right in line with their Likely Voter poll numbers. Here’s the chart.

Politico Reporter Can’t Read But Gallup’s section on early voting by party ID completely lost Politico’s Kevin Robillard.
Robillard looked at the chart that shows when voters intend to vote by party and candidate and mistook it for voting results. This poll question shows that those who support Obama as as likely to vote early as are those who support Romney.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s How Nate Silver Determines Obama’s Chances of Winning</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/29/heres-how-nate-silver-determines-obamas-chances-of-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/29/heres-how-nate-silver-determines-obamas-chances-of-winning/</guid>
      <description>Nate Silver publishes a daily number that represents Barack Obama’s chances of being re-elected. As I write this on October 27, Silver’s magic number is 74%.
[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sKTUiwhac8Q&amp;amp;w=351&amp;amp;h=216&amp;amp;hd=1]
Nate Silver explains his scientific approach to picking winners in elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When The Three O&#39;Clock Call Came, Barack Obama Froze</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</guid>
      <description>The fog of war is lifting from Benghazi, and what lies beneath should shame Obama’s most ardent supporters. Barack Obama choked, and Americans died.

When America came under attack, Obama panicked and froze.
When Americans under his direction pleaded for their lives, he was afraid to pull the trigger.
Here’s the emerging picture.
White House Ordered Military and CIA to Stand Down and Let Al Qaeda Kill Former Navy SEALs Ty Woods and Glen Doherty, so disgusted by the White House’s refusal to help Americans under attack, defied an order to stand down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy Erases 600 years of Scientific Progress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/26/italy-erases-600-years-of-scientific-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/26/italy-erases-600-years-of-scientific-progress/</guid>
      <description>The next time some liberal tells you the United States needs to act more like Europe, tell them, “no, we believe in science.”

Italy sentenced six scientists to prison for the felony of failing to predict an earthquake.
Seriously.
The people who brought us da Vinci, Columbus, and Marconi believe that those wizards in lab coats with all the machines that go “beep” are actually gods who control the earth and the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THis Is How I’m Voting On November 6</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/24/this-is-how-im-voting-on-november-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/24/this-is-how-im-voting-on-november-6/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people want to know how to vote on the ballot measures and major offices in 2 weeks. Here’s how I’m voting, and why.

 Ballot Measures YES on Amendment 3: Change to Judge Appointments Better Courts for Missouri helped promote this measure to arrest the leftward list of appointments. The ballot language is awful, but this amendment is a step in the right direction. From their web site:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socialism Sucks. Here’s How to Avoid It In America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/23/socialism-sucks-heres-how-to-avoid-it-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/23/socialism-sucks-heres-how-to-avoid-it-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Some of the “cool” kids say they like socialism. Of course they have no emotional clue what socialism is.

Maybe they’ve read about socialism, seen the movies, and heard about it from their college professors—ya know, like the one who actually visited the old Soviet Union.
But those sources give only an intellectual view of socialism. You can’t actually _feel _it. And life, in the end, is about feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Pollsters Aren’t Telling You</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/21/what-the-pollsters-arent-telling-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 04:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/21/what-the-pollsters-arent-telling-you/</guid>
      <description>Polls do influence elections. That’s why people like Nate Silver and some of the writers at Business Insider are doing somersaults over Gallup’s Daily Presidential Tracking numbers.

For over a week, Gallup has shown a tidal wave for support for Mitt Romney. Nate Silver of FiveThirtyEight tried to discredit Gallup by blogging about outlier results it’s shown in past years. Here’s the conclusion Business Insider reached:
 Bottom line: Gallup swings wildly and it frequently has results not in line with other pollsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What Robin Carnahan Doesn’t Want You Know About Proposition E</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/17/heres-what-robin-carnahan-doesnt-want-you-know-about-proposition-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 23:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/17/heres-what-robin-carnahan-doesnt-want-you-know-about-proposition-e/</guid>
      <description>Robin Carnahan, the Democrat Missouri Secretary of State, writes ballot language like the editorial page editor of the Post-Dispatch.

Carnahan wrote, perhaps, the most biased and unprofessional ballot initiative ever written regarding Proposition E. She wanted you to think that Proposition E would outlaw all insurance in the state of Missouri and compel pet owners to feed rat poison to their animals. Here’s the original ballot language Carnahan wrote:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will KMOX Drop Candy Crowley Or Lose Its Credibility?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/will-kmox-drop-candy-crowley-or-lose-its-credibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 04:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/will-kmox-drop-candy-crowley-or-lose-its-credibility/</guid>
      <description>CNN’s Candy Crowley talks politics during KMOX’s Total Information AM every Friday. KMOX Presents Crowley as a credible source of political information.
But Crowley’s credibility is gone.
On Tuesday, Crowley jumped into the Presidential Debate by claiming Barack Obama called the Benghazi attack “an act of terror” in the Rose Garden on September 12. In hockey, she’d have earned a game misconduct for being the third player into a fight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss A Rising Conservative Star</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/dont-miss-a-rising-conservative-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 23:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/dont-miss-a-rising-conservative-star/</guid>
      <description>I met Raz Shaver in 2010. Even though he’s many years my junior, Raz has been an insightful, patient, and indispensible to mentor in grassroots activism.

Raz continues to help me and St. Louis Tea Party Coalition from his bunker in Texas. He also helps groups like St. Louis Tea Party all around the country. Victories and 2010, those to come in 2012, owe, in a large degree, to Raz Shafer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turns Out The Guy Dumping On The Middle Class Is Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/09/turns-out-the-guy-dumping-on-the-middle-class-is-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/09/turns-out-the-guy-dumping-on-the-middle-class-is-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, Joe Biden made the news by declaring that the middle class in America has been getting dumped on ever since he and Obama took their oaths of office. The statement marked the first time Biden got something right since that day. What Uncle Joe failed to mention was that he has been in charge of the White House’s Middle Class Task Force since January 30, 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now We Know Why Mitt Romney Has Been Wildly Successful In Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 00:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama’s performance was not nearly as bad as Romney’s performance was good.

Not good—terrific.
I’m not talking about his politics and policies; I’m talking Romney’s remarkable presence. Here are the four principles of presence that Romney knocked out of the park.
Command of the Facts When it came to facts—and to how those facts matter to the listeners—Mitt Romney seemed more prepared for the office of President than the President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners Proves Government Can’t Get Anything Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/04/st-louis-board-of-police-commissioners-proves-government-cant-get-anything-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/04/st-louis-board-of-police-commissioners-proves-government-cant-get-anything-right/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives love cracking on government and its unintended consequences. How often does a government initiative give us backassward results?
Exhibit A: Obama hands Solyndra millions in tax dollars to promote green energy. Solyndra (and numerous other green energy grant recipients) goes bankrupt.
Another example is the St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners.
In 1861, Missouri’s legislature created a board of commissioners to oversee the St. Louis Police Department. Why? Because Missouri was a slave state, but St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday, Jack Hennessy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/02/happy-birthday-jack-hennessy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/02/happy-birthday-jack-hennessy/</guid>
      <description>I don’t get into town to visit my dad often enough. That’s my loss.
Jack Hennessy, my dad, epitomizes what we call The Greatest Generation.
He helped raise his younger brothers and sister after their mother passed away. Jack was ten. His youngest sibling, my uncle Jim, was a newborn.
Jack Hennessy answered the call of World War II. He was a Machinist’s Mate in the Navy. He answered, again, when North Korea crossed the 34th Parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Police Department Is Crumbling, But You Can Vote to Save It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</guid>
      <description>You get the feeling that Rex Sinquefield holds a grudge against his home state, and he’s using some of his fortune to punish us.
Rex gave a quarter million dollars to Obama’s Lawyer, Chris Koster. But that wasn’t his first assault on us. Rex’s war against the St. Louis Police Department is older and far more bitter.
Rex wants to force the state to surrender the Board of Police Commissioners for St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignoramus Rex</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/30/ignoramus-rex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 17:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/30/ignoramus-rex/</guid>
      <description>Arguably, the most important battles for economic liberty in the next four years will be between states and the government in Washington. The progressives in Washington want to consolidate power and money to feed the insatiable appetite of parasites in the USA and the world.

Rex Sinquefield, the billionaire Bishop DuBourg alum who masquerades as a libertarian-ish Republican, lifted his mask this week to help Washington’s progressives steal Missouri’s autonomy and treasures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barack Obama Is Having a Very Bad Week, and Even WaPo Noticed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/26/barack-obamas-having-a-very-bad-week-and-even-wapo-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/26/barack-obamas-having-a-very-bad-week-and-even-wapo-noticed/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;180&amp;rdquo;] Barack Obama (Photo credit: jamesomalley)[/caption]
The smartest man in the world can’t make a gaffe, surely. When Barack Obama says something ridiculous, mean-spirited, wrongheaded, or just plain dumb, he means it.
So we know Obama considers the murders of Ambassador Chris Stevens and three others mere “bumps in the road” to his re-election. Four bumps, to be precise.
When Obama says Israel is just “one of our strongest allies” in the Middle East, no longer our strongest, he means it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Write Yourself Into the Great American Novel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/24/how-to-write-yourself-into-the-great-american-novel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/24/how-to-write-yourself-into-the-great-american-novel/</guid>
      <description>A couple years ago, a lot of folks believed that victory in 2010 would be a cakewalk. Led by Tea Party activists, the GOP picked up over 800 legislative seats, state and federal, in the 2010 off-year election. Rumors of the Republican Party&amp;rsquo;s death had been greatly exaggerated.

Or so it seemed.
Novels and action movies involve a hero&amp;rsquo;s quest. The main character hopes to accomplish something. Dorothy wants to return to Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Barack Obama is Right?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/19/which-barack-obama-is-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/19/which-barack-obama-is-right/</guid>
      <description>A genius is someone who can hold contrary concepts simultaneously in mind.
What, then, do we call a person who simultaneously argues two contrary concepts?

How ‘bout “demagogue?”
A few weeks ago, Barack Obama told America’s business owners that they are not responsible for their success. “Someone else built that.”
Today, the same Obama told Mitt Romney that there not many people who consider themselves victims.
Does Mr. Obama believe that people in dire straights are not victims of circumstances?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Trust Barack Obama for 4 More Years?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/17/can-you-trust-barack-obama-for-4-more-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/17/can-you-trust-barack-obama-for-4-more-years/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama came to office promising to heal the planet (I didn’t know it was sick), lower the waters, and end war as we knew it “whilst waking on water squirting wine out his ass,” to borrow William S. Burroughs’s anti-Christian blasphemy in Naked Lunch. (Funny. I don’t recall reading about Christians blowing up embassies over that book’s publication.)

Four years later, The One might want to let the waters rise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Sums Up Everything I Believe Better Than I Ever Could</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/14/this-sums-up-everything-i-believe-better-than-i-ever-could/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 06:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/14/this-sums-up-everything-i-believe-better-than-i-ever-could/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;463&amp;rdquo;] Buckley (right) and L. Brent Bozell Jr. promote their book McCarthy and His Enemies, 1954 (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
The Liberal Kirsten Powers (my favorite liberal at times) described the leftist media&amp;rsquo;s mania as &amp;ldquo;absolutely, utterly insane.&amp;rdquo;
What triggered the maniacal insanity from MSNBC and The New York Times (among others) was Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s public dismay over the way Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s State Department responded to terror attacks on US embassies in Egypt and Libya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the Romney Campaign Serious About Winning?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/11/is-the-romney-campaign-serious-about-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 10:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/11/is-the-romney-campaign-serious-about-winning/</guid>
      <description>The Romney Campaign today reminded me of the McCain Campaign of 2008.
I&amp;rsquo;m pretty good at ignoring bogus, fraudulent polls like the one CNN released tonight. In that poll, CNN announced a massive 52-46 national lead for Obama. If true, the race would be all but over.
CNN, of course, cooked the books on this one.
About one-third of voters describe themselves as independents, CNN sampled only 3% independents for its latest poll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Rock the Election Like Scott Walker and Richard Mourdock</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/08/how-to-rock-the-election-like-scott-walker-and-richard-mourdock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 20:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/08/how-to-rock-the-election-like-scott-walker-and-richard-mourdock/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] The Gadsden flag (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
We&amp;rsquo;re past Empty Chair Day. The conventions are over. Barack Obama still stands between us and liberty. And the Establishment&amp;rsquo;s more worried about its $$$ future than about America&amp;rsquo;s future.
What does that mean? It means _you and I _ will determine what happens in Election 2012 and beyond.
If you want to have a hand in America&amp;rsquo;s future, listen up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Told You So! Democrats BOO God, Israel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/05/i-told-you-so-democrats-boo-god-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 02:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/05/i-told-you-so-democrats-boo-god-israel/</guid>
      <description>As if reading from a script written by the Romney campaign, the Democrats on Wednesday managed to mangle their public image even further, this time by booing God and Israel.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12536&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;288&amp;rdquo;] Clipped from https://thespeechatimeforchoosing.wordpress.com[/caption]
On Tuesday, the Democratic National Convention stripped God&amp;rsquo;s name from their platform and rejected Israel&amp;rsquo;s choice of Jerusalem as its capital.
Wednesday, the party panicked and rushed in an amendment to restore God and Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Trust the Democcrats&#39; Platform?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/04/can-you-trust-the-democcrats-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 04:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/04/can-you-trust-the-democcrats-platform/</guid>
      <description>For years voters have complained that politicians and parties say anything to get a vote. People have longed for the days of plain talk and honesty.
Well, the Democrats passed a new platform today. Two headlines emerged:
  The Democrats rejected any reference to God.
  The Democrats rejected Jerusalem as Israel&amp;rsquo;s capital.
  The question is: can you trust them? Do Democrats really reject God and reject Jerusalem as the center of Israeli political life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Karl Rove School of Sanctimony</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/03/the-karl-rove-school-of-sanctimony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 23:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/03/the-karl-rove-school-of-sanctimony/</guid>
      <description>When I read about Todd Akin&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate comments to Charles Jaco, my first thought was uncharitable. &amp;ldquo;I could just kill him.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I could kill him,&amp;rdquo; is an idiom. Its cousins include &amp;ldquo;wring his neck&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;poke his eyes out.&amp;rdquo; Idioms hyperbolize our emotional reaction to an event.
I was angry because Todd Akin gave the left a great talking point in the infamous interview. I like Todd Akin. I voted for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Warning Signs That Obama’s Imploding</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/02/7-warning-signs-that-obamas-imploding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 21:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/02/7-warning-signs-that-obamas-imploding/</guid>
      <description>Hurricane Isaac smiled on the Republicans in Tampa and delivered more misery to New Orleans and its surroundings. That was just one of the ominous signs that 2012 is shaping up to be a forgettable year for Democrats, especially for Barack Obama.

Here’s seven more warning signs that Obama’s 6-year campaign is about to implode:
1. Torrential Rains Wipe the Face of Mount Obamamore
Not that weather plays favorites, but you have wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See This Movie Today</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/25/see-this-movie-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 13:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/25/see-this-movie-today/</guid>
      <description>You will irritate the the left. And you will like it.
https://m.deadline.com/2012/08/first-box-office-anti-obama-movie-1/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abraham, Isaac, and Todd</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/24/abraham-isaac-and-todd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/24/abraham-isaac-and-todd/</guid>
      <description>The story Isaac is about tests of faith.
God commanded Abraham to sacrifice Isaac, his only son, born after Abraham and Sarah had given up hope of conceiving.
Once Isaac was bound and placed on the altar, God stayed Abraham&amp;rsquo;s hand. &amp;ldquo;Now I know you fear God.&amp;rdquo;
You know the rest.
It just struck me this morning, listening to the weather during Jamie Allman&amp;rsquo;s show, that Isaac now threatens the GOP convention, dangling above Tampa like Abraham&amp;rsquo;s dagger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3:  Todd Akin Needs to Lead or Get Out of the Way</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] Todd Akin: member of the United States House of Representatives. (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
Part 3 of 3 | Read Part 1 | Read Part 2
Before we get too far down the Akin rally road, let&amp;rsquo;s get some solid advice to Mr. Akin.
His principles, his spine, his grassroots do no good if Missouri turns blue. He cannot advance his causes from his house in Wildwood. Failure to take the Senate makes Obamacare permanent, at least in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: Here Is Todd Akin’s Real Crime</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-2-here-is-todd-akins-real-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-2-here-is-todd-akins-real-crime/</guid>
      <description>Part 2 of 3 | Read Part 1 | Read Part 3
What is Todd&amp;rsquo;s real crime?
He&amp;rsquo;s a damaged candidate, sure, but he is not a damaged man.
He was wrong, but** he erred on the side of life**.
It says something about a society and political mood where a man can be disqualified for loving life and God, but another man celebrated for enabling the slaughter of living children with surgical scissors through the base of their skulls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 1: Contingencies Every Conservatives Needs Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-1-contingencies-every-conservatives-needs-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-1-contingencies-every-conservatives-needs-right-now/</guid>
      <description>Part 1 of 3 | Read Part 2 | Read Part 3
I think it&amp;rsquo;s smart to have a plan in case Todd Akin drops. The GOP central committee is working on a plan. If you wait until after a vacancy occurs, your preferences will be meaningless.
That said, if you should decide to plot a contingency to influence the selection of a candidate to fill a vacancy that might occur, consider this: **the MOGOP central committee is not tea-party-ish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preserving the Republic Is Paramount in 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/20/preserving-the-republic-is-paramount-in-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/20/preserving-the-republic-is-paramount-in-2012/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I blogged about loyalty to people and loyalty to principles. Both are important. Loyalty to people is an honorable principle.
Sometimes, the ideal is paramount. In 2012, we simply must take the US Senate. We must put Claire McCaskill out of office. And we must send a strong conservative to the US House of Representatives from Missouri’s 2nd Congressional district.
Missouri’s 2nd Congressional District has been well served by Todd Akin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Theory and the Ryan Pick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/game-theory-and-the-ryan-pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 21:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/game-theory-and-the-ryan-pick/</guid>
      <description>If Mitt Romney applied game theory in choosing Paul Ryan, I have renewed respect for him. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain why, but first a bit of background on game theory.
Game theory is a branch of social science concerned with strategic decision-making. It is most closely associated with economics. Professor John Nash, the subject of the movie A Beautiful Mind, won a Nobel Prize in Economics for his work in game theory. (For a great primer on the subject, read Thinking Strategically: the competitive advantage in business, politics, and everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Have No Idea How Much Your Boss Pays in Payroll Taxes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/you-have-no-idea-how-much-your-boss-pays-in-payroll-taxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 09:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/you-have-no-idea-how-much-your-boss-pays-in-payroll-taxes/</guid>
      <description>America is suffocating under an amazing tax burden, but most Americans STILL underestimate how much their tax bill really is. That’s because Washington has done a fantastic job of forcing employers to hide most of the taxes you pay. If people had to see and deal with their total liability, the Democratic Party would be swept into the dust bin of history.

Here are some frightening facts from Rasmussen:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Are the Bill in Congress That Need Your Attention</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/these-are-the-bill-in-congress-that-need-your-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/these-are-the-bill-in-congress-that-need-your-attention/</guid>
      <description>Even though Congress is winding down, there are dangerous bills on the desk. I used Heritage Action’s Popvox program to tell Congressman (and future Senator) Todd Akin I oppose the FARM bill that does less for farmers and more for wasteful government statism.

Here’s the whole slate of bills you should write to Congress about:
Oppose the Big-Spending Farm Bill: Email Your Representative Now Tell Blunt and McCaskill to Kill LOST—A Bill to Surrender US Sovereignty</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Two People in West County About The After Party This Thursday at Sky Music Lounge</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/tell-two-people-in-west-county-about-the-after-party-this-thursday-at-sky-music-lounge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/tell-two-people-in-west-county-about-the-after-party-this-thursday-at-sky-music-lounge/</guid>
      <description>A friend from Dallas just called me. He said he met two conservatives from Ballwin who’d love to be involved in movement conservatism . . . but don’t know how.
I was shocked. And a little embarrassed. ** How can someone in West County not know about St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and The After Party?** &#39;

Clearly, I’ve done something wrong. I’m sorry. But I can’t just throw my hands up and walk away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If We Don’t Flip Some Toss-Up States, Romney, Ryan, and the USA Are Screwed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</guid>
      <description>Choosing Paul Ryan as his running mate was a great Romney move. Looking ahead, Romney sees movement conservatives working hard right up to the election—even if he or his advisors continues to say stupid things. That was necessary.
SCROLL DOWN FOR TWO IMPORTANT EVENTS THIS WEEK
But it wasn’t enough to win the election and unseat America’s first anti-American president. To do that, we must find a way to win over the selfish middle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romney-Ryan Have a Vision They Can Talk About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/11/obamas-surrounded-by-really-nasty-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 02:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/11/obamas-surrounded-by-really-nasty-people/</guid>
      <description>Why did murder skyrocket in Chicago as soon as Rahm Emanuel became mayor? Why have Americans become nastier and meaner since Barack Obama became president?

As Michael Dukakis told us, a fish rots from the head down. Obama surrounds himself with people who thrive on decay and death.
After four years, Obama has nothing to say for himself. Nothing. He can only cut and attack and lie and sneer and mock like a high school bully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Grades</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/10/primary-grades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 01:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/10/primary-grades/</guid>
      <description>I was surprised to learn that Sarah Steelman conceded the GOP Senate race at 10:00. I&amp;rsquo;d talked to Todd Akin at my polling place on Tuesday morning, and he confirmed my suspicion the [Missouri](https://maps.google.com/maps?ll=38.5,-92.5&amp;amp;spn=3.0,3.0&amp;amp;q=38.5,-92.5 (Missouri)&amp;amp;t=h) Republican race for US Senate would be close. It really wasn&amp;rsquo;t.
Mr. Akin won handily, considering the 3-way race. John Brunner&amp;rsquo;s remarkably negative, nasty, angry campaign should have made the race much closer. It didn&amp;rsquo;t. Sarah Palin&amp;lsquo;s endorsement of Ms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks to the Candidates Who Took My Survey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/04/thanks-to-the-candidates-who-took-my-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 00:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/04/thanks-to-the-candidates-who-took-my-survey/</guid>
      <description>Thanks, so much, to the candidates who took a moment to respond to my survey. Here are the results, including the candidates&amp;rsquo; verbatim responses.
I will oppose tax credits for private development except for extreme cases, such as recovery from disasters.
Agree 3 100% Disagree 0 0% I will reject federal funds that come with strings attached.
Agree 2 67% Disagree 1 33% I will resist federal mandates that violate the original intent of the Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Search of Loyalty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/26/in-search-of-loyalty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 10:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/26/in-search-of-loyalty/</guid>
      <description>Long
To what and whom do we owe loyalty, and how should we express it?
Generational historians William Strauss and Neil Howe describe a generation of &amp;ldquo;nomads&amp;rdquo; in their prophetic book The Fourth Turning.
 &amp;ldquo;The 13th Generation (Nomad, born 1961-1981) survived a hurried childhood of divorce, latchkeys, open classrooms, devil-child movies, and a shift from G to R ratings. They came of age curtailing the earlier rise in youth crime and fall in test scores—yet heard themselves denounced as so wild and stupid as to put The Nation at Risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Economy Is Getting Worse Thanks to Liberalism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/25/the-economy-is-getting-worse-thanks-to-liberalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 10:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/25/the-economy-is-getting-worse-thanks-to-liberalism/</guid>
      <description>The horror in Aurora, Colorado, gave President Obama a little cover last Friday. That&amp;rsquo;s because the Labor Department announced that unemployment rose in 27 states.
President Obama promised to hold unemployment under eight percent if Congress passed the stimulus package in 2009. Congress did, but Obama failed. Remember all those green jobs? They&amp;rsquo;re gone.
**The problem isn&amp;rsquo;t Barack Obama; the problem is liberalism. **
Liberals believe that only experts can make intelligent decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candidates, Take My Simple Missouri Candidate Questionnaire</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/24/candidates-take-my-simple-missouri-candidate-questionnaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/24/candidates-take-my-simple-missouri-candidate-questionnaire/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m interesting in a few things about candidates. If you are a candidate for the Missouri legislature or for statewide office, I invite you take this short questionnaire.
I will post results before the August 7 primary.

Please note that I do not intend to base my vote solely on your answers to these questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DESE: The original box of rocks that nothing is dumber than</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/24/dese-the-original-box-of-rocks-that-nothing-is-dumber-than/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/24/dese-the-original-box-of-rocks-that-nothing-is-dumber-than/</guid>
      <description>According to research from Missouri Education Watchdog, the Department of Elementary and Secondary Education (DESE) agreed to surrender Missouri&amp;rsquo;s education voice under Obama&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Race to the Top&amp;rdquo; scheme. Race to the Top was a contest in which states agreed to let the federal Department of Education, via two puppet organizations, run all of the state&amp;rsquo;s education systems. In exchange, some states were awarded money, but others were not.
Chris Nicastro, chief rock in the DESE box, applied for the grant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why Tax Credits Kill Society</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/23/heres-why-tax-credits-kill-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 10:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/23/heres-why-tax-credits-kill-society/</guid>
      <description>Tax credits reward particular businesses or developers with tax dollars from the general population. They concentrate wealth in a few hands. Tax credits are the way politicians play the market with someone else&amp;rsquo;s money.

Worse, **Republicans are addicted to tax credits. **
A Missouri House Republican leader told a constituent that his party gives tax dollars to people who &amp;ldquo;spend it smarter.&amp;rdquo; Bill Clinton said the same thing in about 1992.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distrust Adjectives, and the Politicians Who Use Them</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/21/distrust-adjectives-and-the-politicians-who-use-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 16:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/21/distrust-adjectives-and-the-politicians-who-use-them/</guid>
      <description>Missouri&amp;rsquo;s primary is August 7. Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Republicans now litter the airwaves and in-boxes with smears against their Republican opponents. What strikes me is the weakness of so many of their pitches.
Every political ad is a pitch. It&amp;rsquo;s a chance to sell an idea and to volunteer as that idea&amp;rsquo;s champion in some high office. What a noble calling.
Few politicians take that noble path, sadly. Instead, they bully and vilify their opponents&amp;ndash;especially their primary opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Old Reagan Soviet Jokes Are on US</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/18/the-old-reagan-soviet-jokes-are-on-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/18/the-old-reagan-soviet-jokes-are-on-us/</guid>
      <description>Ronald Reagan loved to tell jokes about the Soviet Union.If Obama’s re-elected, though, these same jokes could be turned on the United States.

Some of them already can be.
 It&amp;rsquo;s hard to get an automobile in the United States. They are owned mainly by elite bureaucrats. It takes an average of 10 years to get a car. 1 out of 7 families owned automobiles. You have to go through a major process and put the money out in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If the election were held today, there’d be a lot of crying and gnashing of teeth</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/17/gnashing-of-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/17/gnashing-of-teeth/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a screen grab from RealClearPolitics.com’s presidential tracking poll:

RCP aggregates dozens of polls to produce its RCP average. The method has been remarkably accurate, especially at the state level.
It’s time to focus on preventing the unmitigated disaster of a second Obama term.
In 112 days, Americans will vote on whether or not to continue our experiment in self-government. If the election were held today, that experiment would be aborted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just How Bad Would a Second Obama Term Be?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/16/just-how-bad-would-a-second-obama-term-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/16/just-how-bad-would-a-second-obama-term-be/</guid>
      <description>If you believe that 92 percent of people need to have most aspect of their lives managed by experts, then a second Obama term will make you happy.

If, however, you believe in self-governance, that people are endowed by God and nature with the capacity and unalienable right to manage their own affairs, then a second Obama term will be a massive human rights violation.
Consider what the Obama administration has already brought us:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gary Weigert on WGNU. Listen</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/07/gary-weigert-on-wgnu-listen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2012 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/07/gary-weigert-on-wgnu-listen/</guid>
      <description>Just to let everyone know, Gary Wiegert, is back on the radio. Every Friday at 1200 noon. WGNU 920 AM or you can connect on the computer. Gary Wiegert is also a St Louis Police Officer and a devoted Tea Party Supporter.
wgnu920am.com Listener Call-In Line 314-448-4325
Via Patsy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for Defiance, Resistance, and Resolve in Missouri</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/06/time-for-defiance-resistance-and-resolve-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/06/time-for-defiance-resistance-and-resolve-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>At the Pachyderm Club’s national convention last year, I overheard a Republican Missouri State Representative talking about HB 609. “It was the best bill I’ve ever been involved with,” she said. “Those people who just went nuts don’t know anything about insurance.”

If you read my blog, you’re likely one of the “those people,” the ignorant masses who don’t understand the fineries of the legislative process. You don’t appreciate how hard the insurance industry lobbyists worked with Jefferson City to craft a law that sold only a bit of you into slavery while ensuring the insurance companies remained profitable and your favorite Republican legislators had the money to campaign next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials About To Bite Obama’s Crap Sandwich . . . with Relish</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/05/millennials-about-to-bite-obamas-crap-sandwich-with-relish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/05/millennials-about-to-bite-obamas-crap-sandwich-with-relish/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the folks at Business Insider get fairly simple ideas ass backwards. Take their Winners and Losers story on the Supreme Court’s Obamacare decision. It’s dead wrong about Millennials (born after 1982):
 Young people can also count themselves winners in the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s decision to uphold the Affordable Care Act, which allows children to stay on their parents&amp;rsquo; insurance plan until their 26th birthday. Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/winners-losers-affordable-care-act-supreme-court-obamacare-ruling-2012-6?op=1#ixzz1zP2AiaCO
 [continued after image]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Am Skipping Independence Day This Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/04/im-skipping-independence-day-because-we-gave-our-independence-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/04/im-skipping-independence-day-because-we-gave-our-independence-back/</guid>
      <description>July 4th became my favorite holiday in 1981, replacing Christmas. Maybe it was a sign of my maturity.

It was also a sign of the times. After a ten-year hiatus, patriotism was chic again, thanks to Ronald Reagan. Here’s a few other things that made me fall in love with Independence Day:
 * Fireworks—who doesn’t love blowing stuff up? * Parties * VP Fair (tragically renamed to Fair St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is One Sign That Your Government Is Tyrannical</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/03/here-is-one-sign-your-government-is-tyrannical/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/03/here-is-one-sign-your-government-is-tyrannical/</guid>
      <description>We throw around big scary words like “tyranny” too much. I’m guilty myself. While we get a lot of attention with hyperbole, we’ll lose credibility over time. Then when tyranny emerges, people will ignore our screams.
Like now.

For years, Congress has used the tax code to motivate behavior. Tax credits for insulated windows and electric cars are examples. The home mortgage deduction is another. And tuition tax credits, dependent tax credits, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Depression Be Your Guide</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/02/let-depression-be-your-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/02/let-depression-be-your-guide/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I gave you a reason to celebrate the Supreme Court’s decision. But I never said to let go of your anger or depression. ** That’s because we need creativity, focus, and action, and you get those through emotional distress. **

In his new best-selling book, Jonah Lehrer discusses the link between depression and creativity:
 This helps explain why Forgas has found that states of sadness— he induces the downcast mood with a film about death and cancer— also correlate with better writing samples; subjects compose sentences that are clearer and more compelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Roberts Switched His Vote Under Outside Pressure</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/01/john-roberts-switched-his-vote-under-outside-pressure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 23:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/01/john-roberts-switched-his-vote-under-outside-pressure/</guid>
      <description>It won’t look like decay to many. John Roberts will be the toast of the political class for years to come. He’ll attend all the prettiest events with the prettiest people. Barbara Streisand will have him out to her massively carbon-releasing Hollywood mansion. The Washington Post intelligentsia will place his bust in its pantheon of The Evolved. He might even golf with Bill and Obama.

But beneath the black robe grows a dark stain on his soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What’s Great About the Supreme Court’s Obamacare Decision</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</guid>
      <description>In the Ronald Reagan movie Kings Row, Reagan plays Drake McHugh, whose legs are sawn off by a sadistic, class-conscious doctor.

Everyone remembers the line “Where’s the rest of me?” No remembers what happens after that. I’ll fill you in.
McHugh’s best friend, a psychiatrist, decides to tell McHugh (Reagan) the truth: his legs were perfectly healthy, but the doctor cut them off to keep the lower class McHugh from pursuing the doctor’s debutante daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Insider Has No Idea Where Money Comes From</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/27/business-insider-has-no-idea-where-money-comes-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/27/business-insider-has-no-idea-where-money-comes-from/</guid>
      <description>I love some things about Business Insider. Mostly its great headlines.
Unfortunately, sometimes its writers show an ignorance of basic economics in their rush to catapult Obama to a second term. Joe Weisenthal is just the latest example.
Joe tries to claim that economic recovery in the US is retarded by loss of public sector jobs.

What Joe doesn’t seem to get is this: the private sector pays for those public sector jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Florida Has the Relationship Between Home Ownership and Growth All Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/25/richard-florida-has-the-relationship-between-home-ownership-and-growth-all-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/25/richard-florida-has-the-relationship-between-home-ownership-and-growth-all-wrong/</guid>
      <description>In a column intended to attract readers, not to promote hard economics, Rotman University economist Richard Florida declares that home ownership is terrible for the US Economy.

The problem is, like many economists,** Florida’s understanding of home ownership is 180 degrees ass-backwards**. Florida thinks that home ownership is supposed to _cause_ economic growth.
 Instead of leading to economic development, higher rates of homeownership today are associated with lower levels of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare Ruling Comes Down This Week, and We’re Having a Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/24/obamacare-ruling-comes-down-this-week-and-were-having-a-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 18:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/24/obamacare-ruling-comes-down-this-week-and-were-having-a-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Pack clothes, flags, and signs for an Obamacare Tea Party at Forest Park on Art Hill this week. The rally will begin at 7:00 PM on the day the Supreme Court rules.

We don’t know the day, but we do know the time: 7:00 pm in Forest Park on Art Hill (map below). The most likely days are Monday or Thursday, but because of the magnitude of this case, it could be any day of the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s One Way the Government&#39;s Making Medicine Worse in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 02:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</guid>
      <description>I had to go to the doctor today. The reason&amp;rsquo;s not important. Here&amp;rsquo;s what is:
**It took my doctor 10 minutes to describe my symptoms into a government-mandated voice recognition system. **
In the old days, the doctor took notes. Now, he has to recite his observations into a Mad Men-era dictaphone. &amp;ldquo;Male, age 48, blood pressure one-twenty-one over seventy-three . . . &amp;quot;
The damn machine (government medical technology) couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand half the doctor&amp;rsquo;s words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday (Infographic)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</guid>
      <description>The world&amp;rsquo;s economy&amp;ndash;including BRICs&amp;ndash;is collapsing. The problem is debt, and the youth will set us free. Even if that&amp;rsquo;s a very painful liberation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Never Guess Who&#39;s About to Become Obama&#39;s Biggest Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>In 2008, we heard all about the youth movement for Obama. We heard that the enormous Millennial Generation, born between 1982 and 2001, would destroy the GOP and everything America once stood for&amp;ndash;like jobs, family, faith, and hard work. And when Obama won, many believed the tales of the Obama Youth.

But many were wrong. Voters under 30 have had it with vague promises and glittering bullshit from that punk from Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Differences Between Bain and Solyndra</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/23/3-differences-between-bain-and-solyndra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 09:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/23/3-differences-between-bain-and-solyndra/</guid>
      <description>As Obama and his myrmidons continue to make asses of themselves by arguing that no one should ever put their own capital at risk, it seems timely to point out that Solyndra, and the White House&amp;rsquo;s many gambles on hypothetical energy companies, is not a fair comparison to Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s work at Bain &amp;amp; Co.
   It&amp;rsquo;s legal for individuals and companies to use their own money to buy failing companies and try to save them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry Blodget Freaks Out Completely Over JP Morgan’s $2 Billion Loss</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/12/henry-blodget-freaks-out-completely-over-jp-morgans-2-billion-loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2012 20:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/12/henry-blodget-freaks-out-completely-over-jp-morgans-2-billion-loss/</guid>
      <description>Looks like about $1.2 billion of JP Morgan’s $2 billion loss involved Henry Blodget’s 401k. 
How else to explain his emotional outburst on Business Insider? Why else would he jump to the conclusion that our bankrupt federal government understands finances better than billionaires?
Here’s Blodget:
 Wall Street can&amp;rsquo;t be trusted to manage—or even correctly assess—its own risks.
This is in part because, time and again, Wall Street has demonstrated that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t even KNOW what risks it is taking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Candy Crowley: Tea Party Groups Resemble the 13 Colonies, Not the Balkans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</guid>
      <description>Analogies say more about the speaker than about the subject.
Candy Crowley told KMOX Radio listeners on Friday that Tea Party groups resemble the Balkans without guns.
Wrong. Crappy analogy, Candy. The diverse and autonomous, often quarrelsome,** Tea Party groups remind me of the original 13 colonies.**
The colonies were divided on just about every subject imaginable. The disagreed on slavery, on economics, on agraculture, manufacturing, cities, names &amp;ndash; name it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Performs “Indian Rain Dance” To Quell Dispute</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/elizabeth-warren-performs-indian-rain-dance-to-quell-dispute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/elizabeth-warren-performs-indian-rain-dance-to-quell-dispute/</guid>
      <description>Cambridge, MA—Massachusetts Democratic Senate candidate Elizabeth Warren donned a pink headdress and performed, what she called, an “authentic Indian rain dance” during a press conference today. Ms Warren was hoping to convince skeptics of her claims of Native American heritage. She also hinted that her preference for bison meat to beef indicates her heritage.
“My pepaw taught me this dance when I was a little girl,” Warren said during a short session with reporters at a high school gymnasium in Cambridge, MA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Attends Backyard Barbecue Fundraiser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/05/obama-attends-backyard-barbecue-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 16:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/05/obama-attends-backyard-barbecue-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12133&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;359&amp;rdquo;] President Obama looks over the menu before a campaign backyard barbecue in Ohio.[/caption]
Reports are that he went with the Neapolitan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTION:  Steve Tilley and Kevin Engler Want to Implement Obamacare. Stop Them.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/03/action-steve-tilley-and-kevin-engler-want-to-implement-obamacare-stop-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 02:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/03/action-steve-tilley-and-kevin-engler-want-to-implement-obamacare-stop-them/</guid>
      <description>Missouri House Speaker Steve Tilley and Senate Leader Kevin Engler never tire of implementing Obama’s totalitarian agenda.

This time, Tilley and Engler are shoving HB 1193 through to passage. This bill is designed to score brownie points with Sibelius and Obama by creating a prescription spy network that monitors the prescription drug purchases of every Missouri resident.
If Tilley and Engler get their way, every time your doctor writes a prescription, your pharmacist will be required to inform Jefferson City and Washington bureaucrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Holds Auditions for New Terrorist Mastermind</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/01/u-s-holds-auditions-for-new-terrorist-mastermind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 15:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/01/u-s-holds-auditions-for-new-terrorist-mastermind/</guid>
      <description>Washington, DC&amp;ndash;Reeling from the backlash over a campaign ad that paints President Barack Obama as Osama bin Laden&amp;rsquo;s sole assassin, the White House today announced open auditions for a new global terrorist mastermind.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12119&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;570&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Last year&amp;rsquo;s White House auditions for press secretary&amp;rdquo;][/caption]
White House spokesman Jay Carney told reporters &amp;ldquo;the world needs a dangerous, evil character to worry about . . . and, frankly, so does the President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studies Show Most Americans Are Too Stupid to Vote</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/29/studies-show-most-americans-are-too-stupid-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 21:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/29/studies-show-most-americans-are-too-stupid-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>The new fad among Democrats is to see how many illegal aliens they can pack into a voting booth. While we conservatives decry this illegal and anti-American grab at tyrannical power, we should take some solace in this sobering fact: those illegal aliens probably know as much about the American political system as most 13th generation Americans.

The fact is, most Americans are too stupid about politics to vote, which explains the 2008 election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCaskillPAC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/25/mccaskillpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 03:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/25/mccaskillpac/</guid>
      <description>What I find so funny about Claire McCaskill&amp;rsquo;s war on super pacs is that her husband is a super PAC.
For the record, I have formally endorsed Senator McCaskill in her race to return to private life.
Zimmerman Update Having declared George Zimmerman guilty of first degree, racially motivated murder, the MSM are now investigating the case.
What they&amp;rsquo;re finding:
 The George Zimmerman that Francescani describes is quite different from the &amp;ldquo;delusional racist vigilante&amp;rdquo; that many have made him out to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney Shut Down a Company Over a Young Woman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/24/mitt-romney-shut-down-a-company-over-a-young-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/24/mitt-romney-shut-down-a-company-over-a-young-woman/</guid>
      <description>There are many stories about Mitt Romney’s evil-doings when he ran Bain Capital, a $1 billion company famous for buying troubled companies and making money off them.

Some of the stories involve Bain laying off workers to make companies profitable, then selling them off.
Some of the stories involve Bain and Romney chopping companies to bits and selling off the parts.
This story is about Romney shutting down a thriving business over a woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Times Admits It&#39;s Basically Obama&#39;s Campaign Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/23/new-york-times-admits-its-basically-obamas-campaign-newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 23:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/23/new-york-times-admits-its-basically-obamas-campaign-newsletter/</guid>
      <description>The only surprise here is that the NYT&amp;rsquo;s own ombudsman admits that the paper is Obama&amp;rsquo;s best friend:
 Many critics view The Times as constitutionally unable to address the election in an unbiased fashion. Like a lot of America, it basked a bit in the warm glow of Mr. Obama’s election in 2008. The company published a book about the country’s first African-American president, “Obama: The Historic Journey.” The Times also published a lengthy portrait of him in its Times Topics section on NYTimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Committed Massive Vote Fraud in 2008, They&#39;ll Do It Again in 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/22/democrats-committed-massive-vote-fraud-in-2008-theyll-do-it-again-in-2012-and-few-people-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 02:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/22/democrats-committed-massive-vote-fraud-in-2008-theyll-do-it-again-in-2012-and-few-people-care/</guid>
      <description>John McCain knew that Obama&amp;rsquo;s minions orchestrated massive voter fraud in Ohio and Pennsylvania. Besides using New Black Panther Party soldiers to repel McCain voters from the polls,** Democrats stuff ballot boxes to give Obama the win in two states with a combined 41 electoral votes**.

Here&amp;rsquo;s how a memo leaked by wikileaks summarized McCain&amp;rsquo;s election night decision:
 After discussions with his inner circle, which explains the delay in his speech, McCain decided not to pursue the voter fraud in PA and Ohio, despite his staff&amp;rsquo;s desire to make it an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the GSA&#39;s 8th Grade Minds That Run Your Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/21/meet-the-gsas-8th-grade-minds-that-run-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 18:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/21/meet-the-gsas-8th-grade-minds-that-run-your-life/</guid>
      <description>There are two kinds of people in America: those who grow up to become productive adults, and those who become bureaucrats.
The GSA scandal lit up the 3 Stooges mentality of the &amp;ldquo;men and women&amp;rdquo; who would run every aspect of your life if Obama and his czars get their way.

Jeff Neely&amp;rsquo;s the guy Thomas Jefferson had in mind when wrote:
 He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harass our people, and eat out their substance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYT Describes Mayhem of “Taxmageddon”, And It Will Scare You Sick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</guid>
      <description>What the hell’s going on at NYT? First, they do a piece on Andrew Breitbart. Then they warn the world that Taxmageddon will crush the world in 2013, beginning with the USA.

Here&amp;rsquo;s how Business Insider summarized the David Leohardt article:
 Basically, with no changes to current law, taxes will rise for everyone, and after tax, inflation-adjusted income for the average American will drop to 1998 levels.
 Read more: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Election’s Over, and America Gave Obama His Eviction Notice. Here’s What Went Down.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/the-elections-over-and-america-gave-obama-his-eviction-notice-heres-what-went-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/the-elections-over-and-america-gave-obama-his-eviction-notice-heres-what-went-down/</guid>
      <description>The look on George “Stephie” Stephanopoulos’s face was priceless. He had to say it.

“ABC News now projects that President Obama will go down to defeat.”
He couldn’t bring himself to say, “Romney won” or “Republicans won.” He just couldn’t.
The network analysis was a political cliché run amok. My favorite came from James Carville who told CNN viewers that the election result “proves that crackers and racists vote.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Activist Calls for Stampede</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/frieda-responds-to-the-lake-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 10:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/frieda-responds-to-the-lake-post/</guid>
      <description>I blogged aboutthe battle of the Tea Party&amp;rsquo;s future going on around the Lake of the Ozarks recently.
I received this response from Freida Keough, St. Louis County Director ofMissouri Precinct Project:
 My answer: We have 56 positions for committeemen and women in 28 Townships for St.Louis County. Did you know that 35 new individuals filed for these positions in addition to the incumbents. Coincidence? I don&amp;rsquo;t think this happened because people felt they have nothing else to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hookers By The Dozens and Booze Galore--So Where Was BILL Clinton In All This? *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/hookers-by-the-dozens-and-booze-galore-so-where-was-bill-clinton-in-all-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 01:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/hookers-by-the-dozens-and-booze-galore-so-where-was-bill-clinton-in-all-this/</guid>
      <description>Let me get this straight. Secret Service Agents and some military guys brought more than 20 &amp;ndash; count &amp;lsquo;em, _twenty _&amp;ndash; hookers to a hotel in Cartagena, Columbia. The Americans were drinking&amp;ndash;a lot, according to hotel staff. When the girls were ready to leave, apparently, the Americans refused to pay.
I guess these soldier or sailors or Marines don&amp;rsquo;t watch enough movies. They&amp;rsquo;d know how hookers act when they don&amp;rsquo;t get paid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Cancelled Religious Freedom, But Some People Aren&#39;t Listening to Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/obama-cancelled-religious-freedom-but-some-people-arent-listening-to-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 10:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/obama-cancelled-religious-freedom-but-some-people-arent-listening-to-obama/</guid>
      <description>When Obama decreed that Catholics shall support and provide chemical abortions,he wasn&amp;rsquo;t promoting women. He was shackling religion.
Totalitarian autocrats don&amp;rsquo;t cotton freedom, unless they personally granted it. Obama doesn&amp;rsquo;t believe in individual liberty, but that all power and rights emanate from government. Timothy Cardinal Dolan agrees.
So it&amp;rsquo;s exciting to report that some St. Louisans are fighting back. Here&amp;rsquo;s the details:
Protest for Religious Freedom
Location: Old Courthouse (Directions) Date: Saturday, April 28, 2012 Time: 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: White House Chief of Staff Says Obama Has Complete Power to Decree Healthcare Rules</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/16/video-white-house-chief-of-staff-says-obama-has-complete-power-to-decree-healthcare-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 00:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/16/video-white-house-chief-of-staff-says-obama-has-complete-power-to-decree-healthcare-rules/</guid>
      <description>Jack Lew, Obama’s Chief of Staff, says Obamacare law gives the President the power make rules regarding your health. Period.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NhCxGdTJrxs]
Lee Presser’s comment nails it:
 Chris Wallace states this is precisely the reason why so many people oppose Obamacare.
 Share this frightening power grab with your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“[N]o one did it like Breitbart”</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/16/no-one-did-it-like-breitbart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/16/no-one-did-it-like-breitbart/</guid>
      <description>Last night, someone asked me, “who’s the most influential person in your iPhone contacts?”
“I don’t know,” I said. “Breitbart’s dead.”
David Carr writes in New York Times about the Life and Death of Andrew Breitbart.
Be advised that neither Carr nor NYT shares our political beliefs. And the tactics they cheer from the left, they attack when from the right. Funny how whenKaren Finney lies about Mitt Romney, it&amp;rsquo;s good journalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down at the Lake, They Want to Know &#34;Is the Tea Party Dead?&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/down-at-the-lake-they-want-to-know-is-the-tea-party-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 03:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/down-at-the-lake-they-want-to-know-is-the-tea-party-dead/</guid>
      <description>Is the Tea Party dead? That&amp;rsquo;s the big question this week around the Lake of the Ozarks.

First, Eric Reeve The Lake Liberal wrote this letter-to in Lake News Online. He concludes:
 We may hear of the Tea Party here and there in the future, but I doubt it will ever figure prominently in American politics again. I say we should take a moment and reflect on what it might have been as we say farewell to the once promising Tea Party movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The After Party is Thursday, April 19, at 7 pm</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/the-after-party-is-thursday-april-19-at-7-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 23:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/the-after-party-is-thursday-april-19-at-7-pm/</guid>
      <description>The After Party is Thursday, April 19, at 7 pm. The location is Crowne Plaza Hotel in Clayton.
The subject is the corrupt and corrupting judge selection process in Missouri, and how you can help change it. I learned a lot about the subject when Ed Martin pointed out this National Review article on the subject.
 The structure and left-wing dominance of the nominating commission (the distinctive feature of the Missouri Plan) has led many to argue that the state should amend the constitution to either directly elect judges or have them selected under something mirroring the advice/consent model set forth in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: Rick Santelli Destroys The Buffett Rule Live on CNBC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/video-rick-santelli-destroys-the-buffett-rule-live-on-cnbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 18:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/video-rick-santelli-destroys-the-buffett-rule-live-on-cnbc/</guid>
      <description>The man who&amp;rsquo;s 2009 rant inspired the Tea Party movement shreds Obama&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;soak the rich&amp;rdquo; plan. Shreds I said. [youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bfRxFFhhWnk] Santelli Crushes Buffett Rule
There is no tax solution to America&amp;rsquo;s spending problem. Each additional dollar confiscated from the economy to feed the Washington bureaucracy results in an additional $1.40 in new spending.
Washington IS THE PROBLEM!
Starve the monster. Bleed the monster. But** Don&amp;rsquo;t Feed the Monster!**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Former Governor and a Famous St. Louis Lawyer Indicted for Illegal Contributions to Democrat Party, and A Law Firm Changes Names in Mid-Quote</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/a-former-governor-and-a-famous-st-louis-lawyer-indicted-for-illegal-contributions-to-democrat-party-and-a-law-firm-changes-names-in-mid-quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 18:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/a-former-governor-and-a-famous-st-louis-lawyer-indicted-for-illegal-contributions-to-democrat-party-and-a-law-firm-changes-names-in-mid-quote/</guid>
      <description>Everyone else is writing about the news that former Missouri Democrat Governor, Roger Wilson and local lawyer Ed Griesedieck Jr. were indicted on federal fraud charges today.
The two allegedly made contributions to the Democrat Party (legal), and reimbursed themselves out of Missouri Employers Mutual Insurance Company’s coffers (illegal).
But that’s not the weird part. After all, election fraud is the Democrats’ principal form of amusement.
The weird part is the statement from Griesedieck’s law firm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Election’s Over, and the Republicans Got Creamed. Here’s What Went Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/the-elections-over-and-the-republicans-got-creamed-heres-what-went-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 18:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/the-elections-over-and-the-republicans-got-creamed-heres-what-went-wrong/</guid>
      <description>November 7, 2012—When the AP called Florida for Obama only twenty minutes after polls closed there (8:00 EDT), any hopes of a Republican presidential victory were dashed.

And before polls closed in the West, we knew that the GOP had lost the House as well as seven state legislatures.
In short, the Grand Old Party died last night.
Here’s what went wrong.
Wrong Candidate at the Top: When Republicans run the candidate the liberal press wants them to run, they get creamed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Have a Date Next Thursday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/you-have-a-date-next-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 18:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/you-have-a-date-next-thursday/</guid>
      <description>Of course you do.
It’s at 7:00 at the Crowne Plaza in Clayton. The Crowne Plaza Grille, to be precise. April 19.
It’s the April After Party, and the topic is the Missouri plan.
Your mission: bring one friend who’s never been to a Tea Party event.
If you can’t find someone to bring, come anyway.
Thinking about skipping? Don’t.
The most important election since Lincoln’s first is just seven months away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring view</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/09/spring-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/09/spring-view/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you to just stop and enjoy the view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama, Obamacare and the Supreme Court</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/06/obama-obamacare-and-the-supreme-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 01:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/06/obama-obamacare-and-the-supreme-court/</guid>
      <description>First, my prediction:
 Is Obamacare a tax? (8-1 Against)  Technically speaking, if Obamacare is a tax, it could be non-justiciable until implementation. However, judicial precedence suggests the courts may review a tax before its implementation in certain circumstances. The Government did not even want to argue that Obamacare was a tax, so the Supreme Court (SCOTUS) appointed a separate attorney to make the argument. The only SCOTUS justice that appeared to entertain this line was Justice Breyer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Remove Justice Ginsburg</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/01/time-to-remove-justice-ginsberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/01/time-to-remove-justice-ginsberg/</guid>
      <description>From Mark Steyn:
 Justice Ginsburg swung by Cairo last month to help out the lads from the Muslim Brotherhood building the new Egypt: “I would not look to the United States Constitution if I were drafting a constitution in the year 2012,” she advised them.
 That a sitting Supreme Court justice would denigrate the Constitution she&amp;rsquo;s sworn to uphold in a foreign country deserves the sort of scorn normally reserved for traitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Votes on Obamacare Today</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</guid>
      <description>We won’t know the result until late June, most likely. And the results of today’s vote could change by then.

Still, it’s sort of weird that after three years of public, wildly emotional and stupifyingly complex arguments, the fate of the republic comes down to a short meeting in Washington involving nine people in a paneled room.
Mark Sherman of AP describes the cloistered scene:
 After months of anticipation, thousands of pages of briefs and more than six hours of arguments, the justices will vote on the fate of President Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s health care overhaul in under an hour Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Health Insurance Solution that Some Smart State Should Try</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/a-health-insurance-solution-that-some-smart-state-should-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 15:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/a-health-insurance-solution-that-some-smart-state-should-try/</guid>
      <description>The term “United States” is both plural (many states united) and singular (the United States). The tag line “e pluribus unum” loses its meaning if we cease to be many, if we give up our identities as individual states. As states, we are as different from each other as the United States is from Canada.
The United States are most powerful pursuing opportunities and fixing problems in the plural but defending in the singular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Impossible to Exaggerate the Historical Importance of the Supreme Court’s ObamaCare Decision</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/its-impossible-to-exaggerate-the-historical-importance-of-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/its-impossible-to-exaggerate-the-historical-importance-of-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</guid>
      <description>When the Supreme Court releases its opinion on the ObamaCare case, America will change fundamentally. This is the most important case to the future of the republic since the Great Depression or the Civil War.
 If the court upholds ObamaCare, it will end the principle of government limited by a written Constitution. Anthony Kennedy and Antonin Scalia said as much. A vote by Kennedy to uphold the legislation, then, would be a vote for unlimited government power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the GOP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-state-of-the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-state-of-the-gop/</guid>
      <description>by Bill Hennessy and Jim Durbin
John Knowles’s classic novel, A Separate Peace, begins memorably:
 I went back to the Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there fifteen years before . . . as if a coat of varnish had been put over everything for better preservation.
 I get precisely the opposite feel when I look at the Republican Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Will Also Decide the Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-supreme-court-will-also-decide-the-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-supreme-court-will-also-decide-the-election/</guid>
      <description>When the Supreme Court rules on ObamaCare, it will define Barack Obama as either a winner or loser.

James Carville says overturning ObamaCare would be the best thing that could happen to Democrats. I think he’s wrong.
ObamaCare is the centerpiece of Obama’s term in office. He put all of America’s business on hold for a year to pass it. He coerced, lied, intimidated, and threatened to get the law passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCOTUS Reality Tour</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/scotus-reality-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/scotus-reality-tour/</guid>
      <description>By now you’ve seen the sensational headlines:
* People Are Saying That Obama&#39;s Healthcare Law Got Massacred At The Supreme Court Today*  Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/politics#ixzz1qMjfnTtF** Here Is The Moment When Justice Alito Shredded Verrilli At The Obamacare Hearings* Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/politics#ixzz1qMjjQXFM** Skeptical Kennedy signals trouble for Obama&amp;rsquo;s healthcare law** Supreme Court Health Care Law: Justices Come Down Hard On The Mandate
And so it goes.
Before we start dancing in the streets, let’s face a little reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why People Are Being Unfair to Donald Verrilli</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/why-people-are-being-unfair-to-donal-verrilli/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 04:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/why-people-are-being-unfair-to-donal-verrilli/</guid>
      <description>Everyone (including me) is cracking on Donald Verrilli, Obama’s Solicitor General. He figuratively died on the biggest legal stage in the world today. Here’s a sample of the left’s reaction to Verrilli’s performance:
Mother Jones:
 Solicitor General Donald B. Verrilli Jr. should be grateful to the Supreme Court for refusing to allow cameras in the courtroom, because his defense of Obamacare on Tuesday may go down as one of the most spectacular flameouts in the history of the court.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg’s Crappy Argument In Support of ObamaCare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/ruth-bader-ginsbergs-crappy-argument-in-support-of-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 00:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/ruth-bader-ginsbergs-crappy-argument-in-support-of-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>I’m often amazed at the weakness of arguments before the Supreme Court. Today, Ruth Bader Ginsburg, attempting to help out the Obama Administration’s fumbling solicitor-general, made the weakest argument I’ve ever heard.
First,Ginsburg statement:
 Mr. Verrilli, I thought that your main point is that, unlike food or any other market, when you made the choice not to buy insurance, even though you have every intent in the world to self-insure, to save for it, when disaster strikes, you may not have the money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Herbert Hoover Launched Cardinal Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals were the major league team farthest west and farthest south until the 1950s. But that’s not the only reason the Redbirds built a massive flock of fans from the Alleghenies to the Rockies, and from Canada to the Gulf of Mexico.
The St. Louis Cardinals owe big government statism and technological innovation a big thanks, in addition to geography and great teams. The technology was radio. The big government statist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covenant of Liberty Is Available Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/20/covenant-of-liberty-is-available-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 14:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/20/covenant-of-liberty-is-available-now/</guid>
      <description>Covenant of Liberty is the best American history I’ve read in years.
Michael Patrick Leahy, among a very small group of patriots who hatched the first round of Tea Parties in February 2009, documents the US Government’s 230 year history of Constitutional infidelity.
My full review will be finished soon, but don’t wait: buy Covenant of Liberty today.
https://rcm.amazon.com/e/cm?lt1=_blank&amp;amp;bc1=000000&amp;amp;IS2=1&amp;amp;bg1=FFFFFF&amp;amp;fc1=000000&amp;amp;lc1=0000FF&amp;amp;t=hennesssview-20&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;p=8&amp;amp;l=as4&amp;amp;m=amazon&amp;amp;f=ifr&amp;amp;ref=ss_til&amp;amp;asins=0062066331
Mike Leahy was the keynote speaker on day one of the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Vote in Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/19/go-vote-in-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 04:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/19/go-vote-in-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Go vote, please. Please. Vote now. Don’t Put It Off!!
Did you know that ObamaCare is my fault?
Of course, it is. Read my story below the clock.

**I didn’t vote in 2006. You know why? **
I put it off.
I decided not to stop on my way to work in the morning. Why? _I’ll have plenty of time tonight, _I thought. I’ll stop on my way home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Action Alert: Help a David defeat a Goliath</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/18/action-alert-help-a-david-defeat-a-goliath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 03:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/18/action-alert-help-a-david-defeat-a-goliath/</guid>
      <description>If you think theTea Party’s job was to strengthen the Republican Establishment, stop reading.
**If you think the Tea Party and the conservative grassroots stands for something larger than party, then you’re needed right now. ** A great grassroots candidate in Illinois needs an hour of your time today or tomorrow–to make calls, knock doors, wave signs, or work at polls.
The GOP Establishment is pulling out all the stops. Lacking committed grassroots in Southern Illinois, they’re bringing in hired guns from Chicago and around the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rodger Cook Best Choice for Southern Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/17/rodger-cook-best-choice-for-southern-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/17/rodger-cook-best-choice-for-southern-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Rodger Cook fools no one into thinking he’s a member of the political class. He’s not. Rodger’s a human being, like the rest of us. That’s just one of the reasons that Rodger Cook has earned my personal endorsement in next Tuesday’s (March 20) Illinois primary.*

Actually, Rodger’s not so much like the rest of us. Rodger has served the people of Illinois all of his adult life. Rodger has been a police officer, a detective, a mayor, and private businessman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Plummer Steps In It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/16/jason-plummer-steps-in-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 14:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/16/jason-plummer-steps-in-it/</guid>
      <description>When you’re the Republican Establishment’s candidate, you have one simple assignment: don’t screw up.
Jason Plummer, a 29-year-old lumber heir, is the GOP Establishment’s appointed candidate for US Congress in Illinois’ 12th Congressional District. He’s facing a shockingly tough race from former police detective and former Belleville Mayor, Rodger Cook. (Never underestimate a detective’s tenacity.)
In a debate last week, Plummer failed his one simple assignment. Despite a nearly unlimited war chest from his family’s fortune and the Illinois GOP treasury, Plummer said something stupid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Watch The Kudlow Report at 6 Central Tonight **MARCH 14**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/14/breaking-watch-the-kudlow-report-at-6-central-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 19:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/14/breaking-watch-the-kudlow-report-at-6-central-tonight/</guid>
      <description>I’m honored to return to The Kudlow Report tonight (Wednesday, March 14) at 6:00 pm Central (7 ET) with Larry Kudlow.
I hope to talk about the GOP Presidential primaries, RomneyCare, and the Tea Party movement.
Please watch if you can. Good ratings for Tea Party guests will only increase the number of Tea Party guests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White House Will Ban Rush From Armed Forces Radio</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/12/the-white-house-will-ban-rush-from-armed-forces-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 04:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/12/the-white-house-will-ban-rush-from-armed-forces-radio/</guid>
      <description>When I was on the USS John C. Calhoun, the XO and I were big Rush fans. We stockpiled Snapple in the outboards of the Ship’s Office just to have a little taste of EIB during our three-month patrols.
That was 1992. Back when this country’s government still held onto some strand of connection to its founding.
That&amp;rsquo;s all gone, now. The United States is a shell of its former self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America’s Dictator</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/12/americas-dictator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 07:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/12/americas-dictator/</guid>
      <description>From the New York Times:
 President Obama, who came to office promising transparency and adherence to the rule of law, has become the first president to claim the legal authority to order an American citizen killed without judicial involvement, real oversight or public accountability.
 In one sentence, the newspaper conservatives love to hate condemned Barack Obama to the title “dictator.”
Those who voted for him—the ones who still want to be thought of as “American”—will rationalize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comes Now Gloria Allred and Makes an Ass of Herself</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/09/comes-now-gloria-allred-and-makes-an-ass-of-herself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2012 05:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/09/comes-now-gloria-allred-and-makes-an-ass-of-herself/</guid>
      <description>The feminist attorney famous for making herself famous just couldn&amp;rsquo;t let the Sandra Fluke case go.

Gloria Allred sent a letter to a Florida District Attorney asking him to arrest Rush Limbaugh for violation of an ancient Florida law.
 The statute stipulates that anyone who “speaks of and concerning any woman, married or unmarried, falsely and maliciously imputing to her a want of chastity” is guilty of a misdemeanor of the first degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Government Fails, Americans Step Up</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/08/when-government-fails-american-step-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/08/when-government-fails-american-step-up/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer Pahlka is a remarkable woman. She realized what many have realized: government often fails at its most basic tasks.
Governments don&amp;rsquo;t keep up with technology or culture. Nor can they act nimbly. A start-up produces finished products worth millions in four months; it takes government that long to start the first feasibility study.
Spotting government&amp;rsquo;s shortcomings isn&amp;rsquo;t what makes Jennifer so amazing. Every sane American knows that government is a nightmare of bureaucratic hell that admires problems and punishes the successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romney=money, Santorum=passion, Gingrich</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/08/romneymoney-santorumpassion-gingrich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 01:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/08/romneymoney-santorumpassion-gingrich/</guid>
      <description>Romney=money, Santorum=passion, Gingrich=plan, Paul=principles. We need a blender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You a Superhero?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/06/are-you-a-superhero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/06/are-you-a-superhero/</guid>
      <description>This is a challenge.
I want you to grab a pen and paper (or open your favorite note app). Now write down a list of characteristic you’d expect a **superhero_ _**to display. Write as many or as few as you’d like.
Don’t continue until you’ve written down the characteristics of a superhero.

Welcome back.
Here’s the next step. I want you to look over your list of superhero traits. As you do, think about the amount of that trait you have in you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This David Stockman Quote Should Scare the Hell Out of Everyone</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/05/this-david-stockman-quote-should-scare-the-hell-out-of-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/05/this-david-stockman-quote-should-scare-the-hell-out-of-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Is the US economy about to collapse worse the Greece’s?
Some, like Paul Krugman, say that it’s okay for governments to print unlimited money. Others, who have actually managed businesses, say otherwise.
**David Stockman is among the latter. He was Reagan’s budget director for a few years. He became a media sensation because of his command of numbers. **
He left the White House early, fretting over federal debt. But debt in the 1980s was as a piggy bank to Wells Fargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Rush Limbaugh Could Teach Rush Limbaugh **UPATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/04/what-rush-limbaugh-could-teach-rush-limbaugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/04/what-rush-limbaugh-could-teach-rush-limbaugh/</guid>
      <description>What made Rush Limbaugh so amazing for 24 years was his steadfast resolve. Face it, you have to believe what you believe title your books The Way Things Ought To Be and See, I Told You So.
His fans loved him because he never backed down.
Rush didn’t back down when the left went nuts over his “Obama, The Magic Negro” parody. He didn’t back down from his “hope Obama fails” statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Rush Limbaugh Revived Chivalry</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/03/how-rush-limbaugh-revived-chivalry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 16:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/03/how-rush-limbaugh-revived-chivalry/</guid>
      <description>A Georgetown law student turned the Democrat Party from an androgynous blob into a modern day Ivanhoe. (Yes, I’ll tread carefully around that “Ivanhoe” to spare Democrat sensibilities.)

Sandra Fluke, the student, begged Congress to confiscate property from me and millions of other taxpayers in order to satisfy her sexual appetite.
Rush Limbaugh pointed out that law school lasts three years, condoms cost about a buck each, and Ms. Fluke needed 3,000 of them just to make it to the bar exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIP, Andrew Breitbart **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/01/andrew-breitbart-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 14:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/01/andrew-breitbart-dead/</guid>
      <description>Business Insider has picked up a Big Journalism story that Andrew Breitbart died last night. (Big Journalism is one of Breitbart’s web sites.)
If this is true, then we’ve lost a gallant warrior in the battle to preserve and advance freedom and liberty.
Of course, the lefties will flood the internet with hate and bile. So maybe the obit is a plot to draw the lefties out and reveal them for who and what they really are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes at Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/29/changes-at-hennessys-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 13:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/29/changes-at-hennessys-view/</guid>
      <description>Looks different, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
After hosting my own web sites forever, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to simplify my server admin life. I&amp;rsquo;m moving Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View to another service from my own servers.
The difference you should see is the theme. (I&amp;rsquo;m tired of the minimalism.) Also, some archives from before 2010 might be missing for a while. They&amp;rsquo;ll catch up soon enough.
Thanks
UPDATE In addition to the changes above, a couple of comments posted during the upgrade have been lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America’s Economic Freedom Is Collapsing. Here’s What You Need To Know | Video</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/28/americas-economic-freedom-is-collapsing-heres-what-you-need-to-know-video-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 02:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/28/americas-economic-freedom-is-collapsing-heres-what-you-need-to-know-video-2/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I blogged about freedom envy—the feeling Americans get when they look at countries where the people get freer every day.
Today, thanks to Economic Freedom blog, we have a great video to introduce the idea of economic freedom.
Does that sound silly? I mean, aren’t Americans born with an understanding of economic freedom? And craving to preserve it?
Yes, we are.
But our schools, entertainment, press, and, above all, GOVERNMENT beats economic freedom out of us by the time we’re 14 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Not an Annual Celebration of Freedom?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/28/when-did-we-stop-getting-freer-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/28/when-did-we-stop-getting-freer-in-america/</guid>
      <description>The first entry in National Review’s “The Week” from sometime around 1990 listed ten or so former Soviet bloc countries that recently had shed the yoke of communist repression. And it made a simple statement:
 “It must be nice to live in a country where you get freer every day.”
 I thought of this while talking about the 13th Amendment Freedom Week with its evangelist-in-chief Kariem Haqq at St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd Anniversary Tea Party: Thank You!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/27/3rd-anniversary-tea-party-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/27/3rd-anniversary-tea-party-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>The 3rd Anniversary Tea Party rocked . . . because of the great patriot-activists who have decided it’s time to act and win.

Although Dr. Larry Schweikart couldn’t make it (because of the Chicago snow storm), Friday’s event was better than planned or expected. Tea Party champion Michael Patrick Leahy jumped into fill a last-minute void, and the crowd loved it.
I had the the pleasure of reading and advanced copy of Mike Leahy&amp;rsquo;s new book, Covenant of Liberty: The Ideological Origins of the Tea Party Movementin December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overtime</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/25/overtime-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/25/overtime-2/</guid>
      <description>Just because it’s after 10:00 am, doesn’t mean you can’t come to the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party.
No, we didn’t come up with a policy for people who arrive late to the feast. We will find a way to get you involved that’s fair to everyone.
Grab your laptop or your mobile device, if you have one, get in your car, and drive to the Crowne Plaza in Clayton. Ask for the Tea Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time’s Up!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/24/times-up-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/24/times-up-2/</guid>
      <description>The 3rd Anniversary Tea Party begins tonight at 6:30 at the Crowne Plaza in Clayton.
You can make a difference. But not alone. If you join forces with just three other people, you’ll triple your influence.
Show up. Bring two friends. Leave with a company a soldiers for the America’s liberation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Attend the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/23/why-attend-the-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/23/why-attend-the-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-2/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I’ve written about little else. The 3rd Anniversary Tea Party is something of an obsession with me. And for good reasons: * Obama is surging * Apathy has seized the right * America’s future hangs in the balance
But there’s a much bigger reason you—you, the person reading this blog—should attend the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party.
That reason is personal, powerful, and acute.
That reason is this:You cannot live with yourself if Obama wins and you failed to do everything in your power to stop him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unto Dust We Shall Return</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/22/unto-dust-we-shall-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/22/unto-dust-we-shall-return/</guid>
      <description>Today begins Lent.

Lent prepares us for the cycle of mortality and resurrection, perfected by Christ, without which life has no meaning. It’s a time of humility. We call to mind our human brokenness in hopes of making ourselves better imitators of Christ.
On Ash Wednesday, we mark ourselves with the sign of the cross in ashes. **“Remember, man, that you are dust and unto dust you shall return (Genesis 3:19).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You’re Almost Out of Time</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/22/youre-almost-out-of-time-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/22/youre-almost-out-of-time-2/</guid>
      <description>There will be only one 3rd Anniversary Tea Party, and it will be this coming Friday and Saturday, February 24 and 25. Today’s Wednesday. You have two days. Order today, because the future needs you.
This could be the only chance you get to learn about how the brain votes, how social media can change the outcome, how you can influence casual voters with minimal effort, how to caucus, and how 7 obscure events changed American history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What You Think You Know About Establishment Candidates Is Probably Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-you-know-about-establishment-candidates-is-probably-wrong-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-you-know-about-establishment-candidates-is-probably-wrong-2/</guid>
      <description>I see is all the time. Supporters of Establishment candidates complain that their opponents are establishment, too.
We saw it in the Missouri 2nd District. We see in the GOP Presidential primary. The last refuge of the Establishment’s candidates is to spread the pain of the Establishment label.
What many people don’t get is what the Establishment label actually means. It’s time everyone understood this.
**The Establishment’s candidate is the candidate the Establishment chooses for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Us Happy?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-makes-us-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-makes-us-happy/</guid>
      <description>Marc, at Bad Catholic, rocks.
In this post on Obama’s continuing jihad against Christianity, he answers a burning question: did human happiness exist before artificial contraception?
Put another way, is chemical birth control a natural state of humanity?
Before you answer, read the post. Think about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Conservatives Relate to Washington’s Continental Army</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/how-conservatives-relate-to-washingtons-continental-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 16:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/how-conservatives-relate-to-washingtons-continental-army/</guid>
      <description>Did you know there is no federal holiday called Presidents Day?

Today is Washington’s Birthday. As a posthumous birthday gift to our first president and commander-in-chief of the army that won our war for independence, I offer a simple wish: that the army of liberty formed in February 2009, known as “the Tea Party,” will resist the temptation to resign.
That’s a great word for what a lot of us feel these days: resignation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Surging in the Polls; Here’s Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/obamas-surging-in-the-polls-heres-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/obamas-surging-in-the-polls-heres-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</guid>
      <description>Don’t bother blaming it on poll questions designed to lead respondents. Never mind that it’s a long way until the election. And stop whining about the White House fudging the numbers on unemployment.
The fact is that Obama’s surging at just the right time. His re-election chances are now above 50 percent. His intrade.com chances of winning are near 60 percent. And he’s raising more money than al of the Republican candidates combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Romans Had Nothing on Us | *Video*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/19/the-romans-had-nothing-on-us-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/19/the-romans-had-nothing-on-us-video/</guid>
      <description>Do you know the most persecuted religious group on earth?
History speaks of the massive Roman persecution of Christians. The catacombs of Rome, housing the remains of thousands of Christian martyrs, tell us the story and give voice to the dead.
But the Romans had nothing on we moderns when it comes to persecuting Christians. Today, Christians are the most persecuted religious group on the planet. And the problem grows worse every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apathy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/18/apathy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/18/apathy-2/</guid>
      <description>The world is a dangerous place to live; not because of the people who are evil, but because of the people who don&amp;rsquo;t do anything about it.
&amp;ndash;Albert Einstein
 It’s easy to blame the subject for our apathy. The candidates are uninspiring; the colors are dull; the task is boring.
Blaming the subject is easy because it relieves us, the objects, of any responsibility. “I can’t make Romney less WASPy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Days Until 3rd Anniversary Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/14/10-days-until-3rd-anniversary-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/14/10-days-until-3rd-anniversary-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Are you armed with tickets?
If not, get them today.
Here’s the details:
Join St. Louis Tea Party Coalition&amp;rsquo;s 3rd Anniversary Tea Party Weekend
It&amp;rsquo;s time to prepare for the new Tea Party Revolution. 2012 will be the most important election of our lifetime. We must make sure we are doing everything we can to stop this Administration. Join us February 24th and 25th to learn the MUST know for this election cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Save Religious Freedom in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/13/how-you-can-save-religious-freedom-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/13/how-you-can-save-religious-freedom-in-america/</guid>
      <description>When Barack Obama declared that Catholics must either violate their consciences or face government persecution, he wasn’t going after just Catholics. Nor was he promoting healthcare.
Barack Obama and his myrmidon Kathleen Sebelius tried to erase the First Amendment. They tried to erase religious freedom. They tried to take away yet another foundational liberty that made America America.
**And they will try again**
Unless you stop them.
But how are you going to stop them alone?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santorum Surging Because People Like Him</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/santorum-surging-because-people-like-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 01:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/santorum-surging-because-people-like-him/</guid>
      <description>The latest Public Policy Poll shows Santorum surging—big time.

**Santorum is most appealing to conservatives—from Evangelicals to Tea Partiers: **
 Santorum is now completely dominating with several key segments of the electorate, especially the most right leaning parts of the party. With those describing themselves as &amp;lsquo;very conservative,&amp;rsquo; he&amp;rsquo;s now winning a majority of voters at 53% to 20% for Gingrich and 15% for Romney. Santorum gets a majority with Tea Party voters as well at 51% to 24% for Gingrich and 12% for Romney.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relate to This, Mitt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/relate-to-this-mitt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/relate-to-this-mitt-2/</guid>
      <description>The liberal press cannot issue a story about the Republican presidential race that does not refer to Mitt Romney’s need (and inability) to “relate to” conservatives. Puke.
Relate to this: if Mitt Romney’s a conservative, I’m a Hottentot.

By “relate to,” the media and Romney’s handlers actually mean “hoodwink.” While Romney might secure the GOP nomination without conservative support, his campaign will go down in flames without conservative grassroots boots on the ground from Labor Day to Election Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 Days of Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/40-days-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 20:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/40-days-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Forty Days of Life is a peaceful, prayerful response the poverty of abortion.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x-AfLO6Oevo]
The Coalition for Life is a community based Christian pro-life organization made up of over 90 churches and thousands of individuals who are working to end abortion in St. Louis, peacefully and prayerfully. ____
 The 40 Days for Life St. Louis Adopt-A-Day program is for Churches and/or Organizations that feel God is calling them to a day of prayer at our vigil location near Planned Parenthood on Forest Park Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s War on Catholics Has Nothing To Do With Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Obama’s dictate that Catholic organizations must participate in contraception and abortion has nothing to do with healthcare or rights or contraception or anything of the sort. Not at all. Modern dictatorships don’t operate that way.
**Obama just destroyed the free practice clause of the First Amendment, and that’s exactly what he intended. **
 Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney’s Resume Cover Letter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/09/mitt-romneys-resume-cover-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/09/mitt-romneys-resume-cover-letter/</guid>
      <description>There are some things you just don’t say in a cover letter—or on the campaign trail.
A self-aggrandizing cover letter from an NYU undergrad to some Wall Street banks has the whole financial world laughing. The kid’s naïve hubris and ignorance of what employers look for in a candidate earned him public humiliation on an internet scale. Here’s just a sample of the kid’s self-promotion:
 That semester I achieved a 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wait ‘til These Kids Meet the Tax Man</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/08/wait-til-these-kids-meet-the-tax-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 14:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/08/wait-til-these-kids-meet-the-tax-man/</guid>
      <description>When the rules become so complicated and convoluted that well-meaning people unwittingly break the law, the legal system has lost its moral authority.
Students at Georgetown University are discovering the horrors of, what Tocqueville called “small complicated rules, minute and uniform, through which the most original minds and the most energetic characters cannot penetrate, to rise above the crowd.”
An editorial in The Hoya, the official student newspaper, students advocate “eliminating bureaucracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Bet On Election Outcomes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/01/dont-bet-on-election-outcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/01/dont-bet-on-election-outcomes/</guid>
      <description>“Anybody will beat Obama.”
I get some comments and see a lot of tweets about the inevitability that any Republican will win in November.
That’s frightening.
The prospect of a Republican beating Obama isn&amp;rsquo;t frightening, of course—any of the four remaining candidates would be night and day better for our future. What’s frightening is that so many people bet on the unknowable.
Except in rare cases—one candidate is caught stealing from a church weeks before the election—political elections carry too many variables for anyone to predict their results a month in advance, much less three-quarters of a year ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Rational Is Your Vote?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/31/how-rational-is-your-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/31/how-rational-is-your-vote/</guid>
      <description>Ask a real partisan—someone with a Ron Paul or Ed Martin sticker on his car&amp;ndash;why he supports that candidate. You’ll get a lot of rational reasons.
Then challenge just one of those reasons, and what do you get? More reason?
No, you get raw emotions.

That’s because the emotional mind—the part of the brain designed for survival—exerts far more influence over our thinking that most people are willing to admit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do Presidential Debates and Colonoscopies Have in Common?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/30/what-do-presidential-debates-and-colonoscopies-have-in-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/30/what-do-presidential-debates-and-colonoscopies-have-in-common/</guid>
      <description>At some point, each additional GOP Presidential debate becomes just a bigger pain in the . . . But science shows us that the last debate before a vote—and the last memorable event in the last debate—is paramount to how we remember the entire event.
In fact, memorable moments at the end, not consistent performance throughout, determine who wins and who loses.
In this awesome TED talk, Nobel winning psychologist Daniel Kahneman explains the weird difference between our experiencing selves and our remembering selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Rip-Off in America is College Tuition</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/29/the-biggest-rip-off-in-america-is-college-tuition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/29/the-biggest-rip-off-in-america-is-college-tuition/</guid>
      <description>While everyone was screaming about the rising cost of medical treatment, America’s leftist incubation chambers—colleges and universities—robbed us of our economic future. And the federal government’s misguided student aid program is to blame.
**What allows this growth? ** * Increased per student government funding * Massive private and public debt
Who benefits? * College administrators * Unions working on college campuses * Political causes that college administrators like (liberal)
Who pays?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin’s AG Race Makes 3rd Anniversary Tea Party Even More Important</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/27/ed-martins-ag-race-makes-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-even-more-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 01:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/27/ed-martins-ag-race-makes-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-even-more-important/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago, weeks ago, how many Missouri statewide offices did you expect to flip? Be honest.
Yes, there are great people running for Governor, Secretary of State, and Treasurer. And we already have a fine Lieutenant Governor Kinder running for re-election.
But numerous factors, like name recognition, experience, and Jay Nixon’s weird relationship with Republican House leadership, made a major upset unlikely. And no Republicans had stepped up to challenge Chris Koster for Attorney General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Ed Martin Running for Attorney General in Missouri *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin Jr. of St. Louis has redirected his fire to the Attorney General race, and this is great news for everyone except Chris Koster.
Back when Ed Martin was talking about running for the Republican nod to take on Claire McCaskill, I had another thought. Well, a bunch of people had another thought: Ed would make an outstanding Attorney General.
UPDATE
HUGE list of endorsements on Ed’s official press release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Must Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/25/why-we-must-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/25/why-we-must-win/</guid>
      <description>Think about what’s at stake: * The Supreme Court is one liberal away from imposing a radical, unwritten constitution on the United States * The President has shredded the Constitution by seizing the power to declare when the Senate is or is not in session * The United States has fallen many notches in world prestige * We can no longer fight wars on two fronts * The White House and Democrats in the Senate block every attempt at increasing domestic energy production * Our debt is approaching Greece’s catastrophic levels * The economy, after nearly four years, is flat on its back * America is losing ground on every front * And Obama made it worse</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMSL Econ Professor David Rose on Moral Foundations of Economic Behavior</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/24/umsl-econ-professor-david-rose-on-moral-foundations-of-economic-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 20:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/24/umsl-econ-professor-david-rose-on-moral-foundations-of-economic-behavior/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m proud to know David Rose. Dr. Rose is chairman of UMSL&amp;rsquo;s economics department. He&amp;rsquo;s also the President of the Discussion Club, one of St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s most valuable intellectual assets.
In this interview with Russ Roberts, Dr. Rose discusses his new book Moral Foundations of Economic Behavior.
This is great stuff for everyone, especially economic liberty fiends like me.
https://rcm.amazon.com/e/cm?lt1=_blank&amp;amp;bc1=000000&amp;amp;IS2=1&amp;amp;bg1=FFFFFF&amp;amp;fc1=000000&amp;amp;lc1=0000FF&amp;amp;t=hennesssview-20&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;p=8&amp;amp;l=as4&amp;amp;m=amazon&amp;amp;f=ifr&amp;amp;ref=ss_til&amp;amp;asins=0199781745</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bain of Newt’s Existence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/17/the-bain-of-newts-existence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/17/the-bain-of-newts-existence/</guid>
      <description>Truth is, not all companies, not all business ideas, can make it on their own.
It’s easy to say that a good idea will automatically lead to a successful business. But it’s a lie.
Apple did not become Apple without investors. Sure, there are some examples of businesses that flourished without financial help. But not many. We’ll never know the wonderful ideas that died in their owner’s garage for lack of financing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Were You When Obama Nullified the Constitution?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>Most Americans know more about forensic evidence in the Casey Anthony case than they do about the Constitution. That ignorance gave Barack Obama the hubris to end constitutional government in the United States. He did it, and you probably didn’t even notice.
Over the course of a week, Barack Obama made a series of so-called recess appointments. In the process, he and his henchmen in Eric Holder’s Justice Department effectively nullified the US Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire Exposes GOP’s Diverse Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</guid>
      <description>Okay, Santorum and Gingrich didn’t get a bump out of their debates over the weekend. More like the bump got them.
And Ron Paul did way better than I expected. Congratulations to Dr. Paul and Mitt. 
I still think my Saturday night post accurately reflected the national impressions, though. That’s backed up by this CBS News poll that shows Republicans believe Santorum most closely shares their values, but—and this is a J Lo but—they believe Romney is more electable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Ready to Caucus?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/09/are-you-ready-to-caucus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 02:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/09/are-you-ready-to-caucus/</guid>
      <description>What’s the difference between a caucus and a primary?
Who’s allowed to attend a caucus?
How do I find out my caucus location?
When it the caucus?
How long does it take?
How to do I get ready?
This Is Important Stuff
These are just some of the questions I have about the Missouri Republican Presidential Caucus scheduled for March 17. And I’m not the only with questions.
That’s why St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s a 16th Century Lesson on Focus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/08/heres-a-16th-century-lesson-on-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 03:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/08/heres-a-16th-century-lesson-on-focus/</guid>
      <description>Sundays are useful touchstones for our goals.
Last week, I told you about my maniacal focus for 2012. At the beginning of the week, I stuck carefully to my plan. But after two consecutive 15-hour days at work, I let my mind wander a little. I’m sure you know how that goes.
Well, Sunday is a great touchstone. And who provided my guidance and support? A 16th century saint and Doctor of the Church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Won the New Hampshire Republican Debate?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/07/who-won-the-new-hampshire-republican-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 05:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/07/who-won-the-new-hampshire-republican-debate/</guid>
      <description>It depends on how you score. 
I see three scoring scenarios: 1. Best conservative performance 2. Best electability performance 3. Best positional performance
Conservative performance is pretty clear: whose answers appeal to conservatives? (Does not mean conservatives believed the candidate meant what he said.) This is not Tea Party scoring, either. I’m not limiting my evaluation to the 3 core Tea Party principles of Constitutionally limited government, free markets, and fiscal responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Santorum Pulls Away with 13-Vote Lead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/03/breaking-santorum-pulls-away-with-13-vote-lead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 04:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/03/breaking-santorum-pulls-away-with-13-vote-lead/</guid>
      <description>That’s with 88 percent of the counting complete.
The bigger story: Romney’s underperforming his 2008 results in key counties. Santorum outperforming Huckabee in 2008.

What does it all mean?
Conservatives and libertarians dominate the caucuses.
Romney is the choice of the Republican establishment. The cronies poured millions into his campaign even before he declared himself a conservative. He’s won endorsements from just about every big name general election loser include Bob Dole and George H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imagine That! America Was 40,000 Laws Short of a Full Deck</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/02/imagine-that-america-was-40000-laws-short-of-a-full-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 04:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/02/imagine-that-america-was-40000-laws-short-of-a-full-deck/</guid>
      <description>Until the clock struck twelve on January 1, that is.
That’s when 40,000 – count ‘em, forty thousand—new laws took effect in the United States.
Some of the new laws are, no doubt, good and proper. Some restore liberties lost. But others bind. And some are silly.
Utah’s banning happy hours. (Why not ban melancholy hours instead?) California now prohibits people 18 and under from using tanning beds. Georgia requires golf carts to have turn signals and horns if driven on public roads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Maniacal Focus for 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/01/a-maniacal-focus-for-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 01:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/01/a-maniacal-focus-for-2012/</guid>
      <description>I’m almost finished reading Walter Isaacson’s biography of Apple co-founder and genius Steve Jobs.
Jobs’s life left insanely good lessons. Some lessons instruct us on how to do things. Others warn us of bad things to avoid.
One of the good things Steve Jobs taught us: focus. Maniacal focus on things that mattered, and a pathological aversion to distractions.
One example. When Jobs returned to Apple after 10-year exile, he took stock of all the projects underway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>