<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>teaparty on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/teaparty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in teaparty on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 04:48:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/teaparty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Stop the Commies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/30/stop-commies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 04:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/30/stop-commies/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s all a lie.   It didn&amp;rsquo;t start that way. At first, the Mike Brown protesters were all about Mike Brown and people like him. But not anymore.
Even the New York Times admitted the protests in Mike Brown&amp;rsquo;s name are actually the Revolutionary Communist Party advancing Marxism. (The NYT pulled down the story on Sunday morning. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have linked it, anyway.)
I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of stomping on someone else&amp;rsquo;s parade, even if I disagree with their cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Would Like to Talk to You on Tuesday September 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/28/like-talk-talk-tuesday-september-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 03:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/28/like-talk-talk-tuesday-september-2/</guid>
      <description>Hi. Bill Hennessy here. If you can, please stop by 111 Clarkson Executive Park, Ellisville, MO 63011 on Tuesday, September 2 at 7 p.m. (RSVP Here if you&amp;rsquo;d like.)
I have something I&amp;rsquo;d like to talk to you about. It&amp;rsquo;s about the tea party movement. But it&amp;rsquo;s really about understanding two very important concepts:
*1. Living to our purpose. *2. Doing what&amp;rsquo;s important.
This is not a training session. It&amp;rsquo;s not an After Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Herbert Hoover Launched Cardinal Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals were the major league team farthest west and farthest south until the 1950s. But that’s not the only reason the Redbirds built a massive flock of fans from the Alleghenies to the Rockies, and from Canada to the Gulf of Mexico.
The St. Louis Cardinals owe big government statism and technological innovation a big thanks, in addition to geography and great teams. The technology was radio. The big government statist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Ed Martin Running for Attorney General in Missouri *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin Jr. of St. Louis has redirected his fire to the Attorney General race, and this is great news for everyone except Chris Koster.
Back when Ed Martin was talking about running for the Republican nod to take on Claire McCaskill, I had another thought. Well, a bunch of people had another thought: Ed would make an outstanding Attorney General.
UPDATE
HUGE list of endorsements on Ed’s official press release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISAPPOINTING: Missouri House Leadership Blowing it</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/27/disappointing-missouri-house-leadership-blowing-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/27/disappointing-missouri-house-leadership-blowing-it/</guid>
      <description>I continue hearing reliable reports that the GOP Leadership in the Missouri House keeps its boot on the throat of Tea Party freshmen.
What a shame.
The party that was flat on its back from 2006 to 2009 rose back to power because of the tea party. But, it seems, the Missouri branch of the party didn’t get the message. And its Speaker in the Missouri House has become tighter with left-fringe Democrats that with conservatives of his own party.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>