<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 20:12:36 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Former Obama Officials Tired of His Drunken, Late-Night Calls</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/former-obama-officials-tired-of-his-drunken-late-night-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 20:12:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/former-obama-officials-tired-of-his-drunken-late-night-calls/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON — Members of the so-called &amp;ldquo;Obama Alumni Association&amp;rdquo; feel harassed and abused by the former president whose late-night, drunken conference calls have become annoying, frequent, and less coherent as time goes on.
Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View has learned that Obama began these occasional conference calls with a handful of former officials about six months after leaving office in 2017. Over time, the 44th president stopped following a semi-weekly schedule of planned calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABC News&#39; Jon Karl Plays the Little Snitch</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/abc-news-jon-karl-plays-little-snitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 18:15:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/abc-news-jon-karl-plays-little-snitch/</guid>
      <description>One of the most despicable men alive, ABC News White House reporter Jon Karl, took his shot a Pulitzer for online journalism today by snitching on Fox News&amp;rsquo; John Roberts.
Roberts, aparently, was the last person outdoors in the Rose Garden, to put on his mask.
Look a &amp;ldquo;Karen&amp;rdquo; Karl&amp;rsquo;s snotty tweet:
Almost everybody in the Rose Garden is wearing a mask — almost everybody. pic.twitter.com/JBnEV05HOd
&amp;mdash; jonkarl (@jonkarl) May 11, 2020  Jon Karl was the kid who made sure the teacher didn&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect homework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons Why theFourth Stimulus Bill Is Not a Bill at All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/fourth-stimulus-bill-is-not-a-bill-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:29:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/fourth-stimulus-bill-is-not-a-bill-at-all/</guid>
      <description>Everybody&amp;rsquo;s talking about the fourth stimulus bill. Infrastructure. Payroll tax cut. Vote by mail.
But there won&amp;rsquo;t be one.
There will be a stimulus, but it will not come from Congress. The fourth stimulus will come from you and me.
There are three reasons for this, which I will get to in a moment. But, first, do me a favor: Please share this post with your members of Congress. It&amp;rsquo;s that important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Triumphant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 04:56:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump just had another one of those weeks for which he&amp;rsquo;s become famous.
 There was the week hit bombed Syria while dining with President Xi of China at Mar a Lago. There was Easter Week 2019 when the Mueller Report exonerated and the economy hit new highs. There was the week of the State of the Union Address that included his exoneration in the Senate.  But, this week&amp;rsquo;s outbreak of liberty and its commensurate exposure of Trump&amp;rsquo;s enemies as pure scum is the best so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Andrew Cuomo Intentionally Kill the Elderly of New York?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:50:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</guid>
      <description>It would be the most sinister murder plot in US history. Imagine a governor conspiring to thin the population of elderly people, using a pandemic as both cover and weapon.
As unimaginable as it would be, evidence is mounting New York Governor Andrew Cuomo did just that: culled the herd in nursing homes by weaponizing Coronavirus.
Dumped Off With Their Own Body Bags New York Governor Andrew Cuomo implemented an emergency declaration that required nursing homes to accept active Coronavirus patients regardless of their ability to care for or isolate the infected patients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>