<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 11:22:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Confederate Army</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-new-confederate-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 11:22:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-new-confederate-army/</guid>
      <description>Five hundred West Point Military Academy graduates became the ideological heirs of Robert E. Lee this week. I bet they didn&amp;rsquo;t even realize it. The Gateway Pundit reports that 500 former West Point grads denounce &amp;ldquo;politicization&amp;rdquo; of the military and refuse to defend America against domestic enemies.
Oath of Commissioned Officers  I [state your name], do solemnly swear (or affirm) that I will support and defend the Constitution of the United States against all enemies, foreign and domestic; that I will bear true faith and allegiance to the same; that I take this obligation freely, without any mental reservation or purpose of evasion; and that I will well and faithfully discharge the duties of the office on which I am about to enter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Crazy Democrat Idea That Doesn&#39;t Go Far Enough</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/qualified-immunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 07:57:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/qualified-immunity/</guid>
      <description>House Democrats last week introduced a federal police reform bill. As usual, the bill is terrible, even in concept. Policing is a local issue.
But, like a broken clock, the Democrat bill is right on one matter: their bill makes qualified immunity a legislative issue instead of a judicial concern.
What Is &amp;lsquo;Qualified Immunity&amp;rsquo; Qualified immunity bars lawsuits against public officials whose actions cause actual damages unless those actions violate the law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress shall make no law abridging the ignorance of the Press</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/ignorance-of-the-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 16:43:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/ignorance-of-the-press/</guid>
      <description>The usual suspects on the CNN and MSNBC claim no president has ever called on the National Guard or the Army to put down riots and revolts.
&amp;ldquo;Unprecedented,&amp;rdquo; said Larry O&amp;rsquo;Donnell on MNSBC.
&amp;ldquo;Dictatorship,&amp;rdquo; declared CNN&amp;rsquo;s Don Lemon.
Once upon a time, people in journalism had good historical educations. Reporters of the past didn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily study history in college. Most learned history by researching current stories. This is how most people learn most of what they know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stunning Contrast Between Treatment of Hairdressers vs. Hooligans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/hairdressers-vs-hooligans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 10:53:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/hairdressers-vs-hooligans/</guid>
      <description>A stunning contrast. Our leaders show more patience and respect (or is it fear?) for hooligans, thugs, and terrorists than for small business owners who pay the leaders&amp;rsquo; salaries and fill their campaign coffers.
Political favoritism shown to violent street gangs will end, or the leaders will face a revolt from the right like nobody&amp;rsquo;s every seen before.
When people feel their backs are to the wall, they fight for their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Turn Nursing Homes Into Death Camps</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</guid>
      <description>When I wrote this post on May 6, I worried how it would be received. Accusing a governor of intentionally killing nursing home residents in order to save money is a serious charge. And, with only circumstantial evidence, difficult to prove.
Since then, Andrew Cuomo&amp;rsquo;s behavior has been consistent with guilt. The latest example is deflection. He&amp;rsquo;s trying, now, to blame federal guidelines for his order to force uninfected nursing homes to treat confirmed COVID-19 patients even if they lacked the facilities and skills to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>