<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:29:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons Why theFourth Stimulus Bill Is Not a Bill at All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/fourth-stimulus-bill-is-not-a-bill-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:29:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/fourth-stimulus-bill-is-not-a-bill-at-all/</guid>
      <description>Everybody&amp;rsquo;s talking about the fourth stimulus bill. Infrastructure. Payroll tax cut. Vote by mail.
But there won&amp;rsquo;t be one.
There will be a stimulus, but it will not come from Congress. The fourth stimulus will come from you and me.
There are three reasons for this, which I will get to in a moment. But, first, do me a favor: Please share this post with your members of Congress. It&amp;rsquo;s that important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Triumphant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 04:56:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump just had another one of those weeks for which he&amp;rsquo;s become famous.
 There was the week hit bombed Syria while dining with President Xi of China at Mar a Lago. There was Easter Week 2019 when the Mueller Report exonerated and the economy hit new highs. There was the week of the State of the Union Address that included his exoneration in the Senate.  But, this week&amp;rsquo;s outbreak of liberty and its commensurate exposure of Trump&amp;rsquo;s enemies as pure scum is the best so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Andrew Cuomo Intentionally Kill the Elderly of New York?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:50:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</guid>
      <description>It would be the most sinister murder plot in US history. Imagine a governor conspiring to thin the population of elderly people, using a pandemic as both cover and weapon.
As unimaginable as it would be, evidence is mounting New York Governor Andrew Cuomo did just that: culled the herd in nursing homes by weaponizing Coronavirus.
Dumped Off With Their Own Body Bags New York Governor Andrew Cuomo implemented an emergency declaration that required nursing homes to accept active Coronavirus patients regardless of their ability to care for or isolate the infected patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Was China All Along</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/it-was-china-all-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 06:05:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/it-was-china-all-along/</guid>
      <description>The leaked Five Eyes dossier on China&amp;rsquo;s nefarious Coronavirus pandemic provides all the pieces to figure out what happened and why. The dossier doesn&amp;rsquo;t connect the dots for you, but they&amp;rsquo;re now easy to connect. So easy, even I can do it. The story goes something like this.
 China was playing around with dangerous natural microbes in order to prove that it was as good as the USA at studying and neutralizing infectious diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Rebellion Is Brewing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/a-rebellion-is-brewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 20:11:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/a-rebellion-is-brewing/</guid>
      <description>The only thing more dangerous than a man with unlimited resources is a man with nothing to lose.
Thanks to tyrannical and unlawful restrictions on liberty and commerce by a few governors, mayors, and county executives, 30 million Americans have nothing left to lose except their dignity and freedom.
Millions of American feel threatened by stupid and tyrannical policies that have no basis in science or evidence. Only the will to power drives governors like Gavin Newsom and Gretchen Whitmer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>