<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 01:41:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Losing a Laugher (Video)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/27/nfl-losing-a-laugher-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 01:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/27/nfl-losing-a-laugher-video/</guid>
      <description>Blowout. Embarrassment. Lopsided. Laugher.
Humiliation.
Fans are doing to the NFL what Ray Rice did to his girlfriend in that elevator.
https://youtu.be/Dp47DeNAukw
Bars are banning football.
The VFW has condemned the NFL. 
Fans are burning jerseys.
American Sniper&amp;rsquo;s widow livid.
Viewership is down 11% year-over-year.
Fans boo players they recognize.
Baltimore fans demanding Ray Lewis statue come down like he&amp;rsquo;s General Lee.
Major NFL sponsors are under increasing pressure to pull ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Kemp Stood for Civil Rights . . . And America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</guid>
      <description>Jack Kemp is on the top of my wall of heroes. Literally. An autographed Kemp card sits on top of my bookshelf housing the works and images of my heroes.
As the NFL self-destructs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth reading about Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s work for civil rights. And for the Republican Party. And for conservatism.
Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s Activism Kemp did it all. And, thanks to Jeffrey Lord, we can remember Kemp&amp;rsquo;s finest moments of civil rights activism:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Villanueva Was Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/25/what-villanueva-did-was-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/25/what-villanueva-did-was-wrong/</guid>
      <description>By now you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the photo. The iconic photo. One lone Army Ranger veteran defying his team to salute the flag during the Star-Spangled Banner.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_media-17&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;1200&amp;rdquo;]screenshot CBS[/caption]
You know that Alejandro Villanueva&amp;rsquo;s jersey and t-shirt immediately became the best-selling merchandise from the NFL&amp;rsquo;s store.
Villanueva served three tours of combat duty as an Army Ranger. He&amp;rsquo;s authorized to wear the Bronze Star. He stood for his country. In Afghanistan with the Army and in Pittsburgh alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Else Can You Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/24/what-else-can-you-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 16:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/24/what-else-can-you-do/</guid>
      <description>Brain damage. They all have brain damage. And they&amp;rsquo;ll likely die from it. Like Aaron Hernandez.
99 out of every 100 football players have serious brain damage.
Kneeling for CTE NFL players and owners decided to show their disrespect to the flag, law enforcement, and the USA by kneeling during the national anthem. In a foreign country.
The president responded by saying the NFL (and the TV networks) would be in big trouble if people stopped watching or attending games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franco Harris: All American</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/franco-harris-all-american/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 21:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/franco-harris-all-american/</guid>
      <description>You might not know about Franco Harris. You might wonder why he&amp;rsquo;s so unhappy, like many of us are, with the NFL&amp;rsquo;s anti-American antics lately. But his wonderful heritage tells a lot about why my favorite running back respects America.
His dad was an Army soldier. His dad met his mom in Italy during World War II. They married and returned to New Jersey.
[Read this fantastic 1996 Baltimore Sun biography of Franco Harris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Hates Football Fans; Fire Them All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/nfl-hates-football-fans-fire-them-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 15:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/nfl-hates-football-fans-fire-them-all/</guid>
      <description>You can see the battle brewing. It&amp;rsquo;s coming to a head. And no one is telling you the real reason the NFL is dying before your eyes.
Everyone sees the symptoms of football&amp;rsquo;s death spiral: empty stadiums. Crashed ratings. low quality. Criminals on the field. Some people call it &amp;ldquo;the National Felony League.&amp;rdquo;
Frustrated fans look for better entertainment. Ticket sales remain high for one reason: stupid corporate executives. Stupid executives think it&amp;rsquo;s still a status symbol to control lots of NFL tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kroenke&#39;s Brilliant Move</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/07/kroenkes-brilliant-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 01:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/07/kroenkes-brilliant-move/</guid>
      <description>I figured it out about the same time Ben Hochman of the Post Dispatch did: Stan Kroenke wrote a letter designed to force the owners to move the Rams to Los Angeles right now.
The acrimony created by Kroenke&amp;rsquo;s relocation request letter makes the situation in St. Louis untenable for the team and its owner. In short, Kroenke calls St. Louis a second-rate, economically depressed, crime-infest toilet of a city full of people so obsessed with baseball that no other sports franchise has the ability to compete for entertainment dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the Cardinals’ Reign Over?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/is-the-cardinals-reign-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 06:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/is-the-cardinals-reign-over/</guid>
      <description>Imagine a world in which the Cardinals are not perennial champions. Major league baseball could be working on that scenario right now.
The 1970s in Southwest St. Louis The Red Bird Express ran from Ivanhoe to Busch Stadium along Arsenal Street. For about seven dollars, I could get to a game and back, including bus fare, a bleacher ticket, and a hotdog and soda. My mom didn’t know how many times I made that trip, often for day games while she worked at St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Reforms for the 2014-2015 St. Louis Blues</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/27/four-reforms-for-the-2014-2015-st-louis-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 22:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/27/four-reforms-for-the-2014-2015-st-louis-blues/</guid>
      <description>If you’re reading this, the Blues blew it. Again.
I’m writing this six hours before Game 6 against the Chicago Blackhawks. If I wait to write this after the game, I’ll get a lot of complaints about foul language.
Yes, I expect the Blackhawks to end the Blues’ delusions of Market Street parades this afternoon. The Blues’ tenacity, hitting, and heart can’t overcome their lack of goal scoring and playoff goaltending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Countdown to Post-Linehan Era</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/21/countdown-to-post-linehan-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/21/countdown-to-post-linehan-era/</guid>
      <description>Last week, Rams owner Chip Rosenbloom all but promised Rams fans that head coach Scott Linehan would be fire along with others responsible for assembling and running the worst football in the NFL.
You might think that Linehan and the Rams would have opened a can of backs-against-the-wall whoopass on the 0-2 Seahawks today.
They didn&amp;rsquo;t. Apparently, they fumbled the whoopass can in the locker room before the game, drenching themselves with the toxic substance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Worst Football Team Ever</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/14/the-worst-football-team-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2008 20:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/14/the-worst-football-team-ever/</guid>
      <description>The title probably belongs to the 2008 St. Louis Rams.
For the second week in a row, a team without serious injuries humiliated itself, its city, and the players&amp;rsquo; families on national television.
Defense, offense, and special teams were sickeningly lackadaisical and inept. It was like watching squirrels do trigonometry.
If I owned this team, the entire coaching staff would be fired tonight.
Technorati Tags: St. Louis Rams,football</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rams Worst Game Ever</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/07/rams-worst-game-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 20:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/07/rams-worst-game-ever/</guid>
      <description>Today the St. Louis Rams played the worst game in the history of the oft-horrible history, losing 38-3 to a mediocre Philadelphia Eagles team.
Watching the game on a big, HD television made the spectacle ever more frightening. The incompetence, laziness, lack of preparedness, inept game planning and powder-puff tackling seemed to delight head coach Scott Linehan, who believes winning is over-rated.
Linehan&amp;rsquo;s remarkable leadership and motivation worked magic on new offensive coordinator Al Saunders.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>