<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>michigan on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/michigan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in michigan on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:47:02 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/michigan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Turn Nursing Homes Into Death Camps</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</guid>
      <description>When I wrote this post on May 6, I worried how it would be received. Accusing a governor of intentionally killing nursing home residents in order to save money is a serious charge. And, with only circumstantial evidence, difficult to prove.
Since then, Andrew Cuomo&amp;rsquo;s behavior has been consistent with guilt. The latest example is deflection. He&amp;rsquo;s trying, now, to blame federal guidelines for his order to force uninfected nursing homes to treat confirmed COVID-19 patients even if they lacked the facilities and skills to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Wisconsin Police Chief Admits Illegal Harassment of Tea Party Leader, After Lying About It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/01/campbell-wisconsin-police-chief-admits-illegal-harassment-tea-party-leader-lying/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/01/campbell-wisconsin-police-chief-admits-illegal-harassment-tea-party-leader-lying/</guid>
      <description>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lbYKydZ3T0Q
The weird thing is: isn&amp;rsquo;t that Sharp Elbows questioning the Chief? When did he become a detective in Michigan?
The chief pleaded nolo contendere to identity theft charges. He presented himself as a tea party leader signing up for embarrassing, sexual email lists. From the La Crosse Tea Party:
 A shocking update to the Town of Campbell Situation this week. Detective Spencer from Monroe County Sheriff’s department called and said that Campbell Police Chief Tim Kelemen confessed to harassment/internet stalking/identity theft regarding my complaint filed to La Crosse P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Fund A Terrorist Network?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/15/do-you-fund-a-terrorist-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/15/do-you-fund-a-terrorist-network/</guid>
      <description>According to the FBI:
 Domestic terrorism is the unlawful use, or threatened use, of force or violence by a group or individual based and operating entirely within the United States or Puerto Rico without foreign direction committed against persons or property to intimidate or coerce a government, the civilian population, or any segment thereof in furtherance of political or social objectives. (source)
 In Michigan, union protesters physically assaulted Steven Crowder of Fox News, then destroyed a tent belonging to Americans for Prosperity (video below).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>