<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>elections on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/elections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in elections on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 09:45:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/elections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Know When To Fight Your Own</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/07/know-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 09:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/07/know-fight/</guid>
      <description>I can be pretty hard on Republicans. Not hard enough for some. Too hard for others.
But I, at least, try to time my battles for ideological consistency. As a general rule, odd-numbered years are for cleaning up the GOP. Even-numbered years are for cleaning out Democrats.
This is an odd-numbered year. Right up to the votes on the continuing resolution,my primary targets were Republicans, especially Roy Blunt.
Once the House exercised its Constitutional power of the purse strings, sending a popular continuing resolution to the Senate, the battle lines shifted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Collateral Damage When Hunting for RINOs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/responsible-rino-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/responsible-rino-hunter/</guid>
      <description>Lowell Weicker was a RINO. So was Lincoln Chaffe for a while. And John Linsday, the mayor who tried to destroy New York City in the late 1960s and early 1970s.
RINO stands for &amp;ldquo;Republican In Name Only.&amp;rdquo; Rhinos and Elephants are both pachyderms, so it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty clever name for people who join the Republican Party but prefer the Democrat platform.
The problem is, some people take the concept to extremes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s the Most Encouraging Thing John Boehner Ever Said</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</guid>
      <description>Today on ABC&amp;rsquo;s This Week, Speaker of the House John Boehner spoke very powerful words about himself. They reveal his motivation. And it&amp;rsquo;s very encouraging.
 &amp;ldquo;I’m a reasonable guy. But I didn’t come to Washington to be a congressman. I came to do something for my country.&amp;rdquo;
 Write that down. That statement echos.
Research shows thatpeople motivated by doing, by getting better, by learning, will work harder and stay truer to their principles than people motivated by demonstrating how good they are&amp;ndash;being something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Reasons Why House Republicans Should Pass a Clean Debt Ceiling Bill Now *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/05/4-reasons-to-pass-clean-debt-ceiling-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 16:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/05/4-reasons-to-pass-clean-debt-ceiling-bill/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, I know. Obama&amp;rsquo;s childish, petulant, and tyrannical tantrums over the continuing resolution makes me want to fight like an angry cat, too.
But I don&amp;rsquo;t actually want to fight. Fighting isn&amp;rsquo;t in our interest. As Sun Tzu said:
 Hence to fight and conquer in all your battles is not supreme excellence; supreme excellence consists in breaking the enemy&amp;rsquo;s resistance without fighting.
 I want to succeed in repealing Obamacare and forcing government into its constitutionally limited box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Loathsome War on WWII Vets Deserves Our Scorn and Fury</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/01/obamas-loathsome-war-wwii-vets-deserve-scorn-fury/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 03:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/01/obamas-loathsome-war-wwii-vets-deserve-scorn-fury/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ve all see the reports.
WWII Veterans asked the White House for permission to visit the World War II Memorial in case of a shutdown. The veterans are part of the Honor Flights program that helps aging veterans visit the WWII Memorial.
Even though there&amp;rsquo;s no cost involved, the White House chose to dishonor the veterans&amp;rsquo; request. It send forth &amp;ldquo;goons,&amp;rdquo; in Senator Paul&amp;rsquo;s works, to erect barricades around the memorial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown Week Could Turn Into Big Win for Republicans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/30/shutdown-week-republicans-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/30/shutdown-week-republicans-winning/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to offer anything.&amp;rdquo; Barack Obama on why he&amp;rsquo;s shutting down the government.
Obama keeps forgetting he&amp;rsquo;s not a dictator. Or maybe I keep forgetting he is.
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;441&amp;rdquo;] Democrat Speaker Tip O&amp;rsquo;Neill shut down the government 12 times.[/caption]
Did you see that list of government shutdowns?
1976, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1981, 1982, 1983, 1984, 1986, 1987, 1990, 1995.
Those first four shutdowns came with Democrat majorities in both houses of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Learned the House GOP Is A Lot Tougher Than Senate</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/28/ive-learned-house-gop-lot-tougher-senate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 03:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/28/ive-learned-house-gop-lot-tougher-senate/</guid>
      <description>I was wrong.
As the continuing resolution fight approached, I expected House Republicans to cave. I expected Boehner to make a half-hearted attempt to use debt ceiling, instead of continuing resolution, as leverage to stop Obamacare. And I expected Republican Senators to make a stand.
But that&amp;rsquo;s not what happened.
In reverse order, Senate Republican leadership ran away from confrontation like schoolgirls spying a snake. Led by Mitch McConnell, John Cornyn, and Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Junior Senator Roy Blunt, the GOP attacked Senators Mike Lee and Ted Cruz instead of Obamacare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Condorcet Method Could Save The GOP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/20/how-the-condorcet-method-could-save-the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/20/how-the-condorcet-method-could-save-the-gop/</guid>
      <description>The RNC’s Autopsy report wants to do away with caucuses and conventions, replacing them with regional primaries. But I’ll propose a different reform that will make candidate selection more interesting, whether in a caucus or a primary.
A Word About The Autopsy The idea of compacting the primary season and eliminating caucuses has some merit, but also a lot of downside. On the plus side are splashier events to showcase the party, fewer Tuesdays littered with politics, and, believe it or not, some economies as candidates can focus on one geographical region at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is Exactly How The Special Election To Replace Jo Ann Emerson Will Be Conducted. (We Think)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/05/here-is-exactly-how-the-special-election-to-replace-jo-ann-emerson-will-be-conducted-we-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/05/here-is-exactly-how-the-special-election-to-replace-jo-ann-emerson-will-be-conducted-we-think/</guid>
      <description>I’ve gotten a lot of emails and comments asking for more information on the special election process in Missouri’s 8th Congressional District. So I went to the smartest person I know about this stuff: Frieda Keough.
Here’ what I learned:
 Eddie Justice, the Chair of the 8th Congressional District will call a meeting. Anyone wanting to be appointed to run for the 8th Congressional District shows up at the meeting and will be put before the committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Maximize Your Election Influence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/how-to-maximize-your-election-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/how-to-maximize-your-election-influence/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s What To Do Today And On Election Day
Tuesday is the most important election of your life, but voting is never enough. You can have a bigger impact by using social proof to increase your influence. I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how, and it won&amp;rsquo;t take you long.
First, though, make sure nothing gets in the way of exercising your duty to vote.
Studies have shown that you are more likely to vote if you answer these questions before Election Day:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Barack Obama is Right?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/19/which-barack-obama-is-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/19/which-barack-obama-is-right/</guid>
      <description>A genius is someone who can hold contrary concepts simultaneously in mind.
What, then, do we call a person who simultaneously argues two contrary concepts?

How ‘bout “demagogue?”
A few weeks ago, Barack Obama told America’s business owners that they are not responsible for their success. “Someone else built that.”
Today, the same Obama told Mitt Romney that there not many people who consider themselves victims.
Does Mr. Obama believe that people in dire straights are not victims of circumstances?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apathy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/18/apathy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/18/apathy-2/</guid>
      <description>The world is a dangerous place to live; not because of the people who are evil, but because of the people who don&amp;rsquo;t do anything about it.
&amp;ndash;Albert Einstein
 It’s easy to blame the subject for our apathy. The candidates are uninspiring; the colors are dull; the task is boring.
Blaming the subject is easy because it relieves us, the objects, of any responsibility. “I can’t make Romney less WASPy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do Presidential Debates and Colonoscopies Have in Common?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/30/what-do-presidential-debates-and-colonoscopies-have-in-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/30/what-do-presidential-debates-and-colonoscopies-have-in-common/</guid>
      <description>At some point, each additional GOP Presidential debate becomes just a bigger pain in the . . . But science shows us that the last debate before a vote—and the last memorable event in the last debate—is paramount to how we remember the entire event.
In fact, memorable moments at the end, not consistent performance throughout, determine who wins and who loses.
In this awesome TED talk, Nobel winning psychologist Daniel Kahneman explains the weird difference between our experiencing selves and our remembering selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Two Key Roles in Social Media Activism *Update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/21/the-two-key-roles-in-social-media-activism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/21/the-two-key-roles-in-social-media-activism/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever studied human networks?
I’m not talking about online social networks alone, but any kind of human network.
They’re amazing.

Networks tend to determine who we date, who we marry, and where we work. Our lives are more influenced by networks than we can imagine.
 A network community can be defined as a group of people who are much more connected to one another than they are to other groups of connected people found in other parts of the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoveOnUp.org was never supposed to happen</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/14/moveonup-org-was-never-supposed-to-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2011 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/14/moveonup-org-was-never-supposed-to-happen/</guid>
      <description>This weekend, MoveOnUp.org held its first conference. The location was the Crowne Plaza Hotel at the airport. The event launched the Sherman T. Parker Scholarship for African-American Political Science students.
But that’s not the big story.
The big story is this: MoveOnUp.org has cheated history.
Why “cheated?” Because the past 50 years of American liberal history has prepared American blacks for one purpose: compliance.
Using victimhood, welfare, crime, destructive education, and programs designed to destroy families, American liberals from Ted Kennedy to Barack Obama chained African-Americans to “Uncle Sam’s Plantation,” as Star Parker so aptly puts it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing Battles</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/choosing-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 01:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/choosing-battles/</guid>
      <description>For the record, I do not apologize for focusing on the most important battles facing self-government since the American Revolution.

Earlier this week, McGraw Milhaven of 550 KTRS criticized Tea Partyers for not opposing Missouri legislation, introduced by and championed by Republicans, that will force insurance companies to cover treatment for children diagnosed with Autism and associated conditions. (I personally oppose this legislation, by the way.)
Before that, a few Tea Partyers criticized me and others on facebook for not doing “enough” to support the Missouri Healthcare Free Choice act, which recently passed both the House and the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>