<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boehner on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/boehner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boehner on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 05:18:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/boehner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress Just Increased Deficits By $4 Trillion, And All I Got Was 2.9% Tax Increase</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/01/congress-just-increased-deficits-by-4-trillion-and-all-i-got-was-2-9-tax-increase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 05:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/01/congress-just-increased-deficits-by-4-trillion-and-all-i-got-was-2-9-tax-increase/</guid>
      <description>You’ll need a scorecard to keep up with the insanity in Washington this week.

The Senate’s been a lost cause for a while, so let’s not even bother with the upper house. Besides, it’s really hard to focus on good fiscal policy while Hooter’s Girls are passing out Bacardi 151 shots, Buffalo wings, and “Welcome 2013” horns in the cloak room.
Over in the House, things looked interesting for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What Happens Now That Boehner’s “Plan B” Went Down In Flames</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/21/heres-what-happens-now-that-boehners-plan-b-went-down-in-flames/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 15:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/21/heres-what-happens-now-that-boehners-plan-b-went-down-in-flames/</guid>
      <description>Now that Boehner’s “Plan B” strategy has blown up like a poisoned dog, here’s what Boehner will do.
Remember this chart from last month? It shows strategic options from John Boehner’s point of view:

Yesterday, Boehner tried to land about halfway between the top and bottom quadrant on the left, shown here

Now that Plan B has been rejected, Boehner’s choices are limited to these: * Adjourn and hit the fiscal cliff * Cut a deal that will earn most Democrat votes and enough Republican votes to pass</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Expect Boehner To Play The Black Knight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</guid>
      <description>The GOP didn’t really have a plan in place in case it lost. It certainly didn’t have a plan for getting snotclobbered. And if you try to spin Tuesday’s results as anything less than a good old-fashioned ass-kicking, you’re deluding yourself.

**Republicans Got Creamed ** I know Michelle Malkin found 20 things that went right on election night, but there about 60 million things that went wrong. Let’s take a look:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>