<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>united nations on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/united-nations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in united nations on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 02:06:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/united-nations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally! A President Stands Tall</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/finally-our-president-stands-tall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 02:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/finally-our-president-stands-tall/</guid>
      <description>They were dumbfounded.
Those United Nations stuffed shirts were dumbfounded. Struck dumb. Silenced. Shocked. Floored.
Those sissy diplomats were shaken. Appalled. Frightened.
Never in the sordid history of the United Nations has an American president spoken in unvarnished truth in unvarnished terms.
Trump has the best words.
Trump used his best words today.
The best of the best.
Trump called Kim Jung Un &amp;ldquo;Rocket Man.&amp;rdquo; The funniest and most effective linguistic kill-shot to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weednesday Post: You Want the UN Deciding Your State’s Laws?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/20/the-weednesday-post-you-want-the-un-deciding-your-states-laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/20/the-weednesday-post-you-want-the-un-deciding-your-states-laws/</guid>
      <description>The United Nations wants our federal government to negate the laws of Colorado and Washington regarding marijuana. Attorney General Eric Holder mulls it over.

Americans Believe In Federalism In polls, Americans are consistent: the US government must not impose its morals on states regarding marijuana. After ballot measures in Colorado and Washington approved legalization of pot, Gallup asked whether the United States should honor the will of the people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Libya: To What End?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/20/libya-to-what-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 18:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/20/libya-to-what-end/</guid>
      <description>When the US invaded Iraq in 2003, it do so with the clear intent of bringing its enemy—Saddam’s regime—to an unconditional surrender. That was the objective. Despite what happened after that objective was achieved, we went in with a clear and measurable purpose.
The motivating reason for our foray into Iraq was also clear. We believed at the time that Saddam Hussein’s possession of &amp;ndash; and desire for more &amp;ndash; weapons of mass destruction posed an imminent threat to US interests and citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>