<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/patient-protection-and-affordable-care-act/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/patient-protection-and-affordable-care-act/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why You Are Underemployed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</guid>
      <description>If you can’t find full-time work, blame Obamacare.

One reason the Middle Class has shriveled and wages shrunk over the the past four years is underemployment. People want full time work, but settle for anything. And anything is usually part time.
Most of the fantastic new jobs created since the 2009 have been part-time jobs.
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, 14.6% of Americans want a full-time job but settle for part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Are the Bill in Congress That Need Your Attention</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/these-are-the-bill-in-congress-that-need-your-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/these-are-the-bill-in-congress-that-need-your-attention/</guid>
      <description>Even though Congress is winding down, there are dangerous bills on the desk. I used Heritage Action’s Popvox program to tell Congressman (and future Senator) Todd Akin I oppose the FARM bill that does less for farmers and more for wasteful government statism.

Here’s the whole slate of bills you should write to Congress about:
Oppose the Big-Spending Farm Bill: Email Your Representative Now Tell Blunt and McCaskill to Kill LOST—A Bill to Surrender US Sovereignty</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>