<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RINOs on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/rinos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in RINOs on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 14:00:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/rinos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Collateral Damage When Hunting for RINOs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/responsible-rino-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/responsible-rino-hunter/</guid>
      <description>Lowell Weicker was a RINO. So was Lincoln Chaffe for a while. And John Linsday, the mayor who tried to destroy New York City in the late 1960s and early 1970s.
RINO stands for &amp;ldquo;Republican In Name Only.&amp;rdquo; Rhinos and Elephants are both pachyderms, so it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty clever name for people who join the Republican Party but prefer the Democrat platform.
The problem is, some people take the concept to extremes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s the Most Encouraging Thing John Boehner Ever Said</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</guid>
      <description>Today on ABC&amp;rsquo;s This Week, Speaker of the House John Boehner spoke very powerful words about himself. They reveal his motivation. And it&amp;rsquo;s very encouraging.
 &amp;ldquo;I’m a reasonable guy. But I didn’t come to Washington to be a congressman. I came to do something for my country.&amp;rdquo;
 Write that down. That statement echos.
Research shows thatpeople motivated by doing, by getting better, by learning, will work harder and stay truer to their principles than people motivated by demonstrating how good they are&amp;ndash;being something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Learned the House GOP Is A Lot Tougher Than Senate</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/28/ive-learned-house-gop-lot-tougher-senate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 03:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/28/ive-learned-house-gop-lot-tougher-senate/</guid>
      <description>I was wrong.
As the continuing resolution fight approached, I expected House Republicans to cave. I expected Boehner to make a half-hearted attempt to use debt ceiling, instead of continuing resolution, as leverage to stop Obamacare. And I expected Republican Senators to make a stand.
But that&amp;rsquo;s not what happened.
In reverse order, Senate Republican leadership ran away from confrontation like schoolgirls spying a snake. Led by Mitch McConnell, John Cornyn, and Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Junior Senator Roy Blunt, the GOP attacked Senators Mike Lee and Ted Cruz instead of Obamacare.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>