<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Religion on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/religion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Religion on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 00:41:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Abortion Wars</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/25/abortion-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 00:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/25/abortion-wars/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama and Congressional Democrats could be headed toward a final showdown over abortion and the right of men and women to choose their moral direction.
Obama has promised in bold and belligerent words to make the Freedom of Choice Act his first, most important act as President. Consistent with his lifelong passion for encouraging abortion, even encouraging his daughters to have abortions, Obama&amp;rsquo;s first act as President will be to drive a permanent wedge between the United States and the Catholic church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re All Communists Now *************</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/04/were-all-communists-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 02:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/04/were-all-communists-now/</guid>
      <description>Ignorance is no defense.
Americans, faced with the choice of Marxist-socialism or republican-capitalism, a plurality chose communism.
Their moral weakness, combined with viral corruption of character, has created a majority coalition of indecisive morons known as independents, children who want government to make their decisions and butter their bread, and neo-Marxists, like Obama. We fought the Cold War for nothing.
Over the next two years, we will see the most complete change in a nation seen since the Bolshevik Revolution nearly 100 years ago in Russia:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal Rest Grant Unto Her, Oh Lord</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/04/eternal-rest-grant-unto-her-oh-lord/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 06:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/04/eternal-rest-grant-unto-her-oh-lord/</guid>
      <description>And let perpetual light shine upon her. May her soul and all the souls of the faithful departed, through the mercy of God, rest in peace.
To Obama and his family, my condolences.
This is personal; it isn&amp;rsquo;t business.
Technorati Tags: Madelyn Dunham,Obama grandmother,condolences</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Call for a Rosary Novena</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/26/a-call-for-a-rosary-novena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 05:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/26/a-call-for-a-rosary-novena/</guid>
      <description>Among the most important titles we have in the Catholic Church for the Blessed Virgin Mary are Our Lady of Victory and Our Lady of the Rosary. These titles can be traced back to one of the most decisive times in the history of the world and Christendom. The Battle of Lepanto took place on October 7 (date of feast of Our Lady of Rosary), 1571. This proved to be the most crucial battle for the Christian forces against the radical Muslim navy of Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Late and I&#39;m Bored</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/30/its-late-and-im-bored/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 03:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/30/its-late-and-im-bored/</guid>
      <description>so this will be my only post&amp;ndash;a series of thoughts on the day.
Financial Armageddon
In case you were too busy with your normal life and missed it, the financial armageddon promised/threatened by President Bush, Nancy Pelosi, Hank Paulson, and every other power freak on the planet failed to materialize. The Dow ended up 485 points, erasing well over half of yesterday&amp;rsquo;s losses. Before Congress does something stupid, let&amp;rsquo;s just see what happens if we, the people, are left to our own devices&amp;ndash;the way the founders planned it and the way it worked for 150 years before do-gooder morons fucked everything up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>