<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Fourth Turning on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/the-fourth-turning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Fourth Turning on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 06:16:06 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/the-fourth-turning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fourth Turning Warning for America: Climax</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/a-fourth-turning-warning-for-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 06:16:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/a-fourth-turning-warning-for-america/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I warned, again, that the center didn&amp;rsquo;t hold. There is no center in American politics. Americans are more divided than at any time since the Civil War.
(Read We Have the War Upon Us by William J. Cooper)
Today, I have a short warning from the great book The Fourth Turning by Howe and Strauss.
What Should Have Happened after 2016 Strauss and Howe prophesied an election that changed everything sometime during the Crisis era which began with the fall of Lehman Brothers (the last time Nancy Pelosi was Speaker of the House):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018: The beginning of the end of the Fourth Turning in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/27/2018-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-fourth-turning-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 19:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/27/2018-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-fourth-turning-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Regardless of its ideology, that new leadership will assert public authority and demand private sacrifice. Where leaders had once been inclined to alleviate societal pressures, they will now aggravate them to command the nation&amp;rsquo;s attention.
 —William Strauss and Neil Howe: The Fourth Turning: What the Cycles of History Tell Us About America&amp;rsquo;s Next Rendezvous with Destiny
Donald Trump can&amp;rsquo;t stand festering problems. Trump forces problems to the surface, into the daylight, where they can be fought and settled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Climax</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/22/predicting-the-climax/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 22:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/22/predicting-the-climax/</guid>
      <description>We are watching The Fourth Turning unfold before our eyes.
While you should read all of The Fourth Turning by generational historians William Strauss and Neil Howe, here&amp;rsquo;s one of their predictions for this point in time. The prediction was published in 1997:
 The economy will in time recover from its early and vertiginous reversals. Late in the Crisis, with trust and hope and urgency growing fast, it may even achieve unprecedented levels of efficiency and production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Centre Cannot Hold</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/10/the-centre-cannot-hold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 02:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/10/the-centre-cannot-hold/</guid>
      <description>THE SECOND COMING --William Butler Yeats Turning and turning in the widening gyre The falcon cannot hear the falconer; Things fall apart; the centre cannot hold; Mere anarchy is loosed upon the world, The blood-dimmed tide is loosed, and everywhere The ceremony of innocence is drowned; The best lack all conviction, while the worst Are full of passionate intensity. Surely some revelation is at hand; Surely the Second Coming is at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Conservatives Should Get Involved—Part 4</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/23/why-conservatives-should-get-involved-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 10:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/23/why-conservatives-should-get-involved-part-4/</guid>
      <description>In part 1 of this series, we clarified some misconceptions and falsehoods about the Franklin Project.
In part 2, we examined the debate on the right from 1990 with William F. Buckley and Milton Friedman.
Part 3 was a critique of the Franklin Project&amp;rsquo;s Plan of Action.
Today, we will look at the consequences should conservatives turn their backs on the concept of developing a service ethos in America.
Generations: Saying “No” Won’t Work  Do you remember when Roosevelt died?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>