<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mark Levin on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mark-levin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mark Levin on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:30:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mark-levin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Levin Is Turning On Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/23/mark-levin-is-turning-on-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/23/mark-levin-is-turning-on-trump/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s outstanding,&amp;rdquo; said the Great One.
 The Republican leadership in Congress doesn’t have the guts to go to the floor of the Senate or the floor of the House and make these charges. This is outstanding. You can’t let Hillary Clinton get away with her corruption, her cronyism, her criminality. I don’t care who you support or don’t support. She’s detestable.
 [Via Breitbart.com]
Mark Levin said some terrible things about Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Immigration Fans Need to Read Wong Kim Ark</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 04:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad that Donald Trump has inspired so many good conservatives to promote fantasies about the 14th Amendment.
The Supreme Court addressed the issue of birthright citizenship directly, and Mark Levin and Laura Ingram know it. They are Constitutional lawyers.
Both Levin and Ingraham are familiar with United States v. Wong Kim Ark (1898) which established, thoroughly, that citizenship by birth has been the law of the land since before the Declaration of Independence and was codified by the 14th Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Idiots</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/07/american-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/07/american-idiots/</guid>
      <description>Those who blindly cheer for the fall of Mubarak and the rise of anything else in Egypt are the same as those who cheered the fall of the Shah in Iran. Question their motives.
The Great One, Mark Levin, tweeted attention to this post about an email from Salim Mansur to Claire Berlinski. The email’s purpose was to call Claire’s attention to Mansur’s latest column.
Here’s what Mansur says as an aside:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>