<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FergusonBuycott on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/fergusonbuycott/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FergusonBuycott on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 17:08:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/fergusonbuycott/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a Beautiful Spring Day, And Dellena Struggles to Stay In Business</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/18/its-a-beautiful-spring-day-and-dellena-struggles-to-stay-in-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 17:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/18/its-a-beautiful-spring-day-and-dellena-struggles-to-stay-in-business/</guid>
      <description>We metDellena Jones during our first Ferguson BUYcott in August. Since then, St. Louis Tea Partier, Dottie Bailey, has made it her mission to help Dellena&amp;rsquo;s business survive and flourish.
https://youtu.be/r-ye3nSe2Vk
Dellena&amp;rsquo;s business has fallen 60 percent since the first riots. She&amp;rsquo;s repaired the damage to her salon, but business is slow.
Despite all her challenges, Dellena still found the time and energy to host Center for Self-Governance training in her shop on a Saturday, foregoing that day&amp;rsquo;s revenue to learn about freedom and responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where I&#39;m Kicking Off My Ferguson BUYcott Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/29/im-kicking-ferguson-buycott-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 23:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/29/im-kicking-ferguson-buycott-saturday/</guid>
      <description>At 1:00 PM, I&amp;rsquo;ll be at 911 Beauty Salon: 9193 W Florissant Ave, St Louis, MO 63136, Cross Streets: Between Ferguson Ave and Canfield Dr. Let us knowyour story here. Upload photos, reciepts, and stories. People love stories.
You are welcome to join me there at 1:00, or shop and dine on your own.

This Ferguson BUYcott is getting massive national attention. Big thanks to everyone who took part last week and who&amp;rsquo;s joining in this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Ferguson and Dellwood This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 04:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I&amp;rsquo;m so late on this. This sounds whiny, I know, but I have a really involved week at work this week. Sorry. Crap always seems to work out this way, though. When there&amp;rsquo;s a great need for Tea Party services, I&amp;rsquo;m tied up with work obligations. Something has to give, and it&amp;rsquo;s usually the thing that doesn&amp;rsquo;t generate revenue.
But we all have work to do. Ferguson businesses and families are still struggling with the effects of the riots.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>