<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mayor Slay on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mayor-slay/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mayor Slay on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:05:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mayor-slay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week: November 15, 2015</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/15/the-week-november-15-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/15/the-week-november-15-2015/</guid>
      <description>Viva la France This week, let&amp;rsquo;s say a special prayer for the people of France. And the whole world.
Mayor Slay About to Change Tune on Refugees On September 11, St. Louis Mayor Francis Slay announced plans to accept 10,000 non-Christian Syrian refugees to St. Louis. After the coordinated attacks by ISIS terrorists in Paris on Friday, expect the mayor come under intense pressure to change plans. News that at least one of the Paris attackers entered France from Serbia as a Syrian war refugee will only intensify the pressure on Slay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Hard to Deny North County Has Problems with Police and Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>What did you think when you first heard reports of violence in Ferguson? I mean, after the shooting death of Michael Brown?
Did you ever for a moment think, &amp;ldquo;this is about more than just Michael Brown?&amp;rdquo;
I hate to say that. It&amp;rsquo;s embarrassing to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m so jaded as to think &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;rdquo; when a young man dies. Sorry. I&amp;rsquo;m just being honest.
I understand community grief and anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francis Slay Destroys the Transportation Sales Tax Trying to Support It **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/15/francis-slay-destroys-transportation-sales-tax-trying-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 02:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/15/francis-slay-destroys-transportation-sales-tax-trying-support/</guid>
      <description>Doesn&amp;rsquo;t it suck when Jay Nixon and Francis Slay get on opposite sides of an issue?
Where do we go?
They&amp;rsquo;re on opposite sides of Amendment 7, the largest tax increase in Missouri history. And you need to choose a side before August 5, because the ball&amp;rsquo;s in the voters&amp;rsquo; court.
But there&amp;rsquo;s no need to fear; Hennessy is here. And I heard Francis the talking Mayor on KMOX this morning (or maybe it was yesterday) talking about how much he loves, Loves, LOVES the 3/4 cent sales tax increase theoretically for transportation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>