<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2014 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2014 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress Adjourned and You Need a Drink</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/14/congress-adjourned-need-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 03:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/14/congress-adjourned-need-drink/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the Heritage Action Christmas Party Wednesday, December 17 at 6:00 pm
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_15660&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]Republican Party Animal[/caption]
Scarecrow in Chesterfield ( map )
Heavy Hors d&amp;rsquo;oeuvres complements of Heritage Action for America.
Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about 2015 and $2.15 gasoline.
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to RSVP, but we&amp;rsquo;d appreciate it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Police Officers Like Writing Tickets?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/14/police-officers-like-writing-tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 22:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/14/police-officers-like-writing-tickets/</guid>
      <description>[audio mp3=&amp;quot;https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/do-police-like-ticket-quotas.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
What do police officer think about traffic ticket quotas? Here&amp;rsquo;s one officer&amp;rsquo;s thoughts:
 In my agency, those of us in patrol had to keep a &amp;ldquo;Daily.&amp;rdquo; This would be a formal document that showed the times, addresses where we went, written in code, of what we had done.
 On the back were boxes for how many traffic citations, criminal citations, parking citations and felony and misdemeanor arrests we had made on that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What No One Tells You About Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/13/no-one-tells-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2014 22:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/13/no-one-tells-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s something happening here But what it is ain&amp;rsquo;t exactly clear There&amp;rsquo;s a man with a gun over there Telling me I got to beware &amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;For What It&amp;rsquo;s Worth&amp;rdquo; by The Buffalo Springfield
 &amp;ldquo;This isn&amp;rsquo;t about Michael Brown.&amp;rdquo;
Those words popped out of my mouth as I watched the Sunday evening news with my dad. It was August 10.
Full-scale rioting hadn&amp;rsquo;t erupted, but the battle lines were drawn: police on one side, people, mostly young people, on the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What&#39;s Happening on the Muni Courts Front</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 02:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</guid>
      <description>He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harrass our people, and eat out their substance.
 &amp;ndash; The Declaration of Independence
Back in August, I asked for your help in pushing for municipal court reform.
Cities that abuse their police and courts destroy liberty:
** Abusive citiesturn citizens against their police forces ** Abusive cities sponge off the poor ** Abusive cities operate debtor prisons ** Abusive cities subvert respect for the law and the courts ** Abusive citiesdemean and demoralize their citizens ** Abusive cities repel business and jobs ** Abusive cities condition people to bow down to government</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Shame House Republican Leadership On Immigration  *ACTION*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/02/shame-house-republican-leadership-immigration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/02/shame-house-republican-leadership-immigration/</guid>
      <description>[scroll to updates]
And, yes, &amp;ldquo;House Republican Leadership&amp;rdquo; is a code word for Ann Wagner.
Every victorious Republican ran on a promise to aggressively check Obama&amp;rsquo;s illegal executive actions.
They weren&amp;rsquo;t all lying. Only the &amp;ldquo;leaders&amp;rdquo; lied.
House leadership is trying to weasel out of its commitment to voters to block Obama&amp;rsquo;s illegal activities.
The House can easily** attach a rider to the upcoming spending bill** prohibiting any money from going toward Obama&amp;rsquo;s 10 illegal illegal alien memoranda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Evidence Never Mattered</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/01/evidence-never-mattered/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 04:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/01/evidence-never-mattered/</guid>
      <description>The danger of jumping to conclusions isn’t that you might be wrong. It’s that your brain will be unable to recognize its error.
We’ve all heard of the psychological (or just logical) fallacy of confirmation bias. It’s worth looking at three aspects of confirmation bias from Science Daily:
*1. In psychology and cognitive science, confirmation bias (or confirmatory bias) is a tendency to search for or interpret information in a way that confirms one&amp;rsquo;s preconceptions, leading to statistical errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Stop the Commies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/30/stop-commies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 04:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/30/stop-commies/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s all a lie. It didn&amp;rsquo;t start that way. At first, the Mike Brown protesters were all about Mike Brown and people like him. But not anymore.
Even the New York Times admitted the protests in Mike Brown&amp;rsquo;s name are actually the Revolutionary Communist Party advancing Marxism. (The NYT pulled down the story on Sunday morning. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have linked it, anyway.)
I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of stomping on someone else&amp;rsquo;s parade, even if I disagree with their cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the US House, Insider Money Buys Leadership Positions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/29/us-house-insider-money-buys-leadership-positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 20:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/29/us-house-insider-money-buys-leadership-positions/</guid>
      <description>The US House of Representatives is not a meritocracy. And that&amp;rsquo;s a shame.
House &amp;ldquo;leadership&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually have anything to do with leadership. It has everything to do with money.
In a story about the fall from power of Nancy Pelosi, Michael Barone describes how the House leadership process evolved from seniority to raw cash.
  For years, liberal Democrats had decried the seniority system, which automatically made conservative Southerners (and/or senile members) committee chairmen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Protesters Couldn&#39;t Care Less About Mike Brown</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/28/some-protesters-couldnt-care-less-about-mike-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 02:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/28/some-protesters-couldnt-care-less-about-mike-brown/</guid>
      <description>If you think the mall protests are about the police, Ferguson, Mike Brown, or Darren Wilson, you could be wrong.
For some, Mike Brown is a pawn. The protests are mere opportunities to exploit.
 Travis Martin, a protester who was at the bowling alley and the Justice Center, said he didn&amp;rsquo;t think that activist leaders had done enough planning and promotion for an event at the Galleria.
 “I think the main organizers weren&amp;rsquo;t so focused on anti-capitalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gratitude Is Not a Privilege</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/27/gratitude-not-privilege/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 17:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/27/gratitude-not-privilege/</guid>
      <description>Gratitude, like love, is bound only by our choices. The more we give, the more we keep.
I tried to ignore Ferguson today, but I glanced at Twitter hashtag #Ferguson a moment ago. The first tweet I read inspired this post. Someone wrote that &amp;ldquo;being able to be thankful after #Fergson is a privilege itself.&amp;rdquo;
I understand how someone could feel that their &amp;ldquo;gratitude privilege&amp;rdquo; had been revoked. We lost our daughter just before Christmas in 1994, about four weeks after I got out of the Navy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Ideas to Save Christmas in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Nixon buck-passed while Ferguson burned. With the city’s main business district laid to rubble, buycotts won’t have much effect. And Christmas is around the corner.
Who got hurt last night?
*1. People who own businesses *2. People who work at businesses *3. People who rely on businesses
Time is short. The people affected by last night’s riots need help rebuilding and jobs right now. While I don’t have complete plans, I can throw out eight ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Worst of Humanity and the Absence of Leadership in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/worst-humanity-abence-leadership-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 06:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/worst-humanity-abence-leadership-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>I should be in bed. But I can&amp;rsquo;t take my eyes off the images of Ferguson burning to the ground.
A liberal friend on Twitter admonished me not to be political. Maybe he&amp;rsquo;s right.
But I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Dellena&amp;rsquo;s 911 Beauty Salon burned in Ferguson tonight. It seems everything else has, too. The airport is closed. St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s image may be taking a fatal blow. The region might go the way of Gary, Indiana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big ISPs Will Back Net Neutrality Someday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/24/big-isps-will-back-net-neutrality-someday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 22:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/24/big-isps-will-back-net-neutrality-someday/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t want Barack Obama regulating the internet.
At the same time, conservatives who believe big corporations are always right better pop their heads out of their Chambers of Commerce.
Greens Didn&amp;rsquo;t Kill the Incandescent Light Bulb—Corporatists Did The way big businesses got big and stayed big has nothing to do with business and everything to do with politics. Big corporations use their money and influence to bribe government to kill competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rex Sinquefield Buys High-Priced Call Guv</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/23/rex-sinquefield-buys-high-priced-call-guv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 22:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/23/rex-sinquefield-buys-high-priced-call-guv/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_15564&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]Rex Sinquefield&amp;rsquo;s Mad Scientist Blimp-Piloting X-Ray Glasses.[/caption]
The billionaire with the great big blimp buys another politician.
After a raising a measely $66k in campaign contributions, Catherine Hanaway sold her soul to wierd billionaire Rex Sinquefield. The price? $750,000 down plus $10,000 a week through the election.
With Rex, nothing is ever what it appears.
You might know thatRex is tight with Missouri Attorney General Chris Koster, a Democrat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failed Consultant Seeks Funding for GOP Establishment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/22/failed-consultant-seeks-funding-gop-establishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2014 22:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/22/failed-consultant-seeks-funding-gop-establishment/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_15564&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]Rex Sinquefield&amp;rsquo;s Mad Scientist Blimp Piloting X-Ray Glasses[/caption]
People tell me Republican consultant John Hancock is a really nice guy.
I think they&amp;rsquo;re right. And, as Hancock&amp;rsquo;s clients have learned repeatedly, nice guys finish last.
The clearest example of Hancock&amp;rsquo;s failure was John Brunner&amp;rsquo;s campaign for US Senate in 2012.
Brunner is an exceptional businessman with a remarkably clear and accurate political philosophy. Had Brunner succeeded in winning the GOP nomination for Senate, Claire McCaskill would be retired, the GOP would have a Senate majority already, and Rand Paul would have a philosophical friend in the upper chamber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Is For Sale. Here&#39;s Who&#39;s Buying</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/21/congress-is-for-sale-heres-whos-buying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2014 03:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/21/congress-is-for-sale-heres-whos-buying/</guid>
      <description>_Updated: the original title said &amp;ldquo;Congress is for sale.&amp;rdquo; My mistake. I meant Government. _
Once upon a time in America, people built companies by filling society&amp;rsquo;s unmet needs. To survive, a company relied on innovation, quality, and, of course, good advertising. The best advertisement being word of mouth.
That&amp;rsquo;s all changed now.
The way to grow a successful company is to get government to protect your market, dampen competition, and require people to buy what you sell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Not Pro-Immigrant; It&#39;s Anti-American</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/20/not-pro-immigrant-anti-american/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 11:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/20/not-pro-immigrant-anti-american/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s be honest with ourselves: President Obama&amp;rsquo;s unilateral, dictatorial action on immigration is not to benefit illegals. It&amp;rsquo;s to punish American voters for rejecting him.
This is personal.
In two years, the next American president will let this and many other Obama executive orders expire. Executive orders are not law. They expire with the term of the president who signed them. No future president is bound to renew them. And the next president won&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Governors</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/05/governors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 14:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/05/governors/</guid>
      <description>Governors
Republicans were supposed to lose governor seats. Instead, they picked up nine or ten. That&amp;rsquo;s huge, because governors become presidents. Executive leadership is different from coalition &amp;ldquo;leadership,&amp;rdquo; and governors are real executives. Look for the GOP&amp;rsquo;s gubernatorial wins to play big roles in 2016 and 2020.
This Morning (New York Times):
 Democrats seem to have their best shot in Florida, where the state’s former Republican governor, Charlie Crist, is running as a Democrat against the Republican incumbent, Rick Scott.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You, Heritage Foundation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/30/thank-heritage-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/30/thank-heritage-foundation/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sitting at Reagan National Airport waiting for my flight home. I just spent 24 hours meeting the people who keep America free. Well, besides the people in uniform. It&amp;rsquo;s the Heritage Foundation&amp;rsquo;s donors and leaders. It&amp;rsquo;s Heritage Action and its Sentinels.
It&amp;rsquo;s decidedly NOT the ruling class, the two big parties.
I had the high privilege of sharing a panel with 14 people who work a lot harder than I do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Have Just One Chance for October Surprise</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 16:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</guid>
      <description>The White House and its corrupt Department of Justice has one chance to change the election&amp;rsquo;s outcome.According to Nate Silver&amp;rsquo;s FiveThirtyEight blog, the GOP has a 62.1 percent chance of a Senate majority. With nine days left until the election, and with President Obama&amp;rsquo;s approval and likability plunging, the Democrats face a huge loss.
Apathetic Democrats Many political observers blame Democrat voter apathy, particularly among African-Americans. The black vote that swelled in 2008 and 2012 with Obama on the ballot shows signs of deflating in 2014 as it did in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatever Happened to the Party of Ideas?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</guid>
      <description>From about 1978 until the Monica Lewinsky fiasco, the GOP was called &amp;ldquo;the party of ideas.&amp;rdquo; I miss the ideas.
William F. Buckley helped. Buckley liked big ideas and smart people. He liked politicians who gave legs to great ideas and governors with the guts to experiment. Governor Ronald Reagan appeared on Buckley&amp;rsquo;s Firing Line shortly after the Gipper became California&amp;rsquo;s governor. Reagan talked about many ideas he was trying or hoping to try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Interrupt This Program . . . </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/02/interrupt-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 05:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/02/interrupt-program/</guid>
      <description>I am scaling back my blogging.
I spend about 1-2 hours on most posts. That&amp;rsquo;s writing, researching, photo editing, etc. It&amp;rsquo;s time consuming. It&amp;rsquo;s also worth the effort.
Blogging is an opportunity cost, too. Every hour I spend blogging is an hour I&amp;rsquo;m not doing anything else. The things I&amp;rsquo;m not doing include:
** admiring my wife ** talking to my kids ** catching up with friends ** advancing my career ** cleaning up my office ** changing my underwear ** cheering on the Blues (or Cardinals or Rams) ** working out ** washing my car ** fixing that door that doesn&amp;rsquo;t open right ** training my dogs to make a proper CC and club soda ** paying bills ** answering emails ** blowing the leaves out of the garage ** hunting copperheads and rattlesnakes (we have both out here) ** visiting my parents</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Can I Possibly Vote for Rick Stream for County Executive?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/30/vote-rick-stream-county-exec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 21:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/30/vote-rick-stream-county-exec/</guid>
      <description>Maybe this logic sucks, but this is my logic. When I vote, I ignore my positions on issues. Instead, I use my vote to advance two objectives:
*1. I want my vote to improve policy towards liberty. *2. I want my vote to maximize my political power.
A simple test that I ask myself is this: If I vote for A, do I expect resulting policy to be more or less to my liking?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Diehl Doesn&#39;t Want You to Know There&#39;s a Big Press Conference Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/29/john-diehl-doesnt-want-know-theres-big-press-conference-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 23:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/29/john-diehl-doesnt-want-know-theres-big-press-conference-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>My phone and inbox lit up all morning.
Missouri Republicans are FREAKING OUT that Speaker Apparent John Diehl could go down to defeat at the hands of conservative/libertarian grassroots activists. The freak-out is over a press conference in Queeny Park at 10:00 a.m. on Tuesday, September 30.
[map]
I heard of the Stop Diehl project last week. On Saturday, mostly Republican volunteers began a door-to-door campaign in Diehl&amp;rsquo;s district to block re-election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rick Stream Probably Didn&#39;t Know I Knew His Old Career Counselor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/28/rick-stream-probably-didnt-know-knew-old-transition-counselor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 21:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/28/rick-stream-probably-didnt-know-knew-old-transition-counselor/</guid>
      <description>When people asked me to get behind Rick Stream, I first wanted to make sure that was the right thing. I remembered that I have a friend who helped Rick a while ago. So I asked her.
Rick Stream is &amp;ldquo;a quiet leader.&amp;quot;
&amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t see him as a politician,&amp;rdquo; she told me. We were talking about Rick Stream, the candidate for St. Louis County Executive.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_15477&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] Representative Rick Stream (R-Kirkwood) chairs the House Appropriations Committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Ann Wagner Is Wrong to Attack Heritage Action</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 02:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</guid>
      <description>Accountability? We don&amp;rsquo;t need no stinking accountability.
 No, Ann Wagner didn&amp;rsquo;t actually say that. But her comments to a 2nd District Republican committee meeting on Tuesday gave at least one attendee the impression that Mrs. Wagner opposes the idea of conservatives holding Congress accountable.
Ann Wagner Attacks the Conservative Heritage Action Rep. Ann Wagner accused the conservative Heritage Action for America of &amp;ldquo;pitting Republican against Republican&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;never attacking Dems&amp;rdquo; at the Republican meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Vote for Libertarian Bill Slantz for Congress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/23/will-vote-libertarian-bill-slantz-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 02:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/23/will-vote-libertarian-bill-slantz-congress/</guid>
      <description>Libertarians want to take over the world and leave you alone.
What a refreshing ambition!
A couple days ago, I wrote that I will not vote for Ann Wagner&amp;rsquo;s re-election in 2014. I arrived at that position after realizing that Mrs. Wagner and I share incompatible, mutually exclusive views on the proper relationship between government and people. She believes government should run markets. I believe government should make sure markets are fair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beware Republicans Offering to &#34;Clear the Decks&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/23/beware-republicans-offering-clear-decks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 09:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/23/beware-republicans-offering-clear-decks/</guid>
      <description>Why did the chicken cross the road?
 To get to the lame duck.
You can&amp;rsquo;t trust the GOP establishment.
In case you missed it, the House GOP leadership pushed a Continuing Resolution to fund government through December. Now, these same GOP leaders will tell you they expect Republicans to take over the Senate in January. So why would they give Harry Reid a chance to use the lame duck Congress in December to pass an Obama-friendly long term CR?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Will Not Vote for Ann Wagner in 2014</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/21/will-not-vote-for-wagner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/21/will-not-vote-for-wagner/</guid>
      <description>There is a tide in the affairs of men. Which, taken at the flood, leads on to fortune; Omitted, all the voyage of their life Is bound in shallows and in miseries. On such a full sea are we now afloat, And we must take the current when it serves, Or lose our ventures.
 Julius Caesar Act 4, scene 3, 218–224
 The problem the Republican Party has, too many people are sitting around, waiting for a wave to take them across the election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Are the Ex-Im Facts Ann Wagner and Claire McCaskill Don&#39;t Want You to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/10/heres-ex-im-facts-ann-wagner-claire-mccaskill-wont-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 23:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/10/heres-ex-im-facts-ann-wagner-claire-mccaskill-wont-tell/</guid>
      <description>Rep. Ann Wagner&amp;rsquo;s Heritage Action Score is a disappointing 59. It&amp;rsquo;s about to drop even lower.
Last week, the Republican from Missouri&amp;rsquo;s 2nd Congressional District came out strongly in support of cronyism by endorsing and vowing to fight for extending the Export-Import Bank.
From Wagner&amp;rsquo;s interview with National Public Radio:
 “There is some talk about a short-term reauthorization, perhaps six or seven months on Ex-Im,” she said. “I’d like it to be longer than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Municipal Courts Matter to Liberty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 03:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</guid>
      <description>I am embarrassed.
I am embarrassed that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about this problem sooner. Or I heard about it and ignored it, which is even worse. Maybe I thought it was just the usual liberal whining about trumped up racial problems. Whatever, I should have listened.
On September 2, I asked a room of about 30 tea partiers, &amp;ldquo;Do you trust our justice system?&amp;rdquo; I heard a chorus of &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Ruin a Perfectly Good Joke</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/03/ruin-perfectly-good-joke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 04:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/03/ruin-perfectly-good-joke/</guid>
      <description>If you talk long enough, you can butcher the best joke in the world&amp;ndash;even the one from Monty Python that the Allies used to win WWII.
https://youtu.be/ienp4J3pW7U
Tuesday night at a Tea Party meeting, I managed to destroy a joke of my own, poor making, and insult a friend at the same time. That takes talent. Or . . . something.
So, first, let me apologize to Adam Sharp, the best indy video journalist alive, since he was the victim of my horrible comedic delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where I&#39;m Kicking Off My Ferguson BUYcott Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/29/im-kicking-ferguson-buycott-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 23:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/29/im-kicking-ferguson-buycott-saturday/</guid>
      <description>At 1:00 PM, I&amp;rsquo;ll be at 911 Beauty Salon: 9193 W Florissant Ave, St Louis, MO 63136, Cross Streets: Between Ferguson Ave and Canfield Dr. Let us knowyour story here. Upload photos, reciepts, and stories. People love stories.
You are welcome to join me there at 1:00, or shop and dine on your own.

This Ferguson BUYcott is getting massive national attention. Big thanks to everyone who took part last week and who&amp;rsquo;s joining in this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Would Like to Talk to You on Tuesday September 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/28/like-talk-talk-tuesday-september-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 03:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/28/like-talk-talk-tuesday-september-2/</guid>
      <description>Hi. Bill Hennessy here. If you can, please stop by 111 Clarkson Executive Park, Ellisville, MO 63011 on Tuesday, September 2 at 7 p.m. (RSVP Here if you&amp;rsquo;d like.)
I have something I&amp;rsquo;d like to talk to you about. It&amp;rsquo;s about the tea party movement. But it&amp;rsquo;s really about understanding two very important concepts:
*1. Living to our purpose. *2. Doing what&amp;rsquo;s important.
This is not a training session. It&amp;rsquo;s not an After Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Ferguson and Dellwood This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 04:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I&amp;rsquo;m so late on this. This sounds whiny, I know, but I have a really involved week at work this week. Sorry. Crap always seems to work out this way, though. When there&amp;rsquo;s a great need for Tea Party services, I&amp;rsquo;m tied up with work obligations. Something has to give, and it&amp;rsquo;s usually the thing that doesn&amp;rsquo;t generate revenue.
But we all have work to do. Ferguson businesses and families are still struggling with the effects of the riots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bureaucratizing Street Gangs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/26/bureaucratizing-street-gangs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/26/bureaucratizing-street-gangs/</guid>
      <description>Did you ever wonder why do-gooders and social planners never pay for their crimes?
Yesterday, I wrote about Jesse Jackson dressing down at the hands of activists in a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s parking lot in Ferguson. I pointed out that Martin Luther King and Dick Gregory were similarly dismissed by rioters in the 1960s. Some things never change.
One thing that has changed is the economic gap between whites and blacks. That&amp;rsquo;s gotten worse despite trillions in federal poverty programs that went mostly to &amp;ldquo;community organizing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exposing the Race Hustlers in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/25/exposing-race-hustlers-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 21:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/25/exposing-race-hustlers-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s an awesome YouTube video of Jesse Jackson getting skewered in Ferguson.
First, though, a little history.
One of the greatest books ever on race-based poverty and jobs programs is Tom Wolfe&amp;rsquo;s Mau-Mauing the Flak-Catchers. You won&amp;rsquo;t understand race politics in America without reading it. Twice. Four times, maybe.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve read it, you know why Jesse Jackson and Capt. Ron Johnson and all the other &amp;ldquo;black leaders&amp;rdquo; are impotent to stop riots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Jay Nixon Lost the Liberal Press</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/24/jay-nixon-lost-liberal-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/24/jay-nixon-lost-liberal-press/</guid>
      <description>“And then say what? say, ‘forget you’re hungry, forget you got shot inna back by some racist cop—Chuck was here? Chuck come up to Harlem—’ ”“No, I’ll tell you what—” “‘Chuck come up to Harlem and—’ ”“I’ll tell you what—” “Say,‘Chuck come up to Harlem and gonna take care a business for the black community’?” That does it. Heh-heggggggggggggggggghhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! It’s one of those ungodly contralto cackles somewhere out there in the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**DOH!** ACTION: Tell Missouri Legislature Jay Nixon to Pass Tax Holiday for Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 20:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>****UPDATE
Tim Jones let me know that I&amp;rsquo;m giving the legislature more power than it actually has.
Veto sessions are limited to overriding vetos. Thus the name. BUT the governor can call a Special Session to vote on a Ferguson Tax Holiday. That session can run concurrent with the Veto Session, saving taxpayer dollars.
SO &amp;gt; &amp;gt; &amp;gt; New Action: Ask Jay Nixon (via Twitter and Facebook) to call a Special Session concurrent with the Veto Session to create a Tax Holiday for Ferguson/Dellwood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why St. Louis Tea Party Went to Ferguson To Shop</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/why-st-louis-tea-party-went-to-ferguson-to-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 04:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/why-st-louis-tea-party-went-to-ferguson-to-shop/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;rsquo;t change the world in your living room.
That&amp;rsquo;s why a small band of (mostly) white people from (mostly) West County drove to Ferguson (and Dellwood) to shop tonight.
We targeted the small businesses that were hit hard by violence&amp;ndash;violence committed (mostly) by out of town agitators, criminals, vandals, and hooligans.
We drove to Ferguson to make two statements with our actons: 1) Ferguson is OUR community, and 2) Ferguson is open for business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Export-Import Bank Story the Post-Dispatch Refused to Print</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/export-import-bank-story-post-dispatch-refused-print/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 21:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/export-import-bank-story-post-dispatch-refused-print/</guid>
      <description>Since the Post won&amp;rsquo;t run my reply a recent op-ed about the Ex-Im Bank, I&amp;rsquo;ll publish it here:
Huge multi-national corporations like to preach from the &amp;ldquo;small business&amp;rdquo; bible when it comes to the Export-Import bank. Unfortunately, most of the Ex-Im propaganda about how &amp;ldquo;small business&amp;rdquo; benefits crumbles under scrutiny.
Professor Stanford Levin of Southern Illinois University recently wrote an Op-Ed supporting reauthorization of the Export Import Bank. As the professor states, the Export-Import Bank provides cheap loans to foreign companies and governments with which to buy products sold by mostly large, multi-national companies with headquarters in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferguson Shopping Ideas</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/ferguson-shopping-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/ferguson-shopping-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Here are some businesses people should frequent:
Eat at Sweetie Pies on W. Florrisant, or head to Paul’s Market on Elizabeth, Drive down N./S. Florrisant for Shop-n-Save, Chinese Food, local eats, bakeries, dollar tree, etc. Ferguson also extends to New Halls Ferry and 270, where there is a Home Depot, another Shop-n-Save, Party store, UPS store, and more. https://livewellferguson.com/main/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/FergusonMap5-1.jpg
Also, there is Ferguson Bike shop, The Whistle Stop, and Sportsprint (where you might find an I heart Ferguson shirt).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Municipal Court or Kangaroo Court?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/20/municipal-court-kangaroo-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 22:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/20/municipal-court-kangaroo-court/</guid>
      <description>Guest post by Lee A. Presser
On Wednesday, April 16, 2003, I was in Bel-Ridge, Missouri, Municipal Court to plead “not guilty.” The violation listed on the ticket did not match the reality of what actually happened on the road. In a file folder, I had documents and photographs to rebut the charge. The ticket stated that Court convened at 6:30 P.M. I arrived twenty minutes early.
Before 9:30 that evening, I had been tightly handcuffed twice, verbally abused by police, pushed into a depressing detention cell, and made an example of in front of seventy-five to one hundred people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important Updates on Ferguson BUYcott</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/important-updates-ferguson-buycott/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 04:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/important-updates-ferguson-buycott/</guid>
      <description>Including muster time and location, rules of conduct, and a little story about smiling.
CLICK HERE
I&amp;rsquo;ll be on Jamie in the Morning at 6:10 a.m. today, Wednesday, August 20 on FM 97.1. Please listen.
Thanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Hard to Deny North County Has Problems with Police and Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>What did you think when you first heard reports of violence in Ferguson? I mean, after the shooting death of Michael Brown?
Did you ever for a moment think, &amp;ldquo;this is about more than just Michael Brown?&amp;rdquo;
I hate to say that. It&amp;rsquo;s embarrassing to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m so jaded as to think &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;rdquo; when a young man dies. Sorry. I&amp;rsquo;m just being honest.
I understand community grief and anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUYcott Ferguson **UPDATE** DETAILS ** MORE UPDATES</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/18/buycott-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 04:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/18/buycott-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>DON&amp;rsquo;T STOP SHOPPING!
The Buycott is underway. Great turnout on Thursday. Fantastic support from the media. Even Senator Claire McCaskill joined the buycott. Read all about it here.
In the meantime, keep shopping Ferguson/Dellwood if you get the chance. And make an appointment on your calendar to shop Ferguson/Dellwood on Labor Day Weekend. Have out-of-town guests? Take them on a tour and have a meal in one of the great restaurants in the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferguson is the Canary in the Coal Mine&#34; for St. Louis County</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/18/ferguson-canary-coal-mine-st-louis-county/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 21:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/18/ferguson-canary-coal-mine-st-louis-county/</guid>
      <description>The next St. Louis County Executive better brace himself for this: poverty is exploding in the county.
I&amp;rsquo;m not saying poor people do bad things. I&amp;rsquo;m saying that, at some point, eliminating jobs and hope will drive people to take things. And they will take things by force. And they will show no mercy to anyone who tries to get in their way.
Right or wrong, it happens. And no militarized police force will stop it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Create Hate and Discontent in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/17/create-hate-discontent-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 18:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/17/create-hate-discontent-america/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t written about Ferguson because I&amp;rsquo;ve known too little to add value. But ignorance hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped others from stirring up hate and discontent. For example, Missouri&amp;rsquo;s shakedown artist, Lacy Clay.
Lacy Clay, speaking from a private island in the Carribean, told the St. Louis Post-Dispatch that Michael Brown was murdered. Clay knew or should have known the effect of his words: more violence. Either Clay meant to incite violence or he has a casual disregard for the effect of his irresponsible speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What If We Stopped Shouting?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/14/stopped-shouting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/14/stopped-shouting/</guid>
      <description>I shout a lot.
Not with my lungs. With my pen. Well, not a pen, actually. With a wireless Bluetooth keyboard.
A few years ago, I shouted with my lungs at Tea Party events. I realized pretty quickly that shouting wasn&amp;rsquo;t doing any good. It worked at first. Shouting carried my voice to people who thought &amp;ldquo;no one believes what I believe.&amp;rdquo; Some people heard me yelling at the Arch and came out to see what the hell was going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insane: Stocks Markets Rally On Economic Disasters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/14/insane-stocks-markets-rally-economic-disasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 11:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/14/insane-stocks-markets-rally-economic-disasters/</guid>
      <description>Eurozone&amp;rsquo;s economy is basically in recession.
Walmart lowered expectations. Again.
The world is teetering on the edge of World War.
The US is launching Iraq War 3.0: Mission Accomplished Accomplished.
Germany&amp;rsquo;s economy is flat, and Italy and France are getting worse.
Risk is high.
Corporate debt is staggering.
The Fed&amp;rsquo;s balance sheet is a sea of monetized debt.
The central banks have nothing left to fix another crash.
And the stock markets are rocketing to record highs because of all this news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Might Be Doing Criminal Trials Backwards</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/13/might-criminal-trials-backwards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 21:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/13/might-criminal-trials-backwards/</guid>
      <description>Is it possible that we do criminal trials backwards?
In the United States, criminal trials have two parts:
*1. Determination of guilt or innocence *2. Determination of penalty
Does that make sense?
What if we did it the other way around? What if, first, the prosecutor and defense attorney had to convince the judge or jury of the appropriate punishment for the crime in question. In this phase, the state would present the facts of the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Justify the Death Penalty?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/12/justify-death-penalty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/12/justify-death-penalty/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not being judgmental or rhetorical with that title. I&amp;rsquo;m curious how other people deal with capital punishment.
Here&amp;rsquo; my story:
Once upon a time, I advocated for the death penalty. Loudly. Shrilly, at times.
In the 1980s and into 1990s, I read a lot. Philosophical. Religious. Legal. Historical. Lots of angles, but few perspectives. You see, I sought out confirming information. I searched high and low for perspectives that would justify my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is The Tea Party Suffering From Republican Fatigue Syndrome?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/11/tea-party-republican-fatigue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 21:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/11/tea-party-republican-fatigue/</guid>
      <description>Maybe the chickens are coming home to roost for the GOP in St. Louis County.
In my day job, I focus on two subjects: strategic behavioral science and analytics. Really smart people do most of the heavy analytics work. I deal with the human behavior (neuroeconomics, psychology, etc.). In our narrow field of loyalty and motivation, I think we&amp;rsquo;re the best in the business. Not me, but the people I work with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Simple Questions for Chairman Priebus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/11/3-simple-questions-chairman-priebus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/11/3-simple-questions-chairman-priebus/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, I raised a concern about Erick Erickson&amp;rsquo;s handling of Reince Priebus at Erickson&amp;rsquo;s annual RedState Gathering.
Today, Erick responded to widespread criticism of his decision to protect the GOP Chairman from questions about tactics in the Mississippi Republican Senate Runoff. Here&amp;rsquo;s the heart of Erickson&amp;rsquo;s answer:
 But there was more to it than me knowing people would be angry about Mississippi. First, many of the people told me what they wanted to ask Reince.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are the Missouri August Primary results a fluke or the beginning of a trend?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/10/missouri-august-primary-results-fluke-beginning-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 21:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/10/missouri-august-primary-results-fluke-beginning-trend/</guid>
      <description>Many Republican voters pulled a Democrat ballot August 5th, in St. Louis County. Having crossed over once, how many will do it again in November? It is no secret that the Republican legislature in Jefferson City has exhibited minimal leadership on major issues while spending most of a short legislative calendar talking about issues invented by lobbyists.
Republican voters expected more.
Many St. Louis County Republican voters are baffled by the absence of political ‘guts’ displayed in Jefferson City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Erick Erickson Protecting Reince Priebus?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 22:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE:
Welcome, Donald Trump fans! Thanks for reading.
Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s true, I have had disagreements with Erick in the past. I try to assess the situation, not just the person. It&amp;rsquo;s possible to disagree with someone on one subject and to agree with them on another.
If anything, Erick showed consistency by rescinding Trump&amp;rsquo;s invitation to Red State. Erick didn&amp;rsquo;t want the event to descend into chaos led by my friends over the Barbour episode; he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a descent into chaos led by Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Number One Reason People Hate Elections</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/08/number-one-reason-people-hate-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 19:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/08/number-one-reason-people-hate-elections/</guid>
      <description>I wrote previously that I hate elections.
I have many reasons for hating elections. One reason, though, seems pretty common: horrible, insulting radio ads.
Two ads really stick out:
 The negative ad that mentions the sponsoring candidate&amp;rsquo;s opponent(s) five times as often as it mentions the candidate you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to remember at the poll. The couple having a stilted, phony conversation about the sponsoring candidate using words and interruptions that no human being ever uttered or ever will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check Out The Missouri Torch</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/08/check-missouri-torch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/08/check-missouri-torch/</guid>
      <description>If you don&amp;rsquo;t get The Missouri Torch delivered to your inbox every day, you&amp;rsquo;re missing out.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_15201&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;1000&amp;rdquo;] Duane Lester&amp;rsquo;s Missouri Torch. www.themissouritorch.com[/caption]
Duane Lester has built a fantastic blog. The Missouri Torch captures the most important Missouri political news every day and sends you a convenient link list.
Plus, Duane&amp;rsquo;s original pieces are crisp, smart, witty, and dead on. And, like Rush Limbaugh, Duane is almost always right 99.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri&#39;s Legislature Can Increase Highway Funds</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/07/missouris-legislature-can-increase-highway-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 21:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/07/missouris-legislature-can-increase-highway-funds/</guid>
      <description>Now that Amendment 7 has gone down in flames, let&amp;rsquo;s look at highway funding in Missouri.
Amendment 7 would have authorized a 3/4 cent sales tax increase in Missouri. The money was intended for transportation in the broadest sense of the word. Parks with dirt paths qualify, since people can walk on the paths. Even if the bill tightened down the definition of transportation, municipalities and counties would have merely shifted funds to other projects and replaced that money with Amendment 7 taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin Moves to Censure Henry Barbour Over Racist Mississippi Ads</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/ed-martin-moves-censure-henry-barbour-racist-mississippi-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 04:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/ed-martin-moves-censure-henry-barbour-racist-mississippi-ads/</guid>
      <description>Go Ed!
A few weeks ago, hunkered down at my laptop in my hotel room in Jacksonville, Florida. I was exhausted from seven hours of travel and a time change. But I had to take a moment to recognize Ed Martin&amp;rsquo;s commitment to all the best the Republican Party stands for.
Ed is determined to expose the GOP establishment&amp;rsquo;s willingness to do anything to destroy grassroots insurgents. Thad Cochran&amp;rsquo;s forces in Mississippi threw ethics, morality, and decency to the wind in their quest to stop a Tea Party candidate from unseating the 128-term Cochran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Fascinating Results In The Missouri Primary</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/10-curious-results-missouri-primary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/10-curious-results-missouri-primary/</guid>
      <description>CORRECTION: My sincerest apologies for an inexcusable error in this post earlier. I erroneously congratulated my friend Martin Baker in the US House 1st District primary. I understand that Martin was about 500 votes short. I failed to verify information I received on the race, and I apologize for my irresponsibility.
Well, this got people talking. (See the comments.)
Yesterday was the Missouri Primary. Congratulations to Rick Stream and Jay Ashcrofton their wins in contested races for St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the Hell Is Up In Missouri&#39;s 2nd Congressional District?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/05/hell-missouris-2nd-congressional-district/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 04:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/05/hell-missouris-2nd-congressional-district/</guid>
      <description>No time for deep analysis tonight, but there&amp;rsquo;s a small political earthquake in St. Louis County.
With over 90% of the precincts counted in the Missouri primary, incumbent Congresswoman Ann Wagner has only 500 more votes than her November challenger, Democrat Arthur Lieber.

I get that this is a primary and that the St. Louis County Executive race drew a lot of attention. But Wagner won her seat in 2012 by 20 points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Obama&#39;s Dictates Force Eureka High PTO To Beg</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/04/michelle-obamas-dictates-force-eureka-high-pto-beg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 21:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/04/michelle-obamas-dictates-force-eureka-high-pto-beg/</guid>
      <description>When did first ladies become dictators?
Seriously. The president&amp;rsquo;s family has no more authority than anyone else. The reason people show contempt for activist spouses of presidents is the same reason history hates Marie Antoinette.
I know, the all-Democrat Congress passed the school nutrition law in 2010, but Michelle Obama wrote it.
Michelle Obama has dictated that no tasty foods may enter any school property. That ban includes school bake sales and snack shops which has PTOs scrambling to replace lost income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Biggest Regret of the Tea Party Movement</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/03/biggest-regret-tea-party-movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 15:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/03/biggest-regret-tea-party-movement/</guid>
      <description>It was 2010. St. Louis was the epicenter of the Tea Party movement.
Tea Party Patriots picked St. Louis to host the Gateway to November rally under the Arch. Unlike our rag-tag events, this one would be professional all the way: live music with Sounding Fathers, speakers you heard of before the movement began in February 2009, and real security.
The guest speakers began rolling into town on Friday the tenth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Governance Is the Best Kept Secret in the Fight for Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/02/best-kept-secret-fight-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 03:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/02/best-kept-secret-fight-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to MOPP for this fantastic summary for Center for Self-Governance training opportunities in the show me state. Includes links to enroll in class.
FYI&amp;hellip;
TO: MOPP SUPPORTERS
 MOPP COUNTY COORDINATORS
(please help spread this message by forwarding to your Missouri contacts/networks/thanks!)
**_ _**
**_ _**
**_ _**Citizen involvement is “snowballing” across the State of Missouri as the Center for Self Governance adds more classes to its schedule. The ultimate goal is to have a CSG team in every county in the state in order to influence your elected officials and policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Wisconsin Police Chief Admits Illegal Harassment of Tea Party Leader, After Lying About It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/01/campbell-wisconsin-police-chief-admits-illegal-harassment-tea-party-leader-lying/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/01/campbell-wisconsin-police-chief-admits-illegal-harassment-tea-party-leader-lying/</guid>
      <description>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lbYKydZ3T0Q
The weird thing is: isn&amp;rsquo;t that Sharp Elbows questioning the Chief? When did he become a detective in Michigan?
The chief pleaded nolo contendere to identity theft charges. He presented himself as a tea party leader signing up for embarrassing, sexual email lists. From the La Crosse Tea Party:
 A shocking update to the Town of Campbell Situation this week. Detective Spencer from Monroe County Sheriff’s department called and said that Campbell Police Chief Tim Kelemen confessed to harassment/internet stalking/identity theft regarding my complaint filed to La Crosse P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s How I&#39;m Voting August 5 (with printable grid of ballot measures) *Update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/31/im-voting-august-5-primary-printable-grid-ballot-initiatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/31/im-voting-august-5-primary-printable-grid-ballot-initiatives/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think being a political animal of sorts, election season would be my favorite time of year.
It&amp;rsquo;s not. I hate elections.
I hate the crappy, predictable radio ads (above all else). I know, they do it because it works. Well, not really, but I&amp;rsquo;m not going to give a free marketing statistics lesson here. (No one has any idea if the campaign formula works, because no body ever tries anything different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Libertarian Is The New Mainstream</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/30/libertarian-new-mainstream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 21:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/30/libertarian-new-mainstream/</guid>
      <description>You don&amp;rsquo;t hear the word &amp;ldquo;mainstream&amp;rdquo; in political spin like you used to.
Back in the late 1980s when Jack Kemp, Pat Robertson, Pete DuPont, Al Haig, and George H. W. Bush were battling to replace
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_15090&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] 1988 Republican Candidates[/caption]
Ronald Reagan, &amp;ldquo;mainstream&amp;rdquo; was in. Candidates fought for the title of &amp;ldquo;mainstream Republican,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;mainstream Conservative,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;mainstream everything.&amp;rdquo;
I&amp;rsquo;m glad that word went away. But I&amp;rsquo;m bringing it back, if only for one blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Which Freedoms Are We Losing? </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</guid>
      <description>I confess.
When I write about freedoms lost, I don&amp;rsquo;t itemize the freedoms. I don&amp;rsquo;t feel too bad, though, because almost no one does. Itemizing sucks.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s hard work. &amp;ldquo;Losing freedom,&amp;rdquo; takes about three seconds to type and less time to read. Listing freedoms,on the other hand, takes that much time just to highlight all the freedoms and click the un-ordered list button. God forbid I find myself working in straight HTML and have to hand-type &amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprised? Transportation Empowerment Act Was Ronald Reagan&#39;s Idea—In 1967!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/28/surprised-transportation-empowerment-act-ronald-reagans-idea-1967/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 21:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/28/surprised-transportation-empowerment-act-ronald-reagans-idea-1967/</guid>
      <description>Last week I blogged that Ronald Reagan would love the Transportation Empowerment Act (TEA). I included audio of Reagan talking to Bill Buckley on Firing Line about the burden on states from onerous federal taxes and grants.
Forgive me, but that was sort of a tease. Here&amp;rsquo;s the meat: Reagan wrote a proposal for the Republican Governors&amp;rsquo; Conference of 1967 to allow states to keep about 2 percent of all federal taxes raised in the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Don&#39;t Comment Today, You&#39;ll Be Deleted From Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/28/dont-comment-today-youll-deleted-hennessys-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 12:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/28/dont-comment-today-youll-deleted-hennessys-view/</guid>
      <description>If you registered as a user but never commented AND you want to continue getting an email notification when new blogs are posted, all you have to do is COMMENT on this blog. Say anything, like &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t delete me, bro.&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s why: my blog has about 8,000 registered users. That sounds great, I know, but it&amp;rsquo;s not. Most of these registered users are zombies. They were created by a spam bot so the bot could post spam comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is Rand Paul&#39;s Secret to Broadening the Republican Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/27/rand-pauls-secret-broadening-republican-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 13:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/27/rand-pauls-secret-broadening-republican-base/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever felt like tuning out, giving up, and just riding out whatever storm comes down the pipe next?
I have. Many times. Every week. Sometimes more than once a day.
I think we can both give ourselves a pass on that feeling. In fact, I think we can both give ourselves a pass on acting on that feeling. It&amp;rsquo;s okay to check out occasionally. Everyone needs a break now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Francis Slay Won&#39;t Tell You About Missouri Roads—VIDEO</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/26/francis-slay-wont-tell-missouri-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 03:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/26/francis-slay-wont-tell-missouri-roads/</guid>
      <description>Proponents of Amendment 7 are telling a lot of lies. (I&amp;rsquo;m looking at you, St. Louis Business Journal.) The biggest lie involves the quality of Missouri&amp;rsquo;s roads and bridges.
While Mayor Slay and the St. Louis Business Journal tell you Missouri&amp;rsquo;s roads are &amp;ldquo;crumbling,&amp;quot; two independent studies say the opposite. In fact, Missouri has some of the best roads in the country.
Via Show-Me Institute (h/tDarin Morley):
 We have often commented that Missouri is “middle of the pack” in various state rankings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can Reclaim the 4th Amendment the 5th of August</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/24/can-reclaim-4th-amendment-5th-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/24/can-reclaim-4th-amendment-5th-august/</guid>
      <description>Listen to my short podcast about Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Constitutional Amendment, Amendment 9&amp;ndash;the Electronic Data Protection Act.
[audio mp3=&amp;quot;https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/HennessyView_20140714.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
And don&amp;rsquo;t forget to vote YES on Amendment 9. Restore the4th Amendment.
You can read more about Amendment 9 on Ballotpedia.
And here&amp;rsquo;s the Missouri ACLU&amp;rsquo;s page on Amendment 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Wasn&#39;t Reagan&#39;s 11th Commandment, and He Didn&#39;t Obey It Anyway</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/20/15001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 01:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/20/15001/</guid>
      <description>When a Republican invokes “Reagan’s Sacred and Holy and Inviolable Eleventh Commandment,” (in nomine Patris et Filii et Spritus Sancti, Amen), you can rest assured you&amp;rsquo;re witnessing a frightened establishment type trying get himself out of trouble.
It’s actually comical to watch these guys: shaking with rage, forcing one of those pained, contraindicative grins as they wag a hostile finger at a woman a quarter their size. “Thou shalt NOT speak ill of a fellow Republican!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be President When Russia Goes Berserk Starring Ronald Reagan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 03:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</guid>
      <description>Since the scrawny punk from Chicago still hasn&amp;rsquo;t figured it out, this President 101 lesson delivered without further comment:
https://youtu.be/9VA4W1wDMAk?t=18s
Previously on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View:
We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14949&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]&amp;ldquo;What, me worry?&amp;quot;[/caption]
Russian troops or Russian proxies murdered 293 people, today, including 23 Americans by many reports.
Israel was forced to invade Gaza to destroy tunnels Hamas uses to invade Israel and murder children.
The world teeters on the brink of all-out war.
But the President refused to cancel partisan fundraising efforts tonight.
Via The Blaze:
 At 2:25 p.m., the White House press office e-mailed a response to an inquiry from TheBlaze, “No scheduling changes to be reported at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashcroft Passes on Opportunity to Deny Medicaid Expansion Fix</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/16/ashcroft-passes-opportunity-deny-medicaid-expansion-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 02:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/16/ashcroft-passes-opportunity-deny-medicaid-expansion-fix/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I wrote about the Missouri Republican Establishment&amp;rsquo;s plan to win a windfall for lobbyist Kit Bond via Senate candidate Jay Ashcroft. Not that the Establishment cares about Bond, but they want Medicaid expansion passed before they beg for money for 2016 from the Missouri Hospital Association and Chamber of Commerce.
Well, the St. Louis Post Dispatch asked Ashcroft about the deal, and he couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite bring himself to deny that he would pass Medicaid expansion if elected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francis Slay Destroys the Transportation Sales Tax Trying to Support It **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/15/francis-slay-destroys-transportation-sales-tax-trying-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 02:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/15/francis-slay-destroys-transportation-sales-tax-trying-support/</guid>
      <description>Doesn&amp;rsquo;t it suck when Jay Nixon and Francis Slay get on opposite sides of an issue?
Where do we go?
They&amp;rsquo;re on opposite sides of Amendment 7, the largest tax increase in Missouri history. And you need to choose a side before August 5, because the ball&amp;rsquo;s in the voters&amp;rsquo; court.
But there&amp;rsquo;s no need to fear; Hennessy is here. And I heard Francis the talking Mayor on KMOX this morning (or maybe it was yesterday) talking about how much he loves, Loves, LOVES the 3/4 cent sales tax increase theoretically for transportation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: Ronald Reagan Wants the Transportation Empowerment Act</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/13/ronald-reagan-wants-transportation-empowerment-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 13:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/13/ronald-reagan-wants-transportation-empowerment-act/</guid>
      <description>Want to fix Missouri&amp;rsquo;s roads and cut taxes at the same time? Well, two American conservative icons showed us the way almost 50 years ago.
The Establishment likes to attack grassroots conservatives by claiming Reagan would have opposed the Tea Party. They&amp;rsquo;re wrong, of course, and the Transportation Empowerment Act tells us why.
In 1967, shortly after Ronald Reagan became governor of California, William F. Buckley Jr. asked Governor Reagan if was even possible to be an effective governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chairman Ed Martin Demands Mississippi Investigation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/09/chairman-ed-martin-demands-mississippi-investigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 04:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/09/chairman-ed-martin-demands-mississippi-investigation/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m on the road this week, but I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to get this email from Missouri GOP Chairman Ed Martin:
   Over the past few days, I have reached out to many but not all of you about some of what MissouriRepublicans were asking about re Mississippi especially about the racially divisive ads run in support of Senator Cochran.
 Many of you gave me good advice, some were silent, and I got lots of input from Mississippi too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Katrina</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/09/obamas-katrina/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 03:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/09/obamas-katrina/</guid>
      <description>Visuals: Some of the thousands of children suffering in a humanitarian disaster at the US border on the top of the split screen. On the bottom, President Obama drinking beer and shooting pool with locals 246 miles away.

Audio: President on deploying National Guard to alleviate humanitarian crisis: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to consider it,&amp;rdquo; but it would be &amp;ldquo;a temporary solution.&amp;rdquo;
Face it: the press was going to blame George Bush for Katrina no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am a Right-Leaning Libertarian</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/08/right-leaning-libertarian/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 21:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/08/right-leaning-libertarian/</guid>
      <description>What political label do you give yourself?
Yesterday, I blogged about calling myself a Republican. I was a kid.
Then, from about 1996 on, I called myself a conservative.
Over the past year or so, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken on the label of libertarian. Now, a simple online test confirms that I&amp;rsquo;m a right-leaning conservative. [Take the test yourself]
That&amp;rsquo;s exciting, because I feel like I need a new label.
Labels Matter I know there was a movement a couple of years ago to abolish political and ideological labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Irrefutable Definition of Leadership from Tom Landry</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/07/one-irrefutable-definition-leadership-tom-landry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 23:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/07/one-irrefutable-definition-leadership-tom-landry/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s funny, really, that America celebrates the day we signed up to fight a brutal war for independence, not the day that war was won.
But I want to write about football.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always hated the Dallas Cowboys.
Cut me a little slack, though. I was a Big Red fan from childhood, and a season ticket holder from 1978 to 1983. (&amp;ldquo;Big Red&amp;rdquo; refers to the St. Louis Football Cardinals for those of you under 40.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thad Cochran&#39;s Pyrrhic Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/06/thad-cochran-mortally-wound-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 21:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/06/thad-cochran-mortally-wound-gop/</guid>
      <description>A Pyrrhic victory is a victory with such a devastating cost that it is tantamount to defeat. Someone who wins a Pyrrhic victory has been victorious in some way; however, the heavy toll negates any sense of achievement or profit (another term for this would be &amp;ldquo;hollow victory&amp;rdquo;).
 — from Wikipedia
I keep some things in a little box in my bedroom. Some Navy and submarine mementos, some letters, favorite photos of the kids that mean things only to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Saw Dinesh D&#39;Souza&#39;s America So Now You Have To</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/05/saw-dinesh-dsouzas-america-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 18:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/05/saw-dinesh-dsouzas-america-now/</guid>
      <description>What if America didn&amp;rsquo;t exist?

That&amp;rsquo;s the premise of Dinesh D&amp;rsquo;Souza&amp;rsquo;s new movie America: Imagine the world without her. (Find a theatre near you.)
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vyD13lvE_U0
Last Wednesday, my wife took Samantha, Jordan, and me to see the movie to kick off Independence Day weekend. Even without the movie, this July 4th was special for me. My son, Jack, re-enlisted in the US Navy on board the USS Missouri in Pearl Harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Awesome Military Stories for Independence Day Weekend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/05/awesome-video-us-army-sergeant-tells-iraqi-police-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 17:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/05/awesome-video-us-army-sergeant-tells-iraqi-police-way/</guid>
      <description>I love this video. And I&amp;rsquo;m going to ask you a small favor for my son Jack, so please read all.
WARNING: Strong Language
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cj6AXvkBnv4
What&amp;rsquo;s So Great About It? You have to love this American Army sergeant telling the Iraqi police how it is in strong language. Perhaps if the Iraqi police had listened, they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be defending Baghdad against the Islamic State right now.
But they are.
I know some of you might object to this sergeant&amp;rsquo;s direct assault on these men&amp;rsquo;s manhood and character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chamber Royale</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/04/chamber-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 16:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/04/chamber-royale/</guid>
      <description>Lynd: So as charming as you are, Mister Bond, I&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping my eye on the government&amp;rsquo;s money and off your perfectly formed arse.
 Bond: You noticed.
Lynd: Even accountants have imaginations.
— from Casino Royale, 2006
You have to ask &amp;ldquo;why?&amp;rdquo;
Why would national Republicans like Roy Blunt, Ann Wagner, Billy Long, and Jason Smith jump into a State Senate primary?
The race to replace Senator John Lamping in Missouri&amp;rsquo;s 24th State Senate district is attracting major attention from Missouri&amp;rsquo;s US Congress delegation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Missouri Candidates No One Told You About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/29/7-missouri-candidates-one-told/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 02:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/29/7-missouri-candidates-one-told/</guid>
      <description>How many times have you thought, &amp;ldquo;I really don&amp;rsquo;t care for the Republican, but I&amp;rsquo;ll never vote for a Democrat?&amp;rdquo;
How does that thought make you feel? Weak or strong? Impotent or powerful? Eager or dispirited?
Do you know why you feel forced to choose between the lesser of two evils?
Because you want to.
In almost every race, you have more than two choices. In the 2014 US House elections in Missouri, ballots in all eight districts will have a Libertarian or independent candidate, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Masque of the Red Death - American Style</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/28/masque-red-death-american-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 04:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/28/masque-red-death-american-style/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;Red Death&amp;rdquo; had long devastated the country. No pestilence had ever been so fatal, or so hideous. Blood was its Avatar and its seal—the redness and the horror of blood. There were sharp pains, and sudden dizziness, and then profuse bleeding at the pores, with dissolution. The scarlet stains upon the body and especially upon the face of the victim, were the pest ban which shut him out from the aid and from the sympathy of his fellow-men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not All Lies Are Meant To Fool</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/26/lies-meant-fool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 01:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/26/lies-meant-fool/</guid>
      <description>What line of work was Tony Soprano in? 
Waste management.
Did Tony Soprano expect people to believe he was in waste management?
No. Tony Soprano expected people realize he was a wise guy and treat him with due respect&amp;ndash;or what you and I call fear.
Some lies are meant to make the liar seem more successful or more talented or better than he thinks he is. Trust me, I&amp;rsquo;ve done it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Do About the New Political Dichotomy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/24/new-political-dichotomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 02:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/24/new-political-dichotomy/</guid>
      <description>What do we do with the plank?
Yesterday I wrote about a new political dichotomy in America. This new dichotomy supersedes or suspends all other political dichotomies: left vs. right, Democrat vs. Republican, etc. This new American political dichotomy is elites vs. plebeians.
Elites and Plebeians Think of elites as the people who donate lots of money and give lots of favors to the party in power in exchange for favors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New American Political Dichotomy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/24/new-american-political-dichotomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 08:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/24/new-american-political-dichotomy/</guid>
      <description>Before we get to politics, I want to tell you about a business exercise.
The Universal Veto Game  Sometimes my job as a consultant involves helping people decide what to do when no ideas have a consensus. Sure, someone in a hierarchy can dictate terms, but dictated solutions don&amp;rsquo;t really work in business. Cooperation and collaboration are too important for success, and dictated terms are usually executed half-assed.
So we play this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Crony Capitalism Spreads Bureaucracy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</guid>
      <description>St. Louisan Eric Greitens did more before graduating from college than most people do in a lifetime. And, as if to insult us all, after college, Eric became a Navy SEAL.
In his remarkable book, The Heart and the Fist: The education of a humanitarian, the making of a Navy SEAL, Greitens tells the story of a man who seems too good to be true. Seriously. And the book left me with two big impressions&amp;ndash;probably the wrong ones, but that&amp;rsquo;s how I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Crystal-Clear Images From The Republican Primary De-Cantor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/15/3-crystal-clear-images-from-the-republican-primary-de-cantor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 01:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/15/3-crystal-clear-images-from-the-republican-primary-de-cantor/</guid>
      <description>“Shellacked!”
That was the word that stuck out to me.
Eric Cantor, the Republican House Majority Leader led by 34 points according to his pollster. He lost by 10. That’s a shellacking.
Eric Cantor was the first sitting House Majority Leader ever knocked off in a primary. Cantor was also one of Wall Street’s best friends and the embodiment of crony capitalism—the disease eating the heart out of the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri Republicans Made Jay Nixon Look Like a Statesman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 01:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</guid>
      <description>You know how reckless and tone-deaf Obama is about Army deserters? Missouri&amp;rsquo;s House and Senate Republican leaders are just as clueless and irresponsible about money.
Yes, I said it: the Missouri Republican legislature is about as conservative and principled as Susan Rice on a Sunday talk show.
By going on a votes-for-cash spending spree on the last day of the General Assembly, the House and Senate handed Jay &amp;ldquo;Idiot&amp;rdquo; Nixon a PR prize worth its weight in pork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Your Calendar for June 19</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/04/mark-calendar-june-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 03:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/04/mark-calendar-june-19/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Ben Evans of Heritage Action for America and Michelle Moore of St. Louis Tea Party Coalition, you have a treat coming on June 19.

Heritage Action/St. Louis Tea Party Social: June 19 On Thursday, June 19 at 6:30pm, we will gather informally at Scarecrow in Chesterfield, 1095 Chesterfield Parkway. All are welcome. Appetizers will be provided. Come down and enjoy the company of fellow grassroots activists.
If you have friends who think Tea Partiers are &amp;ldquo;too extreme&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;racist&amp;rdquo; or whatever, bring them along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Changing My Mind About Impeaching Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/03/im-changing-mind-impeaching-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 23:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/03/im-changing-mind-impeaching-obama/</guid>
      <description>A lot of good people I know grumble that the House Republicans don&amp;rsquo;t try to impeach Obama.
I usually don&amp;rsquo;t say much in response. After the disaster of the ill-conceived Clinton impeachment fiasco,** impeachment seems like a superstition**. Like a unicorn. I think impeachment is a dangerous tool and should never be used for political purposes.
Besides, Harry Reid&amp;rsquo;s Senate wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consider articles of impeachment if they included NSA video of Obama throwing adorable, drooling toddlers off the George Washington Bridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memorial Day 2014</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/26/memorial-day-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 09:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/26/memorial-day-2014/</guid>
      <description>Not all casualties of war die in the field. Or even during hostilities.
We&amp;rsquo;ve learned that some of our warriors died because they landed on a &amp;ldquo;secret waiting list.&amp;rdquo;
Bureaucrats love pleasing their bosses. They live for it. In the case of the Veterans Administration, bureaucrats fired the final shot in the wars of at least 40 American warriors.
Sadly, the American government proved a deadlier foe than Hitler, Tito, Saddam, or bin Laden to some of our soldiers, sailors, airmen, and Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Did It Get So Late?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/24/get-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 09:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/24/get-late/</guid>
      <description>I knew it was getting late. I was leaving work, walking to my car, when I got a text message. My nephew scored two tickets to Game 2 of the Stanley Cup Playoffs.I texted my son, Patrick, to see if he was home. I planned to fly home, put on my Blues sweater, grab Patrick, and fly down to the Scot.
But Patrick didn&amp;rsquo;t need a ride or a ticket. He was already on his way to the game with a friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Cried and Made My Bed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/22/cried-made-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 01:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/22/cried-made-bed/</guid>
      <description>I cried this morning. At work. Tears of shame.
Every day when I get to work, I go through a thirty-minute routine. I write down the 3 things I want to accomplish that day. I write down my appointments. I write down a one-sentence prayer. I copy a quote to guide me. With the time remaining, I learn one new thing.
Today that one thing I learned was humbling. Shameful, actually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Happened to the Tea Party?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/21/happened-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 03:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/21/happened-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll give Business Insider some credit. After Tea Party-backed candidates came up empty across the board in Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s Republican primaries, the website that has spent years maligning our rule-of-law movement could have taken the low road.
Instead, blogger Brett Logiurato wrote a fair assessment of what&amp;rsquo;s happened to the GOP since February 27, 2009.
 The much-talked about Republican &amp;ldquo;civil war&amp;rdquo; is over, at least for the people who thought it even existed in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Reforms for the 2014-2015 St. Louis Blues</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/27/four-reforms-for-the-2014-2015-st-louis-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 22:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/27/four-reforms-for-the-2014-2015-st-louis-blues/</guid>
      <description>If you’re reading this, the Blues blew it. Again.
I’m writing this six hours before Game 6 against the Chicago Blackhawks. If I wait to write this after the game, I’ll get a lot of complaints about foul language.
Yes, I expect the Blackhawks to end the Blues’ delusions of Market Street parades this afternoon. The Blues’ tenacity, hitting, and heart can’t overcome their lack of goal scoring and playoff goaltending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Far, Blues Playoff Run Is Carbon Copy of 2013</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/27/far-blues-playoff-run-carbon-copy-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 18:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/27/far-blues-playoff-run-carbon-copy-2013/</guid>
      <description>I told my nephew Scott that I was worried about the parallels between this year&amp;rsquo;s Stanley Cup Playoffs Round 1 and last year&amp;rsquo;s bitter collapse to the LA Kings.
That conversation happened last Sunday at an Easter party. The Blues were up 2-0 at the time, preparing for Game 3 in Chicago. My trepidation stemmed from the pattern emerging:
** Blues playing defending Stanley Cup Champions in Round 1 ** Steen wins Game 1 on overtime goal ** Jackman scores game winner in Game 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the ACLU Teaches Us About Cliven Bundy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/26/aclu-teaches-us-principles-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 09:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/26/aclu-teaches-us-principles-people/</guid>
      <description>In 1977, the National Socialist Party (Nazi) applied to march and rally in Skokie, Illinois. Few communities want Nazis marching down their streets, but Skokie held a stronger case against the Nazis than most towns in America. About one person in every six of Skokie&amp;rsquo;s large Jewish population was a Nazi prison camp survivor.
 The debate was clear-cut: American Nazis claimed the right of free speech while their Jewish &amp;ldquo;targets&amp;rdquo; claimed the right to live without intimidation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah Goldberg Perfectly Defines the GOP Establishment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 18:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</guid>
      <description>I hope you read Jonah Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s short article on National Review Online last week. If not, you missed the best definition of Establishment Republicans EVER!
Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s piece also exploded the myth of &amp;ldquo;pro-business&amp;rdquo; way too many conservatives believe. Conservatism isn&amp;rsquo;t pro-business, it&amp;rsquo;s pro-market. I&amp;rsquo;ll let Jonah explain:
 Just to clarify, the difference between being pro-business and pro-market is categorical. A politician who is a “friend of business” is exactly that, a guy who does favors for his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockwood School Board Quid Pro Quo?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/rockwood-school-board-quid-pro-quo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 21:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/rockwood-school-board-quid-pro-quo/</guid>
      <description>From the &amp;ldquo;see, I told ya so&amp;rdquo; file . . .
Rockwood NEA President Suzanne Dotta worked hard to influence the recent school board election. The candidates Ms. Dotta pushed won.
The new board hired Ms. Dotta as Director of Professional Learning within 72 hours of the election.
I expect Ms. Dotta to teach Rockwood&amp;rsquo;s professionals how to game the system for personal gain at taxpayer expense.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to question this apparent quid pro quo, the next Rockwood Board meeting is April 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, the Government Should Fear the People</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/government-create-free-speech-zones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 14:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/government-create-free-speech-zones/</guid>
      <description>Every inch of US territory is a Constitutionally guaranteed free-speech zone. I am all for arresting and prosecuting without mercy any government employee&amp;ndash;including military&amp;ndash;who attempt to limit the size or scope of this zone.

During the Bundy Ranch standoff in Nevada, the Bureau of Land Management set up &amp;ldquo;free-speech zones.&amp;rdquo; I prefer to call them &amp;ldquo;First Amendment pens.&amp;rdquo;
The government uses these pens to segregate people. The US government says, &amp;ldquo;If you want to speak your mind, you may do so only within the pen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Government’s Surrender to Cliven Bundy Destroys Taleb’s Weak Argument for Gun Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</guid>
      <description>Events of the past week show the power of the Second Amendment to challenge government tyranny, regardless of the government’s firepower advantage. Let me back up, though.
A Smart Man’s Stupid Argument for Gun Control A year ago, the gun control lobby pumped a Facebook post by Nassim Nicholas Taleb, one of my favorite thinkers.
In his post, Taleb argued that the Second Amendment means nothing because the federal government has massively superior firepower:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asia&#39;s Open and NIKKEI Is Diving</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/06/asias-open-and-nikkei-is-diving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 01:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/06/asias-open-and-nikkei-is-diving/</guid>
      <description>The NIKKEI Is down 1.56% already.
This comes on the heels of a terrible day in US momentum stocks Friday. Also Abenomics begins it&amp;rsquo;s tax-hike phase tomorrow when Japan&amp;rsquo;s national sales jumps 60%, to 8 percent from 5 percent.

Zerohedge plots Japan&amp;rsquo;s despair</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Weinstein and His Call to Jail Global Warming Skeptics</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Yet, in holding scientific research and discovery in respect, as we should, we must also be alert to the equal and opposite danger that public policy could itself become the captive of a scientific-technological elite.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ndash;President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Farewell Address, 1961
A young man named Adam Weinstein recently called for incarceration of disbelievers in the cult of catastrophic anthropogenic global warming (CAGW). His argument mirrors the argument Goebbels used in 1930s to quash dissent from eugenics and to take immediate policy actions for the betterment of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe I&#39;m All Wrong About Putin and Poland</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/30/maybe-im-wrong-putin-poland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/30/maybe-im-wrong-putin-poland/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;ve stated your opinion or belief about something important, do you defend your belief to the hilt? Or do you immediately begin questioning your own conclusions?
Most of my life, I would defend my opinion to the point of losing friends. Even if I was wrong. Even I knew I was wrong. I&amp;rsquo;m a coward, what can I say?
I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get better, though. One practice I&amp;rsquo;ve developed and recommend to everyone is pretty simple but difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eileen Tyrrell Is Only Rockwood Candidate In It For All Stakeholders</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/29/eileen-tyrrell-rockwood-candidate-stakeholders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/29/eileen-tyrrell-rockwood-candidate-stakeholders/</guid>
      <description>Eileen Tyrrell is the only candidate who represents ALL the stakeholders in Rockwood School District.
While other candidates focus on more money for the system, Eileen focuses on using Rockwood&amp;rsquo;s (embarrassingly) ample resources better.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to ask youself:
 Do you plan to fulfill your duty to vote on April 8? What time of day do you plan to vote? Where will be and what will you be doing immediately before you go to vote?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Abdullah Kicks Obama Out of Saudia Arabia ? **Video Added**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 00:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think American foreign policy couldn&amp;rsquo;t sink any lower than standing by while Vladimir Putin re-conquers the Warsaw Pact nations. Then you&amp;rsquo;ve underestimated Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s incompetence.
Apparently, Obama didn&amp;rsquo;t bow low enough to King Abdullah of Saudi Arabia. Whatever happened, an &amp;ldquo;intimate&amp;rdquo; evening planned for Obama and Abdullah was abruptly cancelled after a two-hour meeting between the two leaders. A meeting intended to &amp;ldquo;mend fences&amp;rdquo; between the two men.
UPDATE: Here&amp;rsquo;s the video from Lou Dobbs on Fox Business</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop By Tony Pousosa&#39;s Campaign HQ Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/26/stop-tony-pousosas-campaign-hq-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 11:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/26/stop-tony-pousosas-campaign-hq-saturday/</guid>
      <description>Just got a reminder from Tony Pousosa, Republican for St. Louis County Executive:
We will be opening up our campaign HQs on Saturday 3/29 at 5pm. 111 Clarkson Executive Park, Ellisville, MO 63011. Please join us if you can.
I plan to stop by. You should, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pousosa for County Executive</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/25/tony-pousosa-county-executive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 23:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/25/tony-pousosa-county-executive/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t you just love brash upstarts? People with verve and moxie?
I do. I like pesky guys full of gumption, like Vladimir Sobotka. I like energetic young political activists like Kenny Newhouse. And I like bold conservative organizers like Eileen Tyrrell. In fact, nothing pleases me more than seeing young, libertarian-ish Republicans making the establishment squirm.
Sometimes the squirming establishment is as small as a GOP township or a school district.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now, the White House Says Russia Preparing to Invade Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/now-the-white-house-says-russia-preparing-to-invade-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 20:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/now-the-white-house-says-russia-preparing-to-invade-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>This morning, a White House aide told reporters that Obama’s sanctions are visibly “weakening” Putin and Russia.
Hours later, the White House recognizes that Russia’s invasion of Ukraine could come any moment.
 Speaking from the Georgian capital, Tbilisi, Mike Rogers, the chair of the House of Representatives intelligence committee, said US intelligence officials were convinced “that Putin is not done in Ukraine”.
 Surprise. As I’ve written, Russian paranoia demands a larger sphere of influence and a large buffer of puppet governments, all the way to the German border with Poland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Would You Do If You Were Putin?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 18:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</guid>
      <description>You saw Obama stand by as you threatened Georgia in 2009.
You heard Obama whisper to Medvedev that he’ll be willing to defy Congress to capitulate to you after Obama’s re-election.
You watched Obama and his bumbling Secretary of State mangle its its own strategy in Syria—if the US ever had a Syrian strategy at all.
You saw that the US was completely unprepared for your annexation of Crimea.
You see the headlines of massive NSA spying on US citizens, though that same NSA was blind to your invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Secrets Politicians Don&#39;t Want You to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/20/5-secrets-politicians-dont-want-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 14:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/20/5-secrets-politicians-dont-want-know/</guid>
      <description>How long has it been since you said, &amp;ldquo;they just don&amp;rsquo;t listen to us?&amp;rdquo;
By &amp;ldquo;they,&amp;rdquo; you mean politicians, of course. Maybe you feel they listen to lobbyists and big corporations and banksters, but they don&amp;rsquo;t listen to their constituents.
I have to agree with you. Politicians don&amp;rsquo;t listen to their constituents. They don&amp;rsquo;t even know who their constituents are.
They know demographics and statistics about their constituents, but that&amp;rsquo;s like saying you know how a banana tastes because you read a chemical assay report of its contents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Will Putin Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/will-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 01:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/will-putin/</guid>
      <description>Ask yourself this: why did the stock markets rally today after Obama announced sanctions against Russians? I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to that, but first some background.
I&amp;rsquo;ve often said that Putin plays chess while Obama fumbles with checkers. I picture our president, chin resting on fist, brows squeezed in childlike concentration, as he carefully chooses between jumping Putin&amp;rsquo;s piece to end the game or getting another of his pieces &amp;ldquo;kinged.&amp;rdquo;
Of course, Obama goes for the kingship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Million Reasons to Vote for Eileen Tyrrell on April 8</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/1-2-million-reasons-vote-eileen-tyrrell-april-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 18:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/1-2-million-reasons-vote-eileen-tyrrell-april-8/</guid>
      <description>Do you live in Rockwood School District?
I do. My kids all went to Rockwood schools. My wife taught in a Rockwood school for three years.
The teachers in Rockwood tend to think a lot like the people who live here. They&amp;rsquo;re not a bunch of wacked-out lefties. Not most of them.
Still, that good education has come with HUGE price tag. Rockwood is one of the most expensive districts in Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week: March 17, 2014</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/week-march-17-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 09:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/week-march-17-2014/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a roundup of what to look for in the coming week.
St. Louis Monday, 12:30 p.m.: The Ancient Order of Hibernians&amp;rsquo; Annual St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day Parade in Dogtown. Get there early. Give yourself time to park and walk. Dress warmly.
Wednesday, 5:00 p.m.: Protest of St. Louis Archdiocese for its promotion of City-County Merger. Location is Lindell and Grand.
Wednesday, 7:00 p.m.: The activist who helped expose scandal, waste, and corruption at Rockwood School District is running for the Rockwood School Board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Book Predicted Russia&#39;s Ukraine Adventure. Poland&#39;s Next.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/16/predicted-russias-ukraine-adventure-polands-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/16/predicted-russias-ukraine-adventure-polands-next/</guid>
      <description>Did you ever read a book and think, &amp;ldquo;I need to tell people about this?&amp;rdquo;
Then you didn&amp;rsquo;t tell people about it. I mean, you didn&amp;rsquo;t blog about it. You didn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;officially&amp;rdquo; proclaim the book &amp;ldquo;required reading.&amp;rdquo;
Then something happened that you knew could happen because of the book, but you don&amp;rsquo;t get credit for calling it because you never got around to pumping the book.
That&amp;rsquo;s how I feel today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Steps To Negotiating With a Politician</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/15/talk-politician/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 21:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/15/talk-politician/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever said, &amp;ldquo;vote them all out?&amp;rdquo;
Do you sometimes think anybody would do a better job than the incumbent? Do you feel you have no influence in Jefferson City, Springfield, or Washington? Do you feel that way because you don&amp;rsquo;t have thousands of dollars to donate and rich friends with oodles of cash you can bundle?
I feel that way all the time. Ask my friends Ben Evans and Michelle Moore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Messages Backfire?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/04/why-do-messages-backfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/04/why-do-messages-backfire/</guid>
      <description>In the 1970s, a magazine ad for Benson &amp;amp; Hedges cigarettes portrayed a hockey fight. Two players slug it out. Sticks and gloves litter the ice.
The point of view is on-ice, in the midst of the scrum. The crowd is on its feet, banging the glass. You&amp;rsquo;re right there with linesmen trying to break it up.
The hockey gloves are Coopers. Every hockey player knows the name. In the photo, one of the gloves has been doctored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Roy Blunt Needs a Psychologist</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/03/can-roy-blunt-save-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/03/can-roy-blunt-save-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>Senator Roy Blunt (HA-57) proposed that all Obamacare ads contain a disclaimer: &amp;ldquo;Paid for by the American Taxpayer.&amp;rdquo;
I get the idea. I can&amp;rsquo;t stand it when my tax dollars buy ads intended to raise my taxes. It means I&amp;rsquo;m fighting against myself.
Still, I don&amp;rsquo;t like Senator Blunt&amp;rsquo;s plan because I think it could backfire.
The Psychology of Ownership Right now, few people have a sense of ownership of Obamacare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tea Party Is 5 Years Old Today</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/01/tea-party-5-years-old-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 16:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/01/tea-party-5-years-old-today/</guid>
      <description>If you were out on the Arch steps on February 27, 2009, take a moment to consider what&amp;rsquo;s happened.
** From near-spontaneous reaction to bailouts, corporate takeovers, and profligate government spending emerged the largest and most sustained political movement since the 1960s ** Both the GOP and Democrat Party are minority parties, as independents have surged ** A new generation identifies with libertarian ideals like freedom from government spying, freedom from failed wars on activities war was never meant to stop, insane spending, the opaque and manipulative Federal Reserve, government manipulation of information, IRS abuse of political groups, and Obamacare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Tickets For Heritage Action Skills Clinic Thursday **Only 20 Tix Left!**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/02/25/free-tickets-for-heritage-action-skills-clinic-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 02:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/02/25/free-tickets-for-heritage-action-skills-clinic-thursday/</guid>
      <description>Ben Evans of Heritage Action has free tickets for his Activist Skills Training.
 There are still tickets available to the Skills Clinic on Thursday, February 27: https://www.eventbrite.com/e/stl-skills-tickets-10683495623
  Holding Congress accountable can be tough work. Whether you are new to the fight or a seasoned activist, the Heritage Action Skills Clinic will help you better engage Congress, so your voice can be heard. Join fellow liberty-minded, conservatives for this FREE training as we provide the tools to take meaningful action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Years Ago Today, The Tea Party Was Born On a Phone Call</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/02/20/5-years-ago-today-tea-party-born-phone-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/02/20/5-years-ago-today-tea-party-born-phone-call/</guid>
      <description>Give all due credit to Rick Santelli. His rant inspired a movement. But words don&amp;rsquo;t wear boots.
More images like this one available at Doctor Bulldog: https://doctorbulldog.wordpress.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-by-the-arch/  At 7:00 pm on February 20, Mike Leahy, Eric Odom, Jenny Beth Martin, Michelle Moore, Brooks Bayne, and a few others hijacked the TCOT conference call to answer Santelli&amp;rsquo;s call for a Tea Party in Chicago.
Two days after that, I posted this on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View:St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I was talking about defunding Obamacare before it was cool</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/02/17/talking-defunding-obamacare-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 22:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/02/17/talking-defunding-obamacare-cool/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I&amp;rsquo;m fired up. I&amp;rsquo;m fired up about Obamacare.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know what got me onto this, exactly. I talked to Jim Durbin tonight, so maybe that was it.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for video of a speech I gave at the Million Med March in Clayton, MO, in 2009. Two-friggin-thousand-and-nine. (I&amp;rsquo;m a quarter German, so I hold a grudge.)
I found it. Here&amp;rsquo;s the clip I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to show Congress since last August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Interrupt This Blog To Gloat Over T.J. Oshie and Team USA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/02/15/interrupt-blog-gloat-tj-oshie-team-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 17:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/02/15/interrupt-blog-gloat-tj-oshie-team-usa/</guid>
      <description>TV hockey color man Eddie Olczyk said during the USA vs. Slovakia game that TJ Oshie would become well-known in the hockey world during these Olympics.
Eddie nailed it.
@OSH74 scored 4 shootout goals in 6 chances to lead Team USA to 3-2 win over Russia this morning.
The official St. Louis Blues website: T.J. Sochi! [caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14348&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;666&amp;rdquo;] Get your tickets at stlouisblues.com[/caption] Check out these Bruins fans at a Boston bar:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama: Year of Action Figure</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/28/obama-year-action-figure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 04:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/28/obama-year-action-figure/</guid>
      <description>Constitution Not Included</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Companies Should Adopt Conscious Capitalism Because It Pays</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/27/companies-adopt-conscious-capitalism-pays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 04:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/27/companies-adopt-conscious-capitalism-pays/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re going to hit me with the small sample size argument here, but that&amp;rsquo;s okay.
I firmly believe that the purpose of a company is to make life better, and if it does that well, it will make a profit. If, on the other hand, a company makes life worse, the market should let that company die.
Some companies try to improve life with insanely great technology products. Some make life better with fast, safe cars that are fun to drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Not Prove Karl Marx Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/26/lets-prove-karl-marx-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 02:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/26/lets-prove-karl-marx-right/</guid>
      <description>Karl Marx foresaw something that&amp;rsquo;s now playing out. As corporations cut labor costs to increase profits, they also destroy the markets for their goods and services.
This chart shows corporate profits (red) and wages as a percentage of GDP (blue) from 1944 to 2012:
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14282&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;634&amp;rdquo;] Corporate Profits vs. Wages as Percentage of GDP, 1944-2012[/caption]
When the blue line is higher than the red line, you get savings. For the red line to hang above the blue line, you need debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Freaky Index Says 2014 Will See Economic Crash</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/17/freaky-index-says-2014-will-see-economic-crash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 06:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/17/freaky-index-says-2014-will-see-economic-crash/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write this post earlier today, so you&amp;rsquo;d all think I&amp;rsquo;m really smart. But I had to work until 10:00 tonight. I never go to it.
Now, things are happening that might make this post less prescient. I&amp;rsquo;m writing it anyway.
The Weirdest Index The financial world has a lot of weird indexes. They&amp;rsquo;re all correlation, no causation. And many of them fail under scrutiny.
But one freaky index even has banks worried.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What Chris Christie Got Right </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/09/heres-chris-christie-got-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 01:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/09/heres-chris-christie-got-right/</guid>
      <description>I stand by my assessment that Chris Christie&amp;rsquo;s leadership and management played a role in the retaliatory shutdown of Fort Lee&amp;rsquo;s access lanes to the George Washington Bridge. Yesterday,I compared the GWB scandal to several Obama scandals. I pointed out that conservatives must apply the same standards to Christie as we did to Obama when the IRS scandal broke.
Today, let&amp;rsquo;s look at Christie&amp;rsquo;s response and contrast it to Obama&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why &#34;Time for Some Traffic Problems in Fort Lee&#34; Matters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/08/time-traffic-problems-fort-lee-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 03:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/08/time-traffic-problems-fort-lee-matters/</guid>
      <description>One argument put forth by conservatives&amp;ndash;and even some liberals&amp;ndash;regarding the IRS scandal was this:
Obama set a tone that encouraged IRS workers to harass conservative and Tea Party groups. He didn&amp;rsquo;t have to give a direct order. His tone and statements clearly condoned such criminal behavior toward his political enemies.
Kimberly Strassel at WSJ.com:
 Mr. Obama didn&amp;rsquo;t need to pick up the phone. All he needed to do was exactly what he did do, in full view, for three years: Publicly suggest that conservative political groups were engaged in nefarious deeds; publicly call out by name political opponents whom he&amp;rsquo;d like to see harassed; and publicly have his party pressure the IRS to take action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri Statewide Right to Work Meeting Wednesday January 8</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/07/missouri-statewide-right-to-work-meeting-wednesday-january-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 01:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/07/missouri-statewide-right-to-work-meeting-wednesday-january-8/</guid>
      <description>Use your snow day to join the opening of the Missouri General Assembly Speaker of the House Tim Jones • Lieutenant Governor Peter Kinder
Representative Eric Burlison and Senator Ed Emery * State Capitol in the beautiful House Lounge next to room 308 201 W. Capitol Ave. Jefferson City, MO
Wednesday, January 8th at 10am (be early) Questions? Mary Hill mmdacushill@gmail.Missouri Statewide Right to Work Meeting
Afterwards in Hearing room 7 starting at noon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What Marijuana Does To You</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/07/heres-marijuana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 23:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/07/heres-marijuana/</guid>
      <description>Last week&amp;rsquo;s Weednesday Post generated several comments that took my side but the facts wrong. Specifically, a couple of commenters claimed &amp;ldquo;marijuana is harmless.&amp;rdquo; That&amp;rsquo;s not true.
While cannabis may be have fewer harmful effects than alcohol and tobacco, someone who abstains from all three will be healthier mentally and physically than the same person smoking pot.
On the other hand, a lot proponents of prohibition throw around bad science, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Crush Lobbying </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/06/crush-lobbying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 22:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/06/crush-lobbying/</guid>
      <description>Ben Sasse wants to break the back of lobbying and crony capitalism by moving the seat of government from Washington to Nebraska. Sasse is a Republican candidate for US Senate from Nebraska.
Who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to cripple lobbying? But Sasse&amp;rsquo;s plan won&amp;rsquo;t cripple lobbying. It will inconvenience lobbyists for a year while they resettle in the Midwest. Then it&amp;rsquo;s back to business as usual.
Before you throw up your hands and say &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s hopeless,&amp;rdquo; here&amp;rsquo;s an idea that might actually end lobbying as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is What Happens When I Blog About Cannabis Law Reform</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/05/happens-blog-cannabis-law-reform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 03:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/05/happens-blog-cannabis-law-reform/</guid>
      <description>I blog about tea party stuff 90 percent of the time. I get decent readership with those blogs, and I appreciate my loyal followers. Very much.
But as long as I write about stuff only conservatives and activist libertarians care about, only conservatives and libertarians will read my blog. That means our ideas won&amp;rsquo;t escape the echo chamber we&amp;rsquo;ve been yelling in for years.
When I write about the conservative/libertarian perspective on issues of wider interest, though, I bring in people who never otherwise read our views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Are My Replies to Most Serious Arguments Against Ending Cannabis Prohibitions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/04/replies-serious-arguments-ending-cannabis-prohibitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 18:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/04/replies-serious-arguments-ending-cannabis-prohibitions/</guid>
      <description>I repeated my New Year&amp;rsquo;s Day tradition of proposing cannabis law reform in Missouri and America last Wednesday. The post has generated a lot of serious discussion. I have to thank, especially, Dennis Broadbooks and Lisa, Culture Vigilante, for raising valid issues.
Many others commented as well. I will work through your comments as the blizzard rolls through this weekend. But I wanted to pull my reply to Dennis and Lisa and to link directly to their most salient comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The War on Weed Is Over, and Republicans Lost</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/02/war-weed-republicans-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 06:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/02/war-weed-republicans-lost/</guid>
      <description>The Republicans are the Leon Spinks of politics these days.
Remember Leon Spinks? He beat Muhammad Ali. Then he got arrested a bunch, gained a lot of weight, and lost to Ali a few months later. He was pretty much done. And Ali was like 50 when Spinks lost to him.
Spinks had the whole world served up on a plate. He tried to eat it all at once. He choked on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-01-29-will-minimalism-reach-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-01-29-will-minimalism-reach-government/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-01-30-watching-central-bank-era-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-01-30-watching-central-bank-era-end/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-02-17-dont-miss-chance-celebrate-jim-hofts-recovery-february-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-02-17-dont-miss-chance-celebrate-jim-hofts-recovery-february-22/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-05-11-angela-bill-loves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-05-11-angela-bill-loves/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-05-20-politics-linked-stock-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-05-20-politics-linked-stock-market/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-05-25-dont-anti-establishment-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-05-25-dont-anti-establishment-party/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-06-26-rinos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-06-26-rinos/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-12-17-ted-cruz-just-gave-perfect-response-establishment-critics-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2014/2014-12-17-ted-cruz-just-gave-perfect-response-establishment-critics-video/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>