<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seth Godin on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/seth-godin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seth Godin on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 23:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/seth-godin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chains of a Different Master</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/25/chains-of-a-different-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/25/chains-of-a-different-master/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the most famous of all of Karl Marx’s writings was the clause “you have nothing to lose but your chains.”
Many people still believe that human beings are chained to corporate masters. Writers like Seth Godin talk about an awakening in which workers refuse to remain cogs in someone else’s machine.
These well-meaning people (some are well-meaning, anyway) have no problem, though with giving more power to a handful of slave-masters in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apologies to Seth Godin and His Readers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/apologies-to-seth-godin-and-his-readers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 19:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/apologies-to-seth-godin-and-his-readers/</guid>
      <description>I tried to manually trackback to Seth Godin’s post on TV from this post.
Between WordPress’s false negatives on reporting success of links, my laptop’s touchy touchpad, and Typepad’s weird trackback URL system, I managed to:
a. Link once to the wrong blog post
b. Link twice to the right blog post
I pride myself on being respectful of blogging etiquette. I hate trackback spam. I hate it even more when I’m the one creating it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not So Fast, Seth</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/not-so-fast-seth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 13:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/not-so-fast-seth/</guid>
      <description>I am a big fan of Seth Godin’s thinking. He clearly understands that people are rejecting steep hierarchies where an oligarchy makes all the decisions and the rest of us are expected to blindly follow instructions.
He wrote a wonderful book on the subject. Linchpin: Are You Indispensable?  holds some wisdom (and some fallacy) that will empower you to take control of your life if you listen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Has the Fear?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</guid>
      <description>For 100 years in America, government, business, and the education establishment built schools and laws about education. The purpose of these government schools and education laws was to produce compliant, unimaginative, order-taking automatons.
Don’t believe me? Here’s Woodrow Wilson, educator and president, speaking on the American plan for education:
 We want one class of persons to have a liberal education, and we want another class of persons, a very much larger class of necessity in every society, to forgo the privilege of a liberal education and fit themselves to perform specific difficult manual tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dip</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/01/the-dip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 01:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/01/the-dip/</guid>
      <description>Seth Godin is one of my favorite writers, thinkers, marketers, and presenters. Everything he writes is worth your time reading. Two of his books stand out for me. One is Tribes, because Tribes describes the whole Tea Party experience perfectly. And he wrote it a year before the Tea Party things started.
Right now, though, my other favorite Godin book serves as a question and a guide for the Tea Party movement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>