<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 05:00:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How 2012 Might Have Been</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/30/how-2012-might-have-been/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 05:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/30/how-2012-might-have-been/</guid>
      <description>Republican Presidential Primaries
The Republican Primary season was already well underway. Before a single caucus or vote, though, we pretty much knew that Mitt Romney would win the nomination. He had the entire Republican establishment behind him, including true conservatives who wanted a “safe” candidate.
We know how that worked out.

What might have been had a strong conservative emerged in 2011? What if someone without baggage had prepared years in advance for a run against the weakened, staggering Obama?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Never Guess Who&#39;s About to Become Obama&#39;s Biggest Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>In 2008, we heard all about the youth movement for Obama. We heard that the enormous Millennial Generation, born between 1982 and 2001, would destroy the GOP and everything America once stood for&amp;ndash;like jobs, family, faith, and hard work. And when Obama won, many believed the tales of the Obama Youth.
  
But many were wrong. Voters under 30 have had it with vague promises and glittering bullshit from that punk from Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire Exposes GOP’s Diverse Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</guid>
      <description>Okay, Santorum and Gingrich didn’t get a bump out of their debates over the weekend. More like the bump got them.
And Ron Paul did way better than I expected. Congratulations to Dr. Paul and Mitt. 
I still think my Saturday night post accurately reflected the national impressions, though. That’s backed up by this CBS News poll that shows Republicans believe Santorum most closely shares their values, but—and this is a J Lo but—they believe Romney is more electable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Maniacal Focus for 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/01/a-maniacal-focus-for-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 01:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/01/a-maniacal-focus-for-2012/</guid>
      <description>I’m almost finished reading Walter Isaacson’s biography of Apple co-founder and genius Steve Jobs.
Jobs’s life left insanely good lessons. Some lessons instruct us on how to do things. Others warn us of bad things to avoid.
One of the good things Steve Jobs taught us: focus. Maniacal focus on things that mattered, and a pathological aversion to distractions.
One example. When Jobs returned to Apple after 10-year exile, he took stock of all the projects underway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Moves After the Tea Party*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/02/3-moves-after-the-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/02/3-moves-after-the-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>It’s 2011. The Tea Party movement is almost two years old.
Two years after the Boston Tea party, the Revolutionary War was well underway. In April, 1775, British Lieutenant General Gage sent troops to Concord, Massachusetts, to seize a garrison held by revolutionaries. It didn’t go so well for the Brits.

By 1776, the Continental Congress declared our independence from Great Britain citing human rights. With words that echo through the centuries, we declared that human beings have certain rights, and:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>