<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>war on pot on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/war-on-pot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in war on pot on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 13:18:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/war-on-pot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is Rand Paul&#39;s Secret to Broadening the Republican Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/27/rand-pauls-secret-broadening-republican-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 13:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/27/rand-pauls-secret-broadening-republican-base/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever felt like tuning out, giving up, and just riding out whatever storm comes down the pipe next?
I have. Many times. Every week. Sometimes more than once a day.
I think we can both give ourselves a pass on that feeling. In fact, I think we can both give ourselves a pass on acting on that feeling. It&amp;rsquo;s okay to check out occasionally. Everyone needs a break now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Be On Panel at Show-Me Cannabis Conference April 13</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/08/i-will-be-on-panel-at-show-me-cannabis-conference-april-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/08/i-will-be-on-panel-at-show-me-cannabis-conference-april-13/</guid>
      <description>Gary Weigert, State Rep. Paul Curtman, and I will share a panel at Show-Me Cannabis Reform Spring Conference Saturday, April 13 from 1:45 to 2:30 pm at the Crowne Plaza Downtown, 200 N. Fourth St.
Our panel discusses the conservative case for marijuana law reform.
I am honored by the invitation, and I’d love to see a big turnout of tea partiers for the event.
  
Here’s the full schedule of events</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weednesday Post: Why The GOP Needs To Champion Marijuana Law Reform</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/27/weednesday-post-why-the-gop-needs-to-champion-marijuana-law-reform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/27/weednesday-post-why-the-gop-needs-to-champion-marijuana-law-reform/</guid>
      <description>**If Republicans want to put their liberty where their mouths are, they can begin by ending the war on weed. **
When I was a kid in South St. Louis in the 70s, marijuana was the weed in the field that separated traditional post-war American values from the hippies. It was an easy black-and-white issue: smoke dope, you’re un-American. It was the Boomers against the Greatest Generation, and no one questioned the pure evil of pot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>