<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>People Want You Dead on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/people-want-you-dead/</link>
    <description>Recent content in People Want You Dead on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 21:30:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/people-want-you-dead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Slouching Towards the Climax</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/11/slouching-toward-the-climax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 21:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/11/slouching-toward-the-climax/</guid>
      <description>Soon thereafter, this great gate is sealed by the Crisis resolution, when victors are rewarded and enemies punished; when empires or nations are forged or destroyed; when treaties are signed and boundaries redrawn; and when peace is accepted, troops repatriated, and life begun anew. One large chapter of history ends, and another starts.
 In a very real sense, one society dies— and another is born.
—The Fourth Turning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Resistance: Defined</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/10/the-resistance-defined/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 23:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/10/the-resistance-defined/</guid>
      <description>The leftists who want you and me to die (at their hands?) call themselves The Resistance.
Okay. Let&amp;rsquo;s call them that.
Author Steven Pressfield wrote a book about defeating The Resistance. It&amp;rsquo;s called The War of Art, and it&amp;rsquo;s an awesome, wonderful book.
Overcoming and defeating The Resistance, Pressfield tells us, is the key to living the good life. I agree, even if I don&amp;rsquo;t agree on some of his enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Want You Dead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/09/people-want-you-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 23:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/09/people-want-you-dead/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself in the midst of a riot? Even if you’ve only seen riots on television, you can probably imagine how it feels to be inside one.
Imagine yourself surrounded on all sides by angry faces dressed in shabby clothes, some faces covered with bandanas or ski masks. People are chanting something you can&amp;rsquo;t quite understand, like a private joke you&amp;rsquo;re not allowed to get. Or maybe they&amp;rsquo;re chanting at you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>