<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coronavirus on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/coronavirus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coronavirus on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 16:32:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/coronavirus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New CDC Office Guidelines Ignore Science</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/cdc-office-guidelines-ignore-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 16:32:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/cdc-office-guidelines-ignore-science/</guid>
      <description>The CDC, today, issued guidelines for reopening offices that ignore medical guidance regarding masks.
The latest medical guidance, according to May 21 article in the New England Journal of Medicine reported here, says:
 Public health authorities define a significant exposure to Covid-19 as face-to-face contact within 6 feet with a patient with symptomatic Covid-19 that is sustained for at least a few minutes (and some say more than 10 minutes or even 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Masks Are Symbolic,&#39; say Dr Fauci and The New England Journal of Medicine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/masks-are-symbolic-dr-fauci/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 07:41:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/masks-are-symbolic-dr-fauci/</guid>
      <description>In the past week, Dr. Anthony Fauci and the New England Journal of Medicine have admitted that masks are little more than symbols. Virtue signaling.
For those of you who shout &amp;ldquo;science&amp;rdquo; like it&amp;rsquo;s a Tourette tick, this is from the New England Journal of Medicine on May 21, 2020:
 We know that wearing a mask outside health care facilities offers little, if any, protection from infection. Public health authorities define a significant exposure to Covid-19 as face-to-face contact within 6 feet with a patient with symptomatic Covid-19 that is sustained for at least a few minutes (and some say more than 10 minutes or even 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Turn Nursing Homes Into Death Camps</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</guid>
      <description>When I wrote this post on May 6, I worried how it would be received. Accusing a governor of intentionally killing nursing home residents in order to save money is a serious charge. And, with only circumstantial evidence, difficult to prove.
Since then, Andrew Cuomo&amp;rsquo;s behavior has been consistent with guilt. The latest example is deflection. He&amp;rsquo;s trying, now, to blame federal guidelines for his order to force uninfected nursing homes to treat confirmed COVID-19 patients even if they lacked the facilities and skills to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leave the Gun Take the Cannolis</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/leave-the-gun-take-the-cannolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 20:10:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/leave-the-gun-take-the-cannolis/</guid>
      <description>Via WGEM:
 Illinois Gov. J.B. Pritzker responded Friday afternoon to President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s statement earlier in the day where Trump said he had deemed churches and other houses of worship &amp;ldquo;essential&amp;rdquo; and called on governors to allow them to reopen this weekend.
During his COVID-19 press briefing on Friday afternoon, Gov. Pritzker said Illinois would continue to operate on the basis of science and data.
 If JB Pritzker, governor of Illinois, took science and data seriously, he&amp;rsquo;d drop about 280 pounds fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The President&#39;s Authority to Open Churches Is the Constitution - VIDEO RANT</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/presidents-authority-to-open-churches-is-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 13:57:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/presidents-authority-to-open-churches-is-constitution/</guid>
      <description>The morons in the White House press corps spend most of today&amp;rsquo;s briefing screaming at press secretary Kayleigh McEnany about President Trump&amp;rsquo;s order to re-open all churches.
The oft-repeated (shouted) question: &amp;ldquo;What federal law is the president relying on to require states to allow church services?&amp;rdquo;
The question demonstrates the absolute ignorance and laziness, the besst-like stupidity, of most journalists.
  The president&amp;rsquo;s authority is the United States Constitution, you mouth-breathing swine!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>