<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coronavirus on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/coronavirus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coronavirus on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:21:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/coronavirus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Secrets of Coronavirus Data Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:21:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>Nate Silver let the cat out of the bag.
In case you don&amp;rsquo;t recognize his name, Nate Silver is the data analyst who launched Five Thirty-Eight, orignally in the New York Times. He was famous for not predicting an election a few years ago.
Today, Nate unloaded on the media for just one aspect of their narrative-driven Coronavirus coverage. In short, noted the same thing Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View pointed out a month ago: positive tests is meaningless unless it&amp;rsquo;s indexed to the number of tests administered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Andrew Cuomo Intentionally Kill the Elderly of New York?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:50:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</guid>
      <description>It would be the most sinister murder plot in US history. Imagine a governor conspiring to thin the population of elderly people, using a pandemic as both cover and weapon.
As unimaginable as it would be, evidence is mounting New York Governor Andrew Cuomo did just that: culled the herd in nursing homes by weaponizing Coronavirus.
Dumped Off With Their Own Body Bags New York Governor Andrew Cuomo implemented an emergency declaration that required nursing homes to accept active Coronavirus patients regardless of their ability to care for or isolate the infected patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doomsday Doctors Make the Best Case for Opening the Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/doomsday-doctors-make-best-case-for-opening-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 12:12:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/doomsday-doctors-make-best-case-for-opening-economy/</guid>
      <description>A lot of doctors seem to derive much pleasure from convincing people that Coronavirus will kill us all very soon. Very soon. These are the Doomsday Doctors. And if they&amp;rsquo;re right, we need to eliminate all behavior restrictions immediately and enjoy our final days.
The latest tactic of the Doomsday Doctors is to report (non-peer reviewed) that the Coronavirus has mutated into a weapons-grade killer that no one can avoid or resist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shock Therapy: Scott Adams Scooped Me</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/shock-therapy-scott-adams-scooped-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 06:30:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/shock-therapy-scott-adams-scooped-me/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing &amp;ldquo;around&amp;rdquo; this topic for weeks, now. But I have to post this today, because Scott Adams scooped me. Tonight on his Coffee with Scott Adams Periscope he exposed the secret I&amp;rsquo;ve been leading up to. No reason to be subtle any longer. So, here we go.
Watch Scott Adams&amp;rsquo; rant. (Begins about 9:30 mark.)
There will be extra cussing tonight. Put the kids to bed. Close your windows and get under the covers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Was China All Along</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/it-was-china-all-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 06:05:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/it-was-china-all-along/</guid>
      <description>The leaked Five Eyes dossier on China&amp;rsquo;s nefarious Coronavirus pandemic provides all the pieces to figure out what happened and why. The dossier doesn&amp;rsquo;t connect the dots for you, but they&amp;rsquo;re now easy to connect. So easy, even I can do it. The story goes something like this.
 China was playing around with dangerous natural microbes in order to prove that it was as good as the USA at studying and neutralizing infectious diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Is Wrong Two-Thirds of the Time</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/science-is-wrong-two-thirds-of-the-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 11:12:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/science-is-wrong-two-thirds-of-the-time/</guid>
      <description>If you believe science, then you disbelieve 2/3 of science.
In 2017, the BBC reported on a major problem in science in medicine: two-thirds (67%) of all scientific and medical studies cannot be replicated. Via BBC:
 Science is facing a &amp;ldquo;reproducibility crisis&amp;rdquo; where more than two-thirds of researchers have tried and failed to reproduce another scientist&amp;rsquo;s experiments, research suggests.
 Two years earlier, in 2015, a major study found the same problem, with nearly the same numbers, involving psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Rebellion Is Brewing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/a-rebellion-is-brewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 20:11:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/a-rebellion-is-brewing/</guid>
      <description>The only thing more dangerous than a man with unlimited resources is a man with nothing to lose.
Thanks to tyrannical and unlawful restrictions on liberty and commerce by a few governors, mayors, and county executives, 30 million Americans have nothing left to lose except their dignity and freedom.
Millions of American feel threatened by stupid and tyrannical policies that have no basis in science or evidence. Only the will to power drives governors like Gavin Newsom and Gretchen Whitmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The WHO Is a Misinformation Juggernaut</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/who-is-a-misinformation-juggernaut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 16:29:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/who-is-a-misinformation-juggernaut/</guid>
      <description>In the past 48 hours, the World Health Organization has spread misinformation about the Coronavirus intended to keep economies closed for good.
On Saturday, the WHO, through its propaganda tools like the New York Times, Twitter, Facebook, and CNN, released a statement that Coronavirus antibodies offered no protection against catching the disease a second time. This statement was factually wrong, but the media quickly broadcast the false statement.
On Sunday, after an outcry by physicians and researchers, the WHO amended its statement to say &amp;ldquo;there is no evidence&amp;rdquo; that Coronavirus antibodies protect people from the disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Is on the Verge of Depression</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/america-on-verge-of-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 11:36:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/america-on-verge-of-depression/</guid>
      <description>The Congressional Budget Office release a report yesterday (April 24, 2020) that expects our response to Coronavirus will wipe out 40 percent of the US economy and throw 27 million Americans into long-term unemployment. We could see unemployment rates of 20 percent or more for a decade.
The Last Depression My parents were born in 1925. Their understanding of the world was shaped by the Great Depression and World War II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunlight Kills Coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/sunlight-kills-coronavirus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 19:12:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/sunlight-kills-coronavirus/</guid>
      <description>An expert is someone who can&amp;rsquo;t be fired for being wrong about everything 100 percent of the time.
You can call that Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s Law, and Coronavirus is proving this law iron clad. Iron clad.
The latest confirmation of Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s Law just completed.
In March, Donald Trump and others said that warm weather would diminish the spread of Coronavirus, just as it diminishes the flu. The reason: virus that survive well in cool, dry conditions don&amp;rsquo;t do well in warm, humid conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have I Mentioned &#39;Fourth Turning?&#39;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/have-i-mentioned-fourth-turning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 01:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/have-i-mentioned-fourth-turning/</guid>
      <description>About three days ago, as the news spread of our world rapidly grinding to a halt, I sent a text to some friends:
 For you Fourth Turning fans, the Climax is right on time.
 If you&amp;rsquo;ve never read my Fourth Turning posts, now might be a good time to do so. I&amp;rsquo;ll wait right here. (Link to Fourth Turning Posts)
Here are some important quotes about the Climax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like It or Not, Herd Immunity Is Probably Our Only Hope to Stave Off Economy Depression</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/like-it-or-not-herd-immunity-is-probably-our-only-hope-to-stave-off-economy-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 12:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/like-it-or-not-herd-immunity-is-probably-our-only-hope-to-stave-off-economy-depression/</guid>
      <description>I know President Trump mocks the idea of herd immunity, but there&amp;rsquo;s really no other option absent a vaccine. And if we keep in lockdown until a vaccine is widely available, millions will die from the collapsed economy and collapsed infrastructure.
What makes Coronavirus more dangerous than flu is lack of immune people.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say that both kill about .01 to .02 percent of everyone who catches them, just for argument&amp;rsquo;s sake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Media Leading Us Into Despair?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/why-are-media-leading-us-into-despair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 15:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/why-are-media-leading-us-into-despair/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all been seeing the woeful headlines from the media that hates Trump and hates America: CNN, NYTimes, Washington Post, Drudge Report, etc. The headlines combine and conspire to send a single, unmistakable message: DESPAIR.
The headlines and stories are clearly intended to make people panic. The media want people to stay locked in their homes, and they want people to demand that government keeps the brave locked in their homes, as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: COVID-19 Acceleration Tracker</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/covid-19-acceleration-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 19:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/covid-19-acceleration-tracker/</guid>
      <description>This is a live view of the most important COVID-19 metric: acceleration rates of positive tests, hospitalizations, and deaths.
  Source: The Covid Tracking Project
Key Insight: For every week, Hospitalization rate decreases by about 9.19%.
From My Original Tweet The most important number regarding Coronavirus is a number none of the tracking sites or governments will tell you: acceleration. Lower acceleration of hospitalization and deaths is good. It means the number of new incidents yesterday was smaller than the new incidents from the day before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is How Masks Will Change People</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/this-is-how-masks-will-change-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 12:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/this-is-how-masks-will-change-people/</guid>
      <description>Wearing masks in public will change the way people behave, and the consequences for society could be devastating.
The White House released the plan to Open America Again. It&amp;rsquo;s reasonable, 3-phase plan that relaxes Coronavirus restrictions in 14-day increments. As a state achieves certain metrics, based on CDC surveillance data, it advances to the next phase.
Phases one and two allow increased activity with the recommendation of requiring face masks when in confined public places like work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protests to Reopen Missouri and St. Louis County Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/time-to-protest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 02:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/time-to-protest/</guid>
      <description>Governors, mayors, and county executives are drunk with power, and it&amp;rsquo;s our job to sober their asses up.
Thanks to Josh Schisler and the Reopen Missouri movement, protests are a comin&amp;rsquo;. We&amp;rsquo;re gonna pull good ol&amp;rsquo; fashioned 2009 on a new crop of autocrats in a two-part protest to get Missouri Working Again.
Part One: Reopen Missouri @ State Capitol at Noon Jefferson City, Missouri. Noon to 1:00 vehicle protest at the State Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lockdown Will Be Over Before You Know It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/lockdown-will-be-over-before-you-know-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 23:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/lockdown-will-be-over-before-you-know-it/</guid>
      <description>America will reopen for business much, much faster than most people think.
This is only a possible scenario, but it&amp;rsquo;s the scenario I see as likeliest case. But I&amp;rsquo;m realistic enough to know I could be terribly wrong. Be careful about acting on anything you read here.
Some of my friends, relying on the horribly flawed data models that the CDC and many states relied on, seem to believe the economy will be locked down most of the summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All We Are Saying Is Give Walls a Chance</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/walls-are-the-answer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/walls-are-the-answer/</guid>
      <description>If you pay attention to certain sources, you&amp;rsquo;ll know exactly what to do. One of these sources is the Francis Vatican. Whatever the Francis Vatican says, do the opposite.
Francis&amp;rsquo; Vatican recently called China the best example of Christianity in the world. Thinking people immediately treated China like the incarnation of Satan, which it is.
When Francis defiled St. Peter&amp;rsquo;s Basilica with demonic idols, thinking Christians canceled their planned trip to the Vatican</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History Will Little Note Nor Long Remember What COVID-19 Did But Will Never Forget How We Freaked Out</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/history-will-little-note-nor-long-remember-what-covid-19-did-but-will-can-never-forget-how-we-freaked-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 12:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/history-will-little-note-nor-long-remember-what-covid-19-did-but-will-can-never-forget-how-we-freaked-out/</guid>
      <description>If a picture can paint 1,000 words, this infographic would fill a library.
It is a visual representation of the death toll from various plagues throughout history (most of which originated in China), including COVID-19 (which originated in China).
You will notice that COVID-19 is a rather mundane specimen. As of April 10, its death toll fell somewhere between the Yellow Fever of the late 1800s and Ebola of 2014-2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is America Approaching Herd Immunity? **CONFIRMED** </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/is-america-approaching-herd-immunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/is-america-approaching-herd-immunity/</guid>
      <description>Models failed. Miserably.
The IHME models the CDC used as their primary source to justify the destruction of President Trump&amp;rsquo;s beautiful economy turned out to be no better than guesses from three drunks at a bar. The IHME factored in strict mitigation (lockdown), but they still over estimated everything by factors as high as 40.
That models were unbelievably bad is not open to debate. The models were hideously bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Trump&#39;s Humility Is Nearly Perfect</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/president-trumps-humility-is-nearly-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/president-trumps-humility-is-nearly-perfect/</guid>
      <description>If I asked you, &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s the perfect act of love and humility?&amp;rdquo; you&amp;rsquo;d likely answer, &amp;ldquo;to give one&amp;rsquo;s life for his neighbor.&amp;rdquo;
If I asked your for the second greatest, you might say, &amp;ldquo;to sacrifice one&amp;rsquo;s life&amp;rsquo;s greatest work for his neighbor.&amp;rdquo;
Now, if I asked you, &amp;ldquo;what is Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s greatest work?&amp;rdquo; you&amp;rsquo;d probably say, &amp;ldquo;the US economy.&amp;rdquo;
Objectively, the incredible US economy since January 2017 is the greatest accomplishment in Trump&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed! Monkeys Throwing Darts and Bill Gates&#39; Coronavirus Estimates</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/monkeys-and-bill-gates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 21:02:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/monkeys-and-bill-gates/</guid>
      <description>Last week I hoped that the Coronavirus pandemic would kill a few horrible ideas. One of those bad ideas involves bowing down before data models as if they were some sort of pagan god. (I should have added to that list the idea of foundations funded by American billionaires.)
Data models are not science, but most people have no idea what science is, so they fall prey to this insidious myth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Benway Doctor Fauci</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/doctor-benway-doctor-fauci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 13:06:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/doctor-benway-doctor-fauci/</guid>
      <description>I wish I had never read the book Naked Lunch. Once in a while, though, having read it comes in handy.
A Gateway Pundit story about Dr. Anthony Fauci reminded me of something from Naked Lunch.
Dr. Benway is the chief antagonist of that wretched book. He is a sadist who advises governments on ways to keep populations compliant and submissive through fear. For example, from Naked Lunch by William S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus Exposes Medicine&#39;s Herd Mentality</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/coronavirus-exposes-medicines-herd-mentality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 09:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/coronavirus-exposes-medicines-herd-mentality/</guid>
      <description>In the 2003 movie, &amp;ldquo;Northfork,&amp;rdquo; two pseudo-government agents working for a power company try to convince a devout Mormon farmer to get out of his home before the construction of a dam floods him out.
The farmer insists he must first receive a sign from God. The Mormon has built a replica of Noah&amp;rsquo;s ark, which he expects will rise with the waters and sail him and has wives to safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s the Villain of the USS Roosevelt?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/who-is-villain-of-uss-roosevelt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 15:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/who-is-villain-of-uss-roosevelt/</guid>
      <description>People like clean storylines with an obvious, likable hero and a sinister, hateable villain.
When real life tells us a story, our minds will mold the facts to fit our desired storylines. In other words, we will create a hero and a villain for every story, even if there aren&amp;rsquo;t any.
As we retell our semi-fictionalized story to ourselves or others, we pad the hero&amp;rsquo;s character and tarnish the villain&amp;rsquo;s with each telling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survivors Will Envy the Dead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/survivors-will-envy-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 05:01:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/survivors-will-envy-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>What kind of world will emerge from the coronavirus shutdown?
People have gleefully surrendered amazing new powers to governments. We have erected barriers between ourselves and all other humans on the planet. We have surrendered all of our rights, including the First Amendment. We have abandoned religion. The Catholic Church has ordered its priests to disobey Christ&amp;rsquo;s Great Commission by prohibiting baptisms. We have shut down every business that isn&amp;rsquo;t part of a global enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Should I Believe You?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/why-should-i-believe-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 04:17:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/why-should-i-believe-you/</guid>
      <description>Someone sent me a video. The video shows a doctor explaining how coronavirus is worse than the flu. Should we believe him?
I say, no. And the reasons we should not believe this doctor about the relative dangers of two diseases have nothing to do with medicine. They have everything to do with statistics and lying.
First, the statistics.
The Doctor&amp;rsquo;s Statistical Error The doctor, a general surgeon, opens the video by stating his conclusion that coronavirus is deadlier than influenza and his proof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do We Deserve Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/do-we-deserve-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 08:14:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/do-we-deserve-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Do We Deserve Freedom?
You probably know people who are concerned about a &amp;ldquo;surveillance state&amp;rdquo; developing. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re one of them. I know I am.
It&amp;rsquo;s a reasonable fear.
Some police departments are using drones to spy on people in their homes, peering into living rooms and bedrooms with digital cameras and fining or arresting people who have more than the imposed limit of guests. The justification the state gives for these intrusions is, of course, coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Only Covid Number That Matters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-only-covid-number-that-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 10:21:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-only-covid-number-that-matters/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I pointed out that the number of confirmed cases of coronavirus is a meaningless number. The media is all atwitter about it, but the media are mostly idiots. (Never trust a reporter.)
Bloomberg now cites many &amp;ldquo;experts&amp;rdquo; who agree with me on this:
 It doesn’t matter that the United States surpassed China this week in reported Covid-19 cases because those numbers (83,507 and 81,782 respectively as of March 26) don’t tell us how many people actually became infected in either country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Mass for the 5th Sunday of Lent</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/holy-mass-for-the-5th-sunday-of-lent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 18:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/holy-mass-for-the-5th-sunday-of-lent/</guid>
      <description>Bishops have banned public Masses, but that hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped the Mass, especially the Traditional Latin Mass.
Monsignor Eugene Morris of the Oratory of Ss. Gregory and Augustine is livestreaming the Holy Mass each Sunday at 8:00 a.m. You can watch live on the Oratory&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page.
How to Get the Most from the Mass in Time of Pestilence Msgr. Morris has published a guide to keeping the Mass holy in this time of pestilence as we watch from home instead of participating in the pews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Bad Ideas That Coronavirus Might Finally Kill</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/bad-ideas-that-coronavirus-might-finally-kill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 12:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/bad-ideas-that-coronavirus-might-finally-kill/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a silver lining in the coronavirus pandemic, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to look far. Several bad ideas have become institutionalized in America in recent decades. These bad ideas have served the virus well, made it more deadly, and forced us to shut down our economy.
No more!
If we learn anything from this pandemic, these bad ideas will die:
  Open Offices: Millions of people have seen how moves to open office environments kill productivity and destroy previously good companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End the Great American Stand-Down </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/the-great-american-stand-down-is-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/the-great-american-stand-down-is-over/</guid>
      <description>Today, President Trump nailed it.
 “What we did was we closed everything down. That was our public health strategy. Just close everything, all businesses, old workers, young people, old people, short people, tall people. Every school closed, everything.”
  “If you rethought that or had time to analyze that public health strategy, I don&amp;rsquo;t know that you would say quarantine everyone. I don&amp;rsquo;t even know that that was the best public health policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number of Confirmed Cases Doesn&#39;t Matter—Here&#39;s What Does</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/number-of-infections-doesnt-matterheres-what-does/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 22:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/number-of-infections-doesnt-matterheres-what-does/</guid>
      <description>Hysterical headlines scream about the number of new coronavirus infections every hour. This is a mistake. Ignore those headlines. Number of confirmed cases will rise as number of people tested rises. If we tested everyone for the flu, the number of confirmed flu cases would be astronomical.
Doing some casual analysis, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty obvious what drives the death rate: the number of hospitalizations in a given geographic area.
Last week I pointed out that mean averages are meaningless, even destructive if used to project into the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus Isn&#39;t Finally Important. This Is</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/coronavirus-isnt-finally-important-this-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:06:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/coronavirus-isnt-finally-important-this-is/</guid>
      <description>“Conservatism is the tacit acknowledgement that all that is finally important in human experience is behind us; that the crucial explorations have been undertaken, and that it is given to man to know what are the great truths that emerged from them.”
— William F. Buckley Jr.
Moments ago, I caught myself engrossed in a long news story about the goings on in the United States Senate over the two-trillion dollar coronavirus stimulus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Democrats Refuse to Help, Return To Normal Immediately</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/if-democrats-refuse-to-help-return-to-normal-immediately/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 01:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/if-democrats-refuse-to-help-return-to-normal-immediately/</guid>
      <description>Democrats are bent on plunging America into an economic depression. Democrats love misery.
While I&amp;rsquo;ve been in favor of &amp;ldquo;overreacting&amp;rdquo; to the coronavirus pandemic, we will have no choice but to simply return to status quo ante without immediate economic relief.
I urge President Trump to give 24 hours to pass the Republican Senate emergency relief bill. If it hasn&amp;rsquo;t passed, end the national emergency, rescind all disaster declarations declared on behalf of states, and order the DOJ and the National Guard to guarantee freedom of speech, movement, religion, and commerce in every state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Do and Not To Do During the Lockdown</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/what-to-do-and-not-to-do-during-the-lockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 03:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/what-to-do-and-not-to-do-during-the-lockdown/</guid>
      <description>Newspapers are lying to you. They&amp;rsquo;re feeding you ads pretending it&amp;rsquo;s news.
The headlines are not only false, they&amp;rsquo;re dangerous. And wrong.
The most common such lie goes like this: &amp;ldquo;Best Streaming Service For Shelter in Place&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Here&amp;rsquo;s What to Binge Watch While Locked Down&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s the truth: we will not emerge from the coronavirus crisis stronger or better if we spend this time doing what we&amp;rsquo;ve always done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATED: Watch Traditional Latin Mass at Home Tomorrow </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/watch-traditional-latin-mass-at-home-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/watch-traditional-latin-mass-at-home-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE: I saw this too late, but Msgr. Eugene Morris livestreamed his private Missa Cantata at 8:00 a.m. today, preceded by the Most Holy Rosary of the Blessed Virgin Mary. You can watch replay here:
  Please Like the Facebook page of the Oratory of Ss. Gregory and Augustine.
 Chinese coronavirus has moved bishops around the world to shut down the Catholic Church.
Luckily, the Traditional Latin Mass orders continue to offer the Holy Mass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>¡No Mass!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/no-mass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 13:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/no-mass/</guid>
      <description>And in the streets, the children screamed
The lovers cried, and the poets dreamed
But not a word was spoken
The church bells all were broken
And the three men I admire most
The Father, Son, and the Holy Ghost
They caught the last train for the coast
The day the music died
— Don McLean, American Pie
 “We may not get what we want. We may not get what we need,” chanted the young adults in True Colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can We Be Grateful?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/can-we-be-grateful/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 15:17:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/can-we-be-grateful/</guid>
      <description>When you hear &amp;ldquo;coronavirus&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;COVID-19,&amp;rdquo; you probably think of words like fear, disruption, recession, sick, death, inconvenient, and maybe even China.
What if every time you hear &amp;ldquo;coronavirus,&amp;rdquo; you automatically think &amp;ldquo;gratitude?&amp;rdquo;
How do you feel when you feel grateful?
Most people associate feeling grateful with relief, appreciation, happiness, joy, and safety. Good feelings.
Now, why are you grateful for coronavirus?
That&amp;rsquo;s completely up to you. But I bet you can list just two reasons for being grateful for coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spanish Flu vs. Coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/spanish-flu-vs-coronavirus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 18:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/spanish-flu-vs-coronavirus/</guid>
      <description>You might have heard mention of the Spanish Flu epidemic of 1918 to 1919. Being the great-grandson of a doctor who came out of retirement to assist with St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s response to that epidemic, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d should share a little information about the differences and similarities between the Spanish Flu and coronavirus. I&amp;rsquo;ll briefly cover both the diseases and the responses.
 Note: The word &amp;ldquo;pandemic&amp;rdquo; was unknown in 1918, so contemporaneous references to the disease used the term &amp;ldquo;epidemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opportunity for Excellence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/opportunity-for-excellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 19:43:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/opportunity-for-excellence/</guid>
      <description>Horses are prey to many species. Their behavior, their physiology, is that of a beast under constant threat from, usually, smaller, less beautiful organisms.
Yet, wild horses capture our imaginations. Their grace and beauty, their power, and their gentleness reminds us of what we would be if we lived into our highest ideals for ourselves. We would be worthy of our sufferings.
Your routine has been obliterated. Nothing you did routinely two weeks ago will be done for at least a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Was 5 Years Ahead of Coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/trump-was-5-years-ahead-of-coronavirus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 09:32:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/trump-was-5-years-ahead-of-coronavirus/</guid>
      <description>If the world has listened to Trump in 2015, the coronavirus pandemic might have happened, but it would have been a lot less severe. I say this with absolutely no fear of error.
President Trump become an enemy of the left for just one policy proposal: controlling national borders. Trump not only wanted to restore US border controls that were left to decay since the 1960s, he also encouraged other nations to treat their borders like the front doors of their homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should We Overreact?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/should-we-overreact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 13:07:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/should-we-overreact/</guid>
      <description>Several friends tell me we are overreacting to the Coronavirus pandemic. Others say we are too complacent. So, which is it?
When dealing with an epidemic, we need to consider two things:
 Current numbers are not very useful. Effects are non-linear.  Beware Current Numbers The first argument I hear from those who wish we&amp;rsquo;d just go on with life as usual involves current statistics: number of confirmed cases, number of dead, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mass in Time of Pestilence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/mass-in-time-of-pestilence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 14:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/mass-in-time-of-pestilence/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE: St. Louis Archdiocese has ordered all public Masses cancelled until at least April 6, including the planned Mass in Time of Pestilence.
I don&amp;rsquo;t normally invite people to my church explicitly. But I am about to because we are living in a time of pestilence.
Mass in Time of Pestilence: Wednesdays Each Wednesday for the remainder of Lent, my parish, the Oratory of Saints Gregory and Augustine, will offer a Mass in Time of Pestilence at 6:30 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona Couriers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/corona-couriers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:55:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/corona-couriers/</guid>
      <description>Americans, in a crisis, want something to do. Maybe this is something. A mission.
Senator Martha McSally told Judge Jeanine tonight that the next problem to solve in the coronavirus testing problem is the first mile. We have plenty of labs ready to accept specimens, but getting the specimens from the drive-thru test centers to a drop-off point, say a post office or Fedex drop.
Perhaps people could be enlisted to serve as couriers of these specimens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common Knowledge for the Uncommon Cold</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/common-knowledge-uncommon-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 09:22:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/common-knowledge-uncommon-cold/</guid>
      <description>My wife texted me yesterday asking if we should stock up a couple of weeks worth of food and water.
Now, there&amp;rsquo;s really no empirical reason to stock up on food and water. But there is a psychological/economic reason: the Common Knowledge game.
Common Knowledge is something everyone knows everyone knows. When something becomes Common Knowledge, most people will behave as if the &amp;ldquo;thing&amp;rdquo; were true, if it is not. Stock markets are perfect example of Common Knowledge games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Along Came a Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/along-came-a-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 06:45:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/along-came-a-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>The thing that most rankled the left and crony-capitalist &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; about Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Magic Escalator Ride were his statements on illegal immigration. &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re not sending their best.&amp;rdquo;
The left sees open borders as a means of finally reducing the United States to a pauper nation, a dream long shared by socialists and communists in the US and Europe.
Crony capitalists are less prosaic in their aims. They see open borders as a source of cheap labor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>