<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coronavirus on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/coronavirus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coronavirus on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 13:57:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/coronavirus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The President&#39;s Authority to Open Churches Is the Constitution - VIDEO RANT</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/presidents-authority-to-open-churches-is-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 13:57:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/presidents-authority-to-open-churches-is-constitution/</guid>
      <description>The morons in the White House press corps spend most of today&amp;rsquo;s briefing screaming at press secretary Kayleigh McEnany about President Trump&amp;rsquo;s order to re-open all churches.
The oft-repeated (shouted) question: &amp;ldquo;What federal law is the president relying on to require states to allow church services?&amp;rdquo;
The question demonstrates the absolute ignorance and laziness, the besst-like stupidity, of most journalists.
  The president&amp;rsquo;s authority is the United States Constitution, you mouth-breathing swine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyda Krewson and the Joy of Dictatoring</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/lyda-krewson-and-the-joy-of-dictatoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 08:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/lyda-krewson-and-the-joy-of-dictatoring/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis, Missouri, consistently makes everyone&amp;rsquo;s top 10 lists for worst cities in the United States. The reasons given include crime, lack of opportunity, and dilapidated neighborhoods. Having grown up in the city, and with most of my family still living there, I can add to that list unreliable city services, terrible roads, cronyism, and less than ideal weather.
[Cities People Can&amp;rsquo;t Flee Fast Enough: St. Louis Number 4]
Mayors can&amp;rsquo;t do anything about the weather, of course, but St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should I Wear a Mask</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/masks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 12:59:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/masks/</guid>
      <description>Go ahead and wear a mask, especially if a merchant requires you to, or if not wearing a mask will cause someone undue anxiety. It&amp;rsquo;s charitable.
Also, if you&amp;rsquo;re highly active (get out a lot), you should probably wear a mask and wash your hands if you&amp;rsquo;re going to be around people who are more likely to suffer severely from Coronavirus: the elderly, the obese, people with chronic conditions. While we&amp;rsquo;re at it, basic practices our grandmothers taught us should always apply:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masks Are Not to Control a Virus—Masks Are to Control YOU</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/masks-to-control-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 11:04:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/masks-to-control-you/</guid>
      <description>Sadly, very sincere people, almost in tears, ask our forgiveness for wearing masks.
&amp;ldquo;I wear a mask so I don&amp;rsquo;t unknowingly pass a disease to someone else,&amp;rdquo; one such explained to me on Twitter.
These are not bad people. In fact, they think themselves very, very good people, indeed. The best. The ones willing to wear masks so as not to spread their (remotely possible) contagion to others.
[Read why masks actually increase suffering from Coronavirus]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Humane Approach to Coronavirus Is to Open Up Everything</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-humane-approach-to-coronavirus-open-up-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 10:04:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-humane-approach-to-coronavirus-open-up-everything/</guid>
      <description>The most humanane approach to Coronavirus is to let it spread without overwhelming the hospitals in any location. Mitigation orders, such as wearing masks, stay-at-home orders, and maintaining six feet of distance, while well-intentioned, actually prolong the agony, except when required in places that are in danger of overwhelming the hospital system.
The idea that we can maintain this near-complete shutdown of society for as long as Coronavirus exists is a recipe for disaster on a Biblical scale.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>