<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coronavirus on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/coronavirus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coronavirus on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 11:04:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/coronavirus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Masks Are Not to Control a Virus—Masks Are to Control YOU</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/masks-to-control-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 11:04:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/masks-to-control-you/</guid>
      <description>Sadly, very sincere people, almost in tears, ask our forgiveness for wearing masks.
&amp;ldquo;I wear a mask so I don&amp;rsquo;t unknowingly pass a disease to someone else,&amp;rdquo; one such explained to me on Twitter.
These are not bad people. In fact, they think themselves very, very good people, indeed. The best. The ones willing to wear masks so as not to spread their (remotely possible) contagion to others.
[Read why masks actually increase suffering from Coronavirus]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Humane Approach to Coronavirus Is to Open Up Everything</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-humane-approach-to-coronavirus-open-up-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 10:04:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-humane-approach-to-coronavirus-open-up-everything/</guid>
      <description>The most human approach to Coronavirus is to let it spread without overwhelming the hospitals in any location. Mitigation orders, such as wearing masks, stay-at-home orders, and maintaining six feet of distance, while well-intentioned, actually prolong the agony except in places that are in danger of overwhelming the hospital system.
The idea that we can maintain this near-complete shutdown of society for as long as Coronavirus exists is a recipe for disaster on a Biblical scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Short Movie for Our Time</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/perfect-short-movie-for-our-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 20:47:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/perfect-short-movie-for-our-time/</guid>
      <description>No need for set-up. This is simply the perfect short movie for our time.
Please watch and share widely. Especially with your snitch friends.
  God bless Kevin James.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Significant: CDC Death Count Inflated by 25% per Dr. Birx</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/cdc-death-count-inflated-by-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 15:59:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/cdc-death-count-inflated-by-25/</guid>
      <description>We have all come to know some things about Dr. Deborah Birx, the doctor responsible for the White House&amp;rsquo;s Coronavirus response. Her clear explanations often highlighted the nightly White House Coronavirus Task Force press conferences.
Night after night, we watched and listened as Dr. Birx carefully explained complex statistical and medical information in a way even a reporter could understand. Her style is considered and precise. Understatement and exaggeration seem genetic impossibilities for Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Louis: More People Shot Than Diagnosed with Coronavirus Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-more-shot-than-diagnosed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 17:59:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-more-shot-than-diagnosed/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, May 9, in St. Louis, more people were shot than diagnosed with Coronavirus. Two died from gunshot wounds. The other eight are alive in unknown or unreported condition.
Via the Washington Times:
 Authorities say at least 10 people were shot, two of them fatally, in a single day in St. Louis.
  The St. Louis Post-Dispatch reports that the the gunfire began around 1:15 p.m. Saturday when a 28-year-old man was fatally shot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>