<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>media on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in media on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 15:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Ignore the News</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/04/how-to-ignore-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 15:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/04/how-to-ignore-the-news/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Will Trump survive this?&amp;rdquo;
A friend of mine texted me yesterday. I had no idea what the &amp;ldquo;this&amp;rdquo; was. Later, I learned.
Turns out, like most of the media&amp;rsquo;s breathless revelations about Trump&amp;rsquo;s supposed crimes, the story that people reacted to meant little. The anti-Trump media exploded with fake news, fake interpretations of real news, and speculation that supported their own angry fetishes.
But any reasonable person would respond like my friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unprotected Sects</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/28/unprotected-sects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 16:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/28/unprotected-sects/</guid>
      <description>The television activists at CNN look like college seniors who learned upon returning from winter break that credit requirements for graduation were just upped from 120 hours to 180 hours. And there ain&amp;rsquo;t grandfathering!
Diehard NeverTrumpers attack Trump supporters on social media like bitter, divorcing spouses locked in a pitched custody battle. And there ain&amp;rsquo;t no reconciliation!
Establishment Republicans, Democrats who count on union support, the more radical unions like SEIU and NEA, Planned Parenthood baby killers, and tenured communist professors shriek like hormone-crazed adolescents in fall-down hysterics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relate to This, Mitt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/relate-to-this-mitt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/relate-to-this-mitt-2/</guid>
      <description>The liberal press cannot issue a story about the Republican presidential race that does not refer to Mitt Romney’s need (and inability) to “relate to” conservatives. Puke.
Relate to this: if Mitt Romney’s a conservative, I’m a Hottentot.

By “relate to,” the media and Romney’s handlers actually mean “hoodwink.” While Romney might secure the GOP nomination without conservative support, his campaign will go down in flames without conservative grassroots boots on the ground from Labor Day to Election Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s About Love</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/its-about-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/its-about-love/</guid>
      <description>Trent and Jennifer Humphries—hated by all the right people—just brought to tears to 5,200 eyes.
After Trent told us that the secret to our success is Christ’s love, his wife, Jennifer, described the depths to which evil journalists stooped in the moments following the Giffords shooting.
As the Humphries and their small children returned home from the grocery store, they learned that their next door neighbor—and a beloved friend—was killed in the tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACKS: Media Blame Tea Party for Leftist Crimes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/flashbacks-media-blame-tea-party-for-leftist-crimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 23:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/flashbacks-media-blame-tea-party-for-leftist-crimes/</guid>
      <description>The most often repeated story is not the reluctant hero or the hero who wants to get home. Nor is it about a mother’s love.
The ultimate archetypical story line is:
LIBERAL PRESS ERRONEOUSLY BLAMES TEA PARTY FOR LEFTIST CRIMES
As Jarod Lee Loughner’s political bent emerges, we see the same, predictable story playing out:
1. A horrific crime takes place.*2. Leftist bloggers like Markos Moulitsas blame conservatives.*3. CNN, New York Times, Washinton Post, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>