<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scrooge on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/scrooge/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scrooge on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 10:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/scrooge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Scrooge Teaches Millennials</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/28/what-scrooge-teaches-millennials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/28/what-scrooge-teaches-millennials/</guid>
      <description>_This is the fourth in a series. If you haven’t, please read part 1, part 2, and part 3. _
Because so many school systems have driven great English literature out of students’ hands and minds, it’s possible that some kids never read Charles Dickens’s A Christmas Carol. If you’ve never read this classic, please do so now. You need it.

Back? Good. Fascinating stuff, isn’t it? And so much more accessible than David Copperfield, which was my introduction to Dickens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Government Growth Creates Scrooges</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/27/how-government-growth-creates-scrooges/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/27/how-government-growth-creates-scrooges/</guid>
      <description>Scrooge’s nephew left the office and let in two men in the process. They came to ask for a donation for London’s poor.
 &amp;ldquo;At this festive season of the year, Mr. Scrooge,&amp;rdquo; said the gentleman, taking up a pen, &amp;ldquo;it is more than usually desirable that we should make some slight provision for the Poor and destitute, who suffer greatly at the present time. Many thousands are in want of common necessaries; hundreds of thousands are in want of common comforts, sir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are We the Last Americans?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/07/are-we-the-last-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/07/are-we-the-last-americans/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes nightmares end well.
Sometimes they don’t.
Salon carries a depressing story for the lower 48 of North America. Author Alfred McCoy writes:
 Despite the aura of omnipotence most empires project, a look at their history should remind us that they are fragile organisms. So delicate is their ecology of power that, when things start to go truly bad, empires regularly unravel with unholy speed: just a year for Portugal, two years for the Soviet Union, eight years for France, 11 years for the Ottomans, 17 years for Great Britain, and, in all likelihood, 22 years for the United States, counting from the crucial year 2003.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>