<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>terrorists on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/terrorists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in terrorists on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2007 04:29:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/terrorists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Victory in Iraq!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/10/02/victory-in-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2007 04:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/10/02/victory-in-iraq/</guid>
      <description>Tell everyone Hennessy broke the story. America won the Iraq war. The insurgency is broken! Peace prevails. The terrorists are routed!Where are the headlines? A man between the ages of 18 and 30 has a better chance of being murdered in Philadelphiathan of dying in Iraq in September. The third head of al Qaeda in Iraq is dead&amp;ndash;three in 18 months. Ascending to that throne is no promotion. Face it, folks, we won the war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Charleston Terrorist Story **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/06/the-charleston-terrorist-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2007 22:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/06/the-charleston-terrorist-story/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE: 6:42 p.m. CDT: MSNBC.com now reporting that the two Muslim men arrested near the Charleston Naval Weapons Station were in possession of pipe bombs. Their attorney assures us that a) they have a really good reason for possessing pipe bombs, and b) the two Middle Eastern men with pipe bombs near a Navy base are victims of racial profiling. Whatever. Profile away.
   Before details about the pipe bombs were released, the executive director of a civil rights organization for Muslims in Tampa criticized the arrest as racial profiling, an accusation South Carolina police denied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bad Day for Democrats -- and Terrorists</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/a-bad-day-for-democrats-and-terrorists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2007 22:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/a-bad-day-for-democrats-and-terrorists/</guid>
      <description>Gateway Pundit provides this top-shelf story of a US F-16 taking out 30 or so al Qaeda terrorists in Iraq. It&amp;rsquo;s a thing of beauty, and it must make Democrats sick to see their well-trained comrades die under American attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dearborn = Baghdad?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/25/dearborn-baghdad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2007 02:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/25/dearborn-baghdad/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps we need a surge in Dearborn, MI (gateway pundit).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Al Qaeda Impotent?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/23/is-al-qaeda-impotent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/23/is-al-qaeda-impotent/</guid>
      <description>Captain Ed raises an interesting point in response to al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s declaration of war on North Africa
 Despite their general inability to prevail in Iraq, successfully detonate explosives in Britain, and do anything else in the US, AQ warned Muslims to stay away from their own government buildings on the south side of the Mediterranean
 He writes a good piece&amp;ndash;which reminded me of this humor entry I posted in 2003 and agian in 2005:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>