<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Donald Trump on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/donald-trump/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Donald Trump on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 06:45:37 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/donald-trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Along Came a Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/along-came-a-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 06:45:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/along-came-a-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>The thing that most rankled the left and crony-capitalist &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; about Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Magic Escalator Ride were his statements on illegal immigration. &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re not sending their best.&amp;rdquo;
The left sees open borders as a means of finally reducing the United States to a pauper nation, a dream long shared by socialists and communists in the US and Europe.
Crony capitalists are less prosaic in their aims. They see open borders as a source of cheap labor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your President Trump: Season Six</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-season-six/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:18:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-season-six/</guid>
      <description>Scott Adams says Donald Trump lives his life like a movie or television series. (See Looking Ahead to Season Four of Trump for a complete explanation.) Being New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, it&amp;rsquo;s time to look back on Season Five (2019) and, then, look ahead to season six (2020) of Trump.
Season Five: Mueller Report and Ukraine Hoax Going into 2019, the Fed had slowed the incredible Trump Economy with aggressive interest rate hikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do Democrats Expect?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/what-do-democrats-expect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 18:50:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/what-do-democrats-expect/</guid>
      <description>If Democrats cross the Rubicon by impeaching President Trump, they will be sending a strong signal: no Republican president will ever survive his first term.
How do you expect people to respond? I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the people President Obama derisively labeled &amp;ldquo;bitter clingers.&amp;rdquo;
  The people RealPolitics data analyst Sean Trende identified as &amp;ldquo;downscale, Northern, rural &amp;hellip; H. Ross Perot voters.&amp;rdquo;
Or, to put it another way, Tea Partiers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mueller Prophecy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/the-mueller-prophecy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 19:57:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/the-mueller-prophecy/</guid>
      <description>Friends,
Let me begin by saying &amp;ldquo;I am sorry&amp;rdquo; to Robert Mueller and his family.
I have been critical of Mr. Mueller and his sham &amp;ldquo;investigation.&amp;rdquo; I have been uncharitable to him. And I am sorry.
It became clear today that Mr. Mueller wasn&amp;rsquo;t a hostile actor. Obviously, Mueller is seriously impaired. What we saw in his selection of lawyers, in his handling of the investigation, in his management of partisan and criminal conduct by senior Justice Department officials under his command resulted not from malice toward the president but from incompetence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Tweets Trigger Word-Thinkers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-triggers-word-thinkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 15:37:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-triggers-word-thinkers/</guid>
      <description>For a few weeks in June and July, Nancy Pelosi was doing a good job of isolating the Hate Squad. Pelosi realizes that the Hate Squad is bad for Democrats. She saw the Hate Squad growing in media attention, and she worked hard to stop that trend.
Then, like a genius, Donald Trump did what Trump does best: he stuck out his chin to let his opponent (Pelosi) punch herself out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romney Doesn&#39;t Get It: Flanders Fields</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/romney-doesnt-get-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 20:23:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/romney-doesnt-get-it/</guid>
      <description>Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s naïveté is almost cute. He thinks it&amp;rsquo;s still 1982.
But it&amp;rsquo;s not cute because it&amp;rsquo;s destructive. The world has changed, and everything is ready to fall apart.
See, Mitt is mad that President Donald Trump hasn&amp;rsquo;t done more to &amp;ldquo;unite&amp;rdquo; the country. Mittens wants the president to be more &amp;ldquo;unifying.&amp;rdquo;
Because &amp;ldquo;trying&amp;rdquo; to unite the country would solve everything, right?
But the world has changed. Americans today are as polarized as they were 1861.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald the Great</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/06/donald-the-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 01:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/06/donald-the-great/</guid>
      <description>In less than two years, Donald J. Trump has already achieved more as President of the United States than most of his predecessors did in eight or more years.  Trump has eliminated more federal regulations than all past presidents combined Trump pushed through Congress one of the largest tax cuts in history Trump has renegotiated numerous trade agreements, including NAFTA Trump has reinvigorated American manufacturing Trump has sparked the strongest economy in US history Trump has reduce unemployment for blacks and Hispanics to their lowest levels in history Trump has achieved a remarkable 35% favorability rating among blacks, the highest for a Republican in modern times Trump has placed on the Supreme Court two solidly conservative jurists Trump has given Republicans the courage to stand up to evil progressives Trump has reunited the warring factions of the Republican base Trump has changed Americans&amp;rsquo; expectations of the office of president Trump has redefined what it means to be presidential Trump has exposed America&amp;rsquo;s domestic enemies and left vulnerable  Even those who viscerally hate Donald Trump—and there are many—cannot deny that Trump&amp;rsquo;s impact on the USA and on the world exceeds even his impact on the New York City skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Morning in America Part II</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/01/trump-morning-in-america-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 12:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/01/trump-morning-in-america-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>When you hide the name and simply list accomplishments, any reasonable person would agree that Donald Trump has done more good for the country than any president in living memory.
Economy ** African-America unemployment lowest in history ** Hispanic unemployment lowest in history ** Female unemployment lowest in 18 years ** Stock market up 35% since *election
** Manufacturing jobs growing for *first time in decades ** Steelworkers going to back to work after humiliating layoffs ** Regulatory cuts have reinvigorated dying industries ** Millions of new jobs planned across the country</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to spot a #StableGenius</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/01/06/how-to-spot-a-stablegenius/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 17:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/01/06/how-to-spot-a-stablegenius/</guid>
      <description>You probably would like to know how to spot a very stable genius. It&amp;rsquo;s a skill that can come in handy. (Free Bonus: I&amp;rsquo;ll point you to the funniest thing I ever read in my life. Just because I like you. But first . . .)
Well, today, Donald J. Trump gave us a lesson in genius detection.
With the MSM chanting &amp;ldquo;mentally unfit&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;stupid,&amp;rdquo; our very stable genius president took to his favorite persuasion tool, Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking ahead to season four of Trump: The President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/looking-ahead-to-season-four-of-trump-the-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 18:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/looking-ahead-to-season-four-of-trump-the-president/</guid>
      <description>Scott Adams first identified Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s greatest strength. What do you think that might be?
It&amp;rsquo;s not his money or his business experience. Those are strengths, sure, but they&amp;rsquo;re not THE strength.
Scott Adams believes Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign was a movie script. Here&amp;rsquo;s what Adams wrote way, way back when Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy was still just a PR stunt because he had zero chance of winning even a single primary:
 A movie script is almost always arranged in what the professionals call a three-act form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 will change American culture at its core</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/26/2018-will-change-american-culture-at-its-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 18:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/26/2018-will-change-american-culture-at-its-core/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re wondering how things will change in 2018, you might think back the mid-1980s.
In the 1980s, leftist professors, leftist news media, and leftist entertainers were angry. For years, they&amp;rsquo;d preached that Ronald Reagan was a neo-Nazi buffoon whose incompetence and malice would destroy America. Maybe even wipe out the human species. &amp;ldquo;I believe Ronald Reagan can turn America back into what it once was,&amp;rdquo; said comedian Steve Martin on Saturday Night Live in 1980, &amp;ldquo;a vast wasteland covered with ice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Losing a Laugher (Video)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/27/nfl-losing-a-laugher-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 01:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/27/nfl-losing-a-laugher-video/</guid>
      <description>Blowout. Embarrassment. Lopsided. Laugher.
Humiliation.
Fans are doing to the NFL what Ray Rice did to his girlfriend in that elevator.
https://youtu.be/Dp47DeNAukw
Bars are banning football.
The VFW has condemned the NFL. 
Fans are burning jerseys.
American Sniper&amp;rsquo;s widow livid.
Viewership is down 11% year-over-year.
Fans boo players they recognize.
Baltimore fans demanding Ray Lewis statue come down like he&amp;rsquo;s General Lee.
Major NFL sponsors are under increasing pressure to pull ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Hates Football Fans; Fire Them All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/nfl-hates-football-fans-fire-them-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 15:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/nfl-hates-football-fans-fire-them-all/</guid>
      <description>You can see the battle brewing. It&amp;rsquo;s coming to a head. And no one is telling you the real reason the NFL is dying before your eyes.
Everyone sees the symptoms of football&amp;rsquo;s death spiral: empty stadiums. Crashed ratings. low quality. Criminals on the field. Some people call it &amp;ldquo;the National Felony League.&amp;rdquo;
Frustrated fans look for better entertainment. Ticket sales remain high for one reason: stupid corporate executives. Stupid executives think it&amp;rsquo;s still a status symbol to control lots of NFL tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck and Nancy and Donald and Mitch and Paul</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/17/chuck-and-nancy-and-donald-and-mitch-and-paul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 20:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/17/chuck-and-nancy-and-donald-and-mitch-and-paul/</guid>
      <description>You can almost see it in your mind if you try. The cartons of Chinese takeout. The torn blisters of soy sauce. Nancy Pelosi, former swimsuit model, laughing at The Donald&amp;rsquo;s off-color jokes. About Mitch McConnell. Or Paul Ryan. While Chuck fills color of his own, about deals he helped The Donald put together back in New York. Stuff that didn&amp;rsquo;t make it into The Art of the Deal or The Art of the Comeback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strategy That Dare Not Speak Its Name</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/06/the-strategy-that-dare-not-speak-its-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/06/the-strategy-that-dare-not-speak-its-name/</guid>
      <description>By now you&amp;rsquo;ve heard that President Trump struck a deal with Nancy Pelosi and Chuck Schumer. Trump struck a deal to raise the debt ceiling. Trump struck a deal by going around Congressional Republicans. Trump struck a deal with Democrats.
It&amp;rsquo;s about time, frankly. But Trump can go a lot further on this path. If I were his chief strategist, I&amp;rsquo;d tell him to go further. How far? Keep reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laugh at them, not with them</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/03/laugh-at-them-not-with-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 02:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/03/laugh-at-them-not-with-them/</guid>
      <description>The left is crying. One guy on twitter is nearly suicidal. Hoft has more.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened.
Someone posted this photo on twitter. All the sane people laughed.
@realDonaldTrump retweeted. And now it&amp;rsquo;s the left&amp;rsquo;s new Russian conspiracy.
I remember when all the best comedians were liberals. But the new left traded its sense of humor for baseball bats with ten penny nails.
USA!
Meanwhile, the pre-schoolers at CNN have their panties in a bunch because the President of the United States wore a hat emblazoned with USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Character and Leadership in Houston</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/02/character-and-leadership-in-houston/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 18:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/02/character-and-leadership-in-houston/</guid>
      <description>When I watch President Trump in Texas, I am reminded of one of my favorite books.
Arthur C. Brooks wrote in The Conservative Heart:
 There is a common misconception that conservatives are materialistic. We are not, and this confusion is a central political irony of our time. Progressives truly want to help the poor but have tried to solve poverty primarily with government money, relegating talk of culture to the past and focusing more and more on income inequality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In 3 Minutes You&#39;ll Be Able Fend Off Any Verbal Attack About Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/23/in-3-minutes-youll-be-able-fend-off-any-verbal-attack-about-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 04:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/23/in-3-minutes-youll-be-able-fend-off-any-verbal-attack-about-trump/</guid>
      <description>You probably don&amp;rsquo;t believe it. You&amp;rsquo;re probably reading just to argue. But three minutes from now, you&amp;rsquo;ll be armed.
Armed and ready to do verbal combat.
Armed and ready to defend your Trump vote.
Armed and read to win any intellectual confrontation.
Think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible? Keep reading. You&amp;rsquo;ll find out defending your vote for Trump is easier than you could imagine. Your opponent will be standing there, jaw moving, lips quivering, voice lost, brain scrambled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regarding Jeff Sessions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/25/regarding-jeff-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 03:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/25/regarding-jeff-sessions/</guid>
      <description>I campaigned for and voted for Donald Trump. I stand 100% behind Trump today.
I support Trump because he&amp;rsquo;s a fighter. He&amp;rsquo;s a man of action. Trump prosecutes his causes, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t navel gaze.
Jeff Sessions is a good man. He&amp;rsquo;s a good Washington man. He has standards of decorum. Standards I admire.
Trump has no standards of decorum. But I voted for Trump because history has made decorum a liability, even a vice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First 13er President: A Gen X Independence Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/03/first-13er-president-a-gen-x-independence-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 00:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/03/first-13er-president-a-gen-x-independence-day/</guid>
      <description>“As they reach their turn for national leadership, 13ers will produce no-nonsense winners who will excel at cunning, flexibility, and deft timing.”
 —Neil Howe and William Strauss, 13th Gen: Abort, Retry, Ignore, Fail?
I’ve written before that 2016 was the first Gen X Election. And that Donald Trump would be the first Gen X president. Not because he’s an Xer, but because he personifies our coming-of-age view of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greatest 4th of July! WrestlemaniaCNNTakeDown! (Video)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/02/greatest-4th-of-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 15:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/02/greatest-4th-of-july/</guid>
      <description>President Trump makes everything better. Everything. And this video, which he just tweeted, made this 4th of the July the best since 1776. (Click twice to get play this video)
   #FraudNewsCNN #FNN pic.twitter.com/WYUnHjjUjg
 — Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) July 2, 2017
The left and CNN will, of course, be outraged. They don&amp;rsquo;t have a sense of humor.
President Trump has a fine sense of humor. I can see the grin on his face as he tapped out &amp;ldquo;#FraudNewsCNN&amp;rdquo; and hit the send button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I disavow every Republican who disavowed Trump&#39;s tweets</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/29/i-disavow-every-republican-who-disavowed-trumps-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/29/i-disavow-every-republican-who-disavowed-trumps-tweets/</guid>
      <description>When Reagan was president, we wanted him to hit back harder on the press. We wanted him to put Sam Donaldson in his place. We wanted him to call out the fake news.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_22208&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;750&amp;rdquo;]2/5/1981 President Reagan during an interview with Sam Donaldson of ABC News Leslie Stahl of CBS News and Judith Woodruff of NBC News with James Brady at the Cross Hall White House Library[/caption]
But Reagan didn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the Russian Narrative Broke</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/27/when-the-russian-narrative-broke/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 14:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/27/when-the-russian-narrative-broke/</guid>
      <description>When did the narrative break?
Was it the assassination attempt on GOP Congressmen?
Was it Comey&amp;rsquo;s admission that Trump was never under investigation?
Was it Kathy Griffin&amp;rsquo;s grim ISIS imitation?
Was it Trump&amp;rsquo;s 5-0 winning streak in special elections?
Like the ageless question of how many licks it takes to get to the Tootsie-Roll center of a Tootsie-Pop, the world may never know. Never know just when the Russian narrative broke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz: Mensch!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/27/ted-cruz-mensch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 02:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/27/ted-cruz-mensch/</guid>
      <description>If you read my blog, you know I&amp;rsquo;ve had differences with Senator Ted Cruz. But the Senator has stepped up. Bigly! Only a gentleman would do what Cruz just did with his El Chapo bill.
Remember the GOP race? Cruz and Trump went at each other like nobody&amp;rsquo;s business. Wives and all. While Cruz couldn&amp;rsquo;t bring himself to endorse Trump at the convention, Ted has stepped up a lot since the election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>False Flag or Not</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/08/false-flag-or-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/08/false-flag-or-not/</guid>
      <description>The contemporary term false flag describes covert operations that are designed to deceive in such a way that activities appear as though they are being carried out by entities, groups, or nations other than those who actually planned and executed them. [Wikipedia]
 Think of a time when you acted on false information. You knew it might be false, but you acted as if it was true. Why did you do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Launched 59 Cruise Missiles at Leftist Narratives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/06/trump-launched-59-cruise-missiles-at-leftist-narratives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 02:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/06/trump-launched-59-cruise-missiles-at-leftist-narratives/</guid>
      <description>No child of God should ever suffer such horror.
 —President Donald J. Trump
The most powerful weapon in the world is narrative.
The most powerful weapon in the world is narrative.
That&amp;rsquo;s another way of saying the pen is mightier than the sword.
The most powerful weapon in the world is narrative.
Tonight, President Trump blew up four narratives of the left. And he made America great again in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Admin Wiretapped Trump *UPDATE 2*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/31/obama-admin-wiretapped-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/31/obama-admin-wiretapped-trump/</guid>
      <description>Now you know. You can stop doubting. You have more than hope.
The Obama administration spied on Donald Trump and his campaign and transition teams. There is no longer any doubt.
The questions that remain are:
** Who ordered and authorized the illegal wiretaps? ** Who illegally received and disseminated the intelligence? ** What did Obama know?
It&amp;rsquo;s easy to declare the Obama Admin guilty after Evelyn Farkas&amp;rsquo;s admissions on MSNBC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neediness</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/neediness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/neediness/</guid>
      <description>President Trump is teaching the world a huge lesson. That valuable lesson goes something like this:
Don&amp;rsquo;t be needy.
Jim Camp is a world-famous negotiation coach. Jim has led some enormous negotiations: labor disputes, huge multi-national buys, and mergers. This is is what Jim says about neediness in his book Start With No:
 It is absolutely imperative that you as a negotiator understand the importance of this point. You do NOT need this deal, because** to be needy is to lose control and make bad decisions**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Many Times Trump&#39;s Crazy Statements Turned Out to Be Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/07/many-times-trumps-crazy-statements-turned-out-to-be-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 01:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/07/many-times-trumps-crazy-statements-turned-out-to-be-right/</guid>
      <description>Almost every time Donald Trump says something crazy, something so outlandish and wrong, he later turns out to be right.
I know his critics can&amp;rsquo;t read my blog. (Literally, they can&amp;rsquo;t. They have a psychological problem that prevents their brains from processing information that&amp;rsquo;s inconsistent with their beliefs.) But for those of you who want to be right with the truth instead of just right with your own opinion, this will be a great post to forward to your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump&#39;s Crazy Ivan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/06/donald-trumps-crazy-ivan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 03:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/06/donald-trumps-crazy-ivan/</guid>
      <description>Cold War submarine lore. I can&amp;rsquo;t go into all of it here, but I can tell you about one bit of that lore: the Crazy Ivan.
Modern submarines have incredible passive sonar arrays. They can hear everything in the ocean for hundreds of miles around. Everything.
Everything except something directly behind them. Behind a submarine is a big propeller or &amp;ldquo;screw.&amp;rdquo; It turns. It pushes water abaft. The noise and the motion combine to prevent sound waves from reaching the sensors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/17/the-joy-of-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 18:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/17/the-joy-of-trump/</guid>
      <description>What bothers you most when you&amp;rsquo;re in a bad mood?
You can imagine what it&amp;rsquo;s like be in a bad mood, can&amp;rsquo;t you? People go through periods of deep funk when nothing seems bright or cheerful, don&amp;rsquo;t they?
And when you&amp;rsquo;re in those moods, what&amp;rsquo;s the worst thing? That&amp;rsquo;s right, it&amp;rsquo;s being around a bunch of happy people having fun.
And that&amp;rsquo;s exactly how the left feels when they see Trump at a press conference: miserable amid the fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greatest Presser Ever. Wow. Stunned Happy.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/16/greatest-presser-ever-wow-stunned-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 00:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/16/greatest-presser-ever-wow-stunned-happy/</guid>
      <description>Imagine Michael Jordan&amp;rsquo;s best game ever. Or Tiger Woods. That&amp;rsquo;s what it was like watching President Trump today. Amazing.
The President looked poised, cheerful, and humorous. He volleyed with Jim Acosta of CNN. He rated each question &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;bad.&amp;rdquo; He explained why he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a nuclear war with Russia because the press seems to think nuclear war is a good thing. He mocked those in the press who want him to bomb that Russian intel ship off Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unprotected Sects</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/28/unprotected-sects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 16:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/28/unprotected-sects/</guid>
      <description>The television activists at CNN look like college seniors who learned upon returning from winter break that credit requirements for graduation were just upped from 120 hours to 180 hours. And there ain&amp;rsquo;t grandfathering!
Diehard NeverTrumpers attack Trump supporters on social media like bitter, divorcing spouses locked in a pitched custody battle. And there ain&amp;rsquo;t no reconciliation!
Establishment Republicans, Democrats who count on union support, the more radical unions like SEIU and NEA, Planned Parenthood baby killers, and tenured communist professors shriek like hormone-crazed adolescents in fall-down hysterics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrible Day for NeverTrump—Great Day for the Constitution</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/terrible-day-for-nevertrump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/terrible-day-for-nevertrump/</guid>
      <description>One way to summarize Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s first business day in office is to say he followed through on many, many campaign promises. Another way to look at it is that Trump slaughtered NeverTrump. Both explanations are accurate, but one is the cause, the other the effect.
First, you know I pay very little attention to Facebook. Too much craziness over there. But friends of mine do occasionally send me screen shots of things they find outrageous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Spot Journalism&#39;s Psychosis</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/how-to-spot-journalisms-psychosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 12:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/how-to-spot-journalisms-psychosis/</guid>
      <description>When your brain automatically alters perceptions, there&amp;rsquo;s something wrong with you.
Reporters have this psychosis. Journalists. They have very bad ADHD it seems. They can&amp;rsquo;t pay attention. Like kids with ADHD. Chuck Todd and everybody at Business Insider should probably take Ritalin or something.
Reporters are also narcissists. No one goes into journalism unless they have a pathologically inflated ego. No one.
So I&amp;rsquo;m going to walk you through the proof, slowly, so even our narcissistic, hyperactive, attention-deficit-disordered journalists can understand that Sean Spicer played with them like a cat pawing a dying moth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Meant It All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/22/trump-meant-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 18:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/22/trump-meant-it-all/</guid>
      <description>Trump&amp;rsquo;s enemies took refuge in the self-created narrative that his campaign was 100% American showmanship. The crooked press and the corrupt establishment, while dissing Trump publicly, scoffed privately. They &amp;ldquo;knew&amp;rdquo; his supporters were idiots and yahoos—marginally functional Neanderthals from America&amp;rsquo;s unreconstructed backwoods whose ability to think, handicapped by genetics, was further crippled by the moonshine distilled in the shed behind their putrid outhouse for personal consumption by their incest-ridden family of knuckle-dragging racist homophobes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump: The Greatest President-elect in History</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/08/donald-trump-the-greatest-president-elect-in-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 03:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/08/donald-trump-the-greatest-president-elect-in-history/</guid>
      <description>No one saw this coming.
In the month since the election on November 8, America burst out of the longest economic malaise since the Great Depression. Historians will credit the election of Donald Trump as the 45th President of the United States. Those historians will be right, of course, but how can that be? President Trump won&amp;rsquo;t take office until Friday, January 20, 2017. Today is December 8, 2016. Yet Trump has already transformed America more in four weeks than Barack Obama did in eight years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Transformed the Presidency Already</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/01/trump-transformed-the-presidency-already/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 02:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/01/trump-transformed-the-presidency-already/</guid>
      <description>Tonight, Donald Trump delivered what will become the new standard of presidential oratory in Cincinnati, OH. President-elect Trump thanked Ohio voters for a landslide victory in the state with a barnburner of a speech that rivaled his most animated and colorful rally speeches during the 2015-2016 campaign.
The art of the speech will never be the same.
Frequently breaking from prepared remarks, Trump attacked the dishonest media, mocked a leftist reporter who cried when Hillary lost, and reminded voters, &amp;ldquo;Folks, how many times did we hear this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump: America&#39;s Work-craft Carrier</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/30/donald-trump-americas-work-craft-carrier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 13:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/30/donald-trump-americas-work-craft-carrier/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump ran on a promise to bring American jobs back to America. And to make America great again. Even though his presidency is still two months away, he&amp;rsquo;s already delivering.
Ford is staying. Apple is looking to move iPhone assembly to the USA. And, last night, Carrier announced it will keep 1,000 jobin Indianapolis.
**America is #WINNING again. **
When Donald Trump railed against Carrier Air Conditioner&amp;rsquo;s decision to move over 1,000 jobs to Mexico, the fake news media mocked and ridiculed Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glad to See Trump Focusing on Working People Instead of Worrying About Hillary Clinton</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/23/glad-to-see-trump-focusing-on-working-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 15:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/23/glad-to-see-trump-focusing-on-working-people/</guid>
      <description>You might have heard that President-elect Trump has said he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to waste time and attention on Hillary&amp;rsquo;s email server. You also might have heard that some people are upset about that. I&amp;rsquo;m not one of them.
Months ago I was telling people Trump should announce that, if elected, he will pardon Hillary Clinton for all crimes related to her email scandal. I had two reasons for promoting this strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Happening! Divorces Down, Marriage Up</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/17/its-happening-divorces-down-marriage-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 20:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/17/its-happening-divorces-down-marriage-up/</guid>
      <description>Last weekI made three bold predictions about how Trump would change American culture:
*1. Marriage would rebound, as would the fertility rate *2. People would dress better *3. Legacy becomes physical things, not mere laws
Trump&amp;rsquo;s influence on American culture can already be seen in marriage and divorce rates. According to Bloomberg, divorce is down to 35-year lows and marriage rates began pumping up during the recent campaign.
 The U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways President Trump Changes Everything</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/12/3-ways-president-trump-changes-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 02:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/12/3-ways-president-trump-changes-everything/</guid>
      <description>Trump&amp;rsquo;s win is far bigger than the vote. As British General Cornwallis said at the end of the movie &amp;lsquo;The Patriot,&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Everything will change . . . everything has changed.&amp;rdquo;
If you&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about policy, you&amp;rsquo;re thinking really, really small. Trump&amp;rsquo;s influence is way bigger. Here are three ways Trump will change America for a generation.
A Change of Uniform Since the late 1990s, American business and social life have gone uber casual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneur vs. Empress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/11/entrepreneur-vs-empress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 02:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/11/entrepreneur-vs-empress/</guid>
      <description>Adam Carolla noticed something I didn&amp;rsquo;t.
Carolla&amp;rsquo;s first reaction to the election results was this. Hillary Clinton built herself a Logan&amp;rsquo;s Run type palace for her would-be coronation. Donald Trump accepted the presidency in a room that might double as a Hometown Buffet.
Put another way, here&amp;rsquo;s what the winner&amp;rsquo;s auditorium:
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_21054&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;1000&amp;rdquo;]Image clipped from UPI[/caption]
And here&amp;rsquo;s the winner&amp;rsquo;s ballroom:
Let that contrast sink in.
Every penny of the Clintons&amp;rsquo; hundreds of millions came from taxpayers one way or another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Donald Trump Completed the Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/11/how-donald-trump-completed-the-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 02:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/11/how-donald-trump-completed-the-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I forget what originally drove me to call for a tea party protest in St. Louis.
One motivation was fear of missing out because a dozen other cities were planning protests. Another driver was a desire change the direction of the country. And at least some of it was the frustrated actor in me looking for an outlet.
Since two-thirds of those motivations appeal only to me, let’s focus on the middle one: change the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Makes People Better</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/05/trump-makes-people-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 22:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/05/trump-makes-people-better/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/pm8n9qVIK_8
The more you learn about people like William, the more you look forward to President Trump.
Make America Great Again</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Told Us Trump Won</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/10/hillary-told-us-trump-won/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/10/hillary-told-us-trump-won/</guid>
      <description>I really want to go to bed, but my brain won&amp;rsquo;t sleep until I type this out.
Hillary Clinton told us Trump won the debate with her final answer. Final answer.
An audience member asked the closing question. He challenged the candidates to say something nice about their opponents. Hillary went first.
The right way to answer those screwball questions is to say something nice and sit down. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain why in a moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flies Are Coming Home to Roost</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/09/the-flies-are-coming-home-to-roost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 04:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/09/the-flies-are-coming-home-to-roost/</guid>
      <description>Frank Luntz—no fan of Donald J. Trump—said it best: he came into the second debate believing the race was over, but he came out believing Trump is back in the race.
I realize CNN bought a poll that said Clinton won the debate. But CNN has a history of lying, cheating, and hiding facts. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t bet a wooden nickel on anything I heard on CNN.
I watched most of the debate at a bar in South St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Act Like You Learned Something About Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/09/how-to-act-like-you-learned-something-about-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 15:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/09/how-to-act-like-you-learned-something-about-trump/</guid>
      <description>People in the media and the GOP are acting like they learned something on Friday. That&amp;rsquo;s when the Washington Post released an audio (later conjoined with video) of Donald Trump talking lewd about his exploits with women.
I say media people and Republicans are &amp;ldquo;acting&amp;rdquo; like they learned something, because they didn&amp;rsquo;t. We didn&amp;rsquo;t. Everybody who&amp;rsquo;s paid attention to the race (or pop culture) already knew how Trump is. Everybody knows Trump brags about his sexual prowess and how women melt around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinton vs. Trump on Women</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/08/clinton-vs-trump-on-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 15:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/08/clinton-vs-trump-on-women/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Access Hollywood audio has a lot of people cringing. Especially a lot of men who remember the things they&amp;rsquo;ve said about women around other men. And I&amp;rsquo;m talking about men you respect and admire like husbands and dads and brothers. Comedians know what I &amp;lsquo;m talking about.
I won&amp;rsquo;t bore you with the biology of it all, but you probably realize that men and women are fundamentally different. Especially when it comes to reproductive success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Closing Statement Tonight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/26/trumps-closing-statement-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 13:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/26/trumps-closing-statement-tonight/</guid>
      <description>If he asked me, here&amp;rsquo;s how I&amp;rsquo;d end the debate of the century.
First, I&amp;rsquo;d close off any open loops that arose during the debate. Then:
 American children under 10 have never known a year with three-percent GDP growth. Americans under 40 have no memory real wages going up. And American people of every age, from infant to elderly, never knew a time of greater threat from foreign terrorist attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#NeverTrump Self Immolation Over Trusty Ted Cruz</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/24/nevertrump-self-immolation-over-trusty-ted-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 17:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/24/nevertrump-self-immolation-over-trusty-ted-cruz/</guid>
      <description>This is for the people, like me, who realized sometime between June 2015 and June 2016 that Donald Trump is at least better than Hillary and possibly a transformational character who can reverse America&amp;rsquo;s descent into chaos.
 “A leader is a man who can adapt principles to circumstances.” – General George Patton Jr
 You might think this post is an attempt to reach #NeverTrumpers and bring them on board the Trump Train.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Surging Up, Up, and Away</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/04/trump-surging-up-up-and-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 02:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/04/trump-surging-up-up-and-away/</guid>
      <description>Politico announced Tuesday: Clinton&amp;rsquo;s Advisors Tell Her to Prep for a Landslide
Inquisitor said the same day: Hillary Clinton Campaign Preparing for a Landslide
The stories beneath those headlines spoke of the intense hubris inside the Democratic Party and the Clinton campaign. Their &amp;ldquo;experts&amp;rdquo; declared the race over on Tuesday. Assured of a landslide, Clinton stopped campaigning and turned to what the Clinton&amp;rsquo;s do best: extorting money from the ultra-rich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As You Watch, You Will Be Healed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/03/as-you-watch-you-will-be-healed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 17:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/03/as-you-watch-you-will-be-healed/</guid>
      <description>You probably never thought you&amp;rsquo;d see anything like this, but it just happened.
What&amp;rsquo;s it like when a nation turns from strife to peace and healing?
Watch this most amazing moment in politics, in history. You might find yourself tearing up when the Bishop wraps The Donald in a prayer shawl. Powerful.
https://youtu.be/79OAyAc3G-M?t=3m28s
In my remarks to the 500 people at the Tea Party for Trump at Surdyke Harley-Davidson in Festus last Sunday, I spoke about the need for healing in America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Trump-Pena Nieto Communique</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/31/predicting-the-trump-nieto-comminique/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 19:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/31/predicting-the-trump-nieto-comminique/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump will land in Mexico City. He&amp;rsquo;s there for a summit meeting with Mexico&amp;rsquo;s President Pena Nieto.
Before Trump even woke up this morning, the Washington Post declared the future meeting a complete disaster that Trump will never recover from. The Post predicted a complete visual and verbal disaster even though there&amp;rsquo;s no historical evidence on which to base such a prediction.
The WaPo is probably projecting its wishes, not its beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Reagan Almost Blew It in 1980</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/23/how-reagan-almost-blew-it-in-1980/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/23/how-reagan-almost-blew-it-in-1980/</guid>
      <description>If you enjoy this post, you have to thank your fellow reader, Tony, for reading the whole TIME article from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post. He pointed out more similarities between 1980 and 2016. Especially Reagan&amp;rsquo;s gaffes and Democrats&amp;rsquo; complacency.
First, the gaffes.
You hear about Trump stepping on his own applause lines. He announced Steve Bannon and Kellyanne Conway the day after the best speech of his life (until then). He wondered aloud (via Twitter) what Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 looks like a repeat of 1980</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/22/2016-repeat-1980/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 17:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/22/2016-repeat-1980/</guid>
      <description>You probably remember that in September 1980 voters couldn’t wait to cast a vote for Reagan.
If you remember it like that, you remember wrong. At least a little wrong.
TIME magazine examined voter sentiment in its September 15, 1980, issue. Voters that year sounded a lot like voters this year. Here’s how TIME’s Ed Magnuson summarized the voters of 1980:
 Disenchanted, but not apathetic. Caring about issues, although much more concerned about character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Week To Go. Are You Ready?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/21/one-week-to-go-are-you-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 17:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/21/one-week-to-go-are-you-ready/</guid>
      <description>Time is running out fast.
The St. Louis Area Tea Party for Trump is Sunday, August 28 at 4:00 p.m. at Surdyke Harley-Davidson in Festus, MO.
Here&amp;rsquo;s your checklist to make sure you&amp;rsquo;re ready:
[frontend-checklist name=&amp;quot;Tea Party for Trump&amp;rdquo;]
Sign Ideas Make sure your signs embarrass no one. Don&amp;rsquo;t give the liars at CNN anything act all righteous about. Here are some sign ideas:
** Winning with Trump ** Donald Trump: YOU&amp;rsquo;RE HIRED ** Trump Stands With US ** Trump Never Sleeps ** Trump Leads from the FRONT ** All Aboard the TRUMP TRAIN ** I&amp;rsquo;m ALL IN for Trump ** HONK if you&amp;rsquo;re voting TRUMP ** Make America Great Again ** Make America Work Again ** Make America Safe Again ** Make America Strong Again ** I [HEART] Trump ** Build The Wall ** You Can’t Fake Great Kids ** Legal Immigration Rocks ** Borders Define a Country ** Dignity = Meaningful Work ** I’m Choosing Scalia’s Successor ** What’s Wrong with Greatness?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Misdirection Play</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/19/trumps-misdirection-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 22:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/19/trumps-misdirection-play/</guid>
      <description>Everybody loves misdirection. It makes magic shows and movies interesting. You think you know what happens next, then WHAM! the unexpected happens. Now you&amp;rsquo;re plugged in.
Trump gave a head fake. Everybody bought it. (Including me.) Then his legs went the other way, and we stand here flailing at the air. Some people&amp;rsquo;s heads exploded on CNN. BOOM! I&amp;rsquo;ll reveal the real misdirection in a moment. You&amp;rsquo;ll love it.
After declaring &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to change&amp;rdquo; and hiring Stephen K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Liberalism Ruins Black Lives in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/17/how-liberalism-ruins-black-lives-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 04:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/17/how-liberalism-ruins-black-lives-in-america/</guid>
      <description>You probably remember that I love The Conservative Heart by Arthur C. Brooks. I learned so much reading that book, and learning feels great. I read a lot and I&amp;rsquo;m 52-years-old, and I&amp;rsquo;m amazed at how much I didn&amp;rsquo;t know. And it feels so good to learn, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Idle Hands Are the Devil&amp;rsquo;s Workshop One of my favorite stories in The Conservative Heart involves the city of Marienthal, Austria, in the 1930s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Third Act: The Honey Badger</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/17/trumps-third-act-the-honey-badger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 22:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/17/trumps-third-act-the-honey-badger/</guid>
      <description>Can you guess Stephen K. Bannon&amp;rsquo;s mantra at Breitbart? It&amp;rsquo;s not, &amp;ldquo;act like a Republican and lose.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s not &amp;ldquo;pivot,&amp;rdquo; a word I detest. “Honey badger don’t give a s&amp;mdash;” is the Breitbart motto, and &amp;ldquo;the most dangerous political operative in America&amp;rdquo; is now running Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign. Raise the curtain on act three.
https://youtu.be/4r7wHMg5Yjg
The entire political world is reeling today with news that Donald Trump has named the incredible Stephen K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party for Trump Special Offer to Kid Rock</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/12/tea-party-for-trump-special-offer-to-kid-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 22:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/12/tea-party-for-trump-special-offer-to-kid-rock/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/WjQtDEPETAY
No Words Necessary
The Tea Party for Trump is Sunday, August 28, 2016 at 4:00 p.m. at Surdyke Harley-Davidson in Festus, MO.
Details to follow.
GET YOUR FREE TICKETS NOW.
Volunteer to help here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Permission to Trump: Episode 3</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/12/permission-to-trump-episode-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 22:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/12/permission-to-trump-episode-3/</guid>
      <description>[soundcloud url=&amp;quot;https://api.soundcloud.com/tracks/277672779&amp;rdquo; params=&amp;quot;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;100%&amp;rdquo; height=&amp;quot;166&amp;rdquo; iframe=&amp;quot;true&amp;rdquo; /]
Permission to Trump: episode 3
August 8, 2016
Ed Martin and Bill Hennessy. (Tim McNabb on assignment.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Takes While Donald Gives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/26/hillary-takes-while-donald-gives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 13:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/26/hillary-takes-while-donald-gives/</guid>
      <description>Contrasts.
Two Politico stories, just weeks apart, demonstrate the remarkable contrasts between the two candidates for president.
The headline of the Trump story tells it all:
 Trump raised $32 million with RNC, but kept only a fraction.
 And the Hillary story:
 Leaked emails show officials tried to obscure the fact that Clinton allowed states to keep only a tiny fraction of proceeds from joint fundraising.
 Trump is on Team America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Had But One Speech to Give for His Country, and It Was Perfect</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/24/trump-had-but-one-speech-to-give-for-his-country-and-it-was-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 21:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/24/trump-had-but-one-speech-to-give-for-his-country-and-it-was-perfect/</guid>
      <description>Now it makes so much sense. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I missed it. Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign is so perfectly consistent, it&amp;rsquo;s almost scary. No, it is scary. It means we&amp;rsquo;re down to our last hope.
When I Turned On Trump I put this in my book, Turning On Trump. I remember the night. I wrote late. Something hit me like wolves howling in the distance. Telling me something had changed. Or some ancient truth, long buried, had been uncovered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Voice, Not an Echo</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/22/a-voice-not-an-echo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/22/a-voice-not-an-echo/</guid>
      <description>Donald J. Trump overwhelmed the political class last night, smashing up their temple. He destroyed the media myths of everything. Everything. Donald Trump is the anti-myth, the truth-teller, the blunt reporter of reality on reality&amp;rsquo;s terms. And his speech, his reality manifesto, stole the hearts of thevast majority of Americas.
So many myths dispelled.
** The Tea Party myth of a savior in an ill-fitting suit who speaks only two words: constitution and conservatism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why does Ted Cruz&#39;s Speech Bother Me So Much?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/22/why-does-ted-cruzs-speech-bother-me-so-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 13:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/22/why-does-ted-cruzs-speech-bother-me-so-much/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m trying to put my finger on exactly why I found Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s remarks Wednesday night so incredibly distasteful.
The Pledge thing is a goodly part of it.
Simply put, the parties to the Pledge Ted Cruz signed were only Ted Cruz and the RNC (by extension, you can probably include the delegates and voters, too).
The Pledge promised support, including data, from the RNC in exchange for Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s endorsement of the eventual nominee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Donald Trump Destroyed Ted Cruz</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/21/how-donald-trump-destroyed-ted-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/21/how-donald-trump-destroyed-ted-cruz/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re probably thinking that Ted Cruz made Donald Trump look bad last night. And he did. Ted Cruz had a prime time speaking slot and he failed to endorse his party&amp;rsquo;s nominee for president. Hillary Clinton will use it.
A lot of people are saying Trump shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have invited him to speak unless Cruz agreed to endorse Trump. But Trump didn&amp;rsquo;t even ask for Cruz&amp;rsquo;s endorsement. Trump just offered Ted the prime time spot, and Ted took it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What It&#39;s Like to Meet Ted Cruz</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/what-its-like-to-meet-ted-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 03:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/what-its-like-to-meet-ted-cruz/</guid>
      <description>In case you didn&amp;rsquo;t hear, Donald Trump invited Ted Cruz to speak at the RNC in prime time with no expectation that Cruz would keep his word by endorsing Mr. Trump. Senator Cruz immediately accepted the prime time speaking spot.
In case you didn&amp;rsquo;t hear, Donald Trump waived his right to review Senator Cruz&amp;rsquo;s speech in advance, the first time that&amp;rsquo;s happened in our lifetimes according to Tucker Carlson. Mr. Trump respects Senator Cruz enough to let the senator say whatever he wants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can&#39;t Trump Forgiveness</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/you-cant-trump-forgiveness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 22:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/you-cant-trump-forgiveness/</guid>
      <description>You might think big embarrassing mistakes will get you fired, but they don&amp;rsquo;t. As long as you keep making different kinds of mistakes and your managers know what they&amp;rsquo;re doing (big &amp;ldquo;if&amp;rdquo;), you&amp;rsquo;ll be fine. Just don&amp;rsquo;t make the same kind of mistake over and over again. And it helps to work for a guy like Tom Watson or Donald Trump.
While the dollar amount has changed over time, the other details are pretty consistent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being the Oddball Sucks</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/how-leaders-decide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 10:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/how-leaders-decide/</guid>
      <description>Could you stand by a &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; answer?
Let&amp;rsquo;s pretend you&amp;rsquo;re in a room with 10 people about your age and background. You&amp;rsquo;ve been talking for a while, and you&amp;rsquo;ve gotten to know the others. Then the task begins. It&amp;rsquo;s straightforward.
On a large TV, you see a line drawing of a face. The instructor calls out people by name and asks if the face is a happy face, a sad face, or neutral face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3: Trump, The Champion  (plus 25% savings)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/18/part-3-trump-the-champion-plus-25-savings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 03:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/18/part-3-trump-the-champion-plus-25-savings/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/rZPhWRhzGaA
Maybe Mr. Trump read my book Turning On Trump. That&amp;rsquo;s probably where he got the idea for this entrance. Part 3 of Turning On Trump is &amp;ldquo;Trump, The Champion.&amp;rdquo; You should read the book and find out why it&amp;rsquo;s had so much influence.
RNC Special - Save 25% Nobody offers 25% off, but I do. For just 4 days, get the paperback edition of Turning On Trump for 25%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NeverTrump Blows Up Like a Poisoned Dog</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/15/nevertrump-blows-up-like-a-poisoned-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 13:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/15/nevertrump-blows-up-like-a-poisoned-dog/</guid>
      <description>The Never Trump movement tried to make a stand. It failed by a massive margin.
 &amp;ndash;Kyle Cheney, Politico
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t even close, and I feel guilty.
I don&amp;rsquo;t look at Facebook too often. I have been on Facebook lately because it&amp;rsquo;s a great vehicle for book sales, but I really don&amp;rsquo;t like it.
One problem with Facebook is that I can see what people are thinking. And so many people I know and respect think some really dumb things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Many Islamic Terrorist Attacks This Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/15/you-wont-believe-how-many-islamic-terrorist-attacks-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 12:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/15/you-wont-believe-how-many-islamic-terrorist-attacks-this-year/</guid>
      <description>Good morning.
One of the reasons Trump will win in a landslide is safety. Trump has warned for years that we are weak and political correctness makes us weaker. Everybody knows he&amp;rsquo;s right. NeverTrumpers were saying this until Trump said it.
Last night,** a Muslim terrorist killed at least 84 people in Nice, France**. They were ordinary people lined up to watch fireworks, the same way you did on the 4th of July.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg Totally Had This Coming</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/13/ruth-bader-ginsburg-totally-had-this-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 03:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/13/ruth-bader-ginsburg-totally-had-this-coming/</guid>
      <description>You know how this game goes. You make a wish, I&amp;rsquo;ll do my damnedest to grant it. Because I am just that kinkkind of guy.
Ruth Bader Ginsburg, aka Notorious RBG, made a wish last week. Being a lawyer, her wish came with a contingency.
I just launched a GoFund.Meproject to grant her that wish. And why not?
Ruth Bader Ginsburg is a true Horatio Alger story. Born to Russian-Jewish immigrant parents, raised in the Flatbush neighborhood of Brooklyn, RBG rose the highest legal position in the United States: Supreme Court Justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why NeverTrump Will Support Down-Ballot Dems</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/13/why-nevertrump-will-support-down-ballot-dems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 14:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/13/why-nevertrump-will-support-down-ballot-dems/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s possible that some NeverTrumper has already gone there, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it.
Up until now, one complaint of the NeverTurmpers has been that Mr. Trump will hurt Republicans running for Senate, the House, and state offices. They make this claim knowing full well that Trump is ahead of Romney in every poll and with every demographic group. I predict that, come October, people will be saying Trump is virtually running unopposed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How NeverTrump Promotes Race Violence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/how-nevertrump-promotes-race-violence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 06:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/how-nevertrump-promotes-race-violence/</guid>
      <description>NeverTrumpers who don&amp;rsquo;t cross over stand to get a lot of blood on their hands. I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one noticing. If anything, I&amp;rsquo;m understating the case. Now we know: to be anti-Trump is to be pro-abortion and pro-race war. To be anti-Trump is to support violence against police officers, especially white police officers. That&amp;rsquo;s because Hillary is all those things, and to be anti-Trump is, logically, to be pro-Hillary. (If they both live until January 20, either Clinton or Trump will be the next president.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Pretend You&#39;re Not Lying</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/10/how-to-pretend-youre-not-lying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 23:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/10/how-to-pretend-youre-not-lying/</guid>
      <description>Imagine if you posted on Facebook, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m going to the store,&amp;rdquo; and someone replied, &amp;ldquo;How come you&amp;rsquo;re going to buy the world&amp;rsquo;s largest vibrating dildo?&amp;rdquo;
That other person would deny he&amp;rsquo;s lying, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t he? If you accused him of lying, he&amp;rsquo;d fire off a series of defenses:
** It was a question, not a statement ** You didn&amp;rsquo;t say you weren&amp;rsquo;t going to buy the world&amp;rsquo;s largest dildo, did you? ** Can you prove you weren&amp;rsquo;t planning to get the world&amp;rsquo;s largest vibrating dildo?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Radio with Larry Kudlow and Friends</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/09/great-radio-with-larry-kudlow-and-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 20:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/09/great-radio-with-larry-kudlow-and-friends/</guid>
      <description>Wow! Larry Kudlow really like Turning On Trump. You can listen to my interview with Larry here. My hit starts at 1:36:48, but the whole show is great.
[audio preload=&amp;quot;auto&amp;rdquo; mp3=&amp;quot;https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/Kudlow-Hennessy.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
On Wednesday, Mark Reardon and I had a great Trump conversation onKMOX Radio. You can listen to that here. You should probably follow Mark on twitter: https://twitter.com/MarkReardonKMOX
[audio mp3=&amp;quot;https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/Reardon-hennessy.mp3&amp;rdquo; preload=&amp;quot;auto&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
And if you missed it, Jamie Allman was so gracious and kind to have me onThe Allman Report on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Permission to Trump, Episode 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/09/permission-to-trump-episode-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 14:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/09/permission-to-trump-episode-2/</guid>
      <description>[soundcloud url=&amp;quot;https://api.soundcloud.com/tracks/272883927&amp;rdquo; params=&amp;quot;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;100%&amp;rdquo; height=&amp;quot;166&amp;rdquo; iframe=&amp;quot;true&amp;rdquo; /]
Ed Martin Jr. and I got together again to talk about why you might give yourself Permission to Trump. It&amp;rsquo;s important that you do.
This week&amp;rsquo;s episode focuses on:
** FBI Director&amp;rsquo;s report on Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s illegal and dangerous abuse of classified information ** The horrific massacre of police officers in Dallas ** Bill&amp;rsquo;s new book,** Turning On Trump**
Feel free to share this post with all your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Talking on The Allman Report</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/09/trump-talking-on-the-allman-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 13:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/09/trump-talking-on-the-allman-report/</guid>
      <description>Jamie Allman overstates my accomplishments, but I had a great time on The Allman Report talking Trump and my new book, Turning On Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You&#39;re Mad At Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/06/why-youre-mad-at-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 02:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/06/why-youre-mad-at-trump/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people seem to be mad at Trump. You might be one of them.
You probably think you know why you’re mad at him. For instance, you might not like what he said about the judge in a lawsuit he’s involved with. Or maybe you didn’t like what he said about Rosie O’Donnell. You might even be mad that he said Saddam Hussein was a bad man who was good at killing terrorists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Been a Great Month for ISIS</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/04/its-been-a-great-month-for-isis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 21:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/04/its-been-a-great-month-for-isis/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re football team, you&amp;rsquo;re measured by games won. If you&amp;rsquo;re a computer company, you&amp;rsquo;re measured by products shipped. If you&amp;rsquo;re and international terrorist organization, you&amp;rsquo;re measured by mayhem created.
Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, ISIS is on a roll.
What a week! Nearly 200 murders across three countries on two continents. Not bad for a JV team, huh? Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the week:
** Istanbul Airport: 45 murdered, 52 hospitalized. ** Bangladesh Bakery: 20 murdered, 13 escaped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everybody&#39;s Talking About Turning On Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/03/everybodys-talking-about-turning-on-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 04:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/03/everybodys-talking-about-turning-on-trump/</guid>
      <description>I sent one email to Jamie Allman. He&amp;rsquo;s such a great guy, he invited me on two of his shows. Probably not because of me, but because of the subject of Turning On Trump. Still, it&amp;rsquo;s an honor. Thank you, Jamie.
If you&amp;rsquo;re as curious about Turning On Trump as Jamie Allman is, listen to his show on97.1 FM Tuesday, July 5 at 7:20 a.m. We&amp;rsquo;ll wait while you make a note to listen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch the Trailer</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/02/turning-on-trump-book-trailer-youll-love-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 15:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/02/turning-on-trump-book-trailer-youll-love-it/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/d02S3EMY6m8
Read all about my new book here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Feel Safe from Terrorism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/30/how-to-feel-safe-from-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 21:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/30/how-to-feel-safe-from-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>Think about the word &amp;ldquo;news.&amp;rdquo; In a moment, I&amp;rsquo;m going to ask you more questions about the news. Before that, though, you probably heard about the terrible terrorist attack in Istanbul, Turkey. Dozens killed, scores injured. &amp;ldquo;It was like hell,&amp;rdquo; one witness recalled.
Where did you get news of this latest terrorist attack? Facebook? Television? Radio?
Do you remember what you were doing when you heard the news? Take a moment to think back to when you first heard the news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Way to Deal with Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/28/the-best-way-to-deal-with-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/28/the-best-way-to-deal-with-trump/</guid>
      <description>Someone you know is PERFECT for this book. It might be you.
Here you are, looking at your device, reading these words, and trying to figure out the Trump thing. Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve figured it out, but you want to know how people like you think about it. Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re all-in for Trump, but you need help talking to your friends or family about your Trumpism. You might be thinking this book is for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dethroning the Pointy-Haired Bosses of the Universe</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/26/dethroning-the-pointy-haired-bosses-of-the-universe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/26/dethroning-the-pointy-haired-bosses-of-the-universe/</guid>
      <description>Okay, let me explain this in the simplest possible way&amp;hellip;
 you&amp;hellip;are&amp;hellip;an&amp;hellip;idiot.
&amp;ndash;Scott Adams, Dilbert
 Lately&amp;hellip;the Peter Principle has given way to the &amp;ldquo;Dilbert Principle.&amp;rdquo; The basic concept of the Dilbert Principle is that the most ineffective workers are systematically moved to the place where they can do the least damage: management.
 ― Scott Adams, The Dilbert Principle: A Cubicle&amp;rsquo;s-Eye View of Bosses, Meetings, Management Fads &amp;amp; Other Workplace Afflictions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Permission to Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/25/permission-to-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 19:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/25/permission-to-trump/</guid>
      <description>Ever feel like it&amp;rsquo;s not okay to admit you&amp;rsquo;re for Trump?
Everybody who listens to this new podcast, Permission to Trump, will benefit in one way or another. Some people will feel liberated. Others vindicated. Everyone improved.
[soundcloud url=&amp;quot;https://api.soundcloud.com/tracks/270829707&amp;rdquo; params=&amp;quot;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;100%&amp;rdquo; height=&amp;quot;450&amp;rdquo; iframe=&amp;quot;true&amp;rdquo; /]
You will want to listen and share with your friends. And soon you&amp;rsquo;ll want to buy my new book Turning on Trump.Sign up to stay up to date now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Levin Is Turning On Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/23/mark-levin-is-turning-on-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/23/mark-levin-is-turning-on-trump/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s outstanding,&amp;rdquo; said the Great One.
 The Republican leadership in Congress doesn’t have the guts to go to the floor of the Senate or the floor of the House and make these charges. This is outstanding. You can’t let Hillary Clinton get away with her corruption, her cronyism, her criminality. I don’t care who you support or don’t support. She’s detestable.
 [Via Breitbart.com]
Mark Levin said some terrible things about Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where&#39;s the Outrage Over Democrat Death Party?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/22/death-party-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 03:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/22/death-party-blues/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s play a game, shall we?
How would CNN report the following tweets:
These are real tweets from real people with one word changed. I replaced &amp;ldquo;Trump&amp;rdquo; in the original tweets with &amp;ldquo;Hillary.&amp;rdquo; You can see these death-happy tweets and many, many more on Breitbart.com. Real people openly call for assassination as if they were rooting for a basketball team. Scary, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
You didn&amp;rsquo;t miss the media outrage over these tweet&amp;ndash;it didn&amp;rsquo;t happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Government Employees Should Be Scared of Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/21/why-government-employees-should-be-scared-of-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 00:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/21/why-government-employees-should-be-scared-of-trump/</guid>
      <description>Some people say they&amp;rsquo;re afraid of Donald Trump for bizarre reasons. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard he&amp;rsquo;s a dictator, a fascist, a genocidal maniac, and a lousy businessman. If any of that is true, there&amp;rsquo;s no evidence of it, so he must also own all the media already. And the internet. In fact, if Trump is a lousy businessman who managed to bungle his way to a $10 billion fortune, he must really bad at dictatoring, because he hasn&amp;rsquo;t even conquered his home country in 70 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lewandowski Firing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/21/lewandowski-firing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 06:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/21/lewandowski-firing/</guid>
      <description>You knew it would happen, didn&amp;rsquo;t you?
Corey Lewandowski, the obscure, small-potatoes political operative from a tiny state couldn&amp;rsquo;t possibly run a presidential campaign from start to victory, could he?
But this isn&amp;rsquo;t about Corey Lewandowski. It&amp;rsquo;s about the next the president of the United States, Donald Trump. And you&amp;rsquo;ll want to read it all because it&amp;rsquo;s so true. So true.
I read a summary of what happened at Lewandowski&amp;rsquo;s dismissal meeting, and it sounded exactly like an episode of The Apprentice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her Crooked Highness Hillary Just Got Smoked</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/09/her-crooked-highness-hillary-just-got-smoked/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 01:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/09/her-crooked-highness-hillary-just-got-smoked/</guid>
      <description>Trump is now running unopposed for president because his only opponent is an empty pantsuit.
Hillary Clinton uses other people&amp;rsquo;s money to surround herself with nearly 1,000 paid staff. Direct paid staff. That a HUGE support team for a crooked sexist like Hillary.
Donald Trump spends his own money, so he hires only enough people to get the job done. Trump understands money and people, while Hillary understands comfort.
Tonight, Hillary Clinton exposed herself as an amateur in the world of communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forgive Paul Ryan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/09/forgive-paul-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 05:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/09/forgive-paul-ryan/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people are mad at Paul Ryan. Millions of people want Mr. Ryan to step down as Speaker of the House. I am not mad at him. Paul Ryan is a victim of his circumstances, just like a lot of other Republicans.
Paul Ryan stepped up to a microphone this week and said what he was programmed to say. Essentially, Mr. Ryan said he&amp;rsquo;s not happy with Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s statements about a La Raza judge who started issuing anti-Trump rulings after Trump called on America to enforce its immigration laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Truths of Republicans and Race</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/07/forbidden-truths-of-republicans-and-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/07/forbidden-truths-of-republicans-and-race/</guid>
      <description>Republicans hate race. Race has been bad for the GOP ever since Republicans passed the Civil Rights Act of 1964. See, Lyndon Johnson was a Democrat, and he proposed the Civil Rights Act of 1964. Most Democrats violently opposed the bill. But most Republicans supported it. The bill passed, of course, and it survived many Supreme Court challenges.
The Civil Rights Act&amp;rsquo;s aim was to wring racist behavior out of American life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Tell If You&#39;re a Racist</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/06/how-to-tell-if-youre-a-racist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 00:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/06/how-to-tell-if-youre-a-racist/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard the news that Donald Trump believes it&amp;rsquo;s possible for a Muslim judge to treat him unfairly. Do you think Trump is wrong about this?
When asked by a reporter if Trump believed it would be possible for a Muslim judge to treat him unfairly, Trump answered, &amp;ldquo;It’s possible, yes. Yeah. That would be possible, absolutely.&amp;rdquo;
Notice that Trump didn&amp;rsquo;t say, &amp;ldquo;all Muslim judges are unfair to me.&amp;rdquo; Nor did he say all Hispanic judges are unfair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muslim Judge</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/06/muslim-judge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 05:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/06/muslim-judge/</guid>
      <description>Has any judge, anywhere, ever presided unfairly over a trial?
The leftist press is making hay over Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s reasonable assertion that a Muslim judge might not be able to fairly adjudicate a case involving Trump.
The answer to my opening question is &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo; Many judges have presided unfairly over trials. For example, many blacks were sent to prison when the same evidence would have exonerated a white defendant. We all know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Dripping Gift Only for Anti-Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/03/hot-dripping-gift-only-for-anti-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 05:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/03/hot-dripping-gift-only-for-anti-trump/</guid>
      <description>READ THIS ALONE: Are you anti-Trump? You&amp;rsquo;re going to like this. A lot. While you read this post, you&amp;rsquo;re going experience bliss and ecstasy. Have you ever read an orgasmic blog post? You will, and you&amp;rsquo;ll like it. Like it so deeply. Very deep and very satisfying. This will become your favorite blog post ever. You&amp;rsquo;ll probably bookmark it. Maybe even email it to yourself. You&amp;rsquo;ll love it.
This is only for anti-Trump people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The World Needs Now: A Trump Book</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/01/what-the-world-needs-now-a-trump-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 04:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/01/what-the-world-needs-now-a-trump-book/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to know what Trump supporters are thinking? Many people do.
If you supported Ted Cruz, you might not understand how the guy who wrote The Conservative Manifesto in 1993 could support Trump.
If you supported Marco Rubio or Ben Carson last year, how do you reconcile your convictions with Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s bizarre life?
Is Donald Trump a conservative or not?
I&amp;rsquo;ve written a new book about all these things, and you can buy your copy soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It must be a diversion, right?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/01/it-must-be-a-diversion-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 05:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/01/it-must-be-a-diversion-right/</guid>
      <description>I admire David French, David French is running for president, but you probably have no idea who he is, right?
No, it&amp;rsquo;s not Buffy and Jody&amp;rsquo;s man-nanny from the 1960s sitcom Family Affair. That was Mr. French played by Sebastian Cabot, and I forget the character&amp;rsquo;s first name.
Nor is it the guy who publishes most stage play scripts. That&amp;rsquo;s Samuel French. (Only theatre people will know that name.)
If you&amp;rsquo;re a hard-core conservative or you read National Review for any reason, you might have heard of David French.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Thrilla in California</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/27/the-thrilla-in-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 20:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/27/the-thrilla-in-california/</guid>
      <description>Try not to imagine the worldwide television audience for the Trump vs. Sanders debate. Super Bowl ratings would look skimpy by comparison. Trump vs. Sanders would be the most watched political event ever. And I&amp;rsquo;m including the future in &amp;ldquo;ever.&amp;rdquo; And a Trump vs. Sanders debate would effectively kill Democrats&amp;rsquo; chances in November. This is huge.
Yesterday, I wrote about Trump&amp;rsquo;s remarkable honesty at his press conference, but that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the big story of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World&#39;s Greatest Press Conference</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/27/worlds-greatest-press-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/27/worlds-greatest-press-conference/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump just exploded the heads of professional talkers on CNN. It was honestly funny.
Trump reached 1,237 delegates today, clinching the nomination of the Republican Party. He will be the 45th President of the United States, and his press conferences will be the most popular show on television. It will be huge, believe me. And after the press conference, Trump did something that might have sealed the deal with American voters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s About to Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/23/somethings-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 21:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/23/somethings-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>Watch what people do and say because action comes before opinion.
People write &amp;ldquo;President Trump&amp;rdquo; three times as much as they write &amp;ldquo;President Clinton.&amp;rdquo; For every one person who writes &amp;ldquo;President Trump&amp;rdquo; in a column, blog, tweet, or Facebook post, hundreds of thousands more say or think &amp;ldquo;President Trump&amp;rdquo; every day.
That&amp;rsquo;s how I predicted Trump winning by a landslide. I watched what people say and do.
A lot of people who subconsciously think &amp;ldquo;President Trump&amp;rdquo; will touch the screen or check the box or pull the lever for Trump when they step inside the voting booth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What No One&#39;s Telling You About Donald Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/22/what-no-ones-telling-you-about-donald-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/22/what-no-ones-telling-you-about-donald-trump/</guid>
      <description>Relax as you read, because knowledge is power. This simple post will arm you with powerful knowledge that will help you navigate the election. And it will only take a few minutes. No time at all.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the press refuses to tell you: The man in the picture is the next President of the United States. You might as well start calling him &amp;ldquo;President Trump.&amp;rdquo;
Three national polls came out this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump and the TSA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/17/trump-and-the-tsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/17/trump-and-the-tsa/</guid>
      <description>Say what you want about Donald Trump, the customer service at his properties is insanely great. And The Donald personally sets the standard for that service. He also inspects it, and he has a sick level of attention to detail. Donald Trump doesn&amp;rsquo;t miss a thing when it comes to providing a perfect environment for his guests and residents.
The opposite is true of the TSA. Like most government-run operations, the TSA sucks at customer service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/16/president-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 22:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/16/president-trump/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably noticed a lot of people are saying &amp;ldquo;President Trump&amp;rdquo; lately. And reading &amp;ldquo;President Trump&amp;rdquo; online, haven&amp;rsquo;t you?
If not, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably notice it later today or tomorrow.
[Tweet &amp;ldquo;Catch yourself saying &amp;lsquo;President Trump&amp;rsquo; now? @realDonaldTrump&amp;rdquo;]
It&amp;rsquo;s common during election years for pundits to occasionally say &amp;ldquo;President So-and-so,&amp;rdquo; usually sarcastically. And some &amp;ldquo;President Trump&amp;rdquo; talk is sarcastic. But most of this President Trump talk is subconscious prediction. People think President Trump is a thing, so their brains are warming up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Conservatives Abandoned Principles Over Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/14/how-conservatives-abandoned-principles-over-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 18:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/14/how-conservatives-abandoned-principles-over-trump/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably been hearing a lot about &amp;ldquo;principles&amp;rdquo; lately. Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s entire campaign centered &amp;ldquo;conservative principles&amp;rdquo; and being a &amp;ldquo;principled conservative.&amp;rdquo;
Lately, though, most of that &amp;ldquo;principles&amp;rdquo; talk is about how Donald Trump has caused good conservatives to abandon their principles.
Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s true. In fact, I&amp;rsquo;m starting to believe it.
The one principle that many conservatives have abandoned and encouraged others to abandon: keeping your word.
The lead advocate for abandoning this principle of keeping one&amp;rsquo;s word is Jonah Goldberg of National Review and the American Enterprise Institute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Predict Trump&#39;s Landslide Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/13/how-to-predict-trumps-landslide-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 20:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/13/how-to-predict-trumps-landslide-win/</guid>
      <description>You might have noticed that my predictions have been remarkably accurate lately, have you not?
For example, on Sunday, May 1, I predicted Ted Cruz would suspend his campaign after getting trounced in Indiana. Two days later, Cruz lost the Indiana primary to Donald Trump 53 to 36. At the time I wrote, many pundits and pollster still believed Cruz could win that Indiana race, and everyone believed Cruz was telling the truth when he said repeatedly he was staying in the race to Cleveland unless Trump reached 1,237 delegates before then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s How the Ryan-Trump Meeting Ends</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/11/heres-how-the-ryan-trump-meeting-ends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/11/heres-how-the-ryan-trump-meeting-ends/</guid>
      <description>Nothing happens in politics by accident. Every move has an angle. Some players are better than others. Paul Ryan and Donald Trump are two of the best players alive, but one is better than the other. We&amp;rsquo;ll see that tomorrow.
House Speaker Paul Ryan has set aside Thursday for meetings with his party&amp;rsquo;s nominee for President. Every nominee for president meets with the senior members of his party&amp;rsquo;s Congressional caucus, so there&amp;rsquo;s nothing odd about the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Is the Only Viable Pro-Life Choice</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/09/trump-is-the-only-viable-pro-life-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 21:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/09/trump-is-the-only-viable-pro-life-choice/</guid>
      <description>Some pro-life activists like Erick Erickson are plotting ways to sabotage Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy for president. They probably haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped to think. If they succeed in defeating Trump, they will be culpable in many, many abortions. That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of guilt for a guy like Erickson to carry around, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Chances are Congress won&amp;rsquo;t introduce any major abortion laws in the next four years. That means the abortion battle will remain in the courts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Is Conservative?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/08/who-is-conservative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 22:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/08/who-is-conservative/</guid>
      <description>People think they&amp;rsquo;re rational, but we&amp;rsquo;re not. For example, on many issues,** Trump&amp;rsquo;s positions are almost identical to Ronald Reagan&amp;rsquo;s.** When it comes to abortion, trade, taxes, foreign policy and the military, and entitlements like Social Security, you can&amp;rsquo;t fit a dime between Reagan and Trump.
So why do people see Trump as far to the left of Reagan?
Contrasts and comparisons.
Reagan ran against George Bush and John B. Anderson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump for President. I Endorse.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/06/trump-for-president-i-endorse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 18:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/06/trump-for-president-i-endorse/</guid>
      <description>You can choose a ready guide in some celestial voice If you choose not to decide, you still have made a choice You can choose from phantom fears and kindness that can kill I will choose a path that&amp;rsquo;s clear I will choose freewill
 &amp;ndash;RUSH, Freewill
Last July and August and once in September, I was down on Donald Trump. I predicted that a Trump nomination would be the last nail in the coffin of conservatism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Leaders and Paul Ryan Begin Negotiating With Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/05/world-leaders-and-paul-ryan-begin-negotiating-with-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 02:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/05/world-leaders-and-paul-ryan-begin-negotiating-with-trump/</guid>
      <description>Every prediction about Trump has been wrong. Except for two. Ann Coulter and Scott Adams predicted Trump would win the nomination and, eventually, the White House in a landslide. They were right.
World leaders expect Trump to win, and they are lining up to make all his crazy assertions look like brilliant predictions.
Former Mexico president Vicente Fox apologized to Trump, and Trump graciously accepted. That&amp;rsquo;s a sign that Mexicans expect Trump to become the next US president.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Affair to Dismember (Trump)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/04/an-affair-to-dismember/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/04/an-affair-to-dismember/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever cheated on your spouse just to get back at your daughter for dating or marrying the wrong man, you&amp;rsquo;re probably a #nevertrump person like George Will.
Suppose your daughter married a man you didn&amp;rsquo;t approve of. You would probably respond by cheating on your own spouse, would you not? Having an affair would teach your daughter a lesson, right? And if your spouse and your friends and your other children suffered, too bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/03/for-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 04:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/03/for-trump/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m for Trump.
I like stating the positive.
So I&amp;rsquo;m for Trump.
TheNR Against Trump writers can own it if Hillary wins and appoints a Supreme Court justice who&amp;rsquo;s to the left of Bader-Ginsberg as Scalia&amp;rsquo;s replacement. They&amp;rsquo;ll take that to their graves.
For me, I&amp;rsquo;m for Trump. I&amp;rsquo;ll admit he wasn&amp;rsquo;t my first choice, but he was far from my last choice. My first choice, Ben Carson, endorsed The Donald.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Psychology of The Inevitable</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/01/the-psychology-of-the-inevitable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 16:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/01/the-psychology-of-the-inevitable/</guid>
      <description>I have no idea who will win the Indiana primary 72 hours from the time I write. But the people inside Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s campaign seem to have an idea. And it&amp;rsquo;s not good for them. Cruz&amp;rsquo;s top team expects their candidate to lose. And Senator Cruz seems to have accepted that outcome.
Expectations Matter More Than Preferences Regular readers know that polls that ask &amp;ldquo;who do you think will win&amp;rdquo; trump polls that ask &amp;ldquo;who do you intend to vote for&amp;rdquo; or even &amp;ldquo;who did you vote for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Censors Health Information. Collusion! Rigged!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/27/government-censors-health-information-collusion-rigged/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 02:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/27/government-censors-health-information-collusion-rigged/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably found yourself saying words like &amp;ldquo;rigged&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;collusion&amp;rdquo; recently. They&amp;rsquo;ve become sexy words, haven&amp;rsquo;t they. That&amp;rsquo;s because Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s made rigged and collusion household words. He&amp;rsquo;s put them in your head.
You might even use them wrong. &amp;ldquo;There was a collusion on highway forty-four.&amp;rdquo; Or &amp;ldquo;I rigged my shorts.&amp;rdquo; (BTW, Hillary sounds weak and hoarse, doesn&amp;rsquo;t she? Grating.)
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t noticed yourself saying rigged and collusion, pay attention tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How a Strategist Looks at the Supreme Court Nomination Battle</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/02/strategist-looks-supreme-court-nomination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 15:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/02/strategist-looks-supreme-court-nomination/</guid>
      <description>In a moment, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look the Supreme Court nomination of Merrick Garland and find the best strategy for Senate Republicans. In a moment. First, let&amp;rsquo;s just relax and think about a party. And pretend you&amp;rsquo;re a paid strategist.
Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View Podcast: [soundcloud url=&amp;quot;https://api.soundcloud.com/tracks/256943967&amp;rdquo; params=&amp;quot;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;100%&amp;rdquo; height=&amp;quot;450&amp;rdquo; iframe=&amp;quot;true&amp;rdquo; /]
Party Now or Party Later?  Tim and Mary Johnson want to have a party for their friends. They&amp;rsquo;ve been talking about it since spring, and now it&amp;rsquo;s nearly winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m trying to write the truth</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/27/im-trying-to-write-the-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/27/im-trying-to-write-the-truth/</guid>
      <description>I was a pretender.
In 2012, I pretended I believed Mitt Romney would win. But I knew better. I just didn&amp;rsquo;t have the heart to tell the truth to the volunteers banging doors and working call lists from our election office in South County.
But I knew Romney would lose. I suspected the GOP would not regain the Senate.
When some of our hardest workers showed up to help break down the office and move our belongings, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump knocks Rubio out of the news cycle</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/26/trump-knocked-rubio-out-of-the-news-cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/26/trump-knocked-rubio-out-of-the-news-cycle/</guid>
      <description>That was a strategic kill-shot, to borrow Scott Adams&amp;rsquo;s word. And it changes everything for conservatives.
After a so-so debate performance and in the middle of a 16-hour verbal assault from Marco Rubio, Trump went nuclear. But not the way everyone would expect Trump to go nuclear.
Trump didn&amp;rsquo;t need to invent a brilliant new put-down line to counter Marco. Instead, he calmly introduced Chris Christie to 10,000 fans in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How bad would Trump presidency be?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/24/why-so-many-conservatives-are-wrong-about-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/24/why-so-many-conservatives-are-wrong-about-trump/</guid>
      <description>The world is about to end.
Or civil war is about to break out in Dayton, Ohio.
Believe it?
Glenn Beck, Erick Erickson, and other Republicans have convinced a lot of people that we are doomed if Donald Trump wins the Republican nomination. I know some people who are nearly incapacitated with fear and grief after last night&amp;rsquo;s Nevada caucuses. Because they listen to Glenn Beck. Sad!
Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: **nothing is as bad as you think it will be while you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A crushing defeat for Glenn Beck</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/24/a-crushing-defeat-for-glenn-beck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 06:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/24/a-crushing-defeat-for-glenn-beck/</guid>
      <description>Glenn Beck was pretty sure that God killed Antonin Scalia so Ted Cruz would win the presidency.
Glenn Beck&amp;rsquo;s theology is very different from mine.
In 2010, I worried that Glenn Beck was doing more harm than good. For days, I&amp;rsquo;d watched Beck tell his watchers that the world was ending and they would be crushed. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I wrote:
 Beck offers no solutions. At least, he hasn’t in the past two days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I bet Donald Trump reads my blog</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/22/donald-trump-reads-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 03:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/22/donald-trump-reads-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump probably reads my blog first thing every day.
Until today, I figured Donald Trump never heard of me. He&amp;rsquo;s never mentioned me in his tweet storms. He&amp;rsquo;s never called me an idiot or a liar during a debate. He&amp;rsquo;s never pointed to one of my many egregious typos and tweeted:
 &amp;ldquo;@whennessy left out the word &amp;lsquo;for&amp;rsquo;. Confused everyone. Worst blogger in politics. Just sad.&amp;rdquo;
 (The guy has 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz&#39;s ultimate strategy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/21/ted-cruzs-ultimate-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/21/ted-cruzs-ultimate-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Ted Cruz has a powerful strategy available to him. This strategy could not only determine the winner of the Republican convention but put Cruz in position to influence policy for generations.
But it&amp;rsquo;s probably not what you&amp;rsquo;re thinking.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to lay out some assumptions, many of which you could disagree with. That&amp;rsquo;s okay. But for the purposes of this post, let&amp;rsquo;s stipulate:
*1. Ted Cruz believes, like Glenn Beck, that Donald Trump would make a worse president than Barack Obama, Hillary Clinton, or Bernie Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s South Carolina win was impressive</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/21/trumps-south-carolina-win-was-impressive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 08:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/21/trumps-south-carolina-win-was-impressive/</guid>
      <description>I got tire of scrolling.
Politico shows the results of each county in South Carolina, my state of residence from 1985 to 1992.
Abbeville: Trump
Aiken: Trump
Allendale: Trump
Anderson: Trump
Bamberg: Trump
Barnwell: Trump
Beaufort: Trump
Berkeley: Trump
It goes on and on and on.
Donald Trump not only won the geography, he won the demography:
Evangelical Christians: Trump
Born-again Christians: Trump
Conservative Voters: Trump
Moderate Voters: Trump
Young Voters: Trump</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is the Gen X election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/20/this-is-the-gen-x-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 21:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/20/this-is-the-gen-x-election/</guid>
      <description>Who would have thought that Pat Buchanan would become the spokesman for Generation X?
I put a lot of stock into generational history. I am a big fan of Howe and Strauss, a pair of historians whose works include Generations: The History of America&amp;rsquo;s Future, 13ers: Abort, Retry, Ignore, Fail?, Millennials Rising, and, my favorite, The Fourth Turning.
As someone born in the 13th generation of Americans, more commonly called Generation X after the book by Douglas Coupland, I am overly captivated by that generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Pope helped Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/18/how-the-pope-helped-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 04:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/18/how-the-pope-helped-trump/</guid>
      <description>Pope Francis said today that Donald Trump is not a Christian.
I can only assume the Pope has secretly cut a deal with The Donald.
&amp;ldquo;Pope. Donald here. I need you to give me some crap about the wall.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Si.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Just, uh, call me a Muslim or something. Make it look sincere, ya know?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Si.&amp;rdquo;
So the Pope stands at the U.S.-Mexico border and says anyone who wants to build a wall &amp;ldquo;is not a Christian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When does accountability begin?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/07/when-does-accountability-begin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 05:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/07/when-does-accountability-begin/</guid>
      <description>Leverage: don’t make deals without it.
 &amp;ndash;Donald Trump, The Art of the Deal, 1987
It&amp;rsquo;s tempting to go Machiavellian during primaries. Even during general elections after primaries. But there&amp;rsquo;s a great danger for the grassroots.
**If we don&amp;rsquo;t hold candidates accountable during the race when we have all the leverage, how can we possibly hold office-holders accountable? **
Check out this paragraph from the Washington Post:
   Cruz offered a lawyerly defense of his campaign’s actions, blaming media reporting for the mistake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The biggest shock in Iowa</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/01/remarkable-iowa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 04:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/01/remarkable-iowa/</guid>
      <description>The polls were wrong. But that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the biggest shock.
The big shock was . . . who was that guy pretending to be Donald Trump?
Millions and millions of people waited to watch The Donald melt down after finishing second behind Ted Cruz.
But it didn&amp;rsquo;t happen. Instead, Trump managed to show humility and graciousness without giving up his signature bravado. Pretty brilliant. As Romney and Rove learned in 2012, though, air power will not win many races.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if high turnout in Iowa means something else</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/01/what-if-high-turnout-in-iowa-means-something-else/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 01:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/01/what-if-high-turnout-in-iowa-means-something-else/</guid>
      <description>Reports on Twitter say turnout in Iowa very high.
   Some caucuses are reportedly running out of ballots. Huge turnout! #IowaCaucus
 — Jake Putala (@JakePutala) February 2, 2016
  The view at Dubuque&amp;rsquo;s 19th precinct. We had to move to an auditorium to accommodate the large turnout. #IowaCaucus pic.twitter.com/QcWKY1ivAg
— Chris Lammer-Heindel (@lammerheindel) February 2, 2016
   HUGE turnout in both Democratic and Republican caucuses tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cruz campaign&#39;s epic #facepalm</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/31/cruzs-epic-facepalm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 04:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/31/cruzs-epic-facepalm/</guid>
      <description>This &amp;ldquo;VOTING VIOLATION&amp;rdquo; controversy says bad things about the Cruz campaign.
(BTW, Rubio&amp;rsquo;s campaign sent a similar, but less creepy, mailer, too. So far, I have not seen a large number of complaints about the Rubio mailer.)
And I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about the ethics of publicly shaming people who vote sporadically. I&amp;rsquo;m talking two gross electioneering violations from a campaign that markets itself as the most scientifically advanced in history. With the mailer Team Cruz showed a lack of strategic understanding of the science and compounded their ignorance by apparently making up numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump won the Fox News debate</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/27/glenn-beck-is-evil-incarnate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 03:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/27/glenn-beck-is-evil-incarnate/</guid>
      <description>Yes, you can win a contest before it starts.
I gotta tell ya, the people at Fox News are stupid. Dumb. Ignorant. Pliable. Oafish. Any word you want you to use that means cognitively challenged (for the politically correct).
But the Fox Newsmorons have a lot of company at National Review.
Trump is playing these media elites like a fiddle.
When The Donald says &amp;ldquo;dance,&amp;rdquo; they dance. When he says &amp;ldquo;cower,&amp;rdquo; they cower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NRO: Against Jefferson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/26/nro-against-jefferson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 05:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/26/nro-against-jefferson/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Aristocrats fear the people, and wish to transfer all power to the higher classes of society.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ndash;Thomas Jefferson to William Short, 1825.
National Review has entered dangerous territory: they have inadvertently made the case for Trump.
An angry screed by Kevin Williamson titled &amp;ldquo;Our Post-Literate Politics&amp;rdquo; (later renamed to &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s a Book?&amp;quot;) makes the case that Trump supporters are illiterate, uneducated, dim-witted, racist, homophobes. To wit (via Breitbart.com&amp;rsquo;s John Nolte):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Republican elites know something they&#39;re not telling?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/25/do-republican-elites-know-something-theyre-not-telling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 05:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/25/do-republican-elites-know-something-theyre-not-telling/</guid>
      <description>Reading two excellent articles by Nate Silver of FiveThirtyEight (here and here), I remembered a thought that passed through my mind last Friday.
After reading some of National Review&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Against Trump&amp;rdquo; issue,I wrote blog post. To me the NR issue showed the magazine is out of touch with voters. I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about traditional, reliable, motivated, and informed primary voters.** I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the broader pool of voters who vote in general elections every four, eight, or twelve years** and occasionally in local elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How late-deciders are like fish</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/25/late-deciders-like-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 06:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/25/late-deciders-like-fish/</guid>
      <description>**Expectations matter most in how undecided voters decide. **
It&amp;rsquo;s important to understand how late-deciders tend to vote. This knowledge (especially in Iowa and New Hampshire) could decide the outcome.
Primary voters tend to decide whom to for at the last minute.
In 2008, 16 percent of voters said they made their choice on election day. Which means we have a long way to go to know how Iowa will turn out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz and Glenn Beck Were 100% Right about Katrina Pierson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/23/ted-cruz-and-glenn-beck-were-100-right-about-katrina-pierson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 02:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/23/ted-cruz-and-glenn-beck-were-100-right-about-katrina-pierson/</guid>
      <description>_UPDATE: Originally I mentioned &amp;ldquo;apparently fake twitter account.&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve learned (after lots of research) that I was mistaken. I&amp;rsquo;ve removed that statement. Please continue reading. My carelessness was completely my own. _
I agree with Ted Cruz. And welcome Big Government readers.
Senator Cruz said, &amp;ldquo;Katrina Pierson is an utterly fearless principled conservative.&amp;rdquo;
That was just two years ago. Katrina Pierson was challenging Pete Sessions for Congress.
I also agree with Ted&amp;rsquo;s dad, Rafael Cruz, who said of Katrina, &amp;ldquo;She’s a strict constitutionalist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why National Review&#39;s Trump Issue Will Fail</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/22/trumps-conservative-critics-dont-get-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 23:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/22/trumps-conservative-critics-dont-get-it/</guid>
      <description>They. Don&amp;rsquo;t. Care.
The conservative war against Trump won&amp;rsquo;t work.
I get why National Review and The Weekly Standard devote whole issues of magazines to Trump&amp;rsquo;s lack of conservative bonafides. I appreciate it. Their work is important. **But their tactic will prove completely useless in defeating Trump. **In fact, the fight is already over, and the cover story proves it.
Conservative magazines&amp;ndash;online or on paper&amp;ndash;are supposed to weigh events and people against conservative principles and pass judgment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Water/Black Ops</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/12/white-waterblack-ops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/12/white-waterblack-ops/</guid>
      <description>When I was a kid (thought I felt kind of old at the time) disaster movies were the thing.
Before Star Wars, the 1970s were about killer sharks, towering infernos, earthquakes, and capsized cruise ships.
Psychologists and sociologists attributed the genre&amp;rsquo;s popularity to the people&amp;rsquo;s need to assimilate nuclear holocaust.
I think the movies were just good, cathartic entertainment.
 Nonnie Parry: [Deck behind the group is flooding rapidly] How long will we stay afloat?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Cosby Should Ask for a Change of Venue to Cologne Germany</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/11/bill-cosby-should-ask-for-change-of-venue-to-cologne-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/11/bill-cosby-should-ask-for-change-of-venue-to-cologne-germany/</guid>
      <description>On New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, male Muslim refugees rampaged across Europe.
They didn&amp;rsquo;t use guns and bombs. They used their bodies. On women.
This created a political-correctness nightmare for Europe&amp;rsquo;s leaders. On the one hand, the victims were women, and no means no, and we must always believe a woman who accuses a man of sexual predation (unless the man is Bill Clinton in which case we destroy the woman).
On the other hand, the assailants .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Centre Cannot Hold</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/10/the-centre-cannot-hold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 02:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/10/the-centre-cannot-hold/</guid>
      <description>THE SECOND COMING --William Butler Yeats Turning and turning in the widening gyre The falcon cannot hear the falconer; Things fall apart; the centre cannot hold; Mere anarchy is loosed upon the world, The blood-dimmed tide is loosed, and everywhere The ceremony of innocence is drowned; The best lack all conviction, while the worst Are full of passionate intensity. Surely some revelation is at hand; Surely the Second Coming is at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party Like It&#39;s 1992</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/22/party-like-its-1992/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 20:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/22/party-like-its-1992/</guid>
      <description>Five for five.
The first five people who told me they supported Trump in 2015 also supported Ross Perot in 1992.
I realize it&amp;rsquo;s a tiny sample size. Still, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty clear that Donald Trump is the reincarnation of H. Ross Perot. Conservatives&amp;ndash;all conservatives and all center-right voters&amp;ndash;need to come to terms with that fact. We must also deal with the realities of the 2016 election and choose a strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to Choose</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/its-time-to-choose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 05:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/its-time-to-choose/</guid>
      <description>I am a mess.
I am a terrible father, a crappy husband (ask my ex-wives), and a difficult employee. I do a lot of things poorly. Most things, in fact. Especially the things I &amp;ldquo;have&amp;rdquo; to do. Authority irritates me.
While I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at following plans, I write a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of blogs on Saturday and Sunday mornings. The pattern keeps me sane. Or semi-sane. I supplement those when events warrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GOP Establishment Is a Cancer on America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/the-gop-establishment-is-a-cancer-on-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/the-gop-establishment-is-a-cancer-on-america/</guid>
      <description>Former Florida governor Jeb Bush, appearing Thursday on ABC’s “Good Morning America,” said that “of course” he would back Trump, should he emerge triumphant at next year’s GOP convention in Cleveland. “We need to be unified, we need to win,” Bush said.
 &amp;ndash;The Washington Post, September 3, 2015
The Republican Establishment has exposed itself as a political disease willing to kill its host. Unless we seek treatment and remove the tumor first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Strangedebate (or how I learned to stop worrying and love the GOP)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/16/dr-strangedebate-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 06:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/16/dr-strangedebate-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-the-gop/</guid>
      <description>“I’ll build a wall . . . and I’ll make Donald Trump pay for it.” — Ted Cruz
Line of the night in the last GOP Presidential debate of the year of our Lord two thousand and fifteen.
This was the most telling debate of all. And it shouldn’t have happened.
The more you know about anything, the less you like it. That’s a scientific fact.
That’s why the &amp;ldquo;love of your life&amp;rdquo; when you were dating is the &amp;ldquo;lump on the couch&amp;rdquo; 20 years later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America is for Americans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/09/america-is-for-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 01:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/09/america-is-for-americans/</guid>
      <description>Dave: You hear from your folks, Mooch? Moocher: Yeah, my dad called. He wanted to know if the house was sold. He could use the money something fierce. Dave: Well, you can come and live with me when it&amp;rsquo;s sold. In Italy, everybody lives together. Moocher: [laughs] Since you won that Italian bike, man, you&amp;rsquo;ve been acting weird. You&amp;rsquo;re really getting to think you&amp;rsquo;re Italian, aren&amp;rsquo;t you? Cyril: I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind thinking I was someone myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/09/the-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 12:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/09/the-week/</guid>
      <description>Ben Carson The press can&amp;rsquo;t find people who will corroborate Ben Carson&amp;rsquo;s low opinion of himself as a young man. And somehow we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to believe that reflect poorly on Dr. Carson. It reflects poorly on journalism, for sure, but it actually shows that people who knew Dr. Carson won&amp;rsquo;t speak ill of him. Nice problem to have.
Weather Was the weather wonderful this weekend, or what? I hope you got out, even if just to do some yard work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are abortionists manipulating Mizzou&#39;s black athletes?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/08/are-abortionists-manipulating-mizzous-black-athletes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 18:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/08/are-abortionists-manipulating-mizzous-black-athletes/</guid>
      <description>A few Mizzou football players announced they&amp;rsquo;re boycotting all sports activities until University of Missouri system president Tim Wolfe quits or is fired. Considering the football team&amp;rsquo;s dismal performance, the cynic in me wonders if sitting out might help the players&amp;rsquo; chances of getting an NFL draft.
The players and other African-American students at Mizzou believe they are victims of &amp;ldquo;systematic oppression&amp;rdquo; and they want Tim Wolfe to fix it simply by resigning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Debate for Bad Journalists</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/28/the-debate-for-bad-journalists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 03:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/28/the-debate-for-bad-journalists/</guid>
      <description>When Jim Cramer asks a question, you know everything&amp;rsquo;s all boogered up.
The first hour of the GOP Presidential Debate from Colorado will go down as the first official event of the post-journalism world. The debate ended with John Harwood lying about the debate&amp;rsquo;s length. Having been an occasional guest of Larry Kudlow, I&amp;rsquo;m being nice. But the CNBC reporters couldn&amp;rsquo;t write a story for my high school newspaper.
On the substance of what the candidates said, this was the best debate so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate writing this post</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-hate-writing-this-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 03:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-hate-writing-this-post/</guid>
      <description>I like to say I hate electoral politics.
Maybe I just want people to think I&amp;rsquo;m the kind of person who hates electoral politics. (We are all capable of being wrong about ourselves.)
I have to say, briefly, that this was the most encouraging Republican debate since . . . 1980? These are all serious people, and I&amp;rsquo;m including Trump. They all love America, and not just what they might get from America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am honored to question the GOP candidates for you and Heritage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-am-honored-to-question-the-gop-candidates-for-you-and-heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 12:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-am-honored-to-question-the-gop-candidates-for-you-and-heritage/</guid>
      <description>This is pretty cool and a little unnerving.
Heritage Action has extended the honor to be one of three Heritage Action Sentinels to question Republican Presidential candidates on Friday, September 17 in Greenville, South Carolina. So far, 12 candidates have confirmed, including Donald Trump, Jeb Bush, Ben Carson, Carly Fiorina, Ted Cruz, Scott Walker, Rick Santorum, Bobby Jindal, Rand Paul, Chris Christie, and Marco Rubio. (Maybe Trump will make fun of my tie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump: The final nail in the conservative coffin?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/10/trump-the-final-nail-in-the-conservative-coffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 22:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/10/trump-the-final-nail-in-the-conservative-coffin/</guid>
      <description>So many battles are fought in war and in civilian life, and nothing is gained by their victory. Every battle we fight will result in a gain for us or we will not fight . . . There is no great gain in merely being right. To be right about some unimportant subject is not important.
 &amp;ndash;General George S. Patton
Jonah Goldberg explains the problem of Trump better than anyone:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Worst-Case Scenario?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/26/republicans-worst-case-scenario/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 00:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/26/republicans-worst-case-scenario/</guid>
      <description>Things are getting bad for Hillary.
I hear she&amp;rsquo;s losing a lot of support from Democrat Party insiders, at least in private. The DNC is meeting this week, and talk will likely surround an alternative Democrats can vote for.
While Republicans enjoy the Clinton meltdown, we might want to be careful what we wish for.
One of the GOP&amp;rsquo;s best hopes for the White House is voter enthusiasm. Republicans can&amp;rsquo;t wait to vote, Democrats dread it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Good, Bad, and Ugly</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/24/trump-good-bad-and-ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 21:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/24/trump-good-bad-and-ugly/</guid>
      <description>There seems to be a certain air of inevitability that Trump will win the GOP nomination for President. According to a new poll, 57 percent of Republican voters expect that Trump will be the party&amp;rsquo;s candidate next year. Why is that important?
Expectations Beat Preferences It&amp;rsquo;s important because expectations are far better predictors of actual winners than preference polls. From a 2012 NY Times story by David Leonhardt:
 Over the last 60 years, poll questions that asked people which candidate they expected to win have been a better guide to the outcome of the presidential race than questions asking people whom they planned to vote for, the study found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results of the Cabinet Matching Game</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/23/results-of-the-cabinet-matching-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 17:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/23/results-of-the-cabinet-matching-game/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, I published a simple game for political nerds. Assuming the next president must build a cabinet from current candidates for the Republican nomination for president, how would you assign candidates to cabinet positions.
This was meant to be a fun exercise for people who spend too much time thinking about politics. Like the leaders-eat-last poll, this required hide, often dissatisfying choices. As a result, only six people completed the exercise which took up to a half hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Immigration Fans Need to Read Wong Kim Ark</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 04:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad that Donald Trump has inspired so many good conservatives to promote fantasies about the 14th Amendment.
The Supreme Court addressed the issue of birthright citizenship directly, and Mark Levin and Laura Ingram know it. They are Constitutional lawyers.
Both Levin and Ingraham are familiar with United States v. Wong Kim Ark (1898) which established, thoroughly, that citizenship by birth has been the law of the land since before the Declaration of Independence and was codified by the 14th Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fascinating Results from Leaders Eat Last Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</guid>
      <description>This is the story of hard choices and how people resist making them.
Last week&amp;rsquo;s poll asked you to watch a video by Simon Sinek before answering two, simple, two-part questions: which Republican candidate for President and Missouri Governor is most likely and least likely to eat last?
I intended the poll to be hard. Not complicated, not long, but emotionally challenging.
Why the Poll Was Emotionally Challenging For several weeks, I have built a case for the importance of leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Really Left in the GOP Field?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/18/whos-really-left-in-the-gop-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 23:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/18/whos-really-left-in-the-gop-field/</guid>
      <description>If you lack a unique, differentiating value, your only play is price.
In business, you command the price play by being very, very big and very, very efficient. In presidential politics, you&amp;rsquo;re unique or you close up shop and go home. Commodities don&amp;rsquo;t win executive offices. Usually.
Even though it&amp;rsquo;s early, only four Republican candidates for president have differentiating value propositions:
** Ben Carson ** Donald Trump ** Carly Fiorina ** Ted Cruz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Question for Carly Fiorina</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/18/one-question-for-carly-fiorina/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 10:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/18/one-question-for-carly-fiorina/</guid>
      <description>The next US President must be a great communicator.
Distilling complex and controversial problems into mental models accessible to large numbers of people is not deception&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s brilliance. The reason we hang onto sound bites isn&amp;rsquo;t because we&amp;rsquo;re stupid&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s because we&amp;rsquo;re busy. We all don&amp;rsquo;t have time to earn masters-degree understanding of every issue facing society and government. Honest, accurate distillations of the complex ideas allow us to choose and act quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is The Difference Between Leadership and Service?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/16/what-is-the-difference-between-leadership-and-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 01:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/16/what-is-the-difference-between-leadership-and-service/</guid>
      <description>Marine Corps officers eat last.
That simple insight inspired the title of Simon Sinek&amp;rsquo;s latest book, &amp;ldquo;Leaders Eat Last.&amp;rdquo; If I could influence high school or college curricula, no one would graduate without successfully completing a semester course on that principle.
Below is another remarkable video of Simon Sinek discussing how circumstances can override our desire to lead and serve and how leadership and service can fix almost any problem. But first, I&amp;rsquo;d like you think a bit more about these two critical needs: leadership and service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fill the Cabinet</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/fill-the-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/fill-the-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>My friend Scott Oppelt mentioned his complaint that the GOP has so many great candidates all at once. Why can&amp;rsquo;t they be spread out over 20 years?
Great question. History being what it is, we can&amp;rsquo;t spread them across time, only across government. So this week&amp;rsquo;s poll is a little fun.
The rules:
You must fill the next White House cabinet using only the current candidates for President. You do not know who the President or Vice President is, so assume it&amp;rsquo;s none of the current candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Good Issued From the Candidate Debate?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/what-good-issued-from-the-candidate-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 10:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/what-good-issued-from-the-candidate-debate/</guid>
      <description>Did you hear about the ratings?
Over 24 million people watched the first Republican debate Thursday. That&amp;rsquo;s the largest audience ever for a cable program, save for sports.
Everybody knows why so many watched: people wanted to see a fight break out between Chris Christie and Rand Paul.
Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s presence probably didn&amp;rsquo;t hurt. Let me clarify that. Trump&amp;rsquo;s appearance helped rating. His performance might have ended his campaign.
Donald Trump comported himself with all the dignity and gravitas of a George W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Deserve Better</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/we-deserve-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 07:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/we-deserve-better/</guid>
      <description>I should have gone to bed.
I wanted to finish a great book called The Conservative Heart by Arthur C. Brooks of the American Enterprise Institute. The book left me feeling happy, proud, and inspired.
I should have gone to bed as soon as I finished the book. But the feeling of having read something wonderful wanted to linger, so I sat with it for a bit. Then I really screwed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Partiers in St. Louis See Things a Bit Differently</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/tea-partiers-in-st-louis-see-things-a-bit-differently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/tea-partiers-in-st-louis-see-things-a-bit-differently/</guid>
      <description>There’s a huge, important fiinding in a new poll—one I believe will affect a lot of elections nationally and in Missouri in 2016. In fact, 2016 will come down to one word.
Write down what you think that word is before reading on.
STLTPC vs. USA on President First, let’s look at some polls.
St. Louis Tea Party members see the GOP Presidential race a little differently than the country at large.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Donald Trump Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/27/analysis-of-donald-trump-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 10:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/27/analysis-of-donald-trump-poll/</guid>
      <description>Last week&amp;rsquo;s poll asked for your degree of support for Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy. This poll received far less attention than the Missouri GOP Governor poll of the previous week, as only 60 people responded.
On the plus side, there was no detectable cheating on the Trump poll.
One Word: Polarization [caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_16313&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;600&amp;rdquo;]Histogram of Trump Poll[/caption]
Respondents had choices from 0 to 5 to indicate their degree of support for Trump, with 0 = No Support and 5 = Total Support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poll: What Do You Think About Service?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/26/poll-what-do-you-think-about-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/26/poll-what-do-you-think-about-service/</guid>
      <description>Last week, we posted a 5-part series on national service. This week, we&amp;rsquo;d like to see what you think.
Be heard
The poll closes Saturday, August 1 at Midnight. Please vote only once.
Last Week&amp;rsquo;s Poll: Trump Here&amp;rsquo;s my analysis of last week&amp;rsquo;s poll on Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of 2016 GOP Governor Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/19/analysis-of-2016-gop-governor-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 20:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/19/analysis-of-2016-gop-governor-poll/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I launched anonline poll of declared and likely candidates for governor.
This was not a controlled survey, so be careful what you read into it. Instead of using the poll as a measure of breadth, I recommend looking at from a few other angles.
Suspicious Voting Yes, there was a lot of suspicious voting. At least one candidate received his or her strongest support from a single data center in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/19/donald-trump-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 14:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/19/donald-trump-poll/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump is back in the news. This time for attacking John McCain&amp;rsquo;s service record. But he&amp;rsquo;s dominating the polls.
Given what you know of Donald Trump, rate your own support for Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy for president on a scale of 0 to 5 with 0 meaning &amp;ldquo;no support&amp;rdquo; and 5 meaning &amp;ldquo;full support.&amp;rdquo;
[yop_poll id=&amp;quot;3&amp;rdquo;]
This poll closes at Midnight on Saturday, July 25.
Please vote only once.
Last Week&amp;rsquo;s Poll Results</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approaching Excellence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/21/approaching-excellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 21:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/21/approaching-excellence/</guid>
      <description>Could it be?
Am I reading this right?
Has anyone ever surprised you with a wish? A wish that defied logic?
Yesterday, a friend wrote of his concerns about Eric Greitens, the Navy SEAL, humanitarian, Rhodes Scholar, charity founder, and former boxer who’s considering a run for Missouri Governor.
His concern began: “Most all GOP candidates proudly trumpet their positions . . . “
He was right, of course. Almost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Do With the DOJ Report on Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/what-to-do-with-the-doj-report-on-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 17:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/what-to-do-with-the-doj-report-on-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>The will of man is not shattered, but softened, bent, and guided; men are seldom forced by it to act, but they are constantly restrained from acting. Such a power does not destroy, but it prevents existence; it does not tyrannize, but it compresses, enervates, extinguishes, and stupefies a people, till each nation is reduced to nothing better than a flock of timid and industrious animals, of which the government is the shepherd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Municipal Courts Matter to Liberty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 03:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</guid>
      <description>I am embarrassed.
I am embarrassed that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about this problem sooner. Or I heard about it and ignored it, which is even worse. Maybe I thought it was just the usual liberal whining about trumped up racial problems. Whatever, I should have listened.
On September 2, I asked a room of about 30 tea partiers, &amp;ldquo;Do you trust our justice system?&amp;rdquo; I heard a chorus of &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Justify the Death Penalty?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/12/justify-death-penalty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/12/justify-death-penalty/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not being judgmental or rhetorical with that title. I&amp;rsquo;m curious how other people deal with capital punishment.
Here&amp;rsquo; my story:
Once upon a time, I advocated for the death penalty. Loudly. Shrilly, at times.
In the 1980s and into 1990s, I read a lot. Philosophical. Religious. Legal. Historical. Lots of angles, but few perspectives. You see, I sought out confirming information. I searched high and low for perspectives that would justify my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Erick Erickson Protecting Reince Priebus?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 22:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE:
Welcome, Donald Trump fans! Thanks for reading.
Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s true, I have had disagreements with Erick in the past. I try to assess the situation, not just the person. It&amp;rsquo;s possible to disagree with someone on one subject and to agree with them on another.
If anything, Erick showed consistency by rescinding Trump&amp;rsquo;s invitation to Red State. Erick didn&amp;rsquo;t want the event to descend into chaos led by my friends over the Barbour episode; he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a descent into chaos led by Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Weinstein and His Call to Jail Global Warming Skeptics</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Yet, in holding scientific research and discovery in respect, as we should, we must also be alert to the equal and opposite danger that public policy could itself become the captive of a scientific-technological elite.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ndash;President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Farewell Address, 1961
A young man named Adam Weinstein recently called for incarceration of disbelievers in the cult of catastrophic anthropogenic global warming (CAGW). His argument mirrors the argument Goebbels used in 1930s to quash dissent from eugenics and to take immediate policy actions for the betterment of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Boston Marathon Bombing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/15/thoughts-on-boston-marathon-bombing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 02:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/15/thoughts-on-boston-marathon-bombing/</guid>
      <description>. . . What Your Definition of Terrorism Is I heard a lot of people giving their opinions of what constitutes “terrorism.” Here’s the United States Code:
 Definitions &amp;hellip; the term &amp;lsquo;terrorism&amp;rsquo; means premeditated, politically motivated violence perpetrated against noncombatant targets by subnational groups or clandestine agents;
 Let’s stick with that one. To be terrorism, all of these five elements must be present. You can use it as a checklist:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Compromise Is Like Half a Boob Job</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/15/why-compromise-is-like-half-a-boob-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/15/why-compromise-is-like-half-a-boob-job/</guid>
      <description>A man wants his wife to get breast implants. His wife doesn’t want it.
They compromise, and she gets one implant.
Is this the best outcome?
No! It’s the worst possible outcome. Either of the two other outcomes—no implants or two—would be better than the compromise.
So why are Americans so infatuated with political compromise that leaves the country more lopsided?
Why Compromise Produce the Worst Outcome The FBI’s top hostage negotiator provided my example, via Eric Barker’s fabulous blog, Barking Up The Wrong Tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Search of Loyalty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/26/in-search-of-loyalty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 10:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/26/in-search-of-loyalty/</guid>
      <description>Long
To what and whom do we owe loyalty, and how should we express it?
Generational historians William Strauss and Neil Howe describe a generation of &amp;ldquo;nomads&amp;rdquo; in their prophetic book The Fourth Turning.
 &amp;ldquo;The 13th Generation (Nomad, born 1961-1981) survived a hurried childhood of divorce, latchkeys, open classrooms, devil-child movies, and a shift from G to R ratings. They came of age curtailing the earlier rise in youth crime and fall in test scores—yet heard themselves denounced as so wild and stupid as to put The Nation at Risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the GSA&#39;s 8th Grade Minds That Run Your Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/21/meet-the-gsas-8th-grade-minds-that-run-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 18:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/21/meet-the-gsas-8th-grade-minds-that-run-your-life/</guid>
      <description>There are two kinds of people in America: those who grow up to become productive adults, and those who become bureaucrats.
The GSA scandal lit up the 3 Stooges mentality of the &amp;ldquo;men and women&amp;rdquo; who would run every aspect of your life if Obama and his czars get their way.

Jeff Neely&amp;rsquo;s the guy Thomas Jefferson had in mind when wrote:
 He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harass our people, and eat out their substance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Government Growth Creates Scrooges</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/27/how-government-growth-creates-scrooges/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/27/how-government-growth-creates-scrooges/</guid>
      <description>Scrooge’s nephew left the office and let in two men in the process. They came to ask for a donation for London’s poor.
 &amp;ldquo;At this festive season of the year, Mr. Scrooge,&amp;rdquo; said the gentleman, taking up a pen, &amp;ldquo;it is more than usually desirable that we should make some slight provision for the Poor and destitute, who suffer greatly at the present time. Many thousands are in want of common necessaries; hundreds of thousands are in want of common comforts, sir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GOP is to Public Relations What Evel Knievel Was to Motorcycle Safety</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/23/the-gop-is-to-public-relations-what-evel-knievel-was-to-motorcycle-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/23/the-gop-is-to-public-relations-what-evel-knievel-was-to-motorcycle-safety/</guid>
      <description>I live in a very hilly area. Yet I’m still alive. Explain that.
Maybe that’s why I’m a lower-case “r” republican and not an upper-case one.
Republicans seem to feel every hill is worth dying on.
What else could explain the House’s rejection of a silly payroll tax cut extension followed by a doubly-damaging capitulation?
By “silly,” I mean ill-advised, inconsequential, irrational, and fiscally irresponsible. The Senate’s two-month extension of the Social Security tax cut represents the worst of Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Fit?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/23/whos-fit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/23/whos-fit/</guid>
      <description>Take a look at Drudge.
I’ll wait. The day doesn’t really matter. It’s always full of stuff that makes you think rivets are flying out of the planet like a jalopy in a cartoon.
** Two girls beat another girl into convulsions over the course of eight minutes while cowardly young men quiver in fear. (But an old lady steps in and protects the victim.) ** Syrian security opens fire on demonstrators killing 90.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Kill the Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/how-to-kill-the-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/how-to-kill-the-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>If the Tea Party—or ACORN or the Democratic National Committee or anyone or anything else, for that matter—stays in a perpetual state of heightened negative emotions nothing positive gets accomplished.
The gazelle that flees imaginary lions soon dies of exhaustion. As positive emotions researcher Barbara Frederickson puts it:
 when extreme, prolonged, or contextually inappropriate, negative emotions can trigger a wide array of problems for individuals and for society.
 Phobias develop out of unchecked fear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power and the Glory</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/29/the-power-and-the-glory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/29/the-power-and-the-glory/</guid>
      <description>_**&amp;ldquo;For over a thousand years Roman conquerors returning from the wars enjoyed the honor of triumph, a tumultuous parade. In the procession came trumpeteers, musicians and strange animals from conquered territories, together with carts laden with treasure and captured armaments. The conquerors rode in a triumphal chariot, the dazed prisoners walking in chains before him. Sometimes his children robed in white stood with him in the chariot or rode the trace horses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Your Bill and Shove It, Mr. President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/04/take-your-bill-and-shove-it-mr-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 15:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/04/take-your-bill-and-shove-it-mr-president/</guid>
      <description>Missouri voters roundly rejected ObamaCare, all of its works, and all of its empty promises.
By an overwhelming, unmistakable 71 percent, we said to the Obama Regime, “Take this bill and shove it.”
The overwhelming passage was a slap in the face to the Missouri Hospital Association and to BJC President Steven Lipstein who spent nearly $500,000 trying to convince their employees that the hospital chain profits trump the Constitution. Pathetic worms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing Battles</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/choosing-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 01:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/choosing-battles/</guid>
      <description>For the record, I do not apologize for focusing on the most important battles facing self-government since the American Revolution.

Earlier this week, McGraw Milhaven of 550 KTRS criticized Tea Partyers for not opposing Missouri legislation, introduced by and championed by Republicans, that will force insurance companies to cover treatment for children diagnosed with Autism and associated conditions. (I personally oppose this legislation, by the way.)
Before that, a few Tea Partyers criticized me and others on facebook for not doing “enough” to support the Missouri Healthcare Free Choice act, which recently passed both the House and the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geek out on this</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/geek-out-on-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 05:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/geek-out-on-this/</guid>
      <description>You’ll be glad you did.
https://video.ted.com/assets/player/swf/EmbedPlayer.swf
This eighteen minute presentation synthesizes almost everything I believe about leadership and inspiration.
We own Why
We believe that God&amp;rsquo;s law trumps Man&amp;rsquo;s, and that the Constitution trumps Congress. And the President. And the courts. We believe that each one of us has the will and the capacity to dream our own dreams, live our own lives, and die our own noble deaths without government assistance or government contraints.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>