<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Erick Erickson on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/erick-erickson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Erick Erickson on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 22:08:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/erick-erickson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Erick Erickson Protecting Reince Priebus?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 22:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE:
Welcome, Donald Trump fans! Thanks for reading.
Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s true, I have had disagreements with Erick in the past. I try to assess the situation, not just the person. It&amp;rsquo;s possible to disagree with someone on one subject and to agree with them on another.
If anything, Erick showed consistency by rescinding Trump&amp;rsquo;s invitation to Red State. Erick didn&amp;rsquo;t want the event to descend into chaos led by my friends over the Barbour episode; he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a descent into chaos led by Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Reasons Why House Republicans Should Pass a Clean Debt Ceiling Bill Now *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/05/4-reasons-to-pass-clean-debt-ceiling-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 16:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/05/4-reasons-to-pass-clean-debt-ceiling-bill/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, I know. Obama&amp;rsquo;s childish, petulant, and tyrannical tantrums over the continuing resolution makes me want to fight like an angry cat, too.
But I don&amp;rsquo;t actually want to fight. Fighting isn&amp;rsquo;t in our interest. As Sun Tzu said:
 Hence to fight and conquer in all your battles is not supreme excellence; supreme excellence consists in breaking the enemy&amp;rsquo;s resistance without fighting.
 I want to succeed in repealing Obamacare and forcing government into its constitutionally limited box.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>