<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tax code on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tax-code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tax code on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 16:39:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tax-code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Same-Sex Marriage Is a Tax Problem</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/07/same-sex-marriage-is-tax-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 16:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/07/same-sex-marriage-is-tax-problem/</guid>
      <description>Why is government involved in marriage at all? Taxes.
Brian Bollmann makes an excellent point about same-sex marriage.
Brian points out in this post that marriage is not a matter for government; contract law is. Government&amp;rsquo;s only concern in the case of a marriage is with its contractual implications:
 At some point in the short history of the United States (and certainly after the Civil War), state governments stepped onto the wall of separation and began getting involved in the religious institution of marriage in the appropriate area of protecting the rights to property – especially that of women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s the One Thing Congress Should Push Right Now?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/03/whats-the-one-thing-congress-should-push-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/03/whats-the-one-thing-congress-should-push-right-now/</guid>
      <description>It’s not the Balanced Budget Amendment, though that’s a good second choice.
It’s certainly not senseless and impossible ideas like impeaching Obama or suing over birth certificates.
Instead, we should push an idea that’s ripe for quick passage. It’s an idea that cheers political moderates and conservatives. And it doesn’t immediately turn off liberals.
What is it?
It’s an old idea that Jack Kemp championed for decades. It’s an idea that I’ve written about many times before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>