<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>debt on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/debt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in debt on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 21:33:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/debt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If Donald Trump Scares You, You Should See a Depression</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/09/if-donald-trump-scares-you-you-should-see-a-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 21:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/09/if-donald-trump-scares-you-you-should-see-a-depression/</guid>
      <description>Guest post by Lee Presser.
America’s fiscal year is October 1 to September 30. With two month left in FY16, the U.S. Treasury has already paid creditors $380,925,428,211.67 in interest costs. (That’s $381 Billion) https://www.treasurydirect.gov/govt/reports/ir/ir_expense.htm
The average interest rate was just over 2%. https://www.treasurydirect.gov/govt/rates/pd/avg/2016/2016_07.htm
 It is expected that the last two month’s of this fiscal year, interest costs will increase another $45 to $66 Billion. The total FY16 interest cost may be between $426 and $447 Billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chili Palmer</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/13/chili-palmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/13/chili-palmer/</guid>
      <description>The greatest mob movie of all time was Get Shorty. (Please, don’t argue.) The whole movie revolved around this exchange:
 Ronnie Wingate: Excuse me bro&amp;rsquo;, but who the fuck are you? Chili Palmer: I&amp;rsquo;m the one tellin&amp;rsquo; you how it is&amp;hellip;
 Last Sunday, Greece was Chili Palmer. A few days later, Angela Merkel is.
  
Funny how things change.
You probably heard that Greece’s Prime Minister called for a referendum on the troika’s terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Never Guess Who&#39;s About to Become Obama&#39;s Biggest Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>In 2008, we heard all about the youth movement for Obama. We heard that the enormous Millennial Generation, born between 1982 and 2001, would destroy the GOP and everything America once stood for&amp;ndash;like jobs, family, faith, and hard work. And when Obama won, many believed the tales of the Obama Youth.
  
But many were wrong. Voters under 30 have had it with vague promises and glittering bullshit from that punk from Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYT Describes Mayhem of “Taxmageddon”, And It Will Scare You Sick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</guid>
      <description>What the hell’s going on at NYT? First, they do a piece on Andrew Breitbart. Then they warn the world that Taxmageddon will crush the world in 2013, beginning with the USA.

Here&amp;rsquo;s how Business Insider summarized the David Leohardt article:
 Basically, with no changes to current law, taxes will rise for everyone, and after tax, inflation-adjusted income for the average American will drop to 1998 levels.
 Read more: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This David Stockman Quote Should Scare the Hell Out of Everyone</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/05/this-david-stockman-quote-should-scare-the-hell-out-of-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/05/this-david-stockman-quote-should-scare-the-hell-out-of-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Is the US economy about to collapse worse the Greece’s?
Some, like Paul Krugman, say that it’s okay for governments to print unlimited money. Others, who have actually managed businesses, say otherwise.
**David Stockman is among the latter. He was Reagan’s budget director for a few years. He became a media sensation because of his command of numbers. **
He left the White House early, fretting over federal debt. But debt in the 1980s was as a piggy bank to Wells Fargo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>