<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jay Nixon on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jay-nixon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jay Nixon on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 06:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jay-nixon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Worst of Humanity and the Absence of Leadership in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/worst-humanity-abence-leadership-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 06:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/worst-humanity-abence-leadership-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>I should be in bed. But I can&amp;rsquo;t take my eyes off the images of Ferguson burning to the ground.
A liberal friend on Twitter admonished me not to be political. Maybe he&amp;rsquo;s right.
But I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Dellena&amp;rsquo;s 911 Beauty Salon burned in Ferguson tonight. It seems everything else has, too. The airport is closed. St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s image may be taking a fatal blow. The region might go the way of Gary, Indiana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Jay Nixon Lost the Liberal Press</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/24/jay-nixon-lost-liberal-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/24/jay-nixon-lost-liberal-press/</guid>
      <description>“And then say what? say, ‘forget you’re hungry, forget you got shot inna back by some racist cop—Chuck was here? Chuck come up to Harlem—’ ”“No, I’ll tell you what—” “‘Chuck come up to Harlem and—’ ”“I’ll tell you what—” “Say,‘Chuck come up to Harlem and gonna take care a business for the black community’?” That does it. Heh-heggggggggggggggggghhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! It’s one of those ungodly contralto cackles somewhere out there in the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**DOH!** ACTION: Tell Missouri Legislature Jay Nixon to Pass Tax Holiday for Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 20:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>****UPDATE
Tim Jones let me know that I&amp;rsquo;m giving the legislature more power than it actually has.
Veto sessions are limited to overriding vetos. Thus the name. BUT the governor can call a Special Session to vote on a Ferguson Tax Holiday. That session can run concurrent with the Veto Session, saving taxpayer dollars.
SO &amp;gt; &amp;gt; &amp;gt; New Action: Ask Jay Nixon (via Twitter and Facebook) to call a Special Session concurrent with the Veto Session to create a Tax Holiday for Ferguson/Dellwood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Hard to Deny North County Has Problems with Police and Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>What did you think when you first heard reports of violence in Ferguson? I mean, after the shooting death of Michael Brown?
Did you ever for a moment think, &amp;ldquo;this is about more than just Michael Brown?&amp;rdquo;
I hate to say that. It&amp;rsquo;s embarrassing to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m so jaded as to think &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;rdquo; when a young man dies. Sorry. I&amp;rsquo;m just being honest.
I understand community grief and anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri Republicans Made Jay Nixon Look Like a Statesman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 01:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</guid>
      <description>You know how reckless and tone-deaf Obama is about Army deserters? Missouri&amp;rsquo;s House and Senate Republican leaders are just as clueless and irresponsible about money.
Yes, I said it: the Missouri Republican legislature is about as conservative and principled as Susan Rice on a Sunday talk show.
By going on a votes-for-cash spending spree on the last day of the General Assembly, the House and Senate handed Jay &amp;ldquo;Idiot&amp;rdquo; Nixon a PR prize worth its weight in pork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Missouri DOR’s Enhanced Interrogation Methods Should Make You Mad</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/14/why-the-missouri-dors-enhanced-interrogation-methods-should-make-you-mad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/14/why-the-missouri-dors-enhanced-interrogation-methods-should-make-you-mad/</guid>
      <description>Pulled from comments, in response to TJ, you asked: &amp;ldquo;I am somewhat confused about the current outrage. Shouldn’t the DOR verify, to the greatest extent possible, that an applicant for renewal of any state issued ID be who they maintain to be, live where they claim to live and so on.&amp;quot;
If you’re buying beer at Schnuck’s, you expect the cashier to card you, right? That’s because the cashier is required to verify your are 21 or older.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Jay Nixon Spit in Our Faces?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/15/why-did-jay-nixon-spit-in-our-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 18:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/15/why-did-jay-nixon-spit-in-our-faces/</guid>
      <description>When Jay Nixon decided to ignore the voters, ignore the Missouri Constitution, and ignore the power of the legislature, he spit in our faces. But why?
Maybe because his special session is failing.
Maybe because, to save the centerpiece of that legislation, House Speaker Steve Tilley needed protection from the grass roots.
Maybe because Jay Nixon is as crooked as a dog’s hind leg and doesn’t give a hoot about you, your state, your country, or the law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Updates on University of Missouri Story</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/28/3-updates-on-university-of-missouri-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/28/3-updates-on-university-of-missouri-story/</guid>
      <description>Big news day in the advance of liberty in our battle against collectivists.
First, KMOX is reporting that an UMSL professor has resigned** over the controversy**. For the life of me, I cannot find who the professor is. I thought that everyone involved was either an instructor or a guest lecturer. If you know the answer to the riddle, please use the comment form.
Second, University of Kansas City refuses to accept responsibility for what goes on in its classroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Leader condones political violence: “It certainly has its place. It’s a tactic that should be used at the appropriate time. I believe in a violent overthrow . . . , and that freedom is found at the barrel of a gun”</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/27/tea-party-leader-condones-political-violence-it-certainly-has-its-place-its-a-tactic-that-should-be-used-at-the-appropriate-time-i-believe-in-a-violent-overthrow-and-that-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 02:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/27/tea-party-leader-condones-political-violence-it-certainly-has-its-place-its-a-tactic-that-should-be-used-at-the-appropriate-time-i-believe-in-a-violent-overthrow-and-that-free/</guid>
      <description>Did I say “Tea Party Leader?” ** I meant labor union leader Don Giljum condones violence, intimidation, and sabotage.** Giljum’s the business manager for Operating Engineers Local 148 and a lecturer at University of Missouri-St. Louis. It’s in the UMSL classroom that he pontificates and brags about the . . . the uglier side of negotiations.
Here’s what he actually said about violence for political purposes:
 It certainly has its place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTION: Melt the Phones</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/27/action-melt-the-phones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/27/action-melt-the-phones/</guid>
      <description>I’m going to ask you to melt phones in Jefferson City, UMSL, UMKC, and Mizzou. I’m asking you to do this today and tomorrow. I’m following up with an email to you.
It’s sad that our state’s premier University System has fallen so far.
Follow the #mounion hash tag on twitter
Jay Nixon just asked the legislature to transfer $400 million from the taxpayers to the University of Missouri System. Unless the Governor or the Legislature acts at your request, some of that money will go to put you out of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shut Down Labor Studies Now, Governor Nixon</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/26/shut-down-labor-studies-now-governor-nixon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 02:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/26/shut-down-labor-studies-now-governor-nixon/</guid>
      <description>Governor Nixon:
What does it take to get your attention? What does it take to get you to act?
Your University of Missouri System humiliates this state, and you refuse to act.
Under your nose, the UofM teaches or encourages:
* **[Politically motivated](https://biggovernment.com/publius/2011/04/25/union-official-professor-teach-college-course-in-violent-union-tactics/) violence**** **Politically motivated [industrial sabotage](https://biggovernment.com/publius/2011/04/25/how-to-college-course-on-violent-union-tactics-part-ii-case-studies-edition/)**** **Politically motivated threats of violence and sabotage**** **Supporting and aiding [the enemy in Iraq and Afghanistan](https://biggovernment.com/driehl/2011/04/26/college-course-us-flag-is-racist-how-to-defeat-america-in-iraq-and-afghanistan/)**  You have permit these travesties. You, Jay Nixon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jay Nixon Putting Party Ahead of Missouri? *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/jay-nixon-putting-party-ahead-of-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/jay-nixon-putting-party-ahead-of-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Last week, the Illinois legislature passed a massive income tax increase on individuals and businesses. Overall, it represents about a 67 percent income tax increase.
In response, neighboring states of Wisconsin and Indiana have wisely mounted massive campaigns to suck businesses and people out of Illinois. Even New Jersey’s fabulous governor, Chris Christie, plans to fish the Land o’ Lincoln for some business transplants.
One state bordering Illinois has been notoriously silent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>