<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jay Nixon on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jay-nixon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jay Nixon on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 06:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jay-nixon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Worst of Humanity and the Absence of Leadership in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/worst-humanity-abence-leadership-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 06:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/worst-humanity-abence-leadership-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>I should be in bed. But I can&amp;rsquo;t take my eyes off the images of Ferguson burning to the ground.
A liberal friend on Twitter admonished me not to be political. Maybe he&amp;rsquo;s right.
But I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Dellena&amp;rsquo;s 911 Beauty Salon burned in Ferguson tonight. It seems everything else has, too. The airport is closed. St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s image may be taking a fatal blow. The region might go the way of Gary, Indiana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Jay Nixon Lost the Liberal Press</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/24/jay-nixon-lost-liberal-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/24/jay-nixon-lost-liberal-press/</guid>
      <description>“And then say what? say, ‘forget you’re hungry, forget you got shot inna back by some racist cop—Chuck was here? Chuck come up to Harlem—’ ”“No, I’ll tell you what—” “‘Chuck come up to Harlem and—’ ”“I’ll tell you what—” “Say,‘Chuck come up to Harlem and gonna take care a business for the black community’?” That does it. Heh-heggggggggggggggggghhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! It’s one of those ungodly contralto cackles somewhere out there in the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**DOH!** ACTION: Tell Missouri Legislature Jay Nixon to Pass Tax Holiday for Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 20:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>****UPDATE
Tim Jones let me know that I&amp;rsquo;m giving the legislature more power than it actually has.
Veto sessions are limited to overriding vetos. Thus the name. BUT the governor can call a Special Session to vote on a Ferguson Tax Holiday. That session can run concurrent with the Veto Session, saving taxpayer dollars.
SO &amp;gt; &amp;gt; &amp;gt; New Action: Ask Jay Nixon (via Twitter and Facebook) to call a Special Session concurrent with the Veto Session to create a Tax Holiday for Ferguson/Dellwood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Hard to Deny North County Has Problems with Police and Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>What did you think when you first heard reports of violence in Ferguson? I mean, after the shooting death of Michael Brown?
Did you ever for a moment think, &amp;ldquo;this is about more than just Michael Brown?&amp;rdquo;
I hate to say that. It&amp;rsquo;s embarrassing to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m so jaded as to think &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;rdquo; when a young man dies. Sorry. I&amp;rsquo;m just being honest.
I understand community grief and anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri Republicans Made Jay Nixon Look Like a Statesman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 01:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</guid>
      <description>You know how reckless and tone-deaf Obama is about Army deserters? Missouri&amp;rsquo;s House and Senate Republican leaders are just as clueless and irresponsible about money.
Yes, I said it: the Missouri Republican legislature is about as conservative and principled as Susan Rice on a Sunday talk show.
By going on a votes-for-cash spending spree on the last day of the General Assembly, the House and Senate handed Jay &amp;ldquo;Idiot&amp;rdquo; Nixon a PR prize worth its weight in pork.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>