<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Satire on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/satire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Satire on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 00:04:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/satire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghosts Organize in Alton, Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/22/ghosts-organize-alton-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 00:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/22/ghosts-organize-alton-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Alton, Illinois — Spirits of the dead in the river city of Alton, Illinois, voted last night to organize as a union affiliated with the Service Employees International Union (SEIU).
Everett Johnson, a lawyer representing the ghosts, says he will begin negotiations with the town’s haunted house tour guides, spirit shops, and even owners of haunted properties.
“The living have been exploiting these tortured souls for decades,” Johnson told Hennessy’s View.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Performs “Indian Rain Dance” To Quell Dispute</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/elizabeth-warren-performs-indian-rain-dance-to-quell-dispute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/elizabeth-warren-performs-indian-rain-dance-to-quell-dispute/</guid>
      <description>Cambridge, MA—Massachusetts Democratic Senate candidate Elizabeth Warren donned a pink headdress and performed, what she called, an “authentic Indian rain dance” during a press conference today. Ms Warren was hoping to convince skeptics of her claims of Native American heritage. She also hinted that her preference for bison meat to beef indicates her heritage.
“My pepaw taught me this dance when I was a little girl,” Warren said during a short session with reporters at a high school gymnasium in Cambridge, MA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Attends Backyard Barbecue Fundraiser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/05/obama-attends-backyard-barbecue-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 16:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/05/obama-attends-backyard-barbecue-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12133&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;359&amp;rdquo;] President Obama looks over the menu before a campaign backyard barbecue in Ohio.[/caption]
Reports are that he went with the Neapolitan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Holds Auditions for New Terrorist Mastermind</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/01/u-s-holds-auditions-for-new-terrorist-mastermind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 15:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/01/u-s-holds-auditions-for-new-terrorist-mastermind/</guid>
      <description>Washington, DC&amp;ndash;Reeling from the backlash over a campaign ad that paints President Barack Obama as Osama bin Laden&amp;rsquo;s sole assassin, the White House today announced open auditions for a new global terrorist mastermind.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12119&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;570&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Last year&amp;rsquo;s White House auditions for press secretary&amp;rdquo;]  [/caption]
White House spokesman Jay Carney told reporters &amp;ldquo;the world needs a dangerous, evil character to worry about . . . and, frankly, so does the President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White House Unveils Unemployment Strategy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/01/10/white-house-unveils-unemployment-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 19:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/01/10/white-house-unveils-unemployment-strategy/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, DC: The White House unveiled a new strategy to lower the nation’s unemployment rate, currently standing at 10 percent.
In his weekly radio address Saturday, the President announced that he will use remaining funds from the failed Stimulus bill to take advantage of little known variable in the unemployment rate factor: “discouraged workers.”
Pointing out that “discouraged” workers are excluded from the unemployment calculation, the President explained that the government will encourage the unemployed to simply give up hopes for finding work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>