<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>obama lies on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/obama-lies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in obama lies on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 16:17:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/obama-lies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>80 Percent of Americans Read This Blog Every Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/16/80-percent-of-americans-read-this-blog-every-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/16/80-percent-of-americans-read-this-blog-every-day/</guid>
      <description>I’ll be honest with you: I’ve lied.
Usually out of desperation. I’ve lied to those closest to me—those most willing to forgive the thing I lied about.
I’ve also told the truth to my own detriment. In the long run, the latter works best. In fact, telling the truth works best in the short run, too.
So maybe Obama’s desperate. Maybe he knows that the debt ceiling debate is the beginning of the unraveling of Americum Sovieticum, his life-long dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimme More Money or Granny Gets It!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/12/gimme-more-money-or-granny-gets-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/12/gimme-more-money-or-granny-gets-it/</guid>
      <description>Obama showed his breaking point today. The stress got to him.
Today Obama threatened to stop Social Security payments if Congress doesn’t bend to his will on the debt ceiling.
The president told reporters that there may not be enough money to pay Social Security benefits on and after August 3rd.
But the President lies.
Revenue from taxes and other fees would cover Social Security and other payments. What won’t be covered is additional borrowing to service the country’s already outrageous debt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>