<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Living insurance on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/living-insurance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Living insurance on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/living-insurance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Votes on Obamacare Today</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</guid>
      <description>We won’t know the result until late June, most likely. And the results of today’s vote could change by then.

Still, it’s sort of weird that after three years of public, wildly emotional and stupifyingly complex arguments, the fate of the republic comes down to a short meeting in Washington involving nine people in a paneled room.
Mark Sherman of AP describes the cloistered scene:
 After months of anticipation, thousands of pages of briefs and more than six hours of arguments, the justices will vote on the fate of President Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s health care overhaul in under an hour Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Health Insurance Solution that Some Smart State Should Try</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/a-health-insurance-solution-that-some-smart-state-should-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 15:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/a-health-insurance-solution-that-some-smart-state-should-try/</guid>
      <description>The term “United States” is both plural (many states united) and singular (the United States). The tag line “e pluribus unum” loses its meaning if we cease to be many, if we give up our identities as individual states. As states, we are as different from each other as the United States is from Canada.
The United States are most powerful pursuing opportunities and fixing problems in the plural but defending in the singular.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>