<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fiction on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fiction on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapter Twelve</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/03/civil-war-chapter-twelve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/03/civil-war-chapter-twelve/</guid>
      <description>Roger crashed into his office. His sanctuary. It was only two fifteen, but he wanted a drink. Calls first.
He pulled out is cell phone and decided to call the cop again. But the phone buzzed in his hand before he could find the number.
“Hello,” Roger said.
“Hi, Mr. Thompson? This is Amanda Mateo, one of David’s teachers.”
“Hi. Ms. Mateo. Yeah, we met in August.”
“Oh, yeah, right. Parents’ Night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapter Eleven</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/01/civil-war-chapter-eleven/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 19:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/01/civil-war-chapter-eleven/</guid>
      <description>Roger Thompson had completed his checklist. He’d learned from Jack Murphy, his friend and attorney, that the police sergeant seemed cooperative.
With his tasks out of the way, he knew it was time to deal with his wife, Natalie.
Natalie and Roger didn’t see eye to eye politically. Natalie described herself as a progressive. Even though they rarely discussed politics, Roger knew Natalie was politically active before they got married. She worked a lot of referendum campaigns in college and after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapters Nine and Ten</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/29/civil-war-chapters-nine-and-ten/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 19:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/29/civil-war-chapters-nine-and-ten/</guid>
      <description>Chapter Nine “Elizabeth, I’m going to be out of the building the rest of the day. You have my cell. Vice-principal Johnson is in his office.”
Elizabeth had a mouthful of Goldfish and could only grunt. But she wrote a note herself and nodded furiously at her boss.
Nancy Flanders left the building.
Forty-two minutes later, Flanders was parked and walking into the lobby of modern, glass and stainless steel building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapter Eight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/27/civil-war-chapter-eight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 19:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/27/civil-war-chapter-eight/</guid>
      <description>Nancy Flanders sat perfectly still. Amanda Mateo fidgeted and rocked. Between lay a false statement and a pen.
Amanda spoke. “I won’t sign that. I’ll write my own report. I should have spoken to the police yesterday. I’ll write my statement and give it you right now. But I’m not signing that,” pointing toward the statement on the desk.
“That won’t be necessary. I’m afraid I’ll have to place you on suspension until the board reviews your case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapters Six and Seven</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/25/civil-war-chapter-six/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 18:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/25/civil-war-chapter-six/</guid>
      <description>Chapter Six “Evan, this is Roger.”
“How’s it going? Where are you?”
“I’m at home. Listen, I’m going to have to use a sick day today.”
“Everything okay?”
“Not really. It’s a long story. David got beat up pretty bad yesterday at school. In school,” Roger said.
“Well, hell. Sorry to hear that. Don’t worry about anything. I’ve got you covered.”
“Thanks, Evan. Sorry about this.”
“No worries. It’s the slow season anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>