<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Surge on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/surge/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Surge on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2007 20:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/surge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Where I stand on Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/where-i-stand-on-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2007 20:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/where-i-stand-on-iraq/</guid>
      <description>I stand for total victory in Iraq.
Background Some say that I blindly support President Bush and everything he does. I do not. Nor do I publicly lambaste his missteps the way others, like Peggy Noonan, do. This blog, I hope, will explain to my readers and friends how I can hold several seemingly incongruous positions on Bush and the War.
 * The United States, the free world, in fact, was justified in invading Iraq and overthrowing Saddam * The war in Iraq was not successful in its early days despite the perception of a rout * The administration&#39;s greatest failure was kowtowing to the left * The symptom of that kowtowing was establishing a defensive posture instead of continuing the attack * Donald Rumsfeld failed the President by refusing to return to an offensive strategy * The key to victory is ruthless aggression * Republicans should limit criticism of Bush to recommendations that will achieve victory  Justification Following 9/11, President Bush told Peggy Noonan in a private meeting that every night he goes to bed expecting to be woken and told that Saddam has unleashed a WMD in America.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>