<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cronyism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/cronyism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cronyism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 21:31:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/cronyism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Export-Import Bank Story the Post-Dispatch Refused to Print</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/export-import-bank-story-post-dispatch-refused-print/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 21:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/export-import-bank-story-post-dispatch-refused-print/</guid>
      <description>Since the Post won&amp;rsquo;t run my reply a recent op-ed about the Ex-Im Bank, I&amp;rsquo;ll publish it here:
Huge multi-national corporations like to preach from the &amp;ldquo;small business&amp;rdquo; bible when it comes to the Export-Import bank. Unfortunately, most of the Ex-Im propaganda about how &amp;ldquo;small business&amp;rdquo; benefits crumbles under scrutiny.
Professor Stanford Levin of Southern Illinois University recently wrote an Op-Ed supporting reauthorization of the Export Import Bank. As the professor states, the Export-Import Bank provides cheap loans to foreign companies and governments with which to buy products sold by mostly large, multi-national companies with headquarters in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thad Cochran&#39;s Pyrrhic Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/06/thad-cochran-mortally-wound-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 21:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/06/thad-cochran-mortally-wound-gop/</guid>
      <description>A Pyrrhic victory is a victory with such a devastating cost that it is tantamount to defeat. Someone who wins a Pyrrhic victory has been victorious in some way; however, the heavy toll negates any sense of achievement or profit (another term for this would be &amp;ldquo;hollow victory&amp;rdquo;).
 — from Wikipedia
I keep some things in a little box in my bedroom. Some Navy and submarine mementos, some letters, favorite photos of the kids that mean things only to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New American Political Dichotomy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/24/new-american-political-dichotomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 08:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/24/new-american-political-dichotomy/</guid>
      <description>Before we get to politics, I want to tell you about a business exercise.
The Universal Veto Game  Sometimes my job as a consultant involves helping people decide what to do when no ideas have a consensus. Sure, someone in a hierarchy can dictate terms, but dictated solutions don&amp;rsquo;t really work in business. Cooperation and collaboration are too important for success, and dictated terms are usually executed half-assed.
So we play this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Crony Capitalism Spreads Bureaucracy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</guid>
      <description>St. Louisan Eric Greitens did more before graduating from college than most people do in a lifetime. And, as if to insult us all, after college, Eric became a Navy SEAL.
In his remarkable book, The Heart and the Fist: The education of a humanitarian, the making of a Navy SEAL, Greitens tells the story of a man who seems too good to be true. Seriously. And the book left me with two big impressions&amp;ndash;probably the wrong ones, but that&amp;rsquo;s how I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockwood School Board Quid Pro Quo?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/rockwood-school-board-quid-pro-quo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 21:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/rockwood-school-board-quid-pro-quo/</guid>
      <description>From the &amp;ldquo;see, I told ya so&amp;rdquo; file . . .
Rockwood NEA President Suzanne Dotta worked hard to influence the recent school board election. The candidates Ms. Dotta pushed won.
The new board hired Ms. Dotta as Director of Professional Learning within 72 hours of the election.
I expect Ms. Dotta to teach Rockwood&amp;rsquo;s professionals how to game the system for personal gain at taxpayer expense.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to question this apparent quid pro quo, the next Rockwood Board meeting is April 24.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>