<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mike Flynn on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mike-flynn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mike Flynn on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 22:09:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mike-flynn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Flynn, RIP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/24/mike-flynn-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 22:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/24/mike-flynn-rip/</guid>
      <description>When the BBC called Brexit for LEAVE at about 12:30 a.m. CDT today, I thought first of my friend Mike Flynn. Mike had a keen sense of history. He put the Tea Party movement into proper perspective, as he did with all events. Mike kept us from overstating both the Tea Party&amp;rsquo;s effect and its potential. Or he put them in context and reminded us that our potential depends on ourselves, not outside forces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Flynn for Congress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/25/mike-flynn-for-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 21:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/25/mike-flynn-for-congress/</guid>
      <description>I was hungover.
I sat in a booth at the Holiday Inn in Quincy, Illinois, with my wife and two friends from St. Louis. The day before was my wife&amp;rsquo;s birthday, which she graciously spent waiting for me to speak at a tea party in Quincy.
Angela and I sat with Jim Durbin and Ben Evans. About four feet away, sitting at the bar, were Andrew Breitbart and editor-in-chief of Andrew&amp;rsquo;s BigGovernment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Me Apologize</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/21/let-me-apologize/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 01:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/21/let-me-apologize/</guid>
      <description>In my response to Dan Riehl’s hit piece on Ed Martin, I wrote one more line than I should have. I wrote about an establishment takeover of Big Government.
Mike Flynn, the editor of Big Government, has quietly (and not so quietly) led the fight for liberty and good government for decades. His Big Government site has been a backbone in the resurgence of our first principles.
Much more importantly to me, Mike Flynn is a friend of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>