<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Corruption on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/corruption/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Corruption on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:34:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/corruption/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Crooked as a Dog’s Hind Leg</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/19/crooked-as-a-dogs-hind-leg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/19/crooked-as-a-dogs-hind-leg/</guid>
      <description>That’s St. Louis County Executive Charlie Dooley.
It’s bad enough that corruption, nepotism, and Machiavellian favoritism runs rampant in St. Louis County. What’s worse is that Dooley doesn’t seem to care what anyone thinks.
 St. Louis County in the third year of a hiring and pay freeze, Mike Temporiti landed a $70,000 county job.
. . .
The job was never posted, and Temporiti did not have to interview for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Ways to Stop Democrat Sen. Bob Casey From Stealing Your Tax Money to Reimburse SEIU for Bribing Media Matters and Huffington Post</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/28/3-ways-to-stop-democrat-sen-bob-casey-from-stealing-your-tax-money-to-reimburse-seiu-for-bribing-media-matters-and-huffington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 01:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/28/3-ways-to-stop-democrat-sen-bob-casey-from-stealing-your-tax-money-to-reimburse-seiu-for-bribing-media-matters-and-huffington-post/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch and 24th State have revealed the ring of corruption that extends from St. Louis bloggers and local St. Louis leftist rag, through SEIU, to Media Matters and Huffington Post.
An additional crook in this den of thieves is Democrat Senator Bob Casey of Pennsylvania. Casey has introduced yet another bailout package. This time, the bailout is intended to repay corrupt unions like SEIU and AFL-CIO for bankrupting their members’ retirements by bribing the media and politicians.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>