<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 22:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Ideas to Save Christmas in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Nixon buck-passed while Ferguson burned. With the city’s main business district laid to rubble, buycotts won’t have much effect. And Christmas is around the corner.
Who got hurt last night?
*1. People who own businesses *2. People who work at businesses *3. People who rely on businesses
Time is short. The people affected by last night’s riots need help rebuilding and jobs right now. While I don’t have complete plans, I can throw out eight ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/24/merry-christmas-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 05:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/24/merry-christmas-3/</guid>
      <description>I read today that the Christmas shopping season was off. The writer, or his sources, blamed Sandy: Hurricane Sandy and Sandy Hook. Retailers said that shoppers weren’t very jolly. They were serious or worried or distracted. Hurried, as if they didn’t want to be out too long.

I thought of my parents and others at the Christmas of 1941. Americans had endured a decade of economic depression that the planners were impotent to correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Could Be Worse?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/14/what-could-be-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 01:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/14/what-could-be-worse/</guid>
      <description>What could be worse than having no Christmas gift for a child to open?
A Christmas gift with no child to open it.

_Eternal rest grant unto them O Lord, and let perpetual light shine upon them. May their little souls, and all the souls of the faithful departed, through the mercy of God, rest in peace. _</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas on Sunday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/21/christmas-on-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 04:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/21/christmas-on-sunday/</guid>
      <description>When I was a kid, I loved Christmas on Sundays. What I hated were the years before and after the Sunday Christmas.

My problem was I didn’t want to go to Mass two days in a row.
To give some background, I grew up in a Catholic home. Very Catholic. My dad went to Epiphany. My mom’s Catholic, and her dad converted very late in life. Two of my dad’s cousins were Monsignors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas-2/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is the holiday about humility.
The humility of the immortal and all powerful and all knowing stooping to become a mere human being.
The humility of God and king to live among the humblest and poorest&amp;ndash;a carpenter&amp;rsquo;s son.
The humility of belonging to a race so broken that our Creator sent his only Son to redeem us.
For me, the humblest part of this season is what I&amp;rsquo;m doing right now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>