<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jimmy Carter on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jimmy-carter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jimmy Carter on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 22:23:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jimmy-carter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>More 1980 Election Parallels: Passing Out and Falling Down</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/12/more-1980-election-parallels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 22:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/12/more-1980-election-parallels/</guid>
      <description>The more you think about it, the more you realize 2016 gets more and more like 1980 every day.
As you ponder Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s fall from grace (even David Axelrod is trashing her now), you might remember Jimmy Carter&amp;rsquo;s collapse.
I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about his collapse on election night. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about one of the two incidents that psychologically destroyed Carter&amp;rsquo;s image as a leader. In a moment, I&amp;rsquo;ll remind you of the collapse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s My Electoral Map Prediction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I’m feeling a wave toward Romney.

My gut tells me this year is a lot like 1980.
1980 Was A Dead Heat
The final Gallup poll that year had a dead heat. Time Magazine’s November 3, 1980, called the race a dead heat. So did Newsweek.
The press was hoping John B. Anderson, a former Republican Congressman running for president as an independent, would siphon votes from Reagan. He did siphon votes from Reagan, but not nearly enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Warning Signs That Obama’s Imploding</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/02/7-warning-signs-that-obamas-imploding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 21:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/02/7-warning-signs-that-obamas-imploding/</guid>
      <description>Hurricane Isaac smiled on the Republicans in Tampa and delivered more misery to New Orleans and its surroundings. That was just one of the ominous signs that 2012 is shaping up to be a forgettable year for Democrats, especially for Barack Obama.

Here’s seven more warning signs that Obama’s 6-year campaign is about to implode:
1. Torrential Rains Wipe the Face of Mount Obamamore
Not that weather plays favorites, but you have wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wait, what year is this?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/06/wait-what-year-is-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 03:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/06/wait-what-year-is-this/</guid>
      <description>Dig this opening paragraph –&amp;gt;
 As the marathon for the presidency, 1980, begins to quicken, the American electorate is in a singularly sour and pessimistic mood. Not only is the public naturally worried about the economy, energy and inflation, but it doubts things will improve much. The country is anxious to find strong leaders —the evidence is overwhelming—and the public has little faith that Jimmy Carter has the ability, let alone the programs, to solve the nation&amp;rsquo;s problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waning US Influence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/05/waning-us-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/05/waning-us-influence/</guid>
      <description>Pro-Western governments in these countries have fallen to anti-American forces or diminished their support for the US since Barack Obama became president.
* Lebanon** Jordan** Yemen** Qatar** Egypt** Turkey  Obama’s campaign promise to restore respect for America around the world is a joke. A cruel and dangerous joke. Our enemies see Obama’s weakness as American weakness. As they did during Jimmy Carter’s failed presidency, those enemies are advancing.
The next president will have more than a financial catastrophe to fix.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>