<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>big government on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/big-government/</link>
    <description>Recent content in big government on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 01:13:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/big-government/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Me Apologize</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/21/let-me-apologize/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 01:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/21/let-me-apologize/</guid>
      <description>In my response to Dan Riehl’s hit piece on Ed Martin, I wrote one more line than I should have. I wrote about an establishment takeover of Big Government.
Mike Flynn, the editor of Big Government, has quietly (and not so quietly) led the fight for liberty and good government for decades. His Big Government site has been a backbone in the resurgence of our first principles.
Much more importantly to me, Mike Flynn is a friend of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Todd Akin: Putting Al-Qaeda Ahead of the CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/05/rep-todd-akin-putting-al-qaeda-ahead-of-the-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 03:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/05/rep-todd-akin-putting-al-qaeda-ahead-of-the-cia/</guid>
      <description>Hey, one of our favorite members of Congress, and a true gentleman, Todd Akin (R-MO), has made the front page of BigGovernment.com.
The Obama Justice Department is quietly investigating the lawyers associated with the John Adams Project who may have violated a number of laws in place to protect our covert operatives and their families. But so far, with few exceptions, the media and their friends on Capitol Hill haven’t found this case nearly as interesting as Valerie Plame.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>