<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics House on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-house/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics House on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 12:42:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-house/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Candidate With Skin in the Game</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/22/a-candidate-with-skin-in-the-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 12:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/22/a-candidate-with-skin-in-the-game/</guid>
      <description>*Ninety-eight percent of Americans - plumbers, dentists, bus drivers - have skin in the game. We have to worry about the 2 percent - the intellectuals and politicians making the big decisions who don’t have skin in the game and are messing the whole thing up for everybody else. Thirty years ago, the French National Assembly was composed of shop owners, farmers, doctors, veterinarians, and small-town lawyers—people involved in daily activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri&#39;s Legislature Can Increase Highway Funds</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/07/missouris-legislature-can-increase-highway-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 21:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/07/missouris-legislature-can-increase-highway-funds/</guid>
      <description>Now that Amendment 7 has gone down in flames, let&amp;rsquo;s look at highway funding in Missouri.
Amendment 7 would have authorized a 3/4 cent sales tax increase in Missouri. The money was intended for transportation in the broadest sense of the word. Parks with dirt paths qualify, since people can walk on the paths. Even if the bill tightened down the definition of transportation, municipalities and counties would have merely shifted funds to other projects and replaced that money with Amendment 7 taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri Republicans Made Jay Nixon Look Like a Statesman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 01:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</guid>
      <description>You know how reckless and tone-deaf Obama is about Army deserters? Missouri&amp;rsquo;s House and Senate Republican leaders are just as clueless and irresponsible about money.
Yes, I said it: the Missouri Republican legislature is about as conservative and principled as Susan Rice on a Sunday talk show.
By going on a votes-for-cash spending spree on the last day of the General Assembly, the House and Senate handed Jay &amp;ldquo;Idiot&amp;rdquo; Nixon a PR prize worth its weight in pork.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>