<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Federalism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/federalism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Federalism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 20:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/federalism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Common Purpose</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/28/the-joy-of-common-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 20:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/28/the-joy-of-common-purpose/</guid>
      <description>I planned to get new brakes on my car and to rearrange the storage room in the basement with my week off between Christmas and New Year&amp;rsquo;s. Solitary tasks.
Yesterday, though, like many of you, I read about theBlog Burst for Fred Thompson. I linked to Captain&amp;rsquo;s Quarter&amp;rsquo;s (where I first read the story), then to Rick Moran and John Hawkins, who seem to have launched the effort. For the rest of the day, I found myself e-mailing friends and posting updates about the effort to raise enough money for Fred to run a commercial in Iowa lead up to the caucuses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federalism Primer</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/28/federalism-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2007 02:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/28/federalism-primer/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you live on a busy street, and you have small children. You want to get a stop sign put up on one of the cross streets near your house to slow people down. You just need to know whom to talk to.
In a country like the United States where federalism has been replaced by Big Government, you probably need to get hold of your U. S. Congressman. If he&amp;rsquo;s so inclined, he&amp;rsquo;ll attach an amendment that authorizes the placement of the stop sign to some bill.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>