<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brian nieves on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/brian-nieves/</link>
    <description>Recent content in brian nieves on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 23:04:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/brian-nieves/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Help a Brave Missouri Senator and Win an AR-15</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/17/how-you-can-help-a-brave-missouri-senator-and-win-an-ar-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 23:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/17/how-you-can-help-a-brave-missouri-senator-and-win-an-ar-15/</guid>
      <description>For years, conservatives have relied on a handful of brave State Senators to block really bad bills. One of that small group is Senator Brian Nieves.
Here’s how you can help ensure Missouri has some spine in the State Senate for another 4 years. Print 10 copies of this page and hand it to friends. Ask them to join you at Senator Nieves’s Sporting Clays event
**State Senator Brian Nieves ** General Laws Committee Chairman and Senate Majority Whip, Invites you to a Special Event Honoring the TRUE Intent of Our 2nd Amendment where YOU may win a Premium AR15!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for Defiance, Resistance, and Resolve in Missouri</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/06/time-for-defiance-resistance-and-resolve-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/06/time-for-defiance-resistance-and-resolve-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>At the Pachyderm Club’s national convention last year, I overheard a Republican Missouri State Representative talking about HB 609. “It was the best bill I’ve ever been involved with,” she said. “Those people who just went nuts don’t know anything about insurance.”

If you read my blog, you’re likely one of the “those people,” the ignorant masses who don’t understand the fineries of the legislative process. You don’t appreciate how hard the insurance industry lobbyists worked with Jefferson City to craft a law that sold only a bit of you into slavery while ensuring the insurance companies remained profitable and your favorite Republican legislators had the money to campaign next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Tilley vs. Fiscal Responsibility</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/14/steve-tilley-vs-fiscal-responsibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/14/steve-tilley-vs-fiscal-responsibility/</guid>
      <description>Four men risked their political lives to help solve the problem of our lifetimes, but they forgot to massage Steve Tilley’s monstrous ego.
When John McCain (R-AZ) and Roy Blunt (R-MO) agree with Michele Bachmann and Rush Limbaugh, you can bet the issue is beyond debate.
In this case, the issue is the massive U.S. debt and what that debt is about to do to America.
McCain compared the U.S. situation to Greece and Spain, saying we should prepare for a “fiscal meltdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Happy Hour</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/03/friday-happy-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 01:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/03/friday-happy-hour/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch on facebook gave kudos to Missouri State Senators Nieves and Lembke for fighting a federal bribe to the states.
 Major props to Brian Nieves and Jim Lembke for their continued commitment to conservatism in the MO Senate with HB 163 - refusing federal funds for another unemployment extension that costs taxpayers $81 million. They&amp;rsquo;re standing their ground against some of their fellow GOP who need to be reminded what fiscal conservatism is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A View From the Back</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/16/a-view-from-the-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 02:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/16/a-view-from-the-back/</guid>
      <description>I approached the Rennick Park Pavilion with a heavy heart for three reasons. At least three.
First, it was yet another night that I would not be home. And tomorrow’s first day of school. The last first day of school for my son, Patrick. I can’t think of that without thinking about his first day of kindergarten—which seems like yesterday—when he insisted on riding the bus. With his little backpack overflowing with supplies listed on a green sheet of paper (Rockwood-Green Pines-K), he stepped onto that bus in August of 1998.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>