<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Efficiency on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/efficiency/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Efficiency on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 07:36:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/efficiency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>There Are No Experts: Food, Riots, and Coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/there-are-no-experts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 07:36:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/there-are-no-experts/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s post was supposed to be about the public health crisis caused by the Coronavirus quarantine, but something more urgent came up.
The Dunning-Kruger effect is a fascinating cognitive bias that causes enormous human suffering. We see it in the prolonged over-reaction to Coronavirus and the riots following the murder of George Floyd in Minneapolis.
The experts include politicians, police, and community activists (peaceful). Non-experts include anarchists and rioters, on the one side, and anti-riot militias, on the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Efficiency Caused Food and Toilet Paper Shortages</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/how-efficiency-caused-food-shortages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 09:08:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/how-efficiency-caused-food-shortages/</guid>
      <description>If you work for a corporation, you&amp;rsquo;ve undoubtedly heard about the virtues of efficiency. And, if you&amp;rsquo;re living in America, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably noticed shortages of stables like meat, packaged food, cleaning supplies, toilet paper, and more.
What you probably don&amp;rsquo;t realize is that business&amp;rsquo;s pathological concerns for efficiency caused the shortages. And, what&amp;rsquo;s worse, most of the &amp;ldquo;expert&amp;rdquo; recommendations for dealing with pandemics will put us all at risk for precisely the same reason.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>