<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ronald-reagan on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/ronald-reagan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ronald-reagan on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 22:49:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/ronald-reagan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Is Conservative?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/08/who-is-conservative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 22:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/08/who-is-conservative/</guid>
      <description>People think they&amp;rsquo;re rational, but we&amp;rsquo;re not. For example, on many issues,** Trump&amp;rsquo;s positions are almost identical to Ronald Reagan&amp;rsquo;s.** When it comes to abortion, trade, taxes, foreign policy and the military, and entitlements like Social Security, you can&amp;rsquo;t fit a dime between Reagan and Trump.
So why do people see Trump as far to the left of Reagan?
Contrasts and comparisons.
Reagan ran against George Bush and John B. Anderson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belated Gipper Birthday Post</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/09/belated-gipper-birthday-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 20:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/09/belated-gipper-birthday-post/</guid>
      <description>I re-read Ronald Reagan&amp;rsquo;s announcement speech the other day.
Delivered November 13, 1979, these are the words that launched the greatest presidency of my lifetime.
Notice the natural humanity in Reagan&amp;rsquo;s words. He didn&amp;rsquo;t browbeat people with abstract concepts like the Constitution or liberty. Instead, he spoke about the real lives of ordinary Americans. And the everyday life of an America that lived up to its ideal. And notice the complete lack of pomposity, vanity, and vulgarity so prevalent in the frontrunners of 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to Choose</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/its-time-to-choose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 05:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/its-time-to-choose/</guid>
      <description>I am a mess.
I am a terrible father, a crappy husband (ask my ex-wives), and a difficult employee. I do a lot of things poorly. Most things, in fact. Especially the things I &amp;ldquo;have&amp;rdquo; to do. Authority irritates me.
While I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at following plans, I write a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of blogs on Saturday and Sunday mornings. The pattern keeps me sane. Or semi-sane. I supplement those when events warrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We All Need a Drink</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/15/we-all-need-a-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 14:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/15/we-all-need-a-drink/</guid>
      <description>Ever come across a text you know, but forgot?
I did recently. This gem of a paragraph leapt off the page and into my mind:
 I believe this nation hungers for a spiritual revival; hungers to once again see honor placed above political expediency; to see government once again the protector of our liberties, not the distributor of gifts and privilege. Government should uphold and not undermine those institutions which are custodians of the very values upon which civilization is founded &amp;ndash; Faith, education and, above all, family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Ann Wagner Is Wrong to Attack Heritage Action</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 02:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</guid>
      <description>Accountability? We don&amp;rsquo;t need no stinking accountability.
 No, Ann Wagner didn&amp;rsquo;t actually say that. But her comments to a 2nd District Republican committee meeting on Tuesday gave at least one attendee the impression that Mrs. Wagner opposes the idea of conservatives holding Congress accountable.
Ann Wagner Attacks the Conservative Heritage Action Rep. Ann Wagner accused the conservative Heritage Action for America of &amp;ldquo;pitting Republican against Republican&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;never attacking Dems&amp;rdquo; at the Republican meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>