<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>God on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/god/</link>
    <description>Recent content in God on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 14:41:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/god/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Fast: Day 14</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/06/primary-fast-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 14:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/06/primary-fast-day-14/</guid>
      <description>You made it. If you began the Fast with me, today is the last day of skipping breakfast and lunch. (Unless you decide to makeone-meal-a-day a permanent habit.)
What Fasting Can Do Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened to you during the fast (if you followed the prescription):
 You probably lost about five pounds. Your pants feel looser. You pull your belt a notch tighter. You saved money. (I saved $98.)  You learned that food is an option most of the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Told You So! Democrats BOO God, Israel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/05/i-told-you-so-democrats-boo-god-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 02:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/05/i-told-you-so-democrats-boo-god-israel/</guid>
      <description>As if reading from a script written by the Romney campaign, the Democrats on Wednesday managed to mangle their public image even further, this time by booing God and Israel.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12536&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;288&amp;rdquo;]   Clipped from https://thespeechatimeforchoosing.wordpress.com[/caption]
On Tuesday, the Democratic National Convention stripped God&amp;rsquo;s name from their platform and rejected Israel&amp;rsquo;s choice of Jerusalem as its capital.
Wednesday, the party panicked and rushed in an amendment to restore God and Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Trust the Democcrats&#39; Platform?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/04/can-you-trust-the-democcrats-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 04:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/04/can-you-trust-the-democcrats-platform/</guid>
      <description>For years voters have complained that politicians and parties say anything to get a vote. People have longed for the days of plain talk and honesty.
  Well, the Democrats passed a new platform today. Two headlines emerged:
  The Democrats rejected any reference to God.
  The Democrats rejected Jerusalem as Israel&amp;rsquo;s capital.
  The question is: can you trust them? Do Democrats really reject God and reject Jerusalem as the center of Israeli political life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abraham, Isaac, and Todd</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/24/abraham-isaac-and-todd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/24/abraham-isaac-and-todd/</guid>
      <description>The story Isaac is about tests of faith.
God commanded Abraham to sacrifice Isaac, his only son, born after Abraham and Sarah had given up hope of conceiving.
Once Isaac was bound and placed on the altar, God stayed Abraham&amp;rsquo;s hand. &amp;ldquo;Now I know you fear God.&amp;rdquo;
You know the rest.
It just struck me this morning, listening to the weather during Jamie Allman&amp;rsquo;s show, that Isaac now threatens the GOP convention, dangling above Tampa like Abraham&amp;rsquo;s dagger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just How Bad Would a Second Obama Term Be?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/16/just-how-bad-would-a-second-obama-term-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/16/just-how-bad-would-a-second-obama-term-be/</guid>
      <description>If you believe that 92 percent of people need to have most aspect of their lives managed by experts, then a second Obama term will make you happy.

If, however, you believe in self-governance, that people are endowed by God and nature with the capacity and unalienable right to manage their own affairs, then a second Obama term will be a massive human rights violation.
Consider what the Obama administration has already brought us:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>