<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Koster on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/chris-koster/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chris Koster on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 06:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/chris-koster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Worst of Humanity and the Absence of Leadership in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/worst-humanity-abence-leadership-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 06:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/worst-humanity-abence-leadership-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>I should be in bed. But I can&amp;rsquo;t take my eyes off the images of Ferguson burning to the ground.
A liberal friend on Twitter admonished me not to be political. Maybe he&amp;rsquo;s right.
But I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Dellena&amp;rsquo;s 911 Beauty Salon burned in Ferguson tonight. It seems everything else has, too. The airport is closed. St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s image may be taking a fatal blow. The region might go the way of Gary, Indiana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Rights In Missouri Are Unprotected. Vote For Ed Martin For Your Own Security</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/31/your-rights-in-missouri-are-unprotected-vote-for-ed-martin-for-your-own-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 23:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/31/your-rights-in-missouri-are-unprotected-vote-for-ed-martin-for-your-own-security/</guid>
      <description>Please forward this post to everyone in your email address book. Use the buttons below to share on Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, StumbleUpon, Reddit. Tell your family that their vote for Ed Martin for Attorney General is your best defense against a Washington power machine run amok.
https://youtu.be/kRy2XWvGe38
Ed Martin&amp;rsquo;s opponent doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to realize that the job of Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Attorney General is to represent our state. The AG isn&amp;rsquo;t just some high-ranking prosecutor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Police Department Is Crumbling, But You Can Vote to Save It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</guid>
      <description>You get the feeling that Rex Sinquefield holds a grudge against his home state, and he’s using some of his fortune to punish us.
Rex gave a quarter million dollars to Obama’s Lawyer, Chris Koster. But that wasn’t his first assault on us. Rex’s war against the St. Louis Police Department is older and far more bitter.
Rex wants to force the state to surrender the Board of Police Commissioners for St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Ed Martin Running for Attorney General in Missouri *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin Jr. of St. Louis has redirected his fire to the Attorney General race, and this is great news for everyone except Chris Koster.
Back when Ed Martin was talking about running for the Republican nod to take on Claire McCaskill, I had another thought. Well, a bunch of people had another thought: Ed would make an outstanding Attorney General.
UPDATE
HUGE list of endorsements on Ed’s official press release.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>