<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tea Party News on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/tea-party-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tea Party News on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 13:46:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/tea-party-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>KTVI&#39;s Hard News Guy . . . Sgt. Bilko</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/15/ktvis-hard-news-guy-sgt-bilko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/15/ktvis-hard-news-guy-sgt-bilko/</guid>
      <description>Just watch. And laugh. Then call KTVI&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, Spencer Koch at 314-213-2222, and demand an apology for Sgt. Bilko&amp;rsquo;s latest travesty reported on Gateway Pundit.
[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5z0VxWZszyg&amp;amp;w;=425&amp;amp;h;=344]
Too good to be true? Ask Charles: cjaco@charlesjaco.com.
On April 13, Charles Jaco reported on KTVI News that an organization called The Constitution Party sponsored and helped organize the St. Louis Tea Party. Jaco also claimed that The Constitution Party is a white supremacist group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox 2 News St. Louis Lies About Tea Parties **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/14/fox-2-news-st-louis-lies-about-tea-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 05:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/14/fox-2-news-st-louis-lies-about-tea-parties/</guid>
      <description>Charles Jaco of Fox 2 News in St. Louis filed a fabricated story claiming that a) the St. Louis Tea Party is organized by something called The Constitution Party, and b) the Constitution Party is an extremist, white supremacist group.
I will say only this:
   Neither Dana Loesch nor I is a member of the Constitution Party. I did not know of such an organization before April 14, 2009</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 15 is 15 Days Away</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/31/april-15-is-15-days-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 12:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/31/april-15-is-15-days-away/</guid>
      <description>Obama and his minions want to tell you how much you can make, how much water your toilet can flush, where you can work, what career you may pursue, where your kids can go to school, what your college-age kids can major in, the kind of toilet paper you can use, how many sheets of copy paper you may use in a month, and what you can name your children. Don&amp;rsquo;t bother arguing with me&amp;ndash;all of these controls are in place in European &amp;ldquo;democracies&amp;rdquo; or Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Anthem:  MUST LISTEN!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/22/tea-party-anthem-must-listen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 17:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/22/tea-party-anthem-must-listen/</guid>
      <description>[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z2H8xHFXC8U&amp;amp;w;=425&amp;amp;h;=344]
Accompanying message from Lloyd Marcus:
 Hello, it&amp;rsquo;s Lloyd Marcus, one of the spokespersons for the Our Country Deserves Better Committee. I&amp;rsquo;m active with this organization because I believe that Conservatism is compassionate and is the true path to achieving the AmericanDream. Liberalism weakens the human spirit by encouraging people to view themselves as victims.
 Besides political activism, my other great passion in life is as a singer, because that&amp;rsquo;s one of the things God gave me the greatest passion to pursue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Approval Down to &#43;4; More Call Him “Extremely Liberal”</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/20/obama-approval-down-to-4-more-call-him-extremely-liberal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 21:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/20/obama-approval-down-to-4-more-call-him-extremely-liberal/</guid>
      <description>The latest Rasmussen poll has bad news for Obama, good news for those of us who’ve been warning America how dangerous he is.
Highlights:
The number of people calling Obama “extremely liberal” has jumped 16 percentage points since the inauguration
Those expecting government spending to skyrocket is up to 72 percent from 54 percent on election day
Overall approval has fallen to +4 percent from +30 percent just after the inauguration</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>