<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>block captains on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/block-captains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in block captains on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 00:37:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/block-captains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Night at the Ball Park</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/30/a-night-at-the-ball-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 00:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/30/a-night-at-the-ball-park/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes things just happen.
As Jim Durbin points out, last night’s St. Louis Tea Party Night at the Ball Game was a total fluke. A mix-up left us with 46 tickets to last night’s Cardinal’s game against Arizona. (Long story.) But this tea party thing that started over a year ago seems to generate its own publicity.

But the real story, to me, is what happened last night. Three incidents vindicated the shift toward more community building work, even if that work comes at the expense of big, boisterous rallies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Overconfidence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/21/how-to-avoid-overconfidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 00:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/21/how-to-avoid-overconfidence/</guid>
      <description>Do you worry that conservative grassroots might get overconfident and blow our chance to stop the advance of socialism in America?
I do. I am concerned that we keep repeating the same tactics to the same audiences until both the audience and the actors become . . . well, bored.
When I read stories like this one, that GOP sentiment is at an all-time high, I worry that some on our side might decide they can go back to their regularly scheduled programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Must Evangelize Liberty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/why-we-must-evangelize-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 20:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/why-we-must-evangelize-liberty/</guid>
      <description>Earlier I linked to Glenn Reynolds’s Examiner column about the hard work that lies ahead for Tea Partyers. If you haven’t read that piece, do so after reading this.
At Tea Party marches and rallies, we are surrounded by others who understand and cherish liberty. We know the horrors that occur when a government loses accountability to and, yes, fear of the people they govern. Such regimes become murderous, intolerant, and repressive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>