<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>crime on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in crime on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 17:59:11 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>St Louis: More People Shot Than Diagnosed with Coronavirus Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-more-shot-than-diagnosed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 17:59:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-more-shot-than-diagnosed/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, May 9, in St. Louis, more people were shot than diagnosed with Coronavirus. Two died from gunshot wounds. The other eight are alive in unknown or unreported condition.
Via the Washington Times:
 Authorities say at least 10 people were shot, two of them fatally, in a single day in St. Louis.
  The St. Louis Post-Dispatch reports that the the gunfire began around 1:15 p.m. Saturday when a 28-year-old man was fatally shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferguson is the Canary in the Coal Mine&#34; for St. Louis County</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/18/ferguson-canary-coal-mine-st-louis-county/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 21:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/18/ferguson-canary-coal-mine-st-louis-county/</guid>
      <description>The next St. Louis County Executive better brace himself for this: poverty is exploding in the county.
I&amp;rsquo;m not saying poor people do bad things. I&amp;rsquo;m saying that, at some point, eliminating jobs and hope will drive people to take things. And they will take things by force. And they will show no mercy to anyone who tries to get in their way.
Right or wrong, it happens. And no militarized police force will stop it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Create Hate and Discontent in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/17/create-hate-discontent-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 18:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/17/create-hate-discontent-america/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t written about Ferguson because I&amp;rsquo;ve known too little to add value. But ignorance hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped others from stirring up hate and discontent. For example, Missouri&amp;rsquo;s shakedown artist, Lacy Clay.
Lacy Clay, speaking from a private island in the Carribean, told the St. Louis Post-Dispatch that Michael Brown was murdered. Clay knew or should have known the effect of his words: more violence. Either Clay meant to incite violence or he has a casual disregard for the effect of his irresponsible speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Leader Says  Let’s “Take Out” Union Members</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/tea-party-leader-says-lets-take-out-union-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 18:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/tea-party-leader-says-lets-take-out-union-members/</guid>
      <description>We got to keep an eye on the battle that we face: The war on Tea Partiers. And you see it everywhere, it is the Unions. And you know, there is only one way to beat and win that war. The one thing about Tea Party people is we like a good fight. And you know what? They&amp;rsquo;ve got a war, they got a war with us and there&amp;rsquo;s only going to be one winner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>