<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Covenant of Liberty on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/covenant-of-liberty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Covenant of Liberty on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:05:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/covenant-of-liberty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Votes on Obamacare Today</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</guid>
      <description>We won’t know the result until late June, most likely. And the results of today’s vote could change by then.

Still, it’s sort of weird that after three years of public, wildly emotional and stupifyingly complex arguments, the fate of the republic comes down to a short meeting in Washington involving nine people in a paneled room.
Mark Sherman of AP describes the cloistered scene:
 After months of anticipation, thousands of pages of briefs and more than six hours of arguments, the justices will vote on the fate of President Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s health care overhaul in under an hour Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Herbert Hoover Launched Cardinal Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals were the major league team farthest west and farthest south until the 1950s. But that’s not the only reason the Redbirds built a massive flock of fans from the Alleghenies to the Rockies, and from Canada to the Gulf of Mexico.
The St. Louis Cardinals owe big government statism and technological innovation a big thanks, in addition to geography and great teams. The technology was radio. The big government statist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covenant of Liberty Is Available Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/20/covenant-of-liberty-is-available-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 14:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/20/covenant-of-liberty-is-available-now/</guid>
      <description>Covenant of Liberty is the best American history I’ve read in years.
Michael Patrick Leahy, among a very small group of patriots who hatched the first round of Tea Parties in February 2009, documents the US Government’s 230 year history of Constitutional infidelity.
My full review will be finished soon, but don’t wait: buy Covenant of Liberty today.
https://rcm.amazon.com/e/cm?lt1=_blank&amp;amp;bc1=000000&amp;amp;IS2=1&amp;amp;bg1=FFFFFF&amp;amp;fc1=000000&amp;amp;lc1=0000FF&amp;amp;t=hennesssview-20&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;p=8&amp;amp;l=as4&amp;amp;m=amazon&amp;amp;f=ifr&amp;amp;ref=ss_til&amp;amp;asins=0062066331
Mike Leahy was the keynote speaker on day one of the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party in St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>