<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:11:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a New Blog</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2018-11-23-99th-time-the-charm-for-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2018-11-23-99th-time-the-charm-for-bill/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s see if this works, shall we?
I spent all day moving my blog from a self-hosted Wordpress site to a Hugo static site. Since I no longer support advertising, I don&amp;rsquo;t need all the weight of Wordpress. Plus, managing a blog through Github is actually easier for me. I use git professionally. And I pretty much think in Markdown at this point.
The final reason for the move is the change in direction for this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Save Religious Freedom in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/13/how-you-can-save-religious-freedom-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/13/how-you-can-save-religious-freedom-in-america/</guid>
      <description>When Barack Obama declared that Catholics must either violate their consciences or face government persecution, he wasn’t going after just Catholics. Nor was he promoting healthcare.
Barack Obama and his myrmidon Kathleen Sebelius tried to erase the First Amendment. They tried to erase religious freedom. They tried to take away yet another foundational liberty that made America America.
And they will try again  &#34;
Unless you stop them.
But how are you going to stop them alone?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 Days of Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/40-days-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 20:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/40-days-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Forty Days of Life is a peaceful, prayerful response the poverty of abortion.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x-AfLO6Oevo]
The Coalition for Life is a community based Christian pro-life organization made up of over 90 churches and thousands of individuals who are working to end abortion in St. Louis, peacefully and prayerfully. ____
 The 40 Days for Life St. Louis Adopt-A-Day program is for Churches and/or Organizations that feel God is calling them to a day of prayer at our vigil location near Planned Parenthood on Forest Park Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>