<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>United States Congress on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/united-states-congress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in United States Congress on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 20:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/united-states-congress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>These Are the Bill in Congress That Need Your Attention</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/these-are-the-bill-in-congress-that-need-your-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/these-are-the-bill-in-congress-that-need-your-attention/</guid>
      <description>Even though Congress is winding down, there are dangerous bills on the desk. I used Heritage Action’s Popvox program to tell Congressman (and future Senator) Todd Akin I oppose the FARM bill that does less for farmers and more for wasteful government statism.

Here’s the whole slate of bills you should write to Congress about:
Oppose the Big-Spending Farm Bill: Email Your Representative Now Tell Blunt and McCaskill to Kill LOST—A Bill to Surrender US Sovereignty</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just How Bad Would a Second Obama Term Be?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/16/just-how-bad-would-a-second-obama-term-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/16/just-how-bad-would-a-second-obama-term-be/</guid>
      <description>If you believe that 92 percent of people need to have most aspect of their lives managed by experts, then a second Obama term will make you happy.

If, however, you believe in self-governance, that people are endowed by God and nature with the capacity and unalienable right to manage their own affairs, then a second Obama term will be a massive human rights violation.
Consider what the Obama administration has already brought us:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>