<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assessor on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/assessor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assessor on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 18:34:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/assessor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Party, Not a Club</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/08/a-party-not-a-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 18:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/08/a-party-not-a-club/</guid>
      <description>Let’s face it: the Missouri GOP has become a club to advance the careers of a select few favorites. It is not a party to advance conservative principles.
And that needs to change here and now.
And that means some old names need to retire.
Here’s just one example of the ideological impotence of the Missouri Republican Party: The St. Louis County Assessor.
The GOP created the St. Louis County Assessor’s office because of corruption and incompetence in the political patronage version of the office under Democrats Buzz Westfall and Charlie Dooley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Taxes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/24/a-tale-of-two-taxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/24/a-tale-of-two-taxes/</guid>
      <description>On Monday, we learned that US Senator Claire McCaskill failed to pay property taxes on her personal luxury jet for three years. Previously, she had charged taxpayers some of the cost of operating her private plane. Before that, it seems, she registered the plane in property tax-free Delaware.
On Monday, Claire wrote a $287,000 check without batting an eye. Now, St. Louis County says she owes them another $33,000 in interest and penalties, for a total bill of $320,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Top Ways to Clean Up St. Louis County Government</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/20/3-top-ways-to-clean-up-st-louis-county-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 20:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/20/3-top-ways-to-clean-up-st-louis-county-government/</guid>
      <description>Meet Chip Tuesday, March 22 from 5:30 to 7:00. Details below.
You can help clean up St. Louis County government. And you can have a good time doing it. Here’s how.
  Like L. K. “Chip” Wood’s Facebook page. It’ll take only a second, and you’ll feel more connected and productive just by doing it.
  Visit Chip Wood for Assessor and enter your email address in the email sign-up box on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>