<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>über on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/%C3%BCber/</link>
    <description>Recent content in über on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 11:58:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/%C3%BCber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The MTC&#39;s Newest Fight Is For Its Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/22/the-mtcs-newest-fight-is-for-its-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 11:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/22/the-mtcs-newest-fight-is-for-its-life/</guid>
      <description>Uber X St. Louis rolled into existence on Friday.
No, Uber did not win the Metropolitan Taxicab Commission&amp;rsquo;s permission to operate. Instead, the ride-sharing service filed a federal anti-trade suit against the MTC.
In the first weekend, Uber X provided over 5,000 rides, mostly from people leaving bars between 10 p.m. and 3 a.m. In other words, by defying the MTC, Uber X kept 5,000 drunk drivers off the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transportation in the 21st Century Event</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/18/transportation-in-the-21st-century-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 23:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/18/transportation-in-the-21st-century-event/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;rsquo;t get there from here.
 The way people get from here to there&amp;ndash;and how they pay for the privilege&amp;ndash;is about to change. We want you to have a say in the future of transportation.
To help, Heritage Action for America is teaming up with St. Louis Tea Party Coalition to put on a Transportation Empowerment night on Saturday, July 25, 2015 at 6:30 p.m.
Speakers Include:
[gallery ids=&amp;quot;16213,16214,16215&amp;rdquo;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Uber Nada</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/st-louis-uber-nada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/st-louis-uber-nada/</guid>
      <description>About this time, a variety of railroads began trying to build their own networks to the West, but the St. Louis city government refused to grant the permits required for constructing railroad bridges across the river at their location, even though St. Louis was the logical choice and would have been a perfect place for a rail hub. Apparently, the politicians in St. Louis felt their duty was to protect the riverboat industry, at that time their life and blood, from any and all competition.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>