<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nate Silver on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/nate-silver/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nate Silver on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:21:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/nate-silver/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Secrets of Coronavirus Data Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:21:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>Nate Silver let the cat out of the bag.
In case you don&amp;rsquo;t recognize his name, Nate Silver is the data analyst who launched Five Thirty-Eight, orignally in the New York Times. He was famous for not predicting an election a few years ago.
Today, Nate unloaded on the media for just one aspect of their narrative-driven Coronavirus coverage. In short, noted the same thing Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View pointed out a month ago: positive tests is meaningless unless it&amp;rsquo;s indexed to the number of tests administered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Expect Boehner To Play The Black Knight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</guid>
      <description>The GOP didn’t really have a plan in place in case it lost. It certainly didn’t have a plan for getting snotclobbered. And if you try to spin Tuesday’s results as anything less than a good old-fashioned ass-kicking, you’re deluding yourself.

**Republicans Got Creamed ** I know Michelle Malkin found 20 things that went right on election night, but there about 60 million things that went wrong. Let’s take a look:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s How Nate Silver Determines Obama’s Chances of Winning</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/29/heres-how-nate-silver-determines-obamas-chances-of-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/29/heres-how-nate-silver-determines-obamas-chances-of-winning/</guid>
      <description>Nate Silver publishes a daily number that represents Barack Obama’s chances of being re-elected. As I write this on October 27, Silver’s magic number is 74%.
[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sKTUiwhac8Q&amp;amp;w=351&amp;amp;h=216&amp;amp;hd=1]
Nate Silver explains his scientific approach to picking winners in elections.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>