<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Email Server on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/email-server/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Email Server on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 21:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/email-server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seems Like Obama Is Tired of Hillary&#39;s S***</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/31/seems-like-obama-is-tired-of-hillarys-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 21:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/31/seems-like-obama-is-tired-of-hillarys-s/</guid>
      <description>You might have dated someone who was amazingly good looking. Everything&amp;rsquo;s great. For awhile. Then you get to know the person. A little too well. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s on a weekend trip. Or, God forbid, when you move in together. Then you realize looks aren&amp;rsquo;t everything.
The same thing can happen in political &amp;ldquo;marriages.&amp;rdquo; That surface quality that attracted you—donors, influence, contacts, whatever—sometimes isn&amp;rsquo;t worth the price.
Just ask Barack Obama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convict Hillary</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/10/convict-hillary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 15:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/10/convict-hillary/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people are mad at FBI Director James Comey. Comey read a list of crimes committed by Hillary Clinton, then announced he couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend prosecution for those crimes. On its face, it sounds like Comey caved.
Let&amp;rsquo;s play the imagine game. Imagine Comey decided to refer Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s crimes to the Department of Justice for prosecution. What would happen?
First, you&amp;rsquo;d never hear about it. The FBI and the DOJ don&amp;rsquo;t discuss active criminal investigations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Left the Gate Open and Laughed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/05/hillary-left-the-gate-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 23:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/05/hillary-left-the-gate-open/</guid>
      <description>Many people grew up with dogs and backyards. If you are such a person, you probably remember being to told to make sure the gate&amp;rsquo;s shut and locked. Or maybe you were told not to use the gate at all because the dog might get out.
A lot of people who grew up with dogs suffered emotional trauma when something bad happened to their dog. Imagine how you&amp;rsquo;d feel if you were seven or eight and you left the gate open and the dog got out and got hit by a car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Petraeus Paying Price for Hillary&#39;s Crimes?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/19/ponder-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 03:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/19/ponder-this/</guid>
      <description>Beyond Top Secret.
Hillary famously kept an email server in her private bedroom where it was safe from being used as Bill&amp;rsquo;s YouPorn hub. (I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Bill Clinton hasn&amp;rsquo;t visited the inside of his wife&amp;rsquo;s sleeping chamber in the 21st century.)
Being plugged into the internet, though, and lacking even the most rudimentary security, Hillary&amp;rsquo;s server was exposed to the prying eyes of Chinese, North Korean, Russian, and Anonymous spies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>