<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unions on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/unions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unions on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 23:19:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/unions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Fund A Terrorist Network?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/15/do-you-fund-a-terrorist-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/15/do-you-fund-a-terrorist-network/</guid>
      <description>According to the FBI:
 Domestic terrorism is the unlawful use, or threatened use, of force or violence by a group or individual based and operating entirely within the United States or Puerto Rico without foreign direction committed against persons or property to intimidate or coerce a government, the civilian population, or any segment thereof in furtherance of political or social objectives. (source)
 In Michigan, union protesters physically assaulted Steven Crowder of Fox News, then destroyed a tent belonging to Americans for Prosperity (video below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bakers Union Costs 300 St. Louisans Their Jobs  **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/bakers-union-costs-300-st-louisans-their-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 01:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/bakers-union-costs-300-st-louisans-their-jobs/</guid>
      <description>**UPDATE Union Declares Victory AsHostess Goes Out of Business. No more Ho Hos. ****
Unions destroy themselves like pathetic drunks, dragging down everyone around them.

In a fine example of anti-strategic thinking and un-game theory, the Bakers Union put 637 of its members out of work yesterday.
Hostess—makers of Twinkies—is bankrupt. Part of the bankruptcy involved rewriting union contracts to allow the company to stay in business.
Instead of taking one for the team and helping their company crawl out of its fiscal hole, the Bakers went on strike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Leader Says  Let’s “Take Out” Union Members</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/tea-party-leader-says-lets-take-out-union-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 18:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/tea-party-leader-says-lets-take-out-union-members/</guid>
      <description>We got to keep an eye on the battle that we face: The war on Tea Partiers. And you see it everywhere, it is the Unions. And you know, there is only one way to beat and win that war. The one thing about Tea Party people is we like a good fight. And you know what? They&amp;rsquo;ve got a war, they got a war with us and there&amp;rsquo;s only going to be one winner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Times for Unions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/21/bad-times-for-unions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 04:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/21/bad-times-for-unions/</guid>
      <description>Wisconsin The boards at Democratic Underground crackled on June 12.
 It was just announced in Wisconsin that the unprecedented recall elections of Republicans will take place August 9.
 The leftists dreamed. Visions of a union-boss oligarchy danced in their heads. Posters misquoted Marx and Lenin. Others wanted nothing to do with waiting two months for an election: they were ready to take up arms and violently overthrow the Wisconsin government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Updates on University of Missouri Story</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/28/3-updates-on-university-of-missouri-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/28/3-updates-on-university-of-missouri-story/</guid>
      <description>Big news day in the advance of liberty in our battle against collectivists.
First, KMOX is reporting that an UMSL professor has resigned** over the controversy**. For the life of me, I cannot find who the professor is. I thought that everyone involved was either an instructor or a guest lecturer. If you know the answer to the riddle, please use the comment form.
Second, University of Kansas City refuses to accept responsibility for what goes on in its classroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell UMSL to Stop Teaching Industrial Sabotage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/25/tell-umsl-to-stop-teaching-industrial-sabotage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 01:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/25/tell-umsl-to-stop-teaching-industrial-sabotage/</guid>
      <description>[ ](https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/UofMCommie.png)Contact UofM President Steve Owens and demand an immediate end to the communist-led industrial sabotage courses that he’s shoving down your kids’ throats
That’s right, UMSL and UMKC are teaching kids how to destroy business in America. They want your job to go overseas. And the guy leading the class is a proud communist.
No employer in his right might would hire a graduate of the University of Missouri-St. Louis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Empire?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/11/why-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/11/why-empire/</guid>
      <description>“Why would a nation become imperial?,” Steven asked me. “I mean, why would you want to take that on?”
The conversation had been on Japan leading up to World War II. The question was important. Why would a nation conquer dissimilar nations? Why accept that burden and risk?
My answer, which I’ve grown more fond of as time’s passed, was something like this: Imperial people view everything as a fixed pie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forward, Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/09/forward-wisconsin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 04:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/09/forward-wisconsin/</guid>
      <description>Doing the right thing is hard.
Doing the right thing after years of practicing the wrong things is even harder.
  When your senate separated the fiscal responsibility provisions affecting union collective bargaining powers from a bill that previously included tax and spend provisions, you took a big step toward fiscal recovery.
For years, public sector unions have dictated states’ taxing spending policies through brute force. These unions were not elected by the people, but the people were forced to pay—or borrow—what the unions demanded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Would You Give State Workers the Power to Tax?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/03/why-would-you-give-state-workers-the-power-to-tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 01:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/03/why-would-you-give-state-workers-the-power-to-tax/</guid>
      <description>For decades, now, public sector unions have imposed onerous tax increases and service cuts on the net tax payers of many states. Wisconsin being among the worst.
What do I mean by that?
Look at what’s going on in Wisconsin. The people who represent the net tax payers—those who pay more in taxes to the state than they receive in salary—are being vilified, harassed, threatened, and assaulted by the net tax takers—those receive more in state wages than they pay in state taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unions Go Berserk</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/23/unions-go-berserk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/23/unions-go-berserk/</guid>
      <description>Obama’s friends in the public-sector unions stage embarrassing rallies to demand more, More, MORE of other people’s money.
These aren’t unions that represent people who work in mines and factories. No, these are unions representing people who live off your and my tax dollars. (BTW,the military doesn’t have a union.)
So let’s see . . . The government does a bunch of stuff we don’t want them to do. The people who did it get paid twice as much as the people who pay them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Has the Fear?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</guid>
      <description>For 100 years in America, government, business, and the education establishment built schools and laws about education. The purpose of these government schools and education laws was to produce compliant, unimaginative, order-taking automatons.
Don’t believe me? Here’s Woodrow Wilson, educator and president, speaking on the American plan for education:
 We want one class of persons to have a liberal education, and we want another class of persons, a very much larger class of necessity in every society, to forgo the privilege of a liberal education and fit themselves to perform specific difficult manual tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>