<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>st.-louis on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/st.-louis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in st.-louis on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 01:06:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/st.-louis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Reardon for Mayor: Make St. Louis Fun Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/mark-reardon-for-mayor-make-st-louis-fun-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 01:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/mark-reardon-for-mayor-make-st-louis-fun-again/</guid>
      <description>Nobody likes traffic, but St. Louis was built to hold a million people. And it once did, back in the days when Democrats and Republicans took turns being mayor.
[Free Offer for Business Owners at Bottom] (read the small print)
Now, in this foul year of our Lord twenty-sixteen, just over 300,000 people call the city home. A 70 percent decline!
And I&amp;rsquo;m not one of them. For several reasons that no reasonable person could argue with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Uber Nada</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/st-louis-uber-nada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/st-louis-uber-nada/</guid>
      <description>About this time, a variety of railroads began trying to build their own networks to the West, but the St. Louis city government refused to grant the permits required for constructing railroad bridges across the river at their location, even though St. Louis was the logical choice and would have been a perfect place for a rail hub. Apparently, the politicians in St. Louis felt their duty was to protect the riverboat industry, at that time their life and blood, from any and all competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Walk on the Hedonic Treadmill</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/17/take-a-walk-on-the-hedonic-treadmill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 21:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/17/take-a-walk-on-the-hedonic-treadmill/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s what happens when you raise the minimum wage to $15 an hour, according to scientists:
Nothing.
Well, not nothing. All kinds of bad things happen to the economy. But nothing happens for two groups of people central to the whole debate: workers who get a bump to $15 and employers who have to bump to $15 an hour.
Most cities and states that have raised their minimum wage laws to $15 will phase in the increase over five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Crony Capitalism Spreads Bureaucracy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</guid>
      <description>St. Louisan Eric Greitens did more before graduating from college than most people do in a lifetime. And, as if to insult us all, after college, Eric became a Navy SEAL.
In his remarkable book, The Heart and the Fist: The education of a humanitarian, the making of a Navy SEAL  , Greitens tells the story of a man who seems too good to be true. Seriously. And the book left me with two big impressions&amp;ndash;probably the wrong ones, but that&amp;rsquo;s how I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week: March 17, 2014</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/week-march-17-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 09:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/week-march-17-2014/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a roundup of what to look for in the coming week.
St. Louis Monday, 12:30 p.m.: The Ancient Order of Hibernians&amp;rsquo; Annual St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day Parade in Dogtown. Get there early. Give yourself time to park and walk. Dress warmly.
Wednesday, 5:00 p.m.: Protest of St. Louis Archdiocese for its promotion of City-County Merger. Location is Lindell and Grand.
Wednesday, 7:00 p.m.: The activist who helped expose scandal, waste, and corruption at Rockwood School District is running for the Rockwood School Board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners Proves Government Can’t Get Anything Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/04/st-louis-board-of-police-commissioners-proves-government-cant-get-anything-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/04/st-louis-board-of-police-commissioners-proves-government-cant-get-anything-right/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives love cracking on government and its unintended consequences. How often does a government initiative give us backassward results?
Exhibit A: Obama hands Solyndra millions in tax dollars to promote green energy. Solyndra (and numerous other green energy grant recipients) goes bankrupt.
Another example is the St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners.
In 1861, Missouri’s legislature created a board of commissioners to oversee the St. Louis Police Department. Why? Because Missouri was a slave state, but St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Police Department Is Crumbling, But You Can Vote to Save It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</guid>
      <description>You get the feeling that Rex Sinquefield holds a grudge against his home state, and he’s using some of his fortune to punish us.
Rex gave a quarter million dollars to Obama’s Lawyer, Chris Koster. But that wasn’t his first assault on us. Rex’s war against the St. Louis Police Department is older and far more bitter.
Rex wants to force the state to surrender the Board of Police Commissioners for St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOTUday Night Fever on KSDK 5</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/24/sotuday-night-fever-on-ksdk-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 01:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/24/sotuday-night-fever-on-ksdk-5/</guid>
      <description>I’ll participate on KSDK Channel 5’s post-SOTU discussion panel Tuesday following the State of the Union speech. (I being Bill Hennessy, in case you’re reading this from a news feed.)
I don’t know who my fellow panelists will be, but I think it’s pretty cool that a local network invited a tea partier to help break down the President’s State of the Union speech.
The speech starts at 8:00 p.m. CT Tuesday, January 25 on KSDK 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Come to St. Louis If You Can’t Drive to the Beach</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/05/why-you-should-come-to-st-louis-if-you-cant-drive-to-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 16:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/05/why-you-should-come-to-st-louis-if-you-cant-drive-to-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Yes, there are three major Tea Party events on 9-12: Washington, Sacramento, and St. Louis. But if you can’t see the Atlantic or the Pacific from your window, why don’t you make the trip to the middle of the country, to the “Gateway to November” Tea Party under the Arch?

I’m hearing from groups in Florida, Georgia, Indiana, Ohio, West Virginia, Texas, Oklahoma, Nebraska, Iowa, and many from Illinois and Kansas who CANNOT WAIT for the 9-12 &amp;ldquo;Gateway to November&amp;rdquo; Tea Party in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We&#39;ve Made a Difference</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 18:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</guid>
      <description>When you give over most of your private time to a cause, you need some feedback. We got some from former Reagan speechwriter Peggy Noonan on Friday: The Summer of the Angry Mob
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;521&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Dana&amp;rsquo;s Famous &amp;lsquo;Meet the Mob&amp;rsquo; Blog&amp;rdquo;][/caption]
Ms. Noonan reflected on the Townhall Revolt which began in St. Louis one year ago. Writes Noonan:
 When Rep. Russ Carnahan held a town hall meeting at a community college in Missouri on July 20, he tried patiently to explain that ObamaCare not only would be deficit-neutral, it would save money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video of St. Louis Event--Almost as Good as Being There *update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/video-of-st-louis-event-almost-as-good-as-being-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 23:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/video-of-st-louis-event-almost-as-good-as-being-there/</guid>
      <description>My hat&amp;rsquo;s off to Bob Anders and the crew from Creative Video Services for this 3-part series of the St. Louis Nationwide Chicago Tea Party protest held February 27, 2009. If you need videography, you can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with Creative Video.
Part I: https://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=3408578&amp;amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;amp;show_title=1&amp;amp;show_byline=1&amp;amp;show_portrait=0&amp;amp;color=&amp;amp;fullscreen=1 St. Louis Tea Party (Part 1) from CR8VDO on Vimeo.
Click here for Parts 2 and 3.
Dana has lots of great links. UPDATES
   It was a 3-part, not 4-part video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Long, Hot Day in St. Louis</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/16/a-long-hot-day-in-st-louis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2007 02:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/16/a-long-hot-day-in-st-louis/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I heard the news of the murder of a young police officer.
  Officer Norvelle Brown, only 22 years old and a rookie cop, made St. Louis headlines for the second time in his short career&amp;ndash;his short, honorable life. In April, Officer Brown responded to a hostage situation during a barber shop robber, defusing the situation and apprehending the armed robbers. He and another officer received citations for that action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>