<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>st.-louis on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/st.-louis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in st.-louis on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 08:36:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/st.-louis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Prayed at the Statue of St. Louis IX, King of France</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/why-we-prayed-at-statue-of-st-louis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 15:04:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/why-we-prayed-at-statue-of-st-louis/</guid>
      <description>Our purpose in holding this Rosary event at the statue of St. Louis was to satisfy the two greatest commandments: to love God and to love our neighbor as ourselves. To that end, we prayed equally for everyone present at the event:
 For those who attacked us and called us names For those who falsely accused us of being in the KKK For those on both sides of the issues who came to provoke the other side For those police officers who donned riot gear on a hot, humid day to keep us all safe For those who came out to pray  For all of them, we prayed to God that He softens our hearts and fills our souls with gifts of the Holy Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Us Pray at the Statue of St. Louis in Forest Park Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/let-us-pray-at-the-statue-of-st-louis-in-forest-park-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 06:24:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/let-us-pray-at-the-statue-of-st-louis-in-forest-park-saturday/</guid>
      <description>By the grace of God, Jim Hoft, the Gateway Pundit, has called all Catholic Christian men to pray the Rosary at the statue of St. Louis IX, King of France, on Art Hill in Forest Park at Noon on Saturday, June 28, 2020. Please join us. If you cannot join us, please pray for us.
Pray that our intentions align with the will of God, that we do nothing out of vainglory or pride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Louis: More People Shot Than Diagnosed with Coronavirus Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-more-shot-than-diagnosed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 17:59:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-more-shot-than-diagnosed/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, May 9, in St. Louis, more people were shot than diagnosed with Coronavirus. Two died from gunshot wounds. The other eight are alive in unknown or unreported condition.
Via the Washington Times:
 Authorities say at least 10 people were shot, two of them fatally, in a single day in St. Louis.
  The St. Louis Post-Dispatch reports that the the gunfire began around 1:15 p.m. Saturday when a 28-year-old man was fatally shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Reardon for Mayor: Make St. Louis Fun Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/mark-reardon-for-mayor-make-st-louis-fun-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 01:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/mark-reardon-for-mayor-make-st-louis-fun-again/</guid>
      <description>Nobody likes traffic, but St. Louis was built to hold a million people. And it once did, back in the days when Democrats and Republicans took turns being mayor.
[Free Offer for Business Owners at Bottom] (read the small print)
Now, in this foul year of our Lord twenty-sixteen, just over 300,000 people call the city home. A 70 percent decline!
And I&amp;rsquo;m not one of them. For several reasons that no reasonable person could argue with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Uber Nada</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/st-louis-uber-nada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/st-louis-uber-nada/</guid>
      <description>About this time, a variety of railroads began trying to build their own networks to the West, but the St. Louis city government refused to grant the permits required for constructing railroad bridges across the river at their location, even though St. Louis was the logical choice and would have been a perfect place for a rail hub. Apparently, the politicians in St. Louis felt their duty was to protect the riverboat industry, at that time their life and blood, from any and all competition.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>