<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>election on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/election/</link>
    <description>Recent content in election on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 09:45:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rasmussen Poll Shows Dead Head</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/13/rasmussen-poll-shows-dead-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 16:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/13/rasmussen-poll-shows-dead-head/</guid>
      <description>Rasmussen&amp;rsquo;s presidential tracking poll shows a dead heat between Democrat Barack Obama and Republican Presidential Candidate John McCain (h/t Drudge). This poll confirms the Newsweek poll showing the two in a statistical dead heat.
Moreover, according Rasmussen, McCain enjoys higher favorability ratings than Obama.
Considering that McCain has received little media attention since the last Democrat primary in June, Obama&amp;rsquo;s 15 percentage point drop can only be blamed on Obama&amp;rsquo;s dismal performance as a candidate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsweek:  Obama Fading</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/12/newsweek-obama-fading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 00:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/12/newsweek-obama-fading/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s poll lead over John McCain has plummeted from 51-35 to a statistical dead-heat in less than a month.
Obama&amp;rsquo;s downward spiral has Newsweek&amp;rsquo;s headline writers asking if his glow is fading. The polls finds that more than half of voters consider Obama lying opportunist who will take any position for votes.
 Obama&amp;rsquo;s rapid drop comes at a strategically challenging moment for the Democratic candidate. Having vanquished Hillary Clinton in early June, Obama quickly went about repositioning himself for a general-election audience&amp;ndash;an unpleasant task for any nominee emerging from the pander-heavy primary contests and particularly for a candidate who&amp;rsquo;d slogged through a vigorous primary challenge in most every contest from January until June.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Kids and the List of Nos</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/27/five-kids-and-the-list-of-nos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2007 06:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/27/five-kids-and-the-list-of-nos/</guid>
      <description>Five kids is a lot these days. &amp;ldquo;You have five kids? Oh, my God!&amp;rdquo; people say, their eyes bugged out, mouths wide open.
Even when the oldest were babies, developmental psychologists were advising parent not to tell children &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo; Their theory was that &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo; would teach a child limitation and destroy his curiosity. Instead, offer an alternative. Well, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. But the funny thing is, it&amp;rsquo;s the no &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo; advice is totally out of synch with society.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>