<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 02:36:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ll Say It Again:  James Hansen Is a Fraud and a Liar</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/06/ill-say-it-again-james-hansen-is-a-fraud-and-a-liar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 02:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/06/ill-say-it-again-james-hansen-is-a-fraud-and-a-liar/</guid>
      <description>American Thinker Blog: Global Warm-mongering: More Silk from a Pig&amp;rsquo;s Ear
 It seems that NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Hansen, head of the Goddard Institute for Space Studies (GISS), is at it again. He just can&amp;rsquo;t let the data speak for itself. In yet another egregious display of Anthropogenic Global Warming (AGW) arrogance, he changed the temperature data from 1910-2008 to reflect what is clearly a cooling trend to reflect a warming trend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Much For an Ice-Free Arctic</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/05/so-much-for-an-ice-free-arctic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/05/so-much-for-an-ice-free-arctic/</guid>
      <description>DailyTech - Sea Ice Ends Year at Same Level as 1979
 Thanks to a rapid rebound in recent months, global sea ice levels now equal those seen 29 years ago, when the year 1979 also drew to a close.
 Let&amp;rsquo;s give credit where it&amp;rsquo;s due: Al Gore.
When Al Gore speaks, the opposite happens. Where Al Gore goes,snow is sure to follow. So when Al Gorefrightened a bunch of German kids by telling them that the North Pole would be gone in 5 years, that Santa Claus would die along with his reindeer, and that Polar Bears would either become extinct or catch the last few ice floes south to Europe where they&amp;rsquo;d &amp;ldquo;eat little kiddies like you,&amp;rdquo; you just knew that the Arctic would grow ice faster than Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s head grows hair plugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gloriously Goring Gore</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/04/gloriously-goring-gore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 14:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/04/gloriously-goring-gore/</guid>
      <description>The Huffington Post (of all things) brings us a most cogent, concise, and accurate repudiation of Al Gore and the whole &amp;ldquo;climate change&amp;rdquo; Nazi crowd (h/t ICECAP). Harold Ambler deserves the Nobel Prize for truth stating. Some highlights.
Strike One: How Al Gore (and Hansen and the rest) lie to you about climate change:
 First, the expression &amp;ldquo;climate change&amp;rdquo; itself is a redundancy, and contains a lie. Climate has always changed, and always will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bunch of Hooey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/30/a-bunch-of-hooey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 18:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/30/a-bunch-of-hooey/</guid>
      <description>The silliness of companies knows no bounds.
The latest act of corporate stupidity comes from the computer maker Dell.
In its attempt to become the &amp;ldquo;greenest technology company on the planet,&amp;rdquo; Dell made much of achieving some farcically theoretical &amp;ldquo;carbon-neutral&amp;rdquo; status. But, like everything associated with AGW, there&amp;rsquo;s really no so thing. WSJ points out in a wonderful examination today:
 In fact, that&amp;rsquo;s only a small fraction of all the emissions associated with Dell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predictions for 2009</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/predictions-for-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 22:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/predictions-for-2009/</guid>
      <description>After a 2 year hiatus from annual predictions, here&amp;rsquo;s what I see happening in the precarious Year of our Lord Two-thousand nine:
The Dow: The Dow trades within a range of 1,000 points with a daily average closing of 8,500.
GDP and Economy: By July, everyone pretty much calls the situation &amp;ldquo;Great Depression II.&amp;rdquo; Unemployment, which declines in the first quarter, increases to more than 12 percent by fall. Gross Domestic Product by quarter:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>