<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>False Flag on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/false-flag/</link>
    <description>Recent content in False Flag on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 13:20:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/false-flag/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I was wrong! And here&#39;s the lesson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/27/i-was-wrong-and-heres-the-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 13:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/27/i-was-wrong-and-heres-the-lesson/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days back I said the mail &amp;ldquo;bombs&amp;rdquo; looked like a false flag. But I left open the possibility of a crazy Republican. Boy, am I glad I gave myself that out.
I should have paid more attention to Scott Adams in those days. Scott used pure statistical reasoning to conclude that the packages probably came from a crazy Trump supporter: base cases. There are more crazy people than there are brilliant criminal strategists who hate Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the CIA Plotting a Coup? *UPDATE* FBI Disputes CIA Allegation - VIDEOS</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/11/is-the-cia-plotting-a-coup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/11/is-the-cia-plotting-a-coup/</guid>
      <description>Many powerful interests around the world loathe Donald Trump and the people who elected him. There&amp;rsquo;s no disputing that.
One of those powerful interests is the Central Intelligence Agency. One of the CIA&amp;rsquo;s own, Evan McMullin, attempted to disrupt the election. Like Bay of Pigs and Saddam&amp;rsquo;s weapons of mass destruction, that CIA plot failed. Even George Will admits the CIA makes some horrible, deadly mistakes. And sometimes those mistakes come from seeing the results they want to see, not the results presented.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>