<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sarah Steelman on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/sarah-steelman/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sarah Steelman on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 02:07:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/sarah-steelman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Candy Crowley: Tea Party Groups Resemble the 13 Colonies, Not the Balkans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</guid>
      <description>Analogies say more about the speaker than about the subject.
Candy Crowley told KMOX Radio listeners on Friday that Tea Party groups resemble the Balkans without guns.
Wrong. Crappy analogy, Candy. The diverse and autonomous, often quarrelsome,** Tea Party groups remind me of the original 13 colonies.**
The colonies were divided on just about every subject imaginable. The disagreed on slavery, on economics, on agraculture, manufacturing, cities, names &amp;ndash; name it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes a Morris is Just a Morris</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/sometimes-a-morris-is-just-a-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 05:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/sometimes-a-morris-is-just-a-morris/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch invited Dick Morris onto her radio show today. Dana expected to discuss START with Mr. Morris. But Dick has a mind of his own.
Morris decided, about a minute and a half into a five-minute segment, that he wanted to talk about the 2012 US Senate race in Missouri instead. Specifically, he wanted spend the segment campaigning for Sarah Steelman for the the Republican nomination.
Decide for yourself: here’s the link to Dana’s show.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>