<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Republican Establishment on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/republican-establishment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Republican Establishment on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 04:01:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/republican-establishment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin Moves to Censure Henry Barbour Over Racist Mississippi Ads</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/ed-martin-moves-censure-henry-barbour-racist-mississippi-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 04:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/ed-martin-moves-censure-henry-barbour-racist-mississippi-ads/</guid>
      <description>Go Ed!
A few weeks ago, hunkered down at my laptop in my hotel room in Jacksonville, Florida. I was exhausted from seven hours of travel and a time change. But I had to take a moment to recognize Ed Martin&amp;rsquo;s commitment to all the best the Republican Party stands for.
Ed is determined to expose the GOP establishment&amp;rsquo;s willingness to do anything to destroy grassroots insurgents. Thad Cochran&amp;rsquo;s forces in Mississippi threw ethics, morality, and decency to the wind in their quest to stop a Tea Party candidate from unseating the 128-term Cochran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why John Danforth&#39;s Attack On Ed Martin Is So Bad for the GOP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/16/dear-senator-danforth-rockefeller-is-dead-and-so-is-your-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 04:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/16/dear-senator-danforth-rockefeller-is-dead-and-so-is-your-message/</guid>
      <description>Old Jack Danforth is a troubled man.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_13392&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] &amp;ldquo;You once called me a &amp;lsquo;warped, frustrated old man.&amp;rsquo; Well, what are you, but a warped, frustrated young man?&amp;rdquo;
John Danforth Attacked Ed Martin for Supporting Rand Paul[/caption]
Danforth&amp;rsquo;s wiry frame got bent all out of shape because the chairman of Missouri’s GOP stated the uber-obvious in an email to friends: the McCain-Graham angry old man meme ain’t sellin’ no more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Libertarian Kids, Not Drones, Scare McCain and Graham</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/12/why-here-is-the-real-reason-mccain-and-graham-lost-their-minds-over-rand-pauls-filibuster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/12/why-here-is-the-real-reason-mccain-and-graham-lost-their-minds-over-rand-pauls-filibuster/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer Rubin—WaPo’s token conservative—said it perfectly:
 McCain lost his cool with Rand Paul and sounded like the old man down the street screaming to the new kids on the block, “Get off my lawn!”
 The real reason McCain and Lindsey Graham embarrassed themselves on the floor of Senate had nothing to do with what Rand Paul said. Rand Paul&amp;rsquo;s ideas terrify McCain, Graham, and most of the Republican establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin’s Grit Overwhelms Establishment’s Power</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/05/ed-martins-grit-overwhelms-establishments-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 02:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/05/ed-martins-grit-overwhelms-establishments-power/</guid>
      <description>In a blow to the old guard establishment,** the Missouri Republican State Committee elected Ed Martin Jr. as its new party chairman**.

Roy Blunt and all six Republican members of Congress from Missouri lobbied the new state committee over the past few weeks to block Ed and retain the establishment’s choice, David Cole. Jo Mannies of the St. Louis Beacon wrote:
 Cole’s loss appears to be a setback for Missouri’s GOP establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>