<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Debt Ceiling on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/debt-ceiling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Debt Ceiling on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/debt-ceiling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Expect Boehner To Play The Black Knight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</guid>
      <description>The GOP didn’t really have a plan in place in case it lost. It certainly didn’t have a plan for getting snotclobbered. And if you try to spin Tuesday’s results as anything less than a good old-fashioned ass-kicking, you’re deluding yourself.

**Republicans Got Creamed ** I know Michelle Malkin found 20 things that went right on election night, but there about 60 million things that went wrong. Let’s take a look:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Things to Question About Debt Deal</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/01/5-things-to-question-about-debt-deal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 12:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/01/5-things-to-question-about-debt-deal/</guid>
      <description>Yes, the Tea Party movement influenced what went on in Washington.
No, the Tea Party is not the winner. (No one won.)
No, this debt deal won’t guide the government off the road toward bankruptcy. Here’s why.
  No Entitlement Fix: In fact, it appears that entitlements aren’t touched. Entitlements are the nation’s spending problem. Not roads and bridges, not the military. Entitlements. Until we arrest and reverse growth in Social Security, Medicare, and Medicaid, we’re spitting in the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Last, Obama’s Ready to Borrow More Money from China</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/22/at-last-obamas-ready-to-borrow-more-money-from-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/22/at-last-obamas-ready-to-borrow-more-money-from-china/</guid>
      <description>The headline on July 15 was knee-slapping funny:
 Obama says he’s “ready to move**” on debt ceiling. **
 Really? The man who dug a deeper debt hole in two years than anyone else did in 8—or 15—is willing to borrow more?
Say it ain’t so.
For those who believe Obama’s some sort of deficit hawk, let’s take a quick stroll down memory.
 Obama wanted to increase the debt limit by $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>80 Percent of Americans Read This Blog Every Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/16/80-percent-of-americans-read-this-blog-every-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/16/80-percent-of-americans-read-this-blog-every-day/</guid>
      <description>I’ll be honest with you: I’ve lied.
Usually out of desperation. I’ve lied to those closest to me—those most willing to forgive the thing I lied about.
I’ve also told the truth to my own detriment. In the long run, the latter works best. In fact, telling the truth works best in the short run, too.
So maybe Obama’s desperate. Maybe he knows that the debt ceiling debate is the beginning of the unraveling of Americum Sovieticum, his life-long dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimme More Money or Granny Gets It!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/12/gimme-more-money-or-granny-gets-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/12/gimme-more-money-or-granny-gets-it/</guid>
      <description>Obama showed his breaking point today. The stress got to him.
Today Obama threatened to stop Social Security payments if Congress doesn’t bend to his will on the debt ceiling.
The president told reporters that there may not be enough money to pay Social Security benefits on and after August 3rd.
But the President lies.
Revenue from taxes and other fees would cover Social Security and other payments. What won’t be covered is additional borrowing to service the country’s already outrageous debt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>