<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academics &amp;amp; Education on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/academics-amp-education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academics &amp;amp; Education on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 04:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/academics-amp-education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Outliers: The Story of Success</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/30/outliers-the-story-of-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 04:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/30/outliers-the-story-of-success/</guid>
      <description>Rarely does a book require immediate action from the reader. &amp;ldquo;The Rights of Man&amp;rdquo; by Thomas Paine moved America&amp;rsquo;s founder&amp;rsquo;s to action. &amp;ldquo;The Communist Manifesto&amp;rdquo; moved Vladimir Lenin to enslave a nation&amp;ndash;and allowed Stalin to enslave many more. &amp;ldquo;The Origin of Species&amp;rdquo; launched a crusade against tradition that grows in intensity with each subsequent generation. (Listverse has a list of the 10 most influential books of all time, admittedly subjective.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Particularly Beware This Boy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/19/particularly-beware-this-boy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 11:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/19/particularly-beware-this-boy/</guid>
      <description>It turns out, according to a Zogby poll to be released in its entirety today, that most Obama voters are woefully, frighteningly, and unforgivably ignorant of the basic facts of government and of Barack Obama himself. Not surprising. Dickens warned us of the dangers of ignorance in &amp;ldquo;A Christmas Carol&amp;quot;:
 Suddenly, Scrooge noticed something strange about the ghost. Two children-like figures were at the ghost&amp;rsquo;s feet - a boy and a girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey:  Environmental Cost of Plastics</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/04/21/survey-environmental-cost-of-plastics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 03:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/04/21/survey-environmental-cost-of-plastics/</guid>
      <description>Please take a quick, 10-question survey on the environmental cost of plastics.
This survey is for an environmental science class, and will help me get a good grade. Please forward this link to anyone you know might want to help me with this survey. I need at least 25 responses, but the more, the merrier.
https://hennessysview.plastics.sgizmo.com
Thanks, in advance, for your help.
Technorati Tags: Plastics,eduction,environment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quashing Thought</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/11/06/quashing-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 03:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/11/06/quashing-thought/</guid>
      <description>Does your college freshman attend mandatory thought indoctrination camps? Is he formally and publicly humiliated by the university if his view on gay marriage, global warming, or affirmative action differ from Barrack Obama&amp;rsquo;s? Doe his college or university punish him for holding opinions that are inconsistent with the Democrat Underground and other anti-American hate groups?
If he attends University of Delaware, the answer is &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo;
Thanks to Joanne Jacobs on Pajama&amp;rsquo;s Media (h/t The Discerning Texan), we learn that Delaware is holding liberal, Soviet-style thought control experiments on its students, for which its faculty and administration should be taken out and shot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>