<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chris christie on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/chris-christie/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chris christie on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/chris-christie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump knocks Rubio out of the news cycle</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/26/trump-knocked-rubio-out-of-the-news-cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/26/trump-knocked-rubio-out-of-the-news-cycle/</guid>
      <description>That was a strategic kill-shot, to borrow Scott Adams&amp;rsquo;s word. And it changes everything for conservatives.
After a so-so debate performance and in the middle of a 16-hour verbal assault from Marco Rubio, Trump went nuclear. But not the way everyone would expect Trump to go nuclear.
Trump didn&amp;rsquo;t need to invent a brilliant new put-down line to counter Marco. Instead, he calmly introduced Chris Christie to 10,000 fans in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What Chris Christie Got Right </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/09/heres-chris-christie-got-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 01:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/09/heres-chris-christie-got-right/</guid>
      <description>I stand by my assessment that Chris Christie&amp;rsquo;s leadership and management played a role in the retaliatory shutdown of Fort Lee&amp;rsquo;s access lanes to the George Washington Bridge. Yesterday,I compared the GWB scandal to several Obama scandals. I pointed out that conservatives must apply the same standards to Christie as we did to Obama when the IRS scandal broke.
Today, let&amp;rsquo;s look at Christie&amp;rsquo;s response and contrast it to Obama&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why &#34;Time for Some Traffic Problems in Fort Lee&#34; Matters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/08/time-traffic-problems-fort-lee-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 03:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/08/time-traffic-problems-fort-lee-matters/</guid>
      <description>One argument put forth by conservatives&amp;ndash;and even some liberals&amp;ndash;regarding the IRS scandal was this:
Obama set a tone that encouraged IRS workers to harass conservative and Tea Party groups. He didn&amp;rsquo;t have to give a direct order. His tone and statements clearly condoned such criminal behavior toward his political enemies.
Kimberly Strassel at WSJ.com:
 Mr. Obama didn&amp;rsquo;t need to pick up the phone. All he needed to do was exactly what he did do, in full view, for three years: Publicly suggest that conservative political groups were engaged in nefarious deeds; publicly call out by name political opponents whom he&amp;rsquo;d like to see harassed; and publicly have his party pressure the IRS to take action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jay Nixon Putting Party Ahead of Missouri? *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/jay-nixon-putting-party-ahead-of-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/jay-nixon-putting-party-ahead-of-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Last week, the Illinois legislature passed a massive income tax increase on individuals and businesses. Overall, it represents about a 67 percent income tax increase.
In response, neighboring states of Wisconsin and Indiana have wisely mounted massive campaigns to suck businesses and people out of Illinois. Even New Jersey’s fabulous governor, Chris Christie, plans to fish the Land o’ Lincoln for some business transplants.
One state bordering Illinois has been notoriously silent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>