<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>progressives on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/progressives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in progressives on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 13:28:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/progressives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;ve Never Been Closer to Totalitarianism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/30/weve-never-been-closer-to-totalitarianism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 13:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/30/weve-never-been-closer-to-totalitarianism/</guid>
      <description>Very scary thought: If the Democrats take over the House and Senate in January, they could impeach both Trump and Pence and try them in the Senate at the same time making Nancy Pelosi president.
You&amp;rsquo;ve Never Lived in a Time Like This One I&amp;rsquo;m almost old enough to remember the Democrat National Convention of 1968. Almost. What a show. Hippies and Yippies marching, tear gas, Mayor Daley, Buckley threatening to punch Gore Vidal on live TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Are Not the Enemy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/10/01/liberals-are-not-the-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/10/01/liberals-are-not-the-enemy/</guid>
      <description>Forgive me. I say &amp;ldquo;liberal&amp;rdquo; sometimes when I mean something else.
My mistake is habit, not irony. (Irony would require some intent on my part.)
I grew up disparaging liberalism. I grew up reading and watching William F. Buckley Jr., for whom liberalism was the enemy.
In the post-WWII era, the liberalism of the day was a problem. But it was never the problem.
The problem in Western Civilization was a faction that used liberalism as cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Turning Tide Swamps All Lefties</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/a-turning-tide-swamps-all-lefties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/a-turning-tide-swamps-all-lefties/</guid>
      <description>For three consecutive days the hard left of American politics executed a prepared battle plan:
 * Personify the Enemy (Sarah Palin, Rush Limbaugh, Glenn Beck) * Isolate him or her (Rightwing vitriol, conservative talk radio, “crosshairs”) * Vilify without mercy (Hate, violence, accessory to murder)  Democrat Mark Penn showed us the left’s cards in November when he said that Obama needs an Oklahoma bombing to help him “reconnect” with the American people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got Your Back</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/11/got-your-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 23:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/11/got-your-back/</guid>
      <description>Seth Godin’s daily blogs are amazingly timely.
Today Seth talked about having someone’s back. He explained that the time we need to feel that someone has our back is when things are tough, not when they’re going well.
 No, if you want her to go all in, if you want her to take the risk and brave the fear, then it sure helps if you&amp;rsquo;re there too, no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>