<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>freedom on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/freedom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in freedom on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 14:50:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/freedom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday to a Special Friend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/11/happy-birthday-to-a-special-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 14:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/11/happy-birthday-to-a-special-friend/</guid>
      <description>Just a short note to wish my friend Jim a happy birthday.
Jim doesn&amp;rsquo;t know this, but several years ago he planted a seed in my heart that has broken through the crust of the earth and is now starting to bloom. For his birthday, I want him to know how grateful I am for his wisdom.
When Jim was in St. Louis, he helped a great deal in getting the St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Smart Phones Are More Popular Than the Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/why-smart-phones-are-more-popular-than-the-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/why-smart-phones-are-more-popular-than-the-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Does it bother you that people would give up essential freedoms before they’d give up their iPhone?
 While 26 percent of Americans report that they can’t live without their smartphone, only 20 percent of Americans say they can’t live without sex, according to this infographic compiled by FinancesOnline.com, a personal finance website.
 Seriously.
It should bother you. [olympus_highlight color=&#39;yellow]Without essential freedoms, smart phones can be taken away or banned[/olympus_highlight].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Which Freedoms Are We Losing? </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</guid>
      <description>I confess.
When I write about freedoms lost, I don&amp;rsquo;t itemize the freedoms. I don&amp;rsquo;t feel too bad, though, because almost no one does. Itemizing sucks.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s hard work. &amp;ldquo;Losing freedom,&amp;rdquo; takes about three seconds to type and less time to read. Listing freedoms,on the other hand, takes that much time just to highlight all the freedoms and click the un-ordered list button. God forbid I find myself working in straight HTML and have to hand-type &amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Government’s Surrender to Cliven Bundy Destroys Taleb’s Weak Argument for Gun Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</guid>
      <description>Events of the past week show the power of the Second Amendment to challenge government tyranny, regardless of the government’s firepower advantage. Let me back up, though.
A Smart Man’s Stupid Argument for Gun Control A year ago, the gun control lobby pumped a Facebook post by Nassim Nicholas Taleb, one of my favorite thinkers.
In his post, Taleb argued that the Second Amendment means nothing because the federal government has massively superior firepower:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Would Buckley Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/upon-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 09:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/upon-time/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to be William F. Buckley Jr. All I lacked was his intellect, education, and unique experiences.
Well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be him. I wanted to be the next one.
Every day, I wrote a 750-word piece. Poorly. I believed that practice would improve my writing.
It didn&amp;rsquo;t.
One day, I realized, as long as I tried to be the next William F. Buckley, I was destined for frustration and failure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>