<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeff Sessions on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jeff-sessions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jeff Sessions on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 01:02:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jeff-sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Jeff Session</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/fire-jeff-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 01:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/fire-jeff-session/</guid>
      <description>Greg Jarrett thinks Jeff Sessions should resign. I do, too.
I felt like the lone voice on the right last week when I wrote &amp;ldquo;Counseling Sessions.&amp;rdquo; It feels great to have Greg Jarrett agree: Jeff Sessions should resign.
As Jarrett puts it:
 Sessions appears either incapable or incompetent. He has resisted producing the documents relevant to the anti-Trump dossier which were subpoenaed by the House Intelligence Committee. He has failed to appoint a special counsel to reopen the case against Hillary Clinton for likely violations of the Espionage Act in the use of her email server, obstruction of justice for destroying 33,000 emails under congressional subpoena, and potential self-dealing for profit through her foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counselling Sessions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/10/counselling-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 16:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/10/counselling-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Eight months into the Trump Administration, one cabinet appointment stands out as a flop: Attorney General Jeff Sessions.
 We all had a lot of hope. Back in January. Hope.
Hope for the Trump administration. Hope for American greatness. And hope for justice. If you&amp;rsquo;re a Tea Partier, you had a lot of hope.
Jeff Sessions looked like the ultimate pick for Attorney General. Conservatives berated Mitch McConnell to accelerate Sessions&amp;rsquo; confirmation by the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>