<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Millennial on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/millennial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Millennial on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 22:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/millennial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am a Right-Leaning Libertarian</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/08/right-leaning-libertarian/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 21:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/08/right-leaning-libertarian/</guid>
      <description>What political label do you give yourself?
Yesterday, I blogged about calling myself a Republican. I was a kid.
Then, from about 1996 on, I called myself a conservative.
Over the past year or so, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken on the label of libertarian. Now, a simple online test confirms that I&amp;rsquo;m a right-leaning conservative. [Take the test yourself]
That&amp;rsquo;s exciting, because I feel like I need a new label.
Labels Matter I know there was a movement a couple of years ago to abolish political and ideological labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Crystal-Clear Images From The Republican Primary De-Cantor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/15/3-crystal-clear-images-from-the-republican-primary-de-cantor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 01:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/15/3-crystal-clear-images-from-the-republican-primary-de-cantor/</guid>
      <description>“Shellacked!”
That was the word that stuck out to me.
Eric Cantor, the Republican House Majority Leader led by 34 points according to his pollster. He lost by 10. That’s a shellacking.
Eric Cantor was the first sitting House Majority Leader ever knocked off in a primary. Cantor was also one of Wall Street’s best friends and the embodiment of crony capitalism—the disease eating the heart out of the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah Goldberg Perfectly Defines the GOP Establishment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 18:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</guid>
      <description>I hope you read Jonah Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s short article on National Review Online last week. If not, you missed the best definition of Establishment Republicans EVER!
Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s piece also exploded the myth of &amp;ldquo;pro-business&amp;rdquo; way too many conservatives believe. Conservatism isn&amp;rsquo;t pro-business, it&amp;rsquo;s pro-market. I&amp;rsquo;ll let Jonah explain:
 Just to clarify, the difference between being pro-business and pro-market is categorical. A politician who is a “friend of business” is exactly that, a guy who does favors for his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>