<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>russia on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/russia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in russia on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:23:38 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When Democrats Loved &#39;em Some Ruskies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/when-democrats-loved-em-some-ruskies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/when-democrats-loved-em-some-ruskies/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/Py8BF0hHPnc
In 2012, Barack Obama got caught telling Russian Prime Minister Medvedev that he&amp;rsquo;d have more &amp;ldquo;flexibility&amp;rdquo; after the election.
Later in 2012, during a debate, Obama accused GOP candidate Mitt Romney of stoking Cold War fears against our new friends in Moscow. Obama said, “The 1980s are now calling to ask for their foreign policy back because…the Cold War’s been over for 20 years!” In fact, in 2012, the whole pantheon of pantsuit partiersmocked warnings about Russia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Russians Are Coming! The Russians Are Coming!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/the-russians-are-coming-the-russians-are-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/the-russians-are-coming-the-russians-are-coming/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/IEWWRbn4zG0
In 1966, Hollywood liberals made a very funny movie. The Russians Are Coming! The Russians Are Coming! The movie mocked Cold Warriors and ridiculed hyper-paranoia about the dangers posed by Russia.
Some of those same Hollywood liberals are now running around screaming &amp;ldquo;The Russians Are Coming! The Russians Are Coming!&amp;rdquo;
Funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Russian Empire</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</guid>
      <description>The last two years of Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s presidency will see the rise of a new Russian empire.
This new empire will resemble the Soviet Union in shape, the Czars in style.
We looked at this subject over the summer (here and here). To summarize those blogs:
 The US-led coup of Ukraine convinced Putin to reassert safer borders Russia wants to build a buffer between itself and NATO Putin wants to re-establish a Russian Empire to revitalize Russian pride and influence Western debt and war-weariness make NATO impotent Putin knows the next US president might be more of a man than Obama, even if its Hillary Putin will want to complete his expansion by January 20, 2017 Ukraine is as good as done and Poland will fall under Russian influence  I still believe all of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be President When Russia Goes Berserk Starring Ronald Reagan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 03:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</guid>
      <description>Since the scrawny punk from Chicago still hasn&amp;rsquo;t figured it out, this President 101 lesson delivered without further comment:
https://youtu.be/9VA4W1wDMAk?t=18s
Previously on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View:
We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14949&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]&amp;ldquo;What, me worry?&amp;quot;[/caption]
Russian troops or Russian proxies murdered 293 people, today, including 23 Americans by many reports.
Israel was forced to invade Gaza to destroy tunnels Hamas uses to invade Israel and murder children.
The world teeters on the brink of all-out war.
But the President refused to cancel partisan fundraising efforts tonight.
Via The Blaze:
 At 2:25 p.m., the White House press office e-mailed a response to an inquiry from TheBlaze, “No scheduling changes to be reported at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>