<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tom schweich on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tom-schweich/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tom schweich on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 23:28:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tom-schweich/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Judgment on Rockwood School Board (or something worse?)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/31/bad-judgment-rockwood-school-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 23:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/31/bad-judgment-rockwood-school-board/</guid>
      <description>Everyone remembers the horrible audit of the Rockwood School District.
** $1.2 million wasted in double payments ** Contracts awarded to a construction company that had one of its executives on the board ** Feeble, &amp;ldquo;arrogant&amp;rdquo; response to the audit from board members ** Bad management!
But the worst example of cronyism and arrogance went largely unreported. (The great Elliott Davis caught it, though. Video to follow.)
Rockwood Board&amp;rsquo;s Secret Response The late auditor Tom Schweich released Rockwood&amp;rsquo;s horrible audit on February 28, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Do With the DOJ Report on Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/what-to-do-with-the-doj-report-on-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 17:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/what-to-do-with-the-doj-report-on-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>The will of man is not shattered, but softened, bent, and guided; men are seldom forced by it to act, but they are constantly restrained from acting. Such a power does not destroy, but it prevents existence; it does not tyrannize, but it compresses, enervates, extinguishes, and stupefies a people, till each nation is reduced to nothing better than a flock of timid and industrious animals, of which the government is the shepherd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providence and Hope in Missouri</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/providence-and-hope-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 23:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/providence-and-hope-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Fate moves in mysterious ways.
Just days before State Auditor and Republican gubernatorial candidate Tom Schweich died, Eric Greitens announced an exploratory committee. Greitens wants to test the water of a possible run for Missouri Governor as a Republican.
Greitens would be, perhaps, the most remarkable human being ever to pursue the office of Governor of Missouri. Here’s a sampling of Greitens’s achievements:
 Humanitarian who’s worked in Rwanda, Bosnia, Central America, India and other disaster zones—usually man-made disaster zones Boxer who won championships in England Rhodes Scholar who completed the program at Oxford Navy SEAL who earned the Bronze Star among other accolades in four tours in Iraq Founder of The Mission Continues to give wounded veterans a mission and a purpose in life Time Magazine’s 100 most influential people in the world Forbes’ Magazine’s 50 greatest leaders in the world  Purpose Over Party Greitens is no ideologue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Schweich, RIP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/26/tom-schweich-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 20:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/26/tom-schweich-rip/</guid>
      <description>News of Auditor Tom Schweich&amp;rsquo;s death hit me hard. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard, St. Louis Post-Dispatch reported to day that my friend Tom Schweich died of a gunshot wound today. Tom was 54.
I am saddened by this news. I pray for Tom&amp;rsquo;s family and for his rapid entry to eternal happiness.
May perpetual light shine on him, and may his soul and all the souls of all the faithful departed rest in peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>34 to 0: Good Ideas Are Hard to Fight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/13/34-0-good-ideas-hard-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 03:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/13/34-0-good-ideas-hard-fight/</guid>
      <description>I was scared. Not afraid to say it.
And some friends turned hostile. They had good reasons. And I was probably a little cavalier. And I talked way too long.
But last September I wanted to start something that would help real people in our neighborhood while advancing liberty and upsetting abusive government. Sure, I&amp;rsquo;d rather upset the federal government in Washington, but my arms are little short to box with Harry Reid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Define Tom Schweich With One Word</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/18/define-tom-schweich-one-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 22:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/18/define-tom-schweich-one-word/</guid>
      <description>Work screwed up my plans.
Our annual St. Louis Tea Party / Heritage Action Christmas Party started at 6:00 in the evening on December 17. I knew Auditor Tom Schweich planned to attend, and I looked forward to seeing him.
About 3:00 the problems started. People scurrying to wrap up projects before the Christmas break led to errors, questions, and never-ending email threads.
I finally made it out of the office about 7:30 and arrived at Scarecrow in Chesterfield a little after 8:00.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What&#39;s Happening on the Muni Courts Front</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 02:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</guid>
      <description>He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harrass our people, and eat out their substance.
 &amp;ndash; The Declaration of Independence
Back in August, I asked for your help in pushing for municipal court reform.
Cities that abuse their police and courts destroy liberty:
** Abusive citiesturn citizens against their police forces ** Abusive cities sponge off the poor ** Abusive cities operate debtor prisons ** Abusive cities subvert respect for the law and the courts ** Abusive citiesdemean and demoralize their citizens ** Abusive cities repel business and jobs ** Abusive cities condition people to bow down to government</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockwood School District Wants More Money But State Audit Found It Mismanages The Money It Has</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/rockwood-school-district-wants-more-money-but-state-audit-found-it-mismanages-the-money-it-has/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/rockwood-school-district-wants-more-money-but-state-audit-found-it-mismanages-the-money-it-has/</guid>
      <description>Were Rockwood School District to shut down, the entire bond-issue-campaign-financing industry would slump into depression.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12113&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;284&amp;rdquo;] Rockwood School District wants another $38 million bond issue on the heals of scathing audit of its financial management practices.I’ve lived in this district since 1996, and I honestly don’t remember an April in which the board wasn’t asking for more money to carpet the football fields or remodel 12-year-old theatres or build an observatory or whatever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Candidate Who Doesn’t Want You to Know Her</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/the-candidate-who-doesnt-want-you-to-know-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/the-candidate-who-doesnt-want-you-to-know-her/</guid>
      <description>Political candidates want to meet everyone. “If people would just meet me,” they say, “they’ll realize I’m a regular . . .” guy/gal/tea partier/whatever. This seems a good thing—willing to stand before the voters and be judged.
Missouri’s State Auditor, Susan Montee might want to keep her name, her history, and her record out of the spotlight. That’s because Susan Montee is about as hard left as you get.
Here’ just a sample:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On to November</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/on-to-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/on-to-november/</guid>
      <description>The primaries are over.
I honestly believe that in the St. Louis area, the rightward-most, viable candidate won each of the key votes. The people of Missouri are in a position to make historical shifts in our Washington representation. And those shifts are just the first step and restoring America’s First Principles.

View Full Album
Roy Blunt is a conservative. He will be a big step up for conservatism in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Rock Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/05/how-to-rock-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 00:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/05/how-to-rock-freedom/</guid>
      <description>[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bgU7T2au2Wg&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;color1;=0x2b405b&amp;amp;color2;=0x6b8ab6&amp;amp;border;=1]
Wow. A former Ambassador and candidate for Missouri State Auditor. And a Stones fan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>