<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ukraine on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/ukraine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ukraine on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 03:18:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/ukraine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Russian Empire</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</guid>
      <description>The last two years of Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s presidency will see the rise of a new Russian empire.
This new empire will resemble the Soviet Union in shape, the Czars in style.
We looked at this subject over the summer (here and here). To summarize those blogs:
 The US-led coup of Ukraine convinced Putin to reassert safer borders Russia wants to build a buffer between itself and NATO Putin wants to re-establish a Russian Empire to revitalize Russian pride and influence Western debt and war-weariness make NATO impotent Putin knows the next US president might be more of a man than Obama, even if its Hillary Putin will want to complete his expansion by January 20, 2017 Ukraine is as good as done and Poland will fall under Russian influence  I still believe all of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14949&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]&amp;ldquo;What, me worry?&amp;quot;[/caption]
Russian troops or Russian proxies murdered 293 people, today, including 23 Americans by many reports.
Israel was forced to invade Gaza to destroy tunnels Hamas uses to invade Israel and murder children.
The world teeters on the brink of all-out war.
But the President refused to cancel partisan fundraising efforts tonight.
Via The Blaze:
 At 2:25 p.m., the White House press office e-mailed a response to an inquiry from TheBlaze, “No scheduling changes to be reported at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now, the White House Says Russia Preparing to Invade Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/now-the-white-house-says-russia-preparing-to-invade-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 20:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/now-the-white-house-says-russia-preparing-to-invade-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>This morning, a White House aide told reporters that Obama’s sanctions are visibly “weakening” Putin and Russia.
Hours later, the White House recognizes that Russia’s invasion of Ukraine could come any moment.
 Speaking from the Georgian capital, Tbilisi, Mike Rogers, the chair of the House of Representatives intelligence committee, said US intelligence officials were convinced “that Putin is not done in Ukraine”.
 Surprise. As I’ve written, Russian paranoia demands a larger sphere of influence and a large buffer of puppet governments, all the way to the German border with Poland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Would You Do If You Were Putin?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 18:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</guid>
      <description>You saw Obama stand by as you threatened Georgia in 2009.
You heard Obama whisper to Medvedev that he’ll be willing to defy Congress to capitulate to you after Obama’s re-election.
You watched Obama and his bumbling Secretary of State mangle its its own strategy in Syria—if the US ever had a Syrian strategy at all.
You saw that the US was completely unprepared for your annexation of Crimea.
You see the headlines of massive NSA spying on US citizens, though that same NSA was blind to your invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Book Predicted Russia&#39;s Ukraine Adventure. Poland&#39;s Next.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/16/predicted-russias-ukraine-adventure-polands-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/16/predicted-russias-ukraine-adventure-polands-next/</guid>
      <description>Did you ever read a book and think, &amp;ldquo;I need to tell people about this?&amp;rdquo;
Then you didn&amp;rsquo;t tell people about it. I mean, you didn&amp;rsquo;t blog about it. You didn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;officially&amp;rdquo; proclaim the book &amp;ldquo;required reading.&amp;rdquo;
Then something happened that you knew could happen because of the book, but you don&amp;rsquo;t get credit for calling it because you never got around to pumping the book.
That&amp;rsquo;s how I feel today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>