<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>georgetown on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/georgetown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in georgetown on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 16:33:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/georgetown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Rush Limbaugh Revived Chivalry</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/03/how-rush-limbaugh-revived-chivalry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2012 16:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/03/how-rush-limbaugh-revived-chivalry/</guid>
      <description>A Georgetown law student turned the Democrat Party from an androgynous blob into a modern day Ivanhoe. (Yes, I’ll tread carefully around that “Ivanhoe” to spare Democrat sensibilities.)

Sandra Fluke, the student, begged Congress to confiscate property from me and millions of other taxpayers in order to satisfy her sexual appetite.
Rush Limbaugh pointed out that law school lasts three years, condoms cost about a buck each, and Ms. Fluke needed 3,000 of them just to make it to the bar exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wait ‘til These Kids Meet the Tax Man</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/08/wait-til-these-kids-meet-the-tax-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 14:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/08/wait-til-these-kids-meet-the-tax-man/</guid>
      <description>When the rules become so complicated and convoluted that well-meaning people unwittingly break the law, the legal system has lost its moral authority.
Students at Georgetown University are discovering the horrors of, what Tocqueville called “small complicated rules, minute and uniform, through which the most original minds and the most energetic characters cannot penetrate, to rise above the crowd.”
An editorial in The Hoya, the official student newspaper, students advocate “eliminating bureaucracy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>