<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GOP on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/gop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GOP on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/gop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump knocks Rubio out of the news cycle</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/26/trump-knocked-rubio-out-of-the-news-cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/26/trump-knocked-rubio-out-of-the-news-cycle/</guid>
      <description>That was a strategic kill-shot, to borrow Scott Adams&amp;rsquo;s word. And it changes everything for conservatives.
After a so-so debate performance and in the middle of a 16-hour verbal assault from Marco Rubio, Trump went nuclear. But not the way everyone would expect Trump to go nuclear.
Trump didn&amp;rsquo;t need to invent a brilliant new put-down line to counter Marco. Instead, he calmly introduced Chris Christie to 10,000 fans in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Republican elites know something they&#39;re not telling?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/25/do-republican-elites-know-something-theyre-not-telling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 05:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/25/do-republican-elites-know-something-theyre-not-telling/</guid>
      <description>Reading two excellent articles by Nate Silver of FiveThirtyEight (here and here), I remembered a thought that passed through my mind last Friday.
After reading some of National Review&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Against Trump&amp;rdquo; issue,I wrote blog post. To me the NR issue showed the magazine is out of touch with voters. I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about traditional, reliable, motivated, and informed primary voters.** I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the broader pool of voters who vote in general elections every four, eight, or twelve years** and occasionally in local elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri Republicans Made Jay Nixon Look Like a Statesman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 01:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</guid>
      <description>You know how reckless and tone-deaf Obama is about Army deserters? Missouri&amp;rsquo;s House and Senate Republican leaders are just as clueless and irresponsible about money.
Yes, I said it: the Missouri Republican legislature is about as conservative and principled as Susan Rice on a Sunday talk show.
By going on a votes-for-cash spending spree on the last day of the General Assembly, the House and Senate handed Jay &amp;ldquo;Idiot&amp;rdquo; Nixon a PR prize worth its weight in pork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust Is a Bigger Problem for GOP Than Marketing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/trust-is-a-bigger-problem-for-gop-than-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 16:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/trust-is-a-bigger-problem-for-gop-than-marketing/</guid>
      <description>The GOP’s self-examination on the 2012 election debacle rightly identifies marketing and messaging and lack of a ground game as contributors to that mess.

But the GOP’s self-exam missed a potentially fatal problem for the party: the American people simply do not trust Republicans on the budget.
Read this paragraph from The Hill carefully. Read all of it. It should tell you everything you need to know.
 More voters trust the Democratic Party than the Republican Party on budgetary issues, according to the results of a new poll for The Hill — even though a strong majority actually prefer Republican fiscal policies [emphases added].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Lose Because They Don’t Attract Enough Conservatives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/04/republicans-lose-because-they-dont-attract-enough-conservatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/04/republicans-lose-because-they-dont-attract-enough-conservatives/</guid>
      <description>For 20 years, the Battleground Poll of States (now the Politico/GW Battleground Poll) showed a freakish consistency about ideology.
2009: 59% Conservative 
 2012: 57% Conservative 
With almost 60% calling themselves somewhat or very conservative, how could Barack Obama get re-elected? How could Republicans fail to gain the Senate in 2010 and 2012? Come to think of it, how do Democrats win at all?
The answer is simple: being conservative doesn’t make you Republican, but being Democrat makes you a liberal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Grilling Of Bernanke Came From Senator Elizabeth Warren And Republicans Should Be Ashamed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/26/the-best-grilling-of-bernanke-came-from-senator-elizabeth-warren-and-republicans-should-be-ashamed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 03:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/26/the-best-grilling-of-bernanke-came-from-senator-elizabeth-warren-and-republicans-should-be-ashamed/</guid>
      <description>I agree with Republican Senator Corker that inflation is a danger in the future. But inflation doesn’t win the hearts and minds of most Americans right now. No one’s worried about it except economists and economics geeks.
The death of the community and regional bank, however, does bother people. As does the printing of money that goes straight into the 5 biggest banks in history . . . and stays there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why GOP Pandering to Young Voters Backfires</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/25/why-gop-pandering-to-young-voters-backfires/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/25/why-gop-pandering-to-young-voters-backfires/</guid>
      <description>Marco Rubio gave the Republican response to the State of the Union address for two reasons.
First, Rubio’s Cuban, and the GOP wants to court Latinos.
Second, Rubio’s relatively young, and the GOP wants to stop the bleeding when it comes to young voters.
But there’s a fundamental problem with the Republican approach, and it stems from the GOP’s least favorite discipline: behavioral science.
Young People Are Naturally Skeptical You hear about scams that target older folks all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why The Sequester Is Worse Now Than It Will Be After It Happens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/why-the-sequester-is-worse-now-than-it-will-be-after-it-happens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/why-the-sequester-is-worse-now-than-it-will-be-after-it-happens/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Dr. Gina Show Listeners!
Republicans should announce “the sequester won’t be so bad” and shut up, and science tells us why.
Obama, the Dems, liberal pundits, the press, and even John Boehner are running around yelling about how horrible the sequester will be.
In some deep recesses of our minds, we agree. “Oh, my God! We’re all going to do die!”
Fear-mongering only works in the future because, in short, nothing is as bad (or as good) as we think it will be when we think about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is The Infographic That The Whole Republican Party Is Freaking Out About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</guid>
      <description>The 3 million McCain voters who didn’t vote for Romney?
They’re dead.

[Click image to view full size. Please forward, download, and print. This is important.]
To survive, the GOP needs to stop being afraid of Millennials and tell them truth: they can move out of mom and dad’s house, they can drop out of school, they can quit their dead-end job with the idiot supervisor. But they can’t get away from government and debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Conservative Base Is Dying And Taking Your Freedom With It *CORRECTION*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/the-conservative-base-is-dying-and-taking-freedom-with-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 10:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/the-conservative-base-is-dying-and-taking-freedom-with-it/</guid>
      <description>Consider these numbers:
 * **9.8 million** * &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;**11.6 million **&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt;**16.8 million** * **55%** * **61%**  Between the 2008 and 2012 elections:
 * 9.8 million people died*, 55% of them were reliable Republican voters * [16.8 &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;11.6&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; million people reached voting age](https://www.civicyouth.org/you-ask-we-answer-16-8-million-new-youth-eligible-to-vote-in-2012/?%3E)--61% of them are semi-reliable Democrat voters    
Between those years, neither the GOP nor conservative leaning organizations did anything significant to deal with this **demographic cliff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3:  Todd Akin Needs to Lead or Get Out of the Way</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] Todd Akin: member of the United States House of Representatives. (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
Part 3 of 3 | Read Part 1 | Read Part 2
Before we get too far down the Akin rally road, let&amp;rsquo;s get some solid advice to Mr. Akin.
His principles, his spine, his grassroots do no good if Missouri turns blue. He cannot advance his causes from his house in Wildwood. Failure to take the Senate makes Obamacare permanent, at least in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Candy Crowley: Tea Party Groups Resemble the 13 Colonies, Not the Balkans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</guid>
      <description>Analogies say more about the speaker than about the subject.
Candy Crowley told KMOX Radio listeners on Friday that Tea Party groups resemble the Balkans without guns.
Wrong. Crappy analogy, Candy. The diverse and autonomous, often quarrelsome,** Tea Party groups remind me of the original 13 colonies.**
The colonies were divided on just about every subject imaginable. The disagreed on slavery, on economics, on agraculture, manufacturing, cities, names &amp;ndash; name it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Activist Calls for Stampede</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/frieda-responds-to-the-lake-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 10:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/frieda-responds-to-the-lake-post/</guid>
      <description>I blogged aboutthe battle of the Tea Party&amp;rsquo;s future going on around the Lake of the Ozarks recently.
I received this response from Freida Keough, St. Louis County Director ofMissouri Precinct Project:
 My answer: We have 56 positions for committeemen and women in 28 Townships for St.Louis County. Did you know that 35 new individuals filed for these positions in addition to the incumbents. Coincidence? I don&amp;rsquo;t think this happened because people felt they have nothing else to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the GOP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-state-of-the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-state-of-the-gop/</guid>
      <description>by Bill Hennessy and Jim Durbin
John Knowles’s classic novel, A Separate Peace, begins memorably:
 I went back to the Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there fifteen years before . . . as if a coat of varnish had been put over everything for better preservation.
 I get precisely the opposite feel when I look at the Republican Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Watch The Kudlow Report at 6 Central Tonight **MARCH 14**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/14/breaking-watch-the-kudlow-report-at-6-central-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 19:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/14/breaking-watch-the-kudlow-report-at-6-central-tonight/</guid>
      <description>I’m honored to return to The Kudlow Report tonight (Wednesday, March 14) at 6:00 pm Central (7 ET) with Larry Kudlow.
I hope to talk about the GOP Presidential primaries, RomneyCare, and the Tea Party movement.
Please watch if you can. Good ratings for Tea Party guests will only increase the number of Tea Party guests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney’s Resume Cover Letter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/09/mitt-romneys-resume-cover-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/09/mitt-romneys-resume-cover-letter/</guid>
      <description>There are some things you just don’t say in a cover letter—or on the campaign trail.
A self-aggrandizing cover letter from an NYU undergrad to some Wall Street banks has the whole financial world laughing. The kid’s naïve hubris and ignorance of what employers look for in a candidate earned him public humiliation on an internet scale. Here’s just a sample of the kid’s self-promotion:
 That semester I achieved a 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire Exposes GOP’s Diverse Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</guid>
      <description>Okay, Santorum and Gingrich didn’t get a bump out of their debates over the weekend. More like the bump got them.
And Ron Paul did way better than I expected. Congratulations to Dr. Paul and Mitt. 
I still think my Saturday night post accurately reflected the national impressions, though. That’s backed up by this CBS News poll that shows Republicans believe Santorum most closely shares their values, but—and this is a J Lo but—they believe Romney is more electable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GOP’s Predictable Plan to Destroy the Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/07/the-gops-predictable-plan-to-destroy-the-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/07/the-gops-predictable-plan-to-destroy-the-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Yes, the establishment wants you to go away.
Are you going to obey?

With a little help from The Atlantic and New York Times (of all places), we can put together a strategy to recognize and deflect the establishment’s tactics.
Put this in your back pocket. You’ll need it before primary season is over.
Establishment Tactic 1: Never admit membership in the establishment
How To Handle: Never argue about what he establishment is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Moves for Herman Cain Supporters Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</guid>
      <description>Herman Cain is riding a wave of popularity because of his upset win in the Florida straw poll on Saturday. He’s helped by Rick Perry’s free-fall and Mitt Romney’s establishmentarianism. But Cain is a huge underdog.
That’s okay because **America loves an underdog. **
Here’s what must happen right now for Herman Cain to win:
1. Social Media avalanche. Get @THEHermanCain trending on Twitter, and keep it there for five consecutive days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Rick Perry Can Learn From Clark Griswold</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/24/what-rick-perry-can-learn-from-clark-griswold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 17:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/24/what-rick-perry-can-learn-from-clark-griswold/</guid>
      <description>In 2001, I loaded my three boys, ages 13, 10, and 8 at the time, into the car and headed to downtown St. Louis. The Cubs were in town, and I planned to introduce my boys to the greatest rivalry in pro sports. We parked (for twenty dollars) and headed toward the stadium.
There was only one problem: we didn’t have any tickets. I planned to buy some on the street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISAPPOINTING: Missouri House Leadership Blowing it</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/27/disappointing-missouri-house-leadership-blowing-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/27/disappointing-missouri-house-leadership-blowing-it/</guid>
      <description>I continue hearing reliable reports that the GOP Leadership in the Missouri House keeps its boot on the throat of Tea Party freshmen.
What a shame.
The party that was flat on its back from 2006 to 2009 rose back to power because of the tea party. But, it seems, the Missouri branch of the party didn’t get the message. And its Speaker in the Missouri House has become tighter with left-fringe Democrats that with conservatives of his own party.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>