<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GOP on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/gop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GOP on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/gop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump knocks Rubio out of the news cycle</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/26/trump-knocked-rubio-out-of-the-news-cycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/26/trump-knocked-rubio-out-of-the-news-cycle/</guid>
      <description>That was a strategic kill-shot, to borrow Scott Adams&amp;rsquo;s word. And it changes everything for conservatives.
After a so-so debate performance and in the middle of a 16-hour verbal assault from Marco Rubio, Trump went nuclear. But not the way everyone would expect Trump to go nuclear.
Trump didn&amp;rsquo;t need to invent a brilliant new put-down line to counter Marco. Instead, he calmly introduced Chris Christie to 10,000 fans in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Republican elites know something they&#39;re not telling?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/25/do-republican-elites-know-something-theyre-not-telling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 05:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/25/do-republican-elites-know-something-theyre-not-telling/</guid>
      <description>Reading two excellent articles by Nate Silver of FiveThirtyEight (here and here), I remembered a thought that passed through my mind last Friday.
After reading some of National Review&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Against Trump&amp;rdquo; issue,I wrote blog post. To me the NR issue showed the magazine is out of touch with voters. I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about traditional, reliable, motivated, and informed primary voters.** I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the broader pool of voters who vote in general elections every four, eight, or twelve years** and occasionally in local elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri Republicans Made Jay Nixon Look Like a Statesman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 01:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</guid>
      <description>You know how reckless and tone-deaf Obama is about Army deserters? Missouri&amp;rsquo;s House and Senate Republican leaders are just as clueless and irresponsible about money.
Yes, I said it: the Missouri Republican legislature is about as conservative and principled as Susan Rice on a Sunday talk show.
By going on a votes-for-cash spending spree on the last day of the General Assembly, the House and Senate handed Jay &amp;ldquo;Idiot&amp;rdquo; Nixon a PR prize worth its weight in pork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust Is a Bigger Problem for GOP Than Marketing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/trust-is-a-bigger-problem-for-gop-than-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 16:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/trust-is-a-bigger-problem-for-gop-than-marketing/</guid>
      <description>The GOP’s self-examination on the 2012 election debacle rightly identifies marketing and messaging and lack of a ground game as contributors to that mess.

But the GOP’s self-exam missed a potentially fatal problem for the party: the American people simply do not trust Republicans on the budget.
Read this paragraph from The Hill carefully. Read all of it. It should tell you everything you need to know.
 More voters trust the Democratic Party than the Republican Party on budgetary issues, according to the results of a new poll for The Hill — even though a strong majority actually prefer Republican fiscal policies [emphases added].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Lose Because They Don’t Attract Enough Conservatives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/04/republicans-lose-because-they-dont-attract-enough-conservatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/04/republicans-lose-because-they-dont-attract-enough-conservatives/</guid>
      <description>For 20 years, the Battleground Poll of States (now the Politico/GW Battleground Poll) showed a freakish consistency about ideology.
2009: 59% Conservative 
 2012: 57% Conservative 
With almost 60% calling themselves somewhat or very conservative, how could Barack Obama get re-elected? How could Republicans fail to gain the Senate in 2010 and 2012? Come to think of it, how do Democrats win at all?
The answer is simple: being conservative doesn’t make you Republican, but being Democrat makes you a liberal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>