<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Barack Obama on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/barack-obama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Barack Obama on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 21:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/barack-obama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seems Like Obama Is Tired of Hillary&#39;s S***</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/31/seems-like-obama-is-tired-of-hillarys-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 21:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/31/seems-like-obama-is-tired-of-hillarys-s/</guid>
      <description>You might have dated someone who was amazingly good looking. Everything&amp;rsquo;s great. For awhile. Then you get to know the person. A little too well. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s on a weekend trip. Or, God forbid, when you move in together. Then you realize looks aren&amp;rsquo;t everything.
The same thing can happen in political &amp;ldquo;marriages.&amp;rdquo; That surface quality that attracted you—donors, influence, contacts, whatever—sometimes isn&amp;rsquo;t worth the price.
Just ask Barack Obama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Explain Obama&#39;s Childish Defeatism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016-09-20-how-to-explain-obamas-childish-defeatism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016-09-20-how-to-explain-obamas-childish-defeatism/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama has thrown in the towel on Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s failed campaign. Before you see how that is, let&amp;rsquo;s look at a study on a key factor of business success or failure.
CEO Locus of Control In a series of studies, researchers found that companies whose CEO displayed an external locus of control were 650 percent more likely to fail than similar companies whose CEO showed an internal locus of control (source).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama &amp; Hillary Have Lost Control of Cop Killer Rhetoric</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/17/cop-killer-hillary-has-lost-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/17/cop-killer-hillary-has-lost-control/</guid>
      <description>Hillary, Obama, and much of the Democrat Party have fomented race hatred for years. They&amp;rsquo;ve ratcheted up their lies in recent months, hoping to turn race hatred into votes. They are that cynical and self-serving.
Now, Hillary and Obama have lost control of the fire they started. Crazed, racist murderers all across the country have declared war on police officers. From Dallas, Texas, to Ballwin, Missouri, to Baton Rouge, Louisianna, Hillary has sent a message that says it&amp;rsquo;s okay to kill a cop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14949&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]&amp;ldquo;What, me worry?&amp;quot;[/caption]
Russian troops or Russian proxies murdered 293 people, today, including 23 Americans by many reports.
Israel was forced to invade Gaza to destroy tunnels Hamas uses to invade Israel and murder children.
The world teeters on the brink of all-out war.
But the President refused to cancel partisan fundraising efforts tonight.
Via The Blaze:
 At 2:25 p.m., the White House press office e-mailed a response to an inquiry from TheBlaze, “No scheduling changes to be reported at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What Chris Christie Got Right </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/09/heres-chris-christie-got-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 01:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/09/heres-chris-christie-got-right/</guid>
      <description>I stand by my assessment that Chris Christie&amp;rsquo;s leadership and management played a role in the retaliatory shutdown of Fort Lee&amp;rsquo;s access lanes to the George Washington Bridge. Yesterday,I compared the GWB scandal to several Obama scandals. I pointed out that conservatives must apply the same standards to Christie as we did to Obama when the IRS scandal broke.
Today, let&amp;rsquo;s look at Christie&amp;rsquo;s response and contrast it to Obama&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>