<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>focus on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/focus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in focus on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 03:07:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/focus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s a 16th Century Lesson on Focus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/08/heres-a-16th-century-lesson-on-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 03:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/08/heres-a-16th-century-lesson-on-focus/</guid>
      <description>Sundays are useful touchstones for our goals.
Last week, I told you about my maniacal focus for 2012. At the beginning of the week, I stuck carefully to my plan. But after two consecutive 15-hour days at work, I let my mind wander a little. I’m sure you know how that goes.
Well, Sunday is a great touchstone. And who provided my guidance and support? A 16th century saint and Doctor of the Church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Maniacal Focus for 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/01/a-maniacal-focus-for-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 01:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/01/a-maniacal-focus-for-2012/</guid>
      <description>I’m almost finished reading Walter Isaacson’s biography of Apple co-founder and genius Steve Jobs.
Jobs’s life left insanely good lessons. Some lessons instruct us on how to do things. Others warn us of bad things to avoid.
One of the good things Steve Jobs taught us: focus. Maniacal focus on things that mattered, and a pathological aversion to distractions.
One example. When Jobs returned to Apple after 10-year exile, he took stock of all the projects underway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Achieve</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/29/how-to-achieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 12:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/29/how-to-achieve/</guid>
      <description>When a family’s children are small, the family has such unity of purpose. Mom, Dad, and all the kids climb into the mini-van or the SUV and head to the store. From there, they visit her parents. Then stop at McDonald’s on the way home. If one of the older kids is involved in an organized program, the whole family attends.

At bath time, the younger ones are bathed in batch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Paths to Focus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/13/2-paths-to-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 14:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/13/2-paths-to-focus/</guid>
      <description>I had a small revelation yesterday: there are two paths to focus.
One path requires constant vigilance against distraction. This path also demands great awareness of many things, knowledge, and outlandish tenacity. This is the path we recognize as heroic.
The other path gets less notice, less acclaim. Those how follow this other path to focus don’t seem to try hard. These are the “naturals.” Things seem to come easy for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Focus for Better Living</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/25/how-to-focus-for-better-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 23:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/25/how-to-focus-for-better-living/</guid>
      <description>I once thought that focus meant you never got distracted. I was wrong.
A person with a powerful focusing ability gets as distracted as the next guy. The difference is that the Focus Master has learned to recognize distraction and gently guide his thoughts or actions back to the intended task at hand.
That simple skill is rare and remarkably powerful. Pay attention to every word of this two-step process:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>