<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UMKC on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/umkc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UMKC on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 03:44:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/umkc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UMSL Killing American Males</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/10/umsl-killing-american-males/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 03:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/10/umsl-killing-american-males/</guid>
      <description>David Brooks—the former conservative—skewered the University of Missouri St. Louis yesterday. Brooks wasn’t aware, and UMSL administrators don’t read. But some of us caught it.
Brooks wrote of The Missing Fifth. **Did you know that 20 percent of American men in their primes don’t work? **
 Americans should be especially alert to signs that the country is becoming less vital and industrious. One of those signs comes to us from the labor market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMSL: Communist Recruiting With Taxpayer Dollars</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/09/umsl-communist-recruiting-with-taxpayer-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 02:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/09/umsl-communist-recruiting-with-taxpayer-dollars/</guid>
      <description>The University of Missouri St. Louis uses tax dollars to provide a recruiting station for the Communist Party USA—an organization whose purpose is to shred the United States Constitution.
UMSL Student Philip Christofanelli heroically chronicles the remarkable Marxist indoctrination known as “Introduction to Labor Studies” on BigGovernment.com. I’ll give you a taste:
 Prof. Giljum then introduced Tony Pecinovsky, a local organizer for the Communist Party, who proceeded to speak to us for two hours about the beliefs of the Communist Party and the benefits of membership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy Ancel: Teacher of the Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/judy-ancel-teacher-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 18:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/judy-ancel-teacher-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Judy Ancel is the University of Kansas City instructor responsible for teaching students to use violence, sabotage and intimidation as political tools. She’s telling the Kansas City Star that she’s receiving threats from people upset that she teaches students to threaten others.
I oppose violence, sabotage, and intimidation as political tools. But Judy Ancel’s message of violence seems to have gotten through to some people.
Too bad Ancel doesn’t use her skills for goodinstead of evil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Question for Gail Hackett of UMKC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/one-question-for-gail-hackett-of-umkc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 05:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/one-question-for-gail-hackett-of-umkc/</guid>
      <description>Gail Hackett, UMKC Provost, released a deceitful, false, and irresponsible defense of UMKC instructors who encouraged students to use violence, sabotage, and intimidation to their way.
But Gail Hackett refuses to answer hard questions.
I have one question for the UMKC Provost: ****
**Do you agree with Don Giljum’s statement “I believe in a violent overthrow of Bourgeois?” **
Before you answer, remember that Giljum’s use of the personal term “Bourgois” instead of the the class “bourguoisie” indicates that Giljim believes in violence against individual members of the middle class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Updates on University of Missouri Story</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/28/3-updates-on-university-of-missouri-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/28/3-updates-on-university-of-missouri-story/</guid>
      <description>Big news day in the advance of liberty in our battle against collectivists.
First, KMOX is reporting that an UMSL professor has resigned** over the controversy**. For the life of me, I cannot find who the professor is. I thought that everyone involved was either an instructor or a guest lecturer. If you know the answer to the riddle, please use the comment form.
Second, University of Kansas City refuses to accept responsibility for what goes on in its classroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shut Down Labor Studies Now, Governor Nixon</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/26/shut-down-labor-studies-now-governor-nixon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 02:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/26/shut-down-labor-studies-now-governor-nixon/</guid>
      <description>Governor Nixon:
What does it take to get your attention? What does it take to get you to act?
Your University of Missouri System humiliates this state, and you refuse to act.
Under your nose, the UofM teaches or encourages:
* **[Politically motivated](https://biggovernment.com/publius/2011/04/25/union-official-professor-teach-college-course-in-violent-union-tactics/) violence**** **Politically motivated [industrial sabotage](https://biggovernment.com/publius/2011/04/25/how-to-college-course-on-violent-union-tactics-part-ii-case-studies-edition/)**** **Politically motivated threats of violence and sabotage**** **Supporting and aiding [the enemy in Iraq and Afghanistan](https://biggovernment.com/driehl/2011/04/26/college-course-us-flag-is-racist-how-to-defeat-america-in-iraq-and-afghanistan/)**  You have permit these travesties. You, Jay Nixon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell UMSL to Stop Teaching Industrial Sabotage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/25/tell-umsl-to-stop-teaching-industrial-sabotage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 01:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/25/tell-umsl-to-stop-teaching-industrial-sabotage/</guid>
      <description>[ ](https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/UofMCommie.png)Contact UofM President Steve Owens and demand an immediate end to the communist-led industrial sabotage courses that he’s shoving down your kids’ throats
That’s right, UMSL and UMKC are teaching kids how to destroy business in America. They want your job to go overseas. And the guy leading the class is a proud communist.
No employer in his right might would hire a graduate of the University of Missouri-St. Louis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>