<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Repbulican on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/repbulican/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Repbulican on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 16:33:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/repbulican/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust Is a Bigger Problem for GOP Than Marketing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/trust-is-a-bigger-problem-for-gop-than-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 16:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/trust-is-a-bigger-problem-for-gop-than-marketing/</guid>
      <description>The GOP’s self-examination on the 2012 election debacle rightly identifies marketing and messaging and lack of a ground game as contributors to that mess.

But the GOP’s self-exam missed a potentially fatal problem for the party: the American people simply do not trust Republicans on the budget.
Read this paragraph from The Hill carefully. Read all of it. It should tell you everything you need to know.
 More voters trust the Democratic Party than the Republican Party on budgetary issues, according to the results of a new poll for The Hill — even though a strong majority actually prefer Republican fiscal policies [emphases added].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rodger Cook Best Choice for Southern Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/17/rodger-cook-best-choice-for-southern-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/17/rodger-cook-best-choice-for-southern-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Rodger Cook fools no one into thinking he’s a member of the political class. He’s not. Rodger’s a human being, like the rest of us. That’s just one of the reasons that Rodger Cook has earned my personal endorsement in next Tuesday’s (March 20) Illinois primary.*

Actually, Rodger’s not so much like the rest of us. Rodger has served the people of Illinois all of his adult life. Rodger has been a police officer, a detective, a mayor, and private businessman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Surging in the Polls; Here’s Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/obamas-surging-in-the-polls-heres-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/obamas-surging-in-the-polls-heres-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</guid>
      <description>Don’t bother blaming it on poll questions designed to lead respondents. Never mind that it’s a long way until the election. And stop whining about the White House fudging the numbers on unemployment.
The fact is that Obama’s surging at just the right time. His re-election chances are now above 50 percent. His intrade.com chances of winning are near 60 percent. And he’s raising more money than al of the Republican candidates combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney’s Resume Cover Letter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/09/mitt-romneys-resume-cover-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/09/mitt-romneys-resume-cover-letter/</guid>
      <description>There are some things you just don’t say in a cover letter—or on the campaign trail.
A self-aggrandizing cover letter from an NYU undergrad to some Wall Street banks has the whole financial world laughing. The kid’s naïve hubris and ignorance of what employers look for in a candidate earned him public humiliation on an internet scale. Here’s just a sample of the kid’s self-promotion:
 That semester I achieved a 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire Exposes GOP’s Diverse Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</guid>
      <description>Okay, Santorum and Gingrich didn’t get a bump out of their debates over the weekend. More like the bump got them.
And Ron Paul did way better than I expected. Congratulations to Dr. Paul and Mitt. 
I still think my Saturday night post accurately reflected the national impressions, though. That’s backed up by this CBS News poll that shows Republicans believe Santorum most closely shares their values, but—and this is a J Lo but—they believe Romney is more electable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Santorum Pulls Away with 13-Vote Lead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/03/breaking-santorum-pulls-away-with-13-vote-lead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 04:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/03/breaking-santorum-pulls-away-with-13-vote-lead/</guid>
      <description>That’s with 88 percent of the counting complete.
The bigger story: Romney’s underperforming his 2008 results in key counties. Santorum outperforming Huckabee in 2008.

What does it all mean?
Conservatives and libertarians dominate the caucuses.
Romney is the choice of the Republican establishment. The cronies poured millions into his campaign even before he declared himself a conservative. He’s won endorsements from just about every big name general election loser include Bob Dole and George H.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>