<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eric holder on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/eric-holder/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eric holder on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 16:46:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/eric-holder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Have Just One Chance for October Surprise</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 16:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</guid>
      <description>The White House and its corrupt Department of Justice has one chance to change the election&amp;rsquo;s outcome.According to Nate Silver&amp;rsquo;s FiveThirtyEight blog, the GOP has a 62.1 percent chance of a Senate majority. With nine days left until the election, and with President Obama&amp;rsquo;s approval and likability plunging, the Democrats face a huge loss.
Apathetic Democrats Many political observers blame Democrat voter apathy, particularly among African-Americans. The black vote that swelled in 2008 and 2012 with Obama on the ballot shows signs of deflating in 2014 as it did in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Committed Massive Vote Fraud in 2008, They&#39;ll Do It Again in 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/22/democrats-committed-massive-vote-fraud-in-2008-theyll-do-it-again-in-2012-and-few-people-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 02:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/22/democrats-committed-massive-vote-fraud-in-2008-theyll-do-it-again-in-2012-and-few-people-care/</guid>
      <description>John McCain knew that Obama&amp;rsquo;s minions orchestrated massive voter fraud in Ohio and Pennsylvania. Besides using New Black Panther Party soldiers to repel McCain voters from the polls,** Democrats stuff ballot boxes to give Obama the win in two states with a combined 41 electoral votes**.

Here&amp;rsquo;s how a memo leaked by wikileaks summarized McCain&amp;rsquo;s election night decision:
 After discussions with his inner circle, which explains the delay in his speech, McCain decided not to pursue the voter fraud in PA and Ohio, despite his staff&amp;rsquo;s desire to make it an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Were You When Obama Nullified the Constitution?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>Most Americans know more about forensic evidence in the Casey Anthony case than they do about the Constitution. That ignorance gave Barack Obama the hubris to end constitutional government in the United States. He did it, and you probably didn’t even notice.
Over the course of a week, Barack Obama made a series of so-called recess appointments. In the process, he and his henchmen in Eric Holder’s Justice Department effectively nullified the US Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>