<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>new york times on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/new-york-times/</link>
    <description>Recent content in new york times on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 01:25:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/new-york-times/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the New York Times blackmailing FBI and CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 01:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</guid>
      <description>Sounds ridiculous, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
How could a reporter at New York Times blackmail an FBI or CIA agent?
Easily. And everyone who ever went through counter-espionage training knows it.
What Went Down This morning, British Prime Minister Theresa May chastised the US government. The UK freely shares anti-terrorism intelligence with the US. The US is expected to keep secrets secret.
But the US intel community is one gigantic sieve these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why Turning People Off Is A Terrible Idea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a cause’s worst enemies are its best friends.

In 1995, 56 percent of American described themselves as “pro-choice.” At the time, Michael Kinsley on CNN’s Crossfire declared the debate over.
Then something strange happened. Americans started changing their minds. The pro-life movement whittled away at public opinion.
By May of this year, Gallup found “pro-choice” to be at an all-time low:
 The 41% of Americans who now identify themselves as &amp;ldquo;pro-choice&amp;rdquo; is down from 47% last July and is one percentage point below the previous record low in Gallup trends, recorded in May 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Sums Up Everything I Believe Better Than I Ever Could</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/14/this-sums-up-everything-i-believe-better-than-i-ever-could/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 06:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/14/this-sums-up-everything-i-believe-better-than-i-ever-could/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;463&amp;rdquo;] Buckley (right) and L. Brent Bozell Jr. promote their book McCarthy and His Enemies, 1954 (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
The Liberal Kirsten Powers (my favorite liberal at times) described the leftist media&amp;rsquo;s mania as &amp;ldquo;absolutely, utterly insane.&amp;rdquo;
What triggered the maniacal insanity from MSNBC and The New York Times (among others) was Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s public dismay over the way Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s State Department responded to terror attacks on US embassies in Egypt and Libya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYT Describes Mayhem of “Taxmageddon”, And It Will Scare You Sick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</guid>
      <description>What the hell’s going on at NYT? First, they do a piece on Andrew Breitbart. Then they warn the world that Taxmageddon will crush the world in 2013, beginning with the USA.

Here&amp;rsquo;s how Business Insider summarized the David Leohardt article:
 Basically, with no changes to current law, taxes will rise for everyone, and after tax, inflation-adjusted income for the average American will drop to 1998 levels.
 Read more: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“[N]o one did it like Breitbart”</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/16/no-one-did-it-like-breitbart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/16/no-one-did-it-like-breitbart/</guid>
      <description>Last night, someone asked me, “who’s the most influential person in your iPhone contacts?”
“I don’t know,” I said. “Breitbart’s dead.”
David Carr writes in New York Times about the Life and Death of Andrew Breitbart.
Be advised that neither Carr nor NYT shares our political beliefs. And the tactics they cheer from the left, they attack when from the right. Funny how whenKaren Finney lies about Mitt Romney, it&amp;rsquo;s good journalism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>