<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supreme-Court on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/supreme-court/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supreme-Court on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 21:30:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/supreme-court/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Is the Only Viable Pro-Life Choice</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/09/trump-is-the-only-viable-pro-life-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 21:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/09/trump-is-the-only-viable-pro-life-choice/</guid>
      <description>Some pro-life activists like Erick Erickson are plotting ways to sabotage Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy for president. They probably haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped to think. If they succeed in defeating Trump, they will be culpable in many, many abortions. That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of guilt for a guy like Erickson to carry around, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Chances are Congress won&amp;rsquo;t introduce any major abortion laws in the next four years. That means the abortion battle will remain in the courts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Immigration Fans Need to Read Wong Kim Ark</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 04:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad that Donald Trump has inspired so many good conservatives to promote fantasies about the 14th Amendment.
The Supreme Court addressed the issue of birthright citizenship directly, and Mark Levin and Laura Ingram know it. They are Constitutional lawyers.
Both Levin and Ingraham are familiar with United States v. Wong Kim Ark (1898) which established, thoroughly, that citizenship by birth has been the law of the land since before the Declaration of Independence and was codified by the 14th Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Would Vote on Gay Marriage Cases</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/06/25/how-i-would-vote-on-gay-marriage-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 03:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/06/25/how-i-would-vote-on-gay-marriage-cases/</guid>
      <description>I’m not a lawyer. And I’m not particularly smart. But that doesn’t stop me from writing my opinion.
Rather, I’m a libertarian-ish conservative. I like a small central government that protects us from evil people in other countries and delivers mail. And prosecutes people who do great harm across state lines.
The Supreme Court has two big gay marriage cases pending. At issue:
  Do the people of California have the right to define marriage in their state?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Depression Be Your Guide</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/02/let-depression-be-your-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/02/let-depression-be-your-guide/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I gave you a reason to celebrate the Supreme Court’s decision. But I never said to let go of your anger or depression. ** That’s because we need creativity, focus, and action, and you get those through emotional distress. **

In his new best-selling book, Jonah Lehrer discusses the link between depression and creativity:
 This helps explain why Forgas has found that states of sadness— he induces the downcast mood with a film about death and cancer— also correlate with better writing samples; subjects compose sentences that are clearer and more compelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What’s Great About the Supreme Court’s Obamacare Decision</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</guid>
      <description>In the Ronald Reagan movie Kings Row, Reagan plays Drake McHugh, whose legs are sawn off by a sadistic, class-conscious doctor.

Everyone remembers the line “Where’s the rest of me?” No remembers what happens after that. I’ll fill you in.
McHugh’s best friend, a psychiatrist, decides to tell McHugh (Reagan) the truth: his legs were perfectly healthy, but the doctor cut them off to keep the lower class McHugh from pursuing the doctor’s debutante daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare Ruling Comes Down This Week, and We’re Having a Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/24/obamacare-ruling-comes-down-this-week-and-were-having-a-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 18:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/24/obamacare-ruling-comes-down-this-week-and-were-having-a-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Pack clothes, flags, and signs for an Obamacare Tea Party at Forest Park on Art Hill this week. The rally will begin at 7:00 PM on the day the Supreme Court rules.

We don’t know the day, but we do know the time: 7:00 pm in Forest Park on Art Hill (map below). The most likely days are Monday or Thursday, but because of the magnitude of this case, it could be any day of the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCaskillPAC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/25/mccaskillpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 03:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/25/mccaskillpac/</guid>
      <description>What I find so funny about Claire McCaskill&amp;rsquo;s war on super pacs is that her husband is a super PAC.
For the record, I have formally endorsed Senator McCaskill in her race to return to private life.
Zimmerman Update Having declared George Zimmerman guilty of first degree, racially motivated murder, the MSM are now investigating the case.
What they&amp;rsquo;re finding:
 The George Zimmerman that Francescani describes is quite different from the &amp;ldquo;delusional racist vigilante&amp;rdquo; that many have made him out to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Votes on Obamacare Today</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</guid>
      <description>We won’t know the result until late June, most likely. And the results of today’s vote could change by then.

Still, it’s sort of weird that after three years of public, wildly emotional and stupifyingly complex arguments, the fate of the republic comes down to a short meeting in Washington involving nine people in a paneled room.
Mark Sherman of AP describes the cloistered scene:
 After months of anticipation, thousands of pages of briefs and more than six hours of arguments, the justices will vote on the fate of President Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s health care overhaul in under an hour Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Impossible to Exaggerate the Historical Importance of the Supreme Court’s ObamaCare Decision</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/its-impossible-to-exaggerate-the-historical-importance-of-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/its-impossible-to-exaggerate-the-historical-importance-of-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</guid>
      <description>When the Supreme Court releases its opinion on the ObamaCare case, America will change fundamentally. This is the most important case to the future of the republic since the Great Depression or the Civil War.
 If the court upholds ObamaCare, it will end the principle of government limited by a written Constitution. Anthony Kennedy and Antonin Scalia said as much. A vote by Kennedy to uphold the legislation, then, would be a vote for unlimited government power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Will Also Decide the Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-supreme-court-will-also-decide-the-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-supreme-court-will-also-decide-the-election/</guid>
      <description>When the Supreme Court rules on ObamaCare, it will define Barack Obama as either a winner or loser.

James Carville says overturning ObamaCare would be the best thing that could happen to Democrats. I think he’s wrong.
ObamaCare is the centerpiece of Obama’s term in office. He put all of America’s business on hold for a year to pass it. He coerced, lied, intimidated, and threatened to get the law passed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why People Are Being Unfair to Donald Verrilli</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/why-people-are-being-unfair-to-donal-verrilli/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 04:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/why-people-are-being-unfair-to-donal-verrilli/</guid>
      <description>Everyone (including me) is cracking on Donald Verrilli, Obama’s Solicitor General. He figuratively died on the biggest legal stage in the world today. Here’s a sample of the left’s reaction to Verrilli’s performance:
Mother Jones:
 Solicitor General Donald B. Verrilli Jr. should be grateful to the Supreme Court for refusing to allow cameras in the courtroom, because his defense of Obamacare on Tuesday may go down as one of the most spectacular flameouts in the history of the court.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg’s Crappy Argument In Support of ObamaCare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/ruth-bader-ginsbergs-crappy-argument-in-support-of-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 00:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/ruth-bader-ginsbergs-crappy-argument-in-support-of-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>I’m often amazed at the weakness of arguments before the Supreme Court. Today, Ruth Bader Ginsburg, attempting to help out the Obama Administration’s fumbling solicitor-general, made the weakest argument I’ve ever heard.
First,Ginsburg statement:
 Mr. Verrilli, I thought that your main point is that, unlike food or any other market, when you made the choice not to buy insurance, even though you have every intent in the world to self-insure, to save for it, when disaster strikes, you may not have the money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Have Hearings</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/30/why-we-have-hearings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 01:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/30/why-we-have-hearings/</guid>
      <description>Elena Kagan reminds me of Norm Peterson’s (Cheers) meltdown in front the brewery president just before he landed his dream job as a beer taster. Poor Elena can’t remember the simplest things—like her own handwriting.
 
Today, Democrat Arlen Specter warned that he may have to vote “no.”
She might not be the infanticidal maniac some claim. Instead, she seems to be devoid of any substantial legal thought whatsoever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of the Tenth Amendment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/28/the-story-of-the-tenth-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2007 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/28/the-story-of-the-tenth-amendment/</guid>
      <description>**Note: Please read the entire store by clicking on the title or the Continue Reading link below. **
Those of us whose conservative conversions occured in the late 1970s and early 1980s, I think, are particularly fascinated by the 10th Amendment to the Constitution. We also mourn over its senseless destruction by Congress, courts, and citizens.
 The powers not delegated to the United States by the Constitution, nor prohibited by it to the States, are reserved for the States respectively, or to the people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>