<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supreme-Court on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/supreme-court/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supreme-Court on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 21:30:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/supreme-court/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Is the Only Viable Pro-Life Choice</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/09/trump-is-the-only-viable-pro-life-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 21:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/09/trump-is-the-only-viable-pro-life-choice/</guid>
      <description>Some pro-life activists like Erick Erickson are plotting ways to sabotage Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy for president. They probably haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped to think. If they succeed in defeating Trump, they will be culpable in many, many abortions. That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of guilt for a guy like Erickson to carry around, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Chances are Congress won&amp;rsquo;t introduce any major abortion laws in the next four years. That means the abortion battle will remain in the courts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Immigration Fans Need to Read Wong Kim Ark</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 04:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad that Donald Trump has inspired so many good conservatives to promote fantasies about the 14th Amendment.
The Supreme Court addressed the issue of birthright citizenship directly, and Mark Levin and Laura Ingram know it. They are Constitutional lawyers.
Both Levin and Ingraham are familiar with United States v. Wong Kim Ark (1898) which established, thoroughly, that citizenship by birth has been the law of the land since before the Declaration of Independence and was codified by the 14th Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Would Vote on Gay Marriage Cases</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/06/25/how-i-would-vote-on-gay-marriage-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 03:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/06/25/how-i-would-vote-on-gay-marriage-cases/</guid>
      <description>I’m not a lawyer. And I’m not particularly smart. But that doesn’t stop me from writing my opinion.
Rather, I’m a libertarian-ish conservative. I like a small central government that protects us from evil people in other countries and delivers mail. And prosecutes people who do great harm across state lines.
The Supreme Court has two big gay marriage cases pending. At issue:
  Do the people of California have the right to define marriage in their state?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Depression Be Your Guide</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/02/let-depression-be-your-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/02/let-depression-be-your-guide/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I gave you a reason to celebrate the Supreme Court’s decision. But I never said to let go of your anger or depression. ** That’s because we need creativity, focus, and action, and you get those through emotional distress. **

In his new best-selling book, Jonah Lehrer discusses the link between depression and creativity:
 This helps explain why Forgas has found that states of sadness— he induces the downcast mood with a film about death and cancer— also correlate with better writing samples; subjects compose sentences that are clearer and more compelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What’s Great About the Supreme Court’s Obamacare Decision</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</guid>
      <description>In the Ronald Reagan movie Kings Row, Reagan plays Drake McHugh, whose legs are sawn off by a sadistic, class-conscious doctor.

Everyone remembers the line “Where’s the rest of me?” No remembers what happens after that. I’ll fill you in.
McHugh’s best friend, a psychiatrist, decides to tell McHugh (Reagan) the truth: his legs were perfectly healthy, but the doctor cut them off to keep the lower class McHugh from pursuing the doctor’s debutante daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>