<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Heritage Action on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/heritage-action/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Heritage Action on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 12:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/heritage-action/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I am honored to question the GOP candidates for you and Heritage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-am-honored-to-question-the-gop-candidates-for-you-and-heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 12:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-am-honored-to-question-the-gop-candidates-for-you-and-heritage/</guid>
      <description>This is pretty cool and a little unnerving.
Heritage Action has extended the honor to be one of three Heritage Action Sentinels to question Republican Presidential candidates on Friday, September 17 in Greenville, South Carolina. So far, 12 candidates have confirmed, including Donald Trump, Jeb Bush, Ben Carson, Carly Fiorina, Ted Cruz, Scott Walker, Rick Santorum, Bobby Jindal, Rand Paul, Chris Christie, and Marco Rubio. (Maybe Trump will make fun of my tie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatever Happened to the Party of Ideas?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</guid>
      <description>From about 1978 until the Monica Lewinsky fiasco, the GOP was called &amp;ldquo;the party of ideas.&amp;rdquo; I miss the ideas.
William F. Buckley helped. Buckley liked big ideas and smart people. He liked politicians who gave legs to great ideas and governors with the guts to experiment. Governor Ronald Reagan appeared on Buckley&amp;rsquo;s Firing Line shortly after the Gipper became California&amp;rsquo;s governor. Reagan talked about many ideas he was trying or hoping to try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Ann Wagner Is Wrong to Attack Heritage Action</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 02:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</guid>
      <description>Accountability? We don&amp;rsquo;t need no stinking accountability.
 No, Ann Wagner didn&amp;rsquo;t actually say that. But her comments to a 2nd District Republican committee meeting on Tuesday gave at least one attendee the impression that Mrs. Wagner opposes the idea of conservatives holding Congress accountable.
Ann Wagner Attacks the Conservative Heritage Action Rep. Ann Wagner accused the conservative Heritage Action for America of &amp;ldquo;pitting Republican against Republican&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;never attacking Dems&amp;rdquo; at the Republican meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Will Not Vote for Ann Wagner in 2014</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/21/will-not-vote-for-wagner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/21/will-not-vote-for-wagner/</guid>
      <description>There is a tide in the affairs of men. Which, taken at the flood, leads on to fortune; Omitted, all the voyage of their life Is bound in shallows and in miseries. On such a full sea are we now afloat, And we must take the current when it serves, Or lose our ventures.
 Julius Caesar Act 4, scene 3, 218–224
 The problem the Republican Party has, too many people are sitting around, waiting for a wave to take them across the election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: Ronald Reagan Wants the Transportation Empowerment Act</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/13/ronald-reagan-wants-transportation-empowerment-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 13:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/13/ronald-reagan-wants-transportation-empowerment-act/</guid>
      <description>Want to fix Missouri&amp;rsquo;s roads and cut taxes at the same time? Well, two American conservative icons showed us the way almost 50 years ago.
The Establishment likes to attack grassroots conservatives by claiming Reagan would have opposed the Tea Party. They&amp;rsquo;re wrong, of course, and the Transportation Empowerment Act tells us why.
In 1967, shortly after Ronald Reagan became governor of California, William F. Buckley Jr. asked Governor Reagan if was even possible to be an effective governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Your Calendar for June 19</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/04/mark-calendar-june-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 03:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/04/mark-calendar-june-19/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Ben Evans of Heritage Action for America and Michelle Moore of St. Louis Tea Party Coalition, you have a treat coming on June 19.

Heritage Action/St. Louis Tea Party Social: June 19 On Thursday, June 19 at 6:30pm, we will gather informally at Scarecrow in Chesterfield, 1095 Chesterfield Parkway. All are welcome. Appetizers will be provided. Come down and enjoy the company of fellow grassroots activists.
If you have friends who think Tea Partiers are &amp;ldquo;too extreme&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;racist&amp;rdquo; or whatever, bring them along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>