<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brexit on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/brexit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in brexit on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 17:19:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/brexit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Second-Born Twin Can Be Older Than the First</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/12/how-the-second-born-twin-can-be-older-than-the-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 17:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/12/how-the-second-born-twin-can-be-older-than-the-first/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever noticed that twins have a pecking order? Even identical twins born minutes apart show a subtle seniority complex. Usually the first-born twin leads the second-born.
Makes you wonder how these Peterson twins will relate to each other, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Because of the time change at the end of daylight saving time, the second-born twin is officially older than the first. That&amp;rsquo;ll be interesting to watch. And if you find yourself pondering the oddness of those twins&amp;rsquo; birth order, you can easily find yourself pondering America&amp;rsquo;s little sister relationship to the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dethroning the Pointy-Haired Bosses of the Universe</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/26/dethroning-the-pointy-haired-bosses-of-the-universe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/26/dethroning-the-pointy-haired-bosses-of-the-universe/</guid>
      <description>Okay, let me explain this in the simplest possible way&amp;hellip;
 you&amp;hellip;are&amp;hellip;an&amp;hellip;idiot.
&amp;ndash;Scott Adams, Dilbert
 Lately&amp;hellip;the Peter Principle has given way to the &amp;ldquo;Dilbert Principle.&amp;rdquo; The basic concept of the Dilbert Principle is that the most ineffective workers are systematically moved to the place where they can do the least damage: management.
 ― Scott Adams, The Dilbert Principle: A Cubicle&amp;rsquo;s-Eye View of Bosses, Meetings, Management Fads &amp;amp; Other Workplace Afflictions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God Bless the Brits! Freedom Rings!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/23/god-bless-the-brits-freedom-rings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 03:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/23/god-bless-the-brits-freedom-rings/</guid>
      <description>As an American, I am proud of the people from whose loins our nation sprang. United Kingdom has voted to leave the European Union. The Brits rejected globalist, elitist threats and insults to vote for independence. Like America did in 1776.
Savor this moment in history. You were alive to see a nation reject foreign tyranny. Every Brit who voted LEAVE showed courage and love of freedom. God bless them all.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>