<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>taxes on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/taxes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in taxes on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:11:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/taxes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a New Blog</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2018-11-23-99th-time-the-charm-for-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2018-11-23-99th-time-the-charm-for-bill/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s see if this works, shall we?
I spent all day moving my blog from a self-hosted Wordpress site to a Hugo static site. Since I no longer support advertising, I don&amp;rsquo;t need all the weight of Wordpress. Plus, managing a blog through Github is actually easier for me. I use git professionally. And I pretty much think in Markdown at this point.
The final reason for the move is the change in direction for this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Interest Rates Hid True Cost of Increasing Debt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/12/low-interest-rates-hid-true-cost-of-increasing-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/12/low-interest-rates-hid-true-cost-of-increasing-debt/</guid>
      <description>House mortgage-type instrument suggested as means to pay off national debt
Guest Post By Lee A. Presser
Interest rates have been held artificially low by the Federal Reserve since 2008. This has had the effect of hiding the true cost of increasing debt. As interest rates rise back toward 4%, the U.S. Treasury will have less money to spend on discretionary governmental functions.
The FY 2015 budget is approximately $3,900,000,000,000.00. Another way to look at that number is about $12,187.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s How I&#39;m Voting August 5 (with printable grid of ballot measures) *Update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/31/im-voting-august-5-primary-printable-grid-ballot-initiatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/31/im-voting-august-5-primary-printable-grid-ballot-initiatives/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think being a political animal of sorts, election season would be my favorite time of year.
It&amp;rsquo;s not. I hate elections.
I hate the crappy, predictable radio ads (above all else). I know, they do it because it works. Well, not really, but I&amp;rsquo;m not going to give a free marketing statistics lesson here. (No one has any idea if the campaign formula works, because no body ever tries anything different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Obama&#39;s Julia Like Pristomyrmex Punctatus?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/obamas-julia-like-pristomyrmex-punctatus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 01:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/obamas-julia-like-pristomyrmex-punctatus/</guid>
      <description>Before I answer that, a little science.
Scientists study all kinds of things. One thing they study is ants, because ants teach a lot about communities.
In a recent study published in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, ecologists Shigeto Dobata and Kazuki Tsuji studied the effects of &amp;ldquo;cheaters&amp;rdquo; in a colony of Pristomyrmex Punctatus ants.
P. Punctati segment their society into two groups by age. Younger ants tend to hang around the house reproducing asexually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Tax Code: The Fustercluck From Which Everything Rancid Crawls</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/02/our-tax-code-the-fustercluck-from-which-everything-rancid-crawls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 01:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/02/our-tax-code-the-fustercluck-from-which-everything-rancid-crawls/</guid>
      <description>William F. Buckley proposed a simple tax reform in 1973. The language barrier that separates people like Buckley from that odd species we call Congress prevented his thoughts from finding fertile soil. And in the 40 years between, the tax code has become only murkier and more dangerous.

“Our tax laws were,” Buckley wrote in _Four Reforms: A Guide for the Seventies, “_designed historically to raise revenue for the operations of government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYT Describes Mayhem of “Taxmageddon”, And It Will Scare You Sick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/19/nyt-describes-mayhem-of-taxmageddon/</guid>
      <description>What the hell’s going on at NYT? First, they do a piece on Andrew Breitbart. Then they warn the world that Taxmageddon will crush the world in 2013, beginning with the USA.

Here&amp;rsquo;s how Business Insider summarized the David Leohardt article:
 Basically, with no changes to current law, taxes will rise for everyone, and after tax, inflation-adjusted income for the average American will drop to 1998 levels.
 Read more: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: Rick Santelli Destroys The Buffett Rule Live on CNBC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/video-rick-santelli-destroys-the-buffett-rule-live-on-cnbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 18:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/video-rick-santelli-destroys-the-buffett-rule-live-on-cnbc/</guid>
      <description>The man who&amp;rsquo;s 2009 rant inspired the Tea Party movement shreds Obama&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;soak the rich&amp;rdquo; plan. Shreds I said. [youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bfRxFFhhWnk] Santelli Crushes Buffett Rule
There is no tax solution to America&amp;rsquo;s spending problem. Each additional dollar confiscated from the economy to feed the Washington bureaucracy results in an additional $1.40 in new spending.
Washington IS THE PROBLEM!
Starve the monster. Bleed the monster. But** Don&amp;rsquo;t Feed the Monster!**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Ways Warren Buffett Can Take Personal Responsibility and Stop Relying on Government to Solve His Problems</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/15/5-ways-warren-buffett-can-take-personal-responsibility-and-stop-relying-on-government-to-solve-his-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/15/5-ways-warren-buffett-can-take-personal-responsibility-and-stop-relying-on-government-to-solve-his-problems/</guid>
      <description>Warren Buffett makes the erroneous claim that he pays less in taxes than does his secretary. He claims that the government thus “coddles” the rich. He asks the government to increase his taxes, and the taxes of others like him, as if he is incapable of doing that on his own.
Buffett is half right. He proves that government coddles people by** asking the government to solve his problem of guilt**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Your FICA Score?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/20/whats-your-fica-score/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/20/whats-your-fica-score/</guid>
      <description>Your FICO score is a number between 380 and 820 (or something like that) that banks use to determine your credit worthiness. The higher your FICO score, the better.
But that’s not what I’m talking about here.
I’m talking about your FICA score.

Your FICA score is the minimum payment on your federal loan.
You didn’t know you had a federal loan? You do.
If you’re 18 years old, you owe the federal government about $46,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>80 Percent of Americans Read This Blog Every Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/16/80-percent-of-americans-read-this-blog-every-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2011 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/16/80-percent-of-americans-read-this-blog-every-day/</guid>
      <description>I’ll be honest with you: I’ve lied.
Usually out of desperation. I’ve lied to those closest to me—those most willing to forgive the thing I lied about.
I’ve also told the truth to my own detriment. In the long run, the latter works best. In fact, telling the truth works best in the short run, too.
So maybe Obama’s desperate. Maybe he knows that the debt ceiling debate is the beginning of the unraveling of Americum Sovieticum, his life-long dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reason TV Destroys Hillary Clinton’s Tax Theories</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/reason-tv-destroys-hillary-clintons-tax-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 21:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/reason-tv-destroys-hillary-clintons-tax-theories/</guid>
      <description>Hillary Clinton opened her mouth this week—the same mouth that she insisted on opening during the campaign, resulting in our most corrupt and juvenile president ever.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wzg0dGrfP60&amp;amp;color1;=0xb1b1b1&amp;amp;color2;=0xd0d0d0&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;feature;=player_embedded&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bush Policies Balancing Budget</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/11/bush-policies-balancing-budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2007 16:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/11/bush-policies-balancing-budget/</guid>
      <description>The White House announced yesterday that the 2008 budget deficit would be smaller than originally projected, as will the 2007 deficit. The reasons: 1) the economy is strong and 2) tax cuts stimulate taxable economic activity.
We&amp;rsquo;ve know that that tax cuts increase federal revenue (to a point) since John F. Kennedy explained it in 1961. The Laffer Curve was the final word on the subject and should have earned Arthur Laffer the Nobel Prize for economics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>