<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>taxes on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/taxes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in taxes on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:11:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/taxes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a New Blog</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2018-11-23-99th-time-the-charm-for-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2018-11-23-99th-time-the-charm-for-bill/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s see if this works, shall we?
I spent all day moving my blog from a self-hosted Wordpress site to a Hugo static site. Since I no longer support advertising, I don&amp;rsquo;t need all the weight of Wordpress. Plus, managing a blog through Github is actually easier for me. I use git professionally. And I pretty much think in Markdown at this point.
The final reason for the move is the change in direction for this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Interest Rates Hid True Cost of Increasing Debt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/12/low-interest-rates-hid-true-cost-of-increasing-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/12/low-interest-rates-hid-true-cost-of-increasing-debt/</guid>
      <description>House mortgage-type instrument suggested as means to pay off national debt
Guest Post By Lee A. Presser
Interest rates have been held artificially low by the Federal Reserve since 2008. This has had the effect of hiding the true cost of increasing debt. As interest rates rise back toward 4%, the U.S. Treasury will have less money to spend on discretionary governmental functions.
The FY 2015 budget is approximately $3,900,000,000,000.00. Another way to look at that number is about $12,187.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s How I&#39;m Voting August 5 (with printable grid of ballot measures) *Update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/31/im-voting-august-5-primary-printable-grid-ballot-initiatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/31/im-voting-august-5-primary-printable-grid-ballot-initiatives/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think being a political animal of sorts, election season would be my favorite time of year.
It&amp;rsquo;s not. I hate elections.
I hate the crappy, predictable radio ads (above all else). I know, they do it because it works. Well, not really, but I&amp;rsquo;m not going to give a free marketing statistics lesson here. (No one has any idea if the campaign formula works, because no body ever tries anything different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is Obama&#39;s Julia Like Pristomyrmex Punctatus?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/obamas-julia-like-pristomyrmex-punctatus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 01:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/obamas-julia-like-pristomyrmex-punctatus/</guid>
      <description>Before I answer that, a little science.
Scientists study all kinds of things. One thing they study is ants, because ants teach a lot about communities.
In a recent study published in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, ecologists Shigeto Dobata and Kazuki Tsuji studied the effects of &amp;ldquo;cheaters&amp;rdquo; in a colony of Pristomyrmex Punctatus ants.
P. Punctati segment their society into two groups by age. Younger ants tend to hang around the house reproducing asexually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Tax Code: The Fustercluck From Which Everything Rancid Crawls</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/02/our-tax-code-the-fustercluck-from-which-everything-rancid-crawls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 01:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/02/our-tax-code-the-fustercluck-from-which-everything-rancid-crawls/</guid>
      <description>William F. Buckley proposed a simple tax reform in 1973. The language barrier that separates people like Buckley from that odd species we call Congress prevented his thoughts from finding fertile soil. And in the 40 years between, the tax code has become only murkier and more dangerous.

“Our tax laws were,” Buckley wrote in _Four Reforms: A Guide for the Seventies, “_designed historically to raise revenue for the operations of government.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>