<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Islamofascism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/islamofascism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Islamofascism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 05:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/islamofascism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Caves to Fanatical Left</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/22/obama-caves-to-fanatical-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 05:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/22/obama-caves-to-fanatical-left/</guid>
      <description>Obama Intelligence Pick Torpedoed By Bloggers - FOXNews.com Transition Tracker
 John Brennan, Obama&amp;rsquo;s chief intelligence adviser and anticipated CIA chief, was recently forced to withdraw his name. There was no drumbeat of opposition to Brennan from the front pages or on cable. Rather, the pick was torpedoed by the blogosphere.
 &amp;ldquo;Apparently there is a lot of pressure on the Obama team from a blog saying that Brennan couldn&amp;rsquo;t be made the director of the CIA because he was involved in torture and renditions, which he wasn&amp;rsquo;t,&amp;rdquo; said Mark Lowenthal, former assistant CIA director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disgraceful, Selfish Cowards  *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/28/disgraceful-selfish-cowards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 04:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/28/disgraceful-selfish-cowards/</guid>
      <description>Liberal America is a sub-species of selfish cowards.
India suffered its own 9-11 over the past 3 days. It continues at this hour. Yet America&amp;rsquo;s government, its media, its pundits retreated under the cover of Thanksgiving and the excuse of saving their corrupt and incompetent friends on Wall Street and in Detroit. George Bush and Barack Obama are invisible. CNN and MSNBC refused to call the terrorists who murdered over 160 in cold blood anything stronger than &amp;ldquo;militants.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>