<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rasmussen on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/rasmussen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rasmussen on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 09:21:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/rasmussen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Have No Idea How Much Your Boss Pays in Payroll Taxes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/you-have-no-idea-how-much-your-boss-pays-in-payroll-taxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 09:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/you-have-no-idea-how-much-your-boss-pays-in-payroll-taxes/</guid>
      <description>America is suffocating under an amazing tax burden, but most Americans STILL underestimate how much their tax bill really is. That’s because Washington has done a fantastic job of forcing employers to hide most of the taxes you pay. If people had to see and deal with their total liability, the Democratic Party would be swept into the dust bin of history.

Here are some frightening facts from Rasmussen:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Overconfidence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/21/how-to-avoid-overconfidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 00:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/21/how-to-avoid-overconfidence/</guid>
      <description>Do you worry that conservative grassroots might get overconfident and blow our chance to stop the advance of socialism in America?
I do. I am concerned that we keep repeating the same tactics to the same audiences until both the audience and the actors become . . . well, bored.
When I read stories like this one, that GOP sentiment is at an all-time high, I worry that some on our side might decide they can go back to their regularly scheduled programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Message Sinking In</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/28/tea-party-message-sinking-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 22:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/28/tea-party-message-sinking-in/</guid>
      <description>Rasmussen&amp;rsquo;s weekly report shows the Tea Party message of limited government and lower taxes is hitting home with voters.
Tax Cuts: More voters than ever now say tax cuts help the economy. Over 60 percent now agree with JFK, Reagan, Bush, and the undeniable facts of economic history: cutting taxes increases GDP and personal wealth.  A separate survey released earlier today found that 66% of voters think the president is likely to raise taxes on those who make less than $250,000 per year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rasmussen Poll Shows Dead Head</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/13/rasmussen-poll-shows-dead-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 16:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/13/rasmussen-poll-shows-dead-head/</guid>
      <description>Rasmussen&amp;rsquo;s presidential tracking poll shows a dead heat between Democrat Barack Obama and Republican Presidential Candidate John McCain (h/t Drudge). This poll confirms the Newsweek poll showing the two in a statistical dead heat.
Moreover, according Rasmussen, McCain enjoys higher favorability ratings than Obama.
Considering that McCain has received little media attention since the last Democrat primary in June, Obama&amp;rsquo;s 15 percentage point drop can only be blamed on Obama&amp;rsquo;s dismal performance as a candidate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>