<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>republican on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/republican/</link>
    <description>Recent content in republican on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 12:06:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/republican/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Truths of Republicans and Race</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/07/forbidden-truths-of-republicans-and-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/07/forbidden-truths-of-republicans-and-race/</guid>
      <description>Republicans hate race. Race has been bad for the GOP ever since Republicans passed the Civil Rights Act of 1964. See, Lyndon Johnson was a Democrat, and he proposed the Civil Rights Act of 1964. Most Democrats violently opposed the bill. But most Republicans supported it. The bill passed, of course, and it survived many Supreme Court challenges.
The Civil Rights Act&amp;rsquo;s aim was to wring racist behavior out of American life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did the Pritzkers Donate to Greitens?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, the blog Progressives Today ran an attack piece on Eric Greitens for two of his donors (link). The piece generated of lot angst and fury on the right side of social media.
**Turns out the story was pretty shoddy journalism. **
Progressives Today didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to look at the Pritzkers&amp;rsquo; other donations or the military museum they founded. If they had, they&amp;rsquo;d know that Jennifer N. Pritzker (formerly James N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fill the Cabinet</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/fill-the-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/fill-the-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>My friend Scott Oppelt mentioned his complaint that the GOP has so many great candidates all at once. Why can&amp;rsquo;t they be spread out over 20 years?
Great question. History being what it is, we can&amp;rsquo;t spread them across time, only across government. So this week&amp;rsquo;s poll is a little fun.
The rules:
You must fill the next White House cabinet using only the current candidates for President. You do not know who the President or Vice President is, so assume it&amp;rsquo;s none of the current candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missouri Republicans Made Jay Nixon Look Like a Statesman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 01:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/05/missouri-republicans-made-jay-nixon-look-like-statesman/</guid>
      <description>You know how reckless and tone-deaf Obama is about Army deserters? Missouri&amp;rsquo;s House and Senate Republican leaders are just as clueless and irresponsible about money.
Yes, I said it: the Missouri Republican legislature is about as conservative and principled as Susan Rice on a Sunday talk show.
By going on a votes-for-cash spending spree on the last day of the General Assembly, the House and Senate handed Jay &amp;ldquo;Idiot&amp;rdquo; Nixon a PR prize worth its weight in pork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah Goldberg Perfectly Defines the GOP Establishment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 18:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</guid>
      <description>I hope you read Jonah Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s short article on National Review Online last week. If not, you missed the best definition of Establishment Republicans EVER!
Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s piece also exploded the myth of &amp;ldquo;pro-business&amp;rdquo; way too many conservatives believe. Conservatism isn&amp;rsquo;t pro-business, it&amp;rsquo;s pro-market. I&amp;rsquo;ll let Jonah explain:
 Just to clarify, the difference between being pro-business and pro-market is categorical. A politician who is a “friend of business” is exactly that, a guy who does favors for his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>