<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faith on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/faith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faith on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 05:01:43 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/faith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Survivors Will Envy the Dead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/survivors-will-envy-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 05:01:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/survivors-will-envy-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>What kind of world will emerge from the coronavirus shutdown?
People have gleefully surrendered amazing new powers to governments. We have erected barriers between ourselves and all other humans on the planet. We have surrendered all of our rights, including the First Amendment. We have abandoned religion. The Catholic Church has ordered its priests to disobey Christ&amp;rsquo;s Great Commission by prohibiting baptisms. We have shut down every business that isn&amp;rsquo;t part of a global enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do We Deserve Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/do-we-deserve-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 08:14:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/do-we-deserve-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Do We Deserve Freedom?
You probably know people who are concerned about a &amp;ldquo;surveillance state&amp;rdquo; developing. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re one of them. I know I am.
It&amp;rsquo;s a reasonable fear.
Some police departments are using drones to spy on people in their homes, peering into living rooms and bedrooms with digital cameras and fining or arresting people who have more than the imposed limit of guests. The justification the state gives for these intrusions is, of course, coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Mass for the 5th Sunday of Lent</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/holy-mass-for-the-5th-sunday-of-lent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 18:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/holy-mass-for-the-5th-sunday-of-lent/</guid>
      <description>Bishops have banned public Masses, but that hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped the Mass, especially the Traditional Latin Mass.
Monsignor Eugene Morris of the Oratory of Ss. Gregory and Augustine is livestreaming the Holy Mass each Sunday at 8:00 a.m. You can watch live on the Oratory&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page.
How to Get the Most from the Mass in Time of Pestilence Msgr. Morris has published a guide to keeping the Mass holy in this time of pestilence as we watch from home instead of participating in the pews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus Isn&#39;t Finally Important. This Is</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/coronavirus-isnt-finally-important-this-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:06:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/coronavirus-isnt-finally-important-this-is/</guid>
      <description>“Conservatism is the tacit acknowledgement that all that is finally important in human experience is behind us; that the crucial explorations have been undertaken, and that it is given to man to know what are the great truths that emerged from them.”
— William F. Buckley Jr.
Moments ago, I caught myself engrossed in a long news story about the goings on in the United States Senate over the two-trillion dollar coronavirus stimulus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Mass for 4th Sunday of Lent </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/holy-mass-for-4th-sunday-of-lent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 15:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/holy-mass-for-4th-sunday-of-lent/</guid>
      <description>Monsignor Eugene Morris livestreamed his private Mass for the fourth Sunday in Lent today. The Mass is preceded by the Most Holy Rosary of the Blessed Virgin Mary.
Monsignor&amp;rsquo;s wonderful homily is worth sharing with everyone you know.
I apologize that I did not see this earlier.
  You will see why I fell in love with the Oratory of Ss. Gregory and Augustine. You can Like their Facebook page to keep track of future livestreamed Masses here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>