<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faith on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/faith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faith on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 12:11:33 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/faith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Should Christians Prepare for and Respond to New World Order</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/how-should-christians-prepare-for-and-respond-to-new-world-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 12:11:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/how-should-christians-prepare-for-and-respond-to-new-world-order/</guid>
      <description>A recurring theme in the Old Testament went something like this: the people of God (Jews) face a temporal crisis. The people of God surrender to a pagan nation, paying tribute to both the foreigners and to their gods.
Most of the chosen people assimilate with their earthly masters. During the Babylonian Exile, they largely abandoned circumcision and most of the Mosaic laws. The Temple was given over to orgies and terrible sacrilege.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Priests Gamble With Your Soul, and What You can Do About It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/water-gun-baptism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 15:07:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/water-gun-baptism/</guid>
      <description>Could anything be more entertaining than watching a &amp;ldquo;woke&amp;rdquo; priest mock his own religion and its sacraments by spraying an infant with a water gun in the sanctuary?
        Yet, this is where the &amp;ldquo;reforms&amp;rdquo; of Vatican II have landed us. Satan himself has more respect for God than these vested buffoons who use Coronavirus as an excuse to mock God, mock His Church, and mock the seven Holy Sacraments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survivors Will Envy the Dead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/survivors-will-envy-the-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 05:01:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/survivors-will-envy-the-dead/</guid>
      <description>What kind of world will emerge from the coronavirus shutdown?
People have gleefully surrendered amazing new powers to governments. We have erected barriers between ourselves and all other humans on the planet. We have surrendered all of our rights, including the First Amendment. We have abandoned religion. The Catholic Church has ordered its priests to disobey Christ&amp;rsquo;s Great Commission by prohibiting baptisms. We have shut down every business that isn&amp;rsquo;t part of a global enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do We Deserve Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/do-we-deserve-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 08:14:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/do-we-deserve-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Do We Deserve Freedom?
You probably know people who are concerned about a &amp;ldquo;surveillance state&amp;rdquo; developing. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re one of them. I know I am.
It&amp;rsquo;s a reasonable fear.
Some police departments are using drones to spy on people in their homes, peering into living rooms and bedrooms with digital cameras and fining or arresting people who have more than the imposed limit of guests. The justification the state gives for these intrusions is, of course, coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Mass for the 5th Sunday of Lent</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/holy-mass-for-the-5th-sunday-of-lent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 18:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/holy-mass-for-the-5th-sunday-of-lent/</guid>
      <description>Bishops have banned public Masses, but that hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped the Mass, especially the Traditional Latin Mass.
Monsignor Eugene Morris of the Oratory of Ss. Gregory and Augustine is livestreaming the Holy Mass each Sunday at 8:00 a.m. You can watch live on the Oratory&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page.
How to Get the Most from the Mass in Time of Pestilence Msgr. Morris has published a guide to keeping the Mass holy in this time of pestilence as we watch from home instead of participating in the pews.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>