<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>social security on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/social-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in social security on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 17:52:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/social-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are Entitled to Nothing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/22/you-are-entitled-to-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 17:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/22/you-are-entitled-to-nothing/</guid>
      <description>I know &amp;ldquo;House of Cards&amp;rdquo; character Frank Underwood is fictitious, malicious, and evil.
But even an evil fictitious character can hit the nail on its head occasionally.
https://youtu.be/QgTIhT5aLCg
We might not like his prescription, but he diagnoses America&amp;rsquo;s chief problem more concretely, more accurately, and more honestly than any American politician ever has. Ever.
 We’ve been crippled by Social Security, Medicare, Medicaid, by welfare, by entitlements. And that is the root of the problem: entitlements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kudos to President Obama For Touching the Third Rail</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/11/kudos-to-president-obama-for-touching-the-third-rail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 05:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/11/kudos-to-president-obama-for-touching-the-third-rail/</guid>
      <description>President Obama submitted a budget wildly out of balance that increases taxes across the board. But he also stuck his tongue on the infamous ‘third rail’ of American politics by proposing chained CPI for calculating Social Security cost of living increases. Bravo.
We’ve Been Asking For This Economic conservatives have pointed out for years that America’s entitlement programs are bankrupting the country.** The $100 trillion in unfunded liabilities can’t go on**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money Problems? Borrow Your Kids’ Social Security Numbers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/18/money-problems-borrow-your-kids-social-security-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/18/money-problems-borrow-your-kids-social-security-numbers/</guid>
      <description>Why not?
Kids have a clean slate when it comes to credit scores. Sure, they don’t have a long history, but you can help with that.
And you can buy that 56-inch 3D LED TV you’ve been craving. In a few months, you might even be able to buy a new car—on your kid’s credit.
**Best of all, you really don’t need to pay it off. Let your kids pay that loan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimme More Money or Granny Gets It!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/12/gimme-more-money-or-granny-gets-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/12/gimme-more-money-or-granny-gets-it/</guid>
      <description>Obama showed his breaking point today. The stress got to him.
Today Obama threatened to stop Social Security payments if Congress doesn’t bend to his will on the debt ceiling.
The president told reporters that there may not be enough money to pay Social Security benefits on and after August 3rd.
But the President lies.
Revenue from taxes and other fees would cover Social Security and other payments. What won’t be covered is additional borrowing to service the country’s already outrageous debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Are We For?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/what-are-we-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 17:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/what-are-we-for/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back, the Christian Science Monitor asked me to write an op-ed. The subject was, “If the Tea Party ran America, how would things change; and why do you think you’ll win?”
The call was my opportunity to break from the easy, unassailable position that things are bad and getting worse. It meant coming up with a solution or two. And solutions already find disagreement somewhere.
For over a year I’ve said that the Tea Party movement, begun out of anger, must shift its energy over time from anger to solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>