<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>putin on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/putin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in putin on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 03:04:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/putin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be President When Russia Goes Berserk Starring Ronald Reagan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 03:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</guid>
      <description>Since the scrawny punk from Chicago still hasn&amp;rsquo;t figured it out, this President 101 lesson delivered without further comment:
https://youtu.be/9VA4W1wDMAk?t=18s
Previously on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View:
We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14949&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]&amp;ldquo;What, me worry?&amp;quot;[/caption]
Russian troops or Russian proxies murdered 293 people, today, including 23 Americans by many reports.
Israel was forced to invade Gaza to destroy tunnels Hamas uses to invade Israel and murder children.
The world teeters on the brink of all-out war.
But the President refused to cancel partisan fundraising efforts tonight.
Via The Blaze:
 At 2:25 p.m., the White House press office e-mailed a response to an inquiry from TheBlaze, “No scheduling changes to be reported at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe I&#39;m All Wrong About Putin and Poland</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/30/maybe-im-wrong-putin-poland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/30/maybe-im-wrong-putin-poland/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;ve stated your opinion or belief about something important, do you defend your belief to the hilt? Or do you immediately begin questioning your own conclusions?
Most of my life, I would defend my opinion to the point of losing friends. Even if I was wrong. Even I knew I was wrong. I&amp;rsquo;m a coward, what can I say?
I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get better, though. One practice I&amp;rsquo;ve developed and recommend to everyone is pretty simple but difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Abdullah Kicks Obama Out of Saudia Arabia ? **Video Added**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 00:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think American foreign policy couldn&amp;rsquo;t sink any lower than standing by while Vladimir Putin re-conquers the Warsaw Pact nations. Then you&amp;rsquo;ve underestimated Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s incompetence.
Apparently, Obama didn&amp;rsquo;t bow low enough to King Abdullah of Saudi Arabia. Whatever happened, an &amp;ldquo;intimate&amp;rdquo; evening planned for Obama and Abdullah was abruptly cancelled after a two-hour meeting between the two leaders. A meeting intended to &amp;ldquo;mend fences&amp;rdquo; between the two men.
UPDATE: Here&amp;rsquo;s the video from Lou Dobbs on Fox Business</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Would You Do If You Were Putin?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 18:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</guid>
      <description>You saw Obama stand by as you threatened Georgia in 2009.
You heard Obama whisper to Medvedev that he’ll be willing to defy Congress to capitulate to you after Obama’s re-election.
You watched Obama and his bumbling Secretary of State mangle its its own strategy in Syria—if the US ever had a Syrian strategy at all.
You saw that the US was completely unprepared for your annexation of Crimea.
You see the headlines of massive NSA spying on US citizens, though that same NSA was blind to your invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Will Putin Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/will-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 01:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/will-putin/</guid>
      <description>Ask yourself this: why did the stock markets rally today after Obama announced sanctions against Russians? I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to that, but first some background.
I&amp;rsquo;ve often said that Putin plays chess while Obama fumbles with checkers. I picture our president, chin resting on fist, brows squeezed in childlike concentration, as he carefully chooses between jumping Putin&amp;rsquo;s piece to end the game or getting another of his pieces &amp;ldquo;kinged.&amp;rdquo;
Of course, Obama goes for the kingship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brink of World War **UPDATES**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/11/brink-of-world-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 03:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/11/brink-of-world-war/</guid>
      <description>Am I the only person who sees that we are on the brink of world war thanks to those Russian sonsofbitches?
 Russian forces swept across Georgia on Monday, capturing the town of Gori and moving to within 35 miles of the capital city Tbilisi, FOX News confirmed.
 This is very serious stuff. Russia&amp;rsquo;s expansionist intentions are as obvious as they were in the Prague Spring and the Hungarian Revolt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>