<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CNN on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/cnn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CNN on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/cnn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace Through Violence: CNN&#39;s Radical Chic Moment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/20/peace-through-violence-cnns-radical-chic-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/20/peace-through-violence-cnns-radical-chic-moment/</guid>
      <description>CNN screwed up. And it reminds me of an incident from 1970.
A headline writer admitted that the Antifa terror group seeks &amp;ldquo;peace through violence.&amp;rdquo; Later, presumably after receiving threats from Antifa terrorists, CNN removed the &amp;ldquo;peace through violence&amp;rdquo; sub-head.
But the damage was done. CNN stumbled onto real news. Real news that exposes Antifa&amp;rsquo;s terrorist aims.
Before we get to the dangers of normalizing political violence, aka &amp;ldquo;terrorism,&amp;rdquo; let&amp;rsquo;s remember a famous party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gullible Evil Losers at CNN Criticize London Cops for Using Too Many Bullets. UPDATE</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/04/gullible-evil-losers-at-cnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 21:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/04/gullible-evil-losers-at-cnn/</guid>
      <description>Maybe we should consider CNN employees enemy combatants.
CNN&amp;rsquo;s latest hate-crime: **CNN is criticizing London police for using too many bullets. **
That&amp;rsquo;s right. CNN will soon demand a UN war crimes tribunal to try, convict, and hang the London cops who put down the London Bridge terrorists.
This photo caption appeared below this critical headline.
CNN has not responded to my request for comments.
Specifically, I asked CNN to provide the exact number of rounds police are allowed to use to stop a terrorist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally Media Focus On America&#39;s Real Problem</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/19/finally-media-focus-on-americas-real-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 19:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/19/finally-media-focus-on-americas-real-problem/</guid>
      <description>After years wasted as the press and politicians covered secondary matters, the major media have finally stepped up to address America&amp;rsquo;s deepest, most damaging problem. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about alleged plagiarism. And it&amp;rsquo;s about damn time.
While serious problems fester, the media and politicians waste precious time and energy covering the massacres of police officers by black militants and the slaughter of Bastille Day revelers by Islamic terrorists. Is it any wonder that 70 percent of Americans consider the country on the wrong track?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/03/would-the-real-ted-cruz-please-stand-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 01:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/03/would-the-real-ted-cruz-please-stand-up/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to share a secret about manipulation with you. Please do not use this powerful method for sinister deeds.
But first . . .
Disclosure 1: Before I get to the Master Manipulator Model, some important background. I work professionally in the field of persuasion and influence. I even invented a workshop that helps big companies make their stuff more persuasive.
The point is, I study persuasion, and manipulation is persuasion&amp;rsquo;s cousin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is What Evil Looks Like In Action **UPDATES**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/15/this-is-what-evil-looks-like-in-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 20:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/15/this-is-what-evil-looks-like-in-action/</guid>
      <description>This is a Vine clip of the first explosion at the Boston Marathon. Fox 25 in Boston reported moments ago that organizers confirmed that bombs caused the explosions. Clearly many casualties.
“For the sake of His sorrowful passion, have mercy on us and on the whole world.”
UPDATES
   Saudi National Suspected
   CNN&amp;rsquo;s Wolf Blitzer Implicates anti-tax conservatives
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why Turning People Off Is A Terrible Idea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a cause’s worst enemies are its best friends.

In 1995, 56 percent of American described themselves as “pro-choice.” At the time, Michael Kinsley on CNN’s Crossfire declared the debate over.
Then something strange happened. Americans started changing their minds. The pro-life movement whittled away at public opinion.
By May of this year, Gallup found “pro-choice” to be at an all-time low:
 The 41% of Americans who now identify themselves as &amp;ldquo;pro-choice&amp;rdquo; is down from 47% last July and is one percentage point below the previous record low in Gallup trends, recorded in May 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the Romney Campaign Serious About Winning?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/11/is-the-romney-campaign-serious-about-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 10:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/11/is-the-romney-campaign-serious-about-winning/</guid>
      <description>The Romney Campaign today reminded me of the McCain Campaign of 2008.
I&amp;rsquo;m pretty good at ignoring bogus, fraudulent polls like the one CNN released tonight. In that poll, CNN announced a massive 52-46 national lead for Obama. If true, the race would be all but over.
CNN, of course, cooked the books on this one.
About one-third of voters describe themselves as independents, CNN sampled only 3% independents for its latest poll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who will feed the hungry, clothe the naked, tend the sick, visit the imprisoned . . . ?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/19/who-will-feed-the-hungry-clothe-the-naked-tend-the-sick-visit-the-imprisoned/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/19/who-will-feed-the-hungry-clothe-the-naked-tend-the-sick-visit-the-imprisoned/</guid>
      <description>The candidates blew the emotional turning point in Monday’s CNN/Tea Party debate. Blew it. Big.
Before we go into that, hear me out on the pressure on those candidates.
Lights, Camera, Panic
Imagine being on a stage. Searing white brightness reduces your range of vision to a few degrees of arc. You hear hundreds of people making the sounds that audiences make, but you can’t really see them.
Before you are journalists bent on catching in a gaffe, or unprepared, or vulnerable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>