<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steve Jobs on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/steve-jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steve Jobs on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:00:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/steve-jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The SEAL, the Race, and the CEO</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/10/the-seal-the-race-and-the-ceo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/10/the-seal-the-race-and-the-ceo/</guid>
      <description>In its entire history, who was the safest CEO for Apple?
In other words, if you were a corporate recruiter hired by Apple&amp;rsquo;s board to find a chief executive, whom would hire?
I&amp;rsquo;ll answer this later, but first here&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m asking.
Who Would You Recruit? In response to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post on Brunner vs. Greitens, someone asked me a similar question about Eric Greitens. The inquisitor seems to question my judgment for preferring Greitens over John Brunner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives Keep Losing Because They’re Reading The Wrong Books</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/09/conservatives-keep-losing-because-theyre-reading-the-wrong-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/09/conservatives-keep-losing-because-theyre-reading-the-wrong-books/</guid>
      <description>For the past four years. conservatives have worried more about being right while liberals worried about winning.
We all know how that worked out.
It doesn’t matter how right you are if you’re powerless.Right now we are.
Satisfied?
I didn’t think so.

After four years of 5,000 Leap and Constitution study groups, of Constitutional workshops, and rallies in the park, let’s make a vow to ourselves and to each other: We’re Done With Losing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bain of Newt’s Existence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/17/the-bain-of-newts-existence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/17/the-bain-of-newts-existence/</guid>
      <description>Truth is, not all companies, not all business ideas, can make it on their own.
It’s easy to say that a good idea will automatically lead to a successful business. But it’s a lie.
Apple did not become Apple without investors. Sure, there are some examples of businesses that flourished without financial help. But not many. We’ll never know the wonderful ideas that died in their owner’s garage for lack of financing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Maniacal Focus for 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/01/a-maniacal-focus-for-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 01:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/01/a-maniacal-focus-for-2012/</guid>
      <description>I’m almost finished reading Walter Isaacson’s biography of Apple co-founder and genius Steve Jobs.
Jobs’s life left insanely good lessons. Some lessons instruct us on how to do things. Others warn us of bad things to avoid.
One of the good things Steve Jobs taught us: focus. Maniacal focus on things that mattered, and a pathological aversion to distractions.
One example. When Jobs returned to Apple after 10-year exile, he took stock of all the projects underway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>