<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Memorial Day on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/memorial-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Memorial Day on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 14:00:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/memorial-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Faces of Memorial Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/30/two-faces-of-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 14:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/30/two-faces-of-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>The god of Memorial Day is Janus, looking to the future as well as the past.
Memorial Day looks back, but it also warns of something coming. The list of war dead is incomplete. It always will be.
Each generation looks at its wars and finds something final, but the end never comes. Memorials never end while man roams the earth.
When I see the Vietnam Memorial, with its rows and ranks of lost warriors, I see, too, the invisible ledger that stretches to the horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Memorial Day Penance</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/a-memorial-day-penance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 18:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/a-memorial-day-penance/</guid>
      <description>I ran to Walgreen’s at lunch. I needed some medication—maybe for a cold? I don’t remember for sure. While I was there, I picked up a Muscle Milk and a protein bar so I wouldn’t have to make another stop. I had only about 20 minutes to complete the circuit before my next meeting.
Returning to work, I hit a traffic jam in an unusual place. The outer road was backed up—something I’d never seen before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memorial Day 2009</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/memorial-day-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/memorial-day-2009/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not a sale.
It&amp;rsquo;s not a party.
It&amp;rsquo;s not a day off work.
It&amp;rsquo;s a memorial to those who placed freedom, liberty, and dignity above the tiny distractions of life. We memorialize the moments of our heroes&amp;rsquo; lives&amp;ndash;moments that defined their legacy in God&amp;rsquo;s book.
They raised their hands and swore to defend their country and Constitution. They were so young, then. I saw a young Marine, yesterday, at his girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s high school graduation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>