<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Press on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/press/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Press on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 03:33:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/press/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I disavow every Republican who disavowed Trump&#39;s tweets</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/29/i-disavow-every-republican-who-disavowed-trumps-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/29/i-disavow-every-republican-who-disavowed-trumps-tweets/</guid>
      <description>When Reagan was president, we wanted him to hit back harder on the press. We wanted him to put Sam Donaldson in his place. We wanted him to call out the fake news.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_22208&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;750&amp;rdquo;]2/5/1981 President Reagan during an interview with Sam Donaldson of ABC News Leslie Stahl of CBS News and Judith Woodruff of NBC News with James Brady at the Cross Hall White House Library[/caption]
But Reagan didn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean Spicer and the White House Press Corp Proved Me 100% Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/sean-spicer-and-the-white-house-press-corp-proved-me-100-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 22:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/sean-spicer-and-the-white-house-press-corp-proved-me-100-right/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s great to be right.
Yesterday I told you that White House Press Secretary Sean Spicer played the White House press corps by telling the truth. But the press corps and many Americans have a psychosis that literally replaces some words with other words. It&amp;rsquo;s not dyslexia. It&amp;rsquo;s far worse because it&amp;rsquo;s selective.
In this case, Spicer said &amp;ldquo;witness&amp;rdquo; but journalists everywhere repeated, &amp;ldquo;attend.&amp;rdquo; I wrote about it here.
Well, today, Spicer explained the situation to a psychotic journalist almost the same way I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Spot Journalism&#39;s Psychosis</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/how-to-spot-journalisms-psychosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 12:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/how-to-spot-journalisms-psychosis/</guid>
      <description>When your brain automatically alters perceptions, there&amp;rsquo;s something wrong with you.
Reporters have this psychosis. Journalists. They have very bad ADHD it seems. They can&amp;rsquo;t pay attention. Like kids with ADHD. Chuck Todd and everybody at Business Insider should probably take Ritalin or something.
Reporters are also narcissists. No one goes into journalism unless they have a pathologically inflated ego. No one.
So I&amp;rsquo;m going to walk you through the proof, slowly, so even our narcissistic, hyperactive, attention-deficit-disordered journalists can understand that Sean Spicer played with them like a cat pawing a dying moth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do Post Dispatch Reporters and Penn State Have in Common?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/11/19/what-do-post-dispatch-reporters-and-joe-paterno-have-in-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 20:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/11/19/what-do-post-dispatch-reporters-and-joe-paterno-have-in-common/</guid>
      <description>Like the Penn State athletic department, most St. Louis news media covered up a sex crime in order to protect an organization they love.
The St. Louis Post Dispatch, KTVI 2 and KPLR 11, and KSDK 5 each failed to report a sexual assault that took place at the illegal OccupySTL squatters&amp;rsquo; village in Kiener Plaza last week.
The assault came to light only because a citizen-journalist, the POed Patriot, monitors the police crime map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would you do me a favor this Saturday?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/29/would-you-do-me-a-favor-this-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/29/would-you-do-me-a-favor-this-saturday/</guid>
      <description>I try not to ask for much. Okay, maybe that’s not true, but I’m going to ask you a favor, anyway. Mark this down: **7:00 pm, Saturday, October 1. **
It’s weird, I know. But I’m asking for three presents in one.
First, my mom and dad celebrate their wedding anniversary this week. (62nd?) Second, my wife and I celebrate our wedding anniversary this week. Third, next week is my birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s About Love</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/its-about-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/its-about-love/</guid>
      <description>Trent and Jennifer Humphries—hated by all the right people—just brought to tears to 5,200 eyes.
After Trent told us that the secret to our success is Christ’s love, his wife, Jennifer, described the depths to which evil journalists stooped in the moments following the Giffords shooting.
As the Humphries and their small children returned home from the grocery store, they learned that their next door neighbor—and a beloved friend—was killed in the tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Turning Tide Swamps All Lefties</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/a-turning-tide-swamps-all-lefties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/a-turning-tide-swamps-all-lefties/</guid>
      <description>For three consecutive days the hard left of American politics executed a prepared battle plan:
 * Personify the Enemy (Sarah Palin, Rush Limbaugh, Glenn Beck) * Isolate him or her (Rightwing vitriol, conservative talk radio, “crosshairs”) * Vilify without mercy (Hate, violence, accessory to murder)  Democrat Mark Penn showed us the left’s cards in November when he said that Obama needs an Oklahoma bombing to help him “reconnect” with the American people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACKS: Media Blame Tea Party for Leftist Crimes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/flashbacks-media-blame-tea-party-for-leftist-crimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 23:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/flashbacks-media-blame-tea-party-for-leftist-crimes/</guid>
      <description>The most often repeated story is not the reluctant hero or the hero who wants to get home. Nor is it about a mother’s love.
The ultimate archetypical story line is:
LIBERAL PRESS ERRONEOUSLY BLAMES TEA PARTY FOR LEFTIST CRIMES
As Jarod Lee Loughner’s political bent emerges, we see the same, predictable story playing out:
1. A horrific crime takes place.*2. Leftist bloggers like Markos Moulitsas blame conservatives.*3. CNN, New York Times, Washinton Post, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>