<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Israel on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/israel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Israel on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 16:48:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/israel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Had a Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/06/i-had-a-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/06/i-had-a-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>A Scenario: 1. The USA bombs Syria 2. Syria bombs Israel 3. The USA and Israel bomb Syria 4. Russia gives USA ultimatum 5. USA ignores Russia 6. Syria and Iran bomb Israel and Turkey 7. Turkey bombs Syria and Iran 8. Russia lands troops in Syria 9. USA lands troops in Lebanon 10. . Cold sweat</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barack Obama Is Having a Very Bad Week, and Even WaPo Noticed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/26/barack-obamas-having-a-very-bad-week-and-even-wapo-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/26/barack-obamas-having-a-very-bad-week-and-even-wapo-noticed/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;180&amp;rdquo;] Barack Obama (Photo credit: jamesomalley)[/caption]
The smartest man in the world can’t make a gaffe, surely. When Barack Obama says something ridiculous, mean-spirited, wrongheaded, or just plain dumb, he means it.
So we know Obama considers the murders of Ambassador Chris Stevens and three others mere “bumps in the road” to his re-election. Four bumps, to be precise.
When Obama says Israel is just “one of our strongest allies” in the Middle East, no longer our strongest, he means it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Told You So! Democrats BOO God, Israel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/05/i-told-you-so-democrats-boo-god-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 02:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/05/i-told-you-so-democrats-boo-god-israel/</guid>
      <description>As if reading from a script written by the Romney campaign, the Democrats on Wednesday managed to mangle their public image even further, this time by booing God and Israel.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_12536&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;288&amp;rdquo;]   Clipped from https://thespeechatimeforchoosing.wordpress.com[/caption]
On Tuesday, the Democratic National Convention stripped God&amp;rsquo;s name from their platform and rejected Israel&amp;rsquo;s choice of Jerusalem as its capital.
Wednesday, the party panicked and rushed in an amendment to restore God and Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Trust the Democcrats&#39; Platform?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/04/can-you-trust-the-democcrats-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 04:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/04/can-you-trust-the-democcrats-platform/</guid>
      <description>For years voters have complained that politicians and parties say anything to get a vote. People have longed for the days of plain talk and honesty.
  Well, the Democrats passed a new platform today. Two headlines emerged:
  The Democrats rejected any reference to God.
  The Democrats rejected Jerusalem as Israel&amp;rsquo;s capital.
  The question is: can you trust them? Do Democrats really reject God and reject Jerusalem as the center of Israeli political life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abraham, Isaac, and Todd</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/24/abraham-isaac-and-todd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/24/abraham-isaac-and-todd/</guid>
      <description>The story Isaac is about tests of faith.
God commanded Abraham to sacrifice Isaac, his only son, born after Abraham and Sarah had given up hope of conceiving.
Once Isaac was bound and placed on the altar, God stayed Abraham&amp;rsquo;s hand. &amp;ldquo;Now I know you fear God.&amp;rdquo;
You know the rest.
It just struck me this morning, listening to the weather during Jamie Allman&amp;rsquo;s show, that Isaac now threatens the GOP convention, dangling above Tampa like Abraham&amp;rsquo;s dagger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stand With Israel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/20/stand-with-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 03:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/20/stand-with-israel/</guid>
      <description>Dear friend,
In the wake of President Obama&amp;rsquo;s reckless comments directed towards Israel, I have just added my name to Grassfire Nation&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;I Support Israel&amp;rdquo; petition, and I&amp;rsquo;m urging you to do the same.
Click here for more and to add your name to Grassfire Nation&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;I Support Israel&amp;rdquo; petition by clicking below: https://www.grassfire.com/159/petition.asp?PID=31372586&amp;amp;NID=1
Sincerely, Bill
P.S. I find this site interesting, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the International Fellowship of Christians and Jews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Israel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/13/go-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 23:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/13/go-israel/</guid>
      <description>No, I’m not a war monger. But peace is not the absence of war. It’s the presence of peace.

If you live in Israel, you are not at peace. You are at war. War against a massive body of people who want to destroy you before they move on to destroy Christendom. If Christendom doesn’t destroy itself first.
So let’s all thank Israel for standing tall on the front lines of this epic battle between good and evil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel Continues Assault on Terrorists</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/israel-continues-assault-on-terrorists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 13:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/israel-continues-assault-on-terrorists/</guid>
      <description>Israel&amp;rsquo;s assault on Hamas terrorists in Gaza continued for a second day. As if reading from a script, the UN Security Council called for an immediate stop to Israel&amp;rsquo;s self-defense. As the air strikes continued, Israel has moved more troops and tanks to the border, possibly in preparation for an incursion into the area now under terrorist control.
Some internation responses were less than predictable, though. France, for instance, demands first that the terrorists stop pitching rockets at Israeli school kids, then that Israel stop its air assault.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>