<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Early Voting on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/early-voting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Early Voting on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 18:27:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/early-voting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Maximize Your Election Influence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/how-to-maximize-your-election-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/how-to-maximize-your-election-influence/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s What To Do Today And On Election Day
Tuesday is the most important election of your life, but voting is never enough. You can have a bigger impact by using social proof to increase your influence. I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how, and it won&amp;rsquo;t take you long.
  First, though, make sure nothing gets in the way of exercising your duty to vote.
Studies have shown that you are more likely to vote if you answer these questions before Election Day:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney’s Cleaning Up in Early Voting, but It’s Confused the Hell Out of Politico</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/30/mitt-romneys-cleaning-up-in-early-voting-but-its-confused-the-hell-out-of-politico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/30/mitt-romneys-cleaning-up-in-early-voting-but-its-confused-the-hell-out-of-politico/</guid>
      <description>Gallup released its early voting poll today, and it shows Mitt Romney winning 52% to 45%—right in line with their Likely Voter poll numbers. Here’s the chart.

Politico Reporter Can’t Read But Gallup’s section on early voting by party ID completely lost Politico’s Kevin Robillard.
Robillard looked at the chart that shows when voters intend to vote by party and candidate and mistook it for voting results. This poll question shows that those who support Obama as as likely to vote early as are those who support Romney.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>