<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>social media on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in social media on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:29:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter and YouTube Reject Science</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/twitter-and-youtub-reject-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 21:29:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/twitter-and-youtub-reject-science/</guid>
      <description>Why would YouTube and Twitter executives attack an innovative biotech company?
Hatred. Pure, unadulterated hate.
Nothing but raging emotion can explain why both YouTube and Twitter went on the offensive against the biotech company AYTU Healight this weekend, banning the company from their platforms.
What AYTU Healight did to earn deplatforming: it found favor with the man the China-controlled World Health Organization hates.
Donald Trump merely asked his mecical experts about the possibilities of AYTU Healight&amp;rsquo;s Far-UVC catheter technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Get More Twitter Followers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/05/how-to-get-more-twitter-followers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/05/how-to-get-more-twitter-followers/</guid>
      <description>Unless you just want to vent, the reason you post things on Twitter is to influence people. But you can’t influence people who don’t see your tweets. **The more people who see your tweets, the more influential you are. **So you should increase your Twitter followers.

How can you increase your followers? Research at Georgia Tech gives you the answer.
Twitter Things To Do Be Positive. Positive tweets are more likely to be retweeted and people who use positive words have more followers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Moves for Herman Cain Supporters Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</guid>
      <description>Herman Cain is riding a wave of popularity because of his upset win in the Florida straw poll on Saturday. He’s helped by Rick Perry’s free-fall and Mitt Romney’s establishmentarianism. But Cain is a huge underdog.
That’s okay because **America loves an underdog. **
Here’s what must happen right now for Herman Cain to win:
1. Social Media avalanche. Get @THEHermanCain trending on Twitter, and keep it there for five consecutive days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>