<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>democrats on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/democrats/</link>
    <description>Recent content in democrats on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 03:14:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/democrats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Ruin the World (f-bombs included!)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/17/democrats-ruin-the-world-f-bombs-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/17/democrats-ruin-the-world-f-bombs-included/</guid>
      <description>Picture this.
Every time you leave your teenage kids home alone for a weekend, you come back to stink-eyes from your neighbors, a living room that&amp;rsquo;s a sea of empty beer cans, a yard filled with cigarette butts, and a pregnant cat.
Pretty soon, you&amp;rsquo;d stop leaving those kids to their own devices, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you? If you had to leave town, you&amp;rsquo;d find a sitter. Maybe a retired Marine uncle. Or a friendly cop to send a car by the house every half hour during the dark hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Trust the Democcrats&#39; Platform?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/04/can-you-trust-the-democcrats-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 04:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/04/can-you-trust-the-democcrats-platform/</guid>
      <description>For years voters have complained that politicians and parties say anything to get a vote. People have longed for the days of plain talk and honesty.
  Well, the Democrats passed a new platform today. Two headlines emerged:
  The Democrats rejected any reference to God.
  The Democrats rejected Jerusalem as Israel&amp;rsquo;s capital.
  The question is: can you trust them? Do Democrats really reject God and reject Jerusalem as the center of Israeli political life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why Tax Credits Kill Society</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/23/heres-why-tax-credits-kill-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 10:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/23/heres-why-tax-credits-kill-society/</guid>
      <description>Tax credits reward particular businesses or developers with tax dollars from the general population. They concentrate wealth in a few hands. Tax credits are the way politicians play the market with someone else&amp;rsquo;s money.
  
Worse, **Republicans are addicted to tax credits. **
A Missouri House Republican leader told a constituent that his party gives tax dollars to people who &amp;ldquo;spend it smarter.&amp;rdquo; Bill Clinton said the same thing in about 1992.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studies Show Most Americans Are Too Stupid to Vote</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/29/studies-show-most-americans-are-too-stupid-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 21:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/29/studies-show-most-americans-are-too-stupid-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>The new fad among Democrats is to see how many illegal aliens they can pack into a voting booth. While we conservatives decry this illegal and anti-American grab at tyrannical power, we should take some solace in this sobering fact: those illegal aliens probably know as much about the American political system as most 13th generation Americans.
  
The fact is, most Americans are too stupid about politics to vote, which explains the 2008 election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Former Governor and a Famous St. Louis Lawyer Indicted for Illegal Contributions to Democrat Party, and A Law Firm Changes Names in Mid-Quote</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/a-former-governor-and-a-famous-st-louis-lawyer-indicted-for-illegal-contributions-to-democrat-party-and-a-law-firm-changes-names-in-mid-quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 18:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/15/a-former-governor-and-a-famous-st-louis-lawyer-indicted-for-illegal-contributions-to-democrat-party-and-a-law-firm-changes-names-in-mid-quote/</guid>
      <description>Everyone else is writing about the news that former Missouri Democrat Governor, Roger Wilson and local lawyer Ed Griesedieck Jr. were indicted on federal fraud charges today.
The two allegedly made contributions to the Democrat Party (legal), and reimbursed themselves out of Missouri Employers Mutual Insurance Company’s coffers (illegal).
But that’s not the weird part. After all, election fraud is the Democrats’ principal form of amusement.
The weird part is the statement from Griesedieck’s law firm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>