<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/latest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Latest on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 00:23:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/latest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Gear Store Open Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/28/tea-party-gear-store-open-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 00:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/28/tea-party-gear-store-open-again/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for the interruption, but we’ve worked out the kinks.
Do you want to show the world your colors?
Do you want to say, “I’m a tea partier?”
Do you want your style to shout, “FREEDOM!”
Then get to the official St. Louis Tea Party store and stock up. We’ve added T.E.A. ball caps to go with the T.E.A Special Forces t-shirts (our best seller).
You’ll look terrific reading Zen Conservatism in your Tea Party Hoodie!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Conservative Paperback Available Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/27/zen-conservative-paperback-available-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 20:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/27/zen-conservative-paperback-available-now/</guid>
      <description>** You Can Order My Book Online Today **Zen Conservatism is now available in paperback.
    I began this book in December 2008, just after the election. My goal was to produce a book that would inspire people to restore our republic. At the time, conservatives were disheartened, dismayed, and distracted.
Then the Tea Party movement began, and I had to put my book project on hold. But thanks to your work, I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to return to my project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Back Globe-Democrat</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/12/welcome-back-globe-democrat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/12/welcome-back-globe-democrat/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Globe-Democrat is back as an online newspaper. That’s good news for all of us, regardless of their editorial positions. The other paper in St. Louis has fallen without competition. People have found alternatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junk Bond</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 01:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond-2/</guid>
      <description>John is a Vietnam veteran and retired business executive. He loves America and hates to see what’s happened in Washington the past few years. He believes in liberty and Constitutional limitations on government growth.
He called the Tea Party just to vent and to see if it’s just him.
Recently, John had called Senator Kit Bond’s (R-MO) office in Washington. He wanted to know whether stories that Bond had signed off a $659 million earmark for soy bean farmers were true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are there any courageous business executives alive today?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/09/are-there-any-courageous-business-executives-alive-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/09/are-there-any-courageous-business-executives-alive-today/</guid>
      <description>The most disappointing thing about leaving the military is that it usually means leaving the last bastion of leadership in America. If you open your own business or freelance, you probably don’t notice the cowardly bastards populating corner offices in most American enterprises. You’d puke, as Holden Caulfield might say.
John Mackey of Whole Foods had the courage to oppose socialized medicine AND to defend his position and his right to say it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>