<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>J. Eric Fuller on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/j.-eric-fuller/</link>
    <description>Recent content in J. Eric Fuller on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:24:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/j.-eric-fuller/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Left Doubles Down on Threats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</guid>
      <description>What would you do?
Suppose you did something stupid. You blamed the wrong person, for instance, for a capital crime. Then supposed one of your comrades compounded your . . . error . . . by threatening to kill someone on national television?
If you’re an American leftist, you might double down by issuing even more death threats to even more people.
That’s what’ happening right now in America. Death threats are pouring into Trent Humphries, Tucson Tea Party organizer, Dana Loesch, Sarah Palin (who vows not to be silenced), Glenn Beck, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bill Maher’s Vitriol Responsible for Arrest?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</guid>
      <description>Last week, America’s sleaziest leftists—Bill Maher, Chris Matthews, Keith Olbermann, E. J. Dionne, Paul Krugman, others – have [executed a prepared propaganda war](https://hennessysview.com/crime/a-national-day-of-shame/) against anyone who disagrees with them. Their theorem is: vitriolic rhetoric inspires conservatives to act out in violence.
Unfortunately for the loony left, there was no evidence to support their theorem. The evidence they falsely pointed to—Jarod Lee Loughner’s deranged murder rampage in Tucson—was determined to be a lie only hours after the event.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>