<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General Flynn on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/general-flynn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General Flynn on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 15:21:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/general-flynn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Today, Watergate Became the Second Worst Abuse of Power in American History</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/watergate-now-second-worst-abuse-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 15:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/watergate-now-second-worst-abuse-of-power/</guid>
      <description>Releasing national security intercepts to unauthorized persons is a federal felony punishable by 10 years in prison. And at least one of the names on this list of top Obama Administration officials is guilty beyond a reasonable doubt. 18 U.S. Code § 798(a)(4):
 Whoever knowingly and willfully communicates, furnishes, transmits, or otherwise makes available to an unauthorized person, or publishes, or uses in any manner prejudicial to the safety or interest of the United States or for the benefit of any foreign government to the detriment of the United States any classified information—obtained by the processes of communication intelligence from the communications of any foreign government, knowing the same to have been obtained by such processes—Shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than ten years, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Note That Killed the FBI</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-note-that-killed-the-fbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 18:34:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-note-that-killed-the-fbi/</guid>
      <description>Agents of the FBI plotted to frame and destroy General James Flynn for politic purposes according to handwritten notes released today.
General Flynn, a 30-year Army veteran and 3-star General, pled guilty to false charges in order to protect his family from further harassment by the FBI in 2017.
Now, the law firm that once represented Flynn has release thousands of documents it previously illegally refused to turn over. One of those documents is a handwritten note.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>