<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ann Wagner on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/ann-wagner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ann Wagner on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 20:35:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/ann-wagner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We Heard From Ann Wagner. Now Let&#39;s Hear From the Clintons&#39; Victims</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/08/lets-hear-from-the-clintons-victims/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 20:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/08/lets-hear-from-the-clintons-victims/</guid>
      <description>Today, Rep. Ann Wagner (R-MO) abandoned her party&amp;rsquo;s nominee to support a rape accomplice for President. Ann Wagner has lost her moral authority on all matters outside of her own home. I call on Mrs. Wagner to resign from the House of Representatives and to retire gracefully from public life.
Mrs. Wagner seems to believe that being a woman gives her some unique moral vantage point. She forgets that she&amp;rsquo;s not the only woman in America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strangest Governor Race Ever</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/05/the-strangest-governor-race-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/05/the-strangest-governor-race-ever/</guid>
      <description>You might be wondering why the Missouri Farm Bureau endorsed Democrat Chris Koster instead of Republican Eric Greitens. The Farm Bureau endorses Republicans about 99% of the time.
If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking it had to do with policy or personality, you&amp;rsquo;re thinking wrong. (And, no, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t because of Koster&amp;rsquo;s hair, Mark Reardon.) This was all about the establishment vs. the people. It&amp;rsquo;s about power and control. Greitens threatens the establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whip It. Whip It Good.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/11/whip-it-whip-it-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/11/whip-it-whip-it-good/</guid>
      <description>Maybe Ann Wagner&amp;rsquo;s the problem.
Rep. Ann Wagner (HA-64) is the House Majority Whip. Her job is to know how every GOP member will vote on bills and to cut deals until House leadership gets the numbers it wants.
It&amp;rsquo;s unfathomable that a majority whip would not have seen the Kevin McCarthy meltdown coming long before the House Republican caucus met to nominate a candidate for speaker. But many accounts suggest that the Republican House leadership thought McCarthy had the votes up to the moment he withdrew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the US House, Insider Money Buys Leadership Positions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/29/us-house-insider-money-buys-leadership-positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 20:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/29/us-house-insider-money-buys-leadership-positions/</guid>
      <description>The US House of Representatives is not a meritocracy. And that&amp;rsquo;s a shame.
House &amp;ldquo;leadership&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually have anything to do with leadership. It has everything to do with money.
In a story about the fall from power of Nancy Pelosi, Michael Barone describes how the House leadership process evolved from seniority to raw cash.
  For years, liberal Democrats had decried the seniority system, which automatically made conservative Southerners (and/or senile members) committee chairmen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatever Happened to the Party of Ideas?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</guid>
      <description>From about 1978 until the Monica Lewinsky fiasco, the GOP was called &amp;ldquo;the party of ideas.&amp;rdquo; I miss the ideas.
William F. Buckley helped. Buckley liked big ideas and smart people. He liked politicians who gave legs to great ideas and governors with the guts to experiment. Governor Ronald Reagan appeared on Buckley&amp;rsquo;s Firing Line shortly after the Gipper became California&amp;rsquo;s governor. Reagan talked about many ideas he was trying or hoping to try.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>