<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>union violence on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/union-violence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in union violence on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 23:19:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/union-violence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Fund A Terrorist Network?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/15/do-you-fund-a-terrorist-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/15/do-you-fund-a-terrorist-network/</guid>
      <description>According to the FBI:
 Domestic terrorism is the unlawful use, or threatened use, of force or violence by a group or individual based and operating entirely within the United States or Puerto Rico without foreign direction committed against persons or property to intimidate or coerce a government, the civilian population, or any segment thereof in furtherance of political or social objectives. (source)
 In Michigan, union protesters physically assaulted Steven Crowder of Fox News, then destroyed a tent belonging to Americans for Prosperity (video below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Leader Says  Let’s “Take Out” Union Members</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/tea-party-leader-says-lets-take-out-union-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 18:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/tea-party-leader-says-lets-take-out-union-members/</guid>
      <description>We got to keep an eye on the battle that we face: The war on Tea Partiers. And you see it everywhere, it is the Unions. And you know, there is only one way to beat and win that war. The one thing about Tea Party people is we like a good fight. And you know what? They&amp;rsquo;ve got a war, they got a war with us and there&amp;rsquo;s only going to be one winner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy Ancel: Teacher of the Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/judy-ancel-teacher-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 18:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/judy-ancel-teacher-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Judy Ancel is the University of Kansas City instructor responsible for teaching students to use violence, sabotage and intimidation as political tools. She’s telling the Kansas City Star that she’s receiving threats from people upset that she teaches students to threaten others.
I oppose violence, sabotage, and intimidation as political tools. But Judy Ancel’s message of violence seems to have gotten through to some people.
Too bad Ancel doesn’t use her skills for goodinstead of evil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Leader condones political violence: “It certainly has its place. It’s a tactic that should be used at the appropriate time. I believe in a violent overthrow . . . , and that freedom is found at the barrel of a gun”</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/27/tea-party-leader-condones-political-violence-it-certainly-has-its-place-its-a-tactic-that-should-be-used-at-the-appropriate-time-i-believe-in-a-violent-overthrow-and-that-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 02:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/27/tea-party-leader-condones-political-violence-it-certainly-has-its-place-its-a-tactic-that-should-be-used-at-the-appropriate-time-i-believe-in-a-violent-overthrow-and-that-free/</guid>
      <description>Did I say “Tea Party Leader?” ** I meant labor union leader Don Giljum condones violence, intimidation, and sabotage.** Giljum’s the business manager for Operating Engineers Local 148 and a lecturer at University of Missouri-St. Louis. It’s in the UMSL classroom that he pontificates and brags about the . . . the uglier side of negotiations.
Here’s what he actually said about violence for political purposes:
 It certainly has its place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>