<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tucson on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tucson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tucson on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 17:30:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tucson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s About Love</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/its-about-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/its-about-love/</guid>
      <description>Trent and Jennifer Humphries—hated by all the right people—just brought to tears to 5,200 eyes.
After Trent told us that the secret to our success is Christ’s love, his wife, Jennifer, described the depths to which evil journalists stooped in the moments following the Giffords shooting.
As the Humphries and their small children returned home from the grocery store, they learned that their next door neighbor—and a beloved friend—was killed in the tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bill Maher’s Vitriol Responsible for Arrest?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</guid>
      <description>Last week, America’s sleaziest leftists—Bill Maher, Chris Matthews, Keith Olbermann, E. J. Dionne, Paul Krugman, others – have [executed a prepared propaganda war](https://hennessysview.com/crime/a-national-day-of-shame/) against anyone who disagrees with them. Their theorem is: vitriolic rhetoric inspires conservatives to act out in violence.
Unfortunately for the loony left, there was no evidence to support their theorem. The evidence they falsely pointed to—Jarod Lee Loughner’s deranged murder rampage in Tucson—was determined to be a lie only hours after the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I went to a memorial. . . and all I got was this lousy t-shirt *UPDATE* Michelle Malkin Reminds Us of Another Massacre Memorial</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/i-went-to-a-memorial-and-all-i-got-was-this-lousy-t-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 04:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/i-went-to-a-memorial-and-all-i-got-was-this-lousy-t-shirt/</guid>
      <description>**Obama Productions Inc. **   Garish chic. No other way to describe it.
Where were the Greek columns? No official sponsors? Why not GM and Goldman Sachs?
While Obama’s speech was appropriate and well delivered—his best since taking office—the crass and tasteless setting, the shouting and cheering, the lack of dignity and solemnity, will mark this event as an embarrassment to the country and an affront to the families and victims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Turning Tide Swamps All Lefties</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/a-turning-tide-swamps-all-lefties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/a-turning-tide-swamps-all-lefties/</guid>
      <description>For three consecutive days the hard left of American politics executed a prepared battle plan:
 * Personify the Enemy (Sarah Palin, Rush Limbaugh, Glenn Beck) * Isolate him or her (Rightwing vitriol, conservative talk radio, “crosshairs”) * Vilify without mercy (Hate, violence, accessory to murder)  Democrat Mark Penn showed us the left’s cards in November when he said that Obama needs an Oklahoma bombing to help him “reconnect” with the American people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got Your Back</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/11/got-your-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 23:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/11/got-your-back/</guid>
      <description>Seth Godin’s daily blogs are amazingly timely.
Today Seth talked about having someone’s back. He explained that the time we need to feel that someone has our back is when things are tough, not when they’re going well.
 No, if you want her to go all in, if you want her to take the risk and brave the fear, then it sure helps if you&amp;rsquo;re there too, no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>