<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>youtube on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/youtube/</link>
    <description>Recent content in youtube on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 21:29:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/youtube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This. Not That.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/10/this-not-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/10/this-not-that/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/mQNqZFqQoMU
Please share this. You’ll look good.
About the Real Conservative National Committee
 The Real Conservatives National Committee is a political action committee organized under Section 527 of the IRS Code. We only endorse and support conservative Republican candidates. We do not support third party candidates. We will operate as an independent expenditure SUPER PAC as defined by the Federal Election Commission.
Our mission is to help conservative candidates win Republican primary elections against incumbent RINOs, and help conservative Republicans win general elections against Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When The Three O&#39;Clock Call Came, Barack Obama Froze</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</guid>
      <description>The fog of war is lifting from Benghazi, and what lies beneath should shame Obama’s most ardent supporters. Barack Obama choked, and Americans died.

When America came under attack, Obama panicked and froze.
When Americans under his direction pleaded for their lives, he was afraid to pull the trigger.
Here’s the emerging picture.
White House Ordered Military and CIA to Stand Down and Let Al Qaeda Kill Former Navy SEALs Ty Woods and Glen Doherty, so disgusted by the White House’s refusal to help Americans under attack, defied an order to stand down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Giffords Shooter: Jared Loughner Leaves Video *UPDATES*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/alleged-giffords-shooter-jared-loughner-leaves-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 21:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/alleged-giffords-shooter-jared-loughner-leaves-video/</guid>
      <description>Update: Gateway Pundit has much more on the alleged shooter.
These appear to be the paranoid ramblings of the man in custody for shooting Rep. Gabrielle Giffords and 11 others, including a federal judge, in Tucson, AZ. Lots of hard left references in his favorite books, including Mein Kampf and The Communist Manifesto. Politico’s Ben Smith calls Laughner’s writings “socialist.”
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nHoaZaLbqB4&amp;amp;hl;=en&amp;amp;hd;=1]
Another Video by alleged shooter in Arizona made 3 weeks before shooting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond YouTube:  The Blog Campaign</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/beyond-youtube-the-blog-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2007 04:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/beyond-youtube-the-blog-campaign/</guid>
      <description>Matt Margolis at GOP Bloggers questions the cutting-edginess of the YouTube debate. He&amp;rsquo;s right in his various points about the ordinariness of the whole affair.
To make the presidential race more interesting, I propose a blog-off. The candidates have to start a blog using a commonly available blog app: WordPress (my fave), MoveableType, etc. The candidate with the highest TLB Ecosystem score wins his party&amp;rsquo;s nomination.
The rules
 1. Posts must be submitted by the candidate himself or herself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>