<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ed Martin Jr on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/ed-martin-jr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ed Martin Jr on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 14:38:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/ed-martin-jr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Permission to Trump, Episode 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/09/permission-to-trump-episode-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 14:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/09/permission-to-trump-episode-2/</guid>
      <description>[soundcloud url=&amp;quot;https://api.soundcloud.com/tracks/272883927&amp;rdquo; params=&amp;quot;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;100%&amp;rdquo; height=&amp;quot;166&amp;rdquo; iframe=&amp;quot;true&amp;rdquo; /]
Ed Martin Jr. and I got together again to talk about why you might give yourself Permission to Trump. It&amp;rsquo;s important that you do.
This week&amp;rsquo;s episode focuses on:
** FBI Director&amp;rsquo;s report on Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s illegal and dangerous abuse of classified information ** The horrific massacre of police officers in Dallas ** Bill&amp;rsquo;s new book,** Turning On Trump**
Feel free to share this post with all your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Simple Questions for Chairman Priebus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/11/3-simple-questions-chairman-priebus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/11/3-simple-questions-chairman-priebus/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, I raised a concern about Erick Erickson&amp;rsquo;s handling of Reince Priebus at Erickson&amp;rsquo;s annual RedState Gathering.
Today, Erick responded to widespread criticism of his decision to protect the GOP Chairman from questions about tactics in the Mississippi Republican Senate Runoff. Here&amp;rsquo;s the heart of Erickson&amp;rsquo;s answer:
 But there was more to it than me knowing people would be angry about Mississippi. First, many of the people told me what they wanted to ask Reince.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Republican Party Seems Bent On Self-Destruction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/the-republican-party-seems-bent-on-destruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 13:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/the-republican-party-seems-bent-on-destruction/</guid>
      <description>Every election cycle millions of reliable Republican voters die and even more millions of Democrat voters get the vote. Messaging and pandering won’t fix the problem. Reforming the party might.
Libertarian reforms offer the best hope, because all the other conservative factions – evangelicals, Second Amendment, home schoolers, fiscal &amp;ndash; have hit their high-water marks. We saw that in 2012. Liberty, however, sells with the kids. Or it might, if Republicans would try it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Prostitutes In Business Suits Cost Ed Martin A Place On The Rules Committee?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/23/did-prostitutes-in-business-suits-cost-ed-martin-a-place-on-the-rules-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 16:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/23/did-prostitutes-in-business-suits-cost-ed-martin-a-place-on-the-rules-committee/</guid>
      <description>You probably never heard of Lance Beshore of Joplin, MO. He’s been Missouri’s delegate to the Republican National Committee’s Rules Committee for 12 years. He runs the lobbying department of Leggett &amp;amp; Platt furniture company. He’s on the Missouri Chamber of Commerce, and he’s chairman of the board of Freeman Health Systems.

In his roles at Freeman and the Missouri Chamber, Beshore advocates for Obamacare Medicaid Expansion in Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin’s Grit Overwhelms Establishment’s Power</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/05/ed-martins-grit-overwhelms-establishments-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 02:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/05/ed-martins-grit-overwhelms-establishments-power/</guid>
      <description>In a blow to the old guard establishment,** the Missouri Republican State Committee elected Ed Martin Jr. as its new party chairman**.

Roy Blunt and all six Republican members of Congress from Missouri lobbied the new state committee over the past few weeks to block Ed and retain the establishment’s choice, David Cole. Jo Mannies of the St. Louis Beacon wrote:
 Cole’s loss appears to be a setback for Missouri’s GOP establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>