<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tyranny on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tyranny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tyranny on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 09:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tyranny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is One Sign That Your Government Is Tyrannical</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/03/here-is-one-sign-your-government-is-tyrannical/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/03/here-is-one-sign-your-government-is-tyrannical/</guid>
      <description>We throw around big scary words like “tyranny” too much. I’m guilty myself. While we get a lot of attention with hyperbole, we’ll lose credibility over time. Then when tyranny emerges, people will ignore our screams.
Like now.

For years, Congress has used the tax code to motivate behavior. Tax credits for insulated windows and electric cars are examples. The home mortgage deduction is another. And tuition tax credits, dependent tax credits, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Tea Party?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/19/why-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/19/why-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>A college student asked me a question: Why join the Tea Party?

He was wondering why anyone would want to associate with people who behaved reprehensibly at two earlier Republican debates.
Here’s how I replied:
 Johnny,
 Sorry that I&amp;rsquo;m just getting to this. I get a lot of email, and sometimes I miss things.
I organized the tea party in St. Louis in 2009. I did so because I&amp;rsquo;ve seen that governments accumulate power until they crush liberty and freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Insults Americans . . . Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/obama-insults-americans-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 23:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/obama-insults-americans-again/</guid>
      <description>An arrogant and distracted Barack Obama appeared at a press conference for the G20 Summit today. His purpose: to insult, threaten, and cajole the American people from an international stage.
 I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because I said I was going to do it and I think it&amp;rsquo;s the right thing to do. People should learn that lesson about me because next year when I start presenting some very difficult choices to the country, I hope some of these folks who are hollering about deficits and debt step-up because I&amp;rsquo;m calling their bluff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Days of Free Markets Numbered</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/days-of-free-markets-numbered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/days-of-free-markets-numbered/</guid>
      <description>The statists are moving faster through the Constitution than Hitler moved through France. Today, Democrats in the House of Representatives voted to advance a bill to socialize medicine without debate.
 House Democrats went on record again in favor of advancing the legislation while allowing only limited debate, which would hobble the ability of Republicans to wrest concessions on one of Obama&amp;rsquo;s top domestic priorities.
 **Accelerating the **Banana Republic</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>