<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>libertarian on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/libertarian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in libertarian on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 21:31:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/libertarian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Will Not Vote for Ann Wagner in 2014</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/21/will-not-vote-for-wagner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/21/will-not-vote-for-wagner/</guid>
      <description>There is a tide in the affairs of men. Which, taken at the flood, leads on to fortune; Omitted, all the voyage of their life Is bound in shallows and in miseries. On such a full sea are we now afloat, And we must take the current when it serves, Or lose our ventures.
 Julius Caesar Act 4, scene 3, 218–224
 The problem the Republican Party has, too many people are sitting around, waiting for a wave to take them across the election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Municipal Courts Matter to Liberty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 03:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</guid>
      <description>I am embarrassed.
I am embarrassed that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about this problem sooner. Or I heard about it and ignored it, which is even worse. Maybe I thought it was just the usual liberal whining about trumped up racial problems. Whatever, I should have listened.
On September 2, I asked a room of about 30 tea partiers, &amp;ldquo;Do you trust our justice system?&amp;rdquo; I heard a chorus of &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Fascinating Results In The Missouri Primary</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/10-curious-results-missouri-primary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/10-curious-results-missouri-primary/</guid>
      <description>CORRECTION: My sincerest apologies for an inexcusable error in this post earlier. I erroneously congratulated my friend Martin Baker in the US House 1st District primary. I understand that Martin was about 500 votes short. I failed to verify information I received on the race, and I apologize for my irresponsibility.
Well, this got people talking. (See the comments.)
Yesterday was the Missouri Primary. Congratulations to Rick Stream and Jay Ashcrofton their wins in contested races for St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Libertarian Is The New Mainstream</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/30/libertarian-new-mainstream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 21:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/30/libertarian-new-mainstream/</guid>
      <description>You don&amp;rsquo;t hear the word &amp;ldquo;mainstream&amp;rdquo; in political spin like you used to.
Back in the late 1980s when Jack Kemp, Pat Robertson, Pete DuPont, Al Haig, and George H. W. Bush were battling to replace
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_15090&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] 1988 Republican Candidates[/caption]
Ronald Reagan, &amp;ldquo;mainstream&amp;rdquo; was in. Candidates fought for the title of &amp;ldquo;mainstream Republican,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;mainstream Conservative,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;mainstream everything.&amp;rdquo;
I&amp;rsquo;m glad that word went away. But I&amp;rsquo;m bringing it back, if only for one blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am a Right-Leaning Libertarian</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/08/right-leaning-libertarian/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 21:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/08/right-leaning-libertarian/</guid>
      <description>What political label do you give yourself?
Yesterday, I blogged about calling myself a Republican. I was a kid.
Then, from about 1996 on, I called myself a conservative.
Over the past year or so, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken on the label of libertarian. Now, a simple online test confirms that I&amp;rsquo;m a right-leaning conservative. [Take the test yourself]
That&amp;rsquo;s exciting, because I feel like I need a new label.
Labels Matter I know there was a movement a couple of years ago to abolish political and ideological labels.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>