<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tocqueville on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tocqueville/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tocqueville on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 21:31:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tocqueville/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Which Freedoms Are We Losing? </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</guid>
      <description>I confess.
When I write about freedoms lost, I don&amp;rsquo;t itemize the freedoms. I don&amp;rsquo;t feel too bad, though, because almost no one does. Itemizing sucks.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s hard work. &amp;ldquo;Losing freedom,&amp;rdquo; takes about three seconds to type and less time to read. Listing freedoms,on the other hand, takes that much time just to highlight all the freedoms and click the un-ordered list button. God forbid I find myself working in straight HTML and have to hand-type &amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Would Buckley Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/upon-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 09:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/upon-time/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to be William F. Buckley Jr. All I lacked was his intellect, education, and unique experiences.
Well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be him. I wanted to be the next one.
Every day, I wrote a 750-word piece. Poorly. I believed that practice would improve my writing.
It didn&amp;rsquo;t.
One day, I realized, as long as I tried to be the next William F. Buckley, I was destined for frustration and failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wait ‘til These Kids Meet the Tax Man</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/08/wait-til-these-kids-meet-the-tax-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 14:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/08/wait-til-these-kids-meet-the-tax-man/</guid>
      <description>When the rules become so complicated and convoluted that well-meaning people unwittingly break the law, the legal system has lost its moral authority.
Students at Georgetown University are discovering the horrors of, what Tocqueville called “small complicated rules, minute and uniform, through which the most original minds and the most energetic characters cannot penetrate, to rise above the crowd.”
An editorial in The Hoya, the official student newspaper, students advocate “eliminating bureaucracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditate on This, Why Don’t You?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/01/meditate-on-this-why-dont-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/01/meditate-on-this-why-dont-you/</guid>
      <description>I was 18 and a college freshman. It was a Tuesday night in October. My 1970 Chevy Impala felt wide open in the fifty-degree air and the smell of freshly fallen leaves.
I drove through Forest Park feeling the rhythm of the yellow street lights as I moved between light and dark. &amp;ldquo;Memory&amp;rdquo; from Cats came on the radio. I lit a Camel (no filter).
I was free.

In America, we often think of independence as a collective thing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>