<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Brown on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/michael-brown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Michael Brown on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 17:54:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/michael-brown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gratitude Is Not a Privilege</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/27/gratitude-not-privilege/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 17:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/27/gratitude-not-privilege/</guid>
      <description>Gratitude, like love, is bound only by our choices. The more we give, the more we keep.
I tried to ignore Ferguson today, but I glanced at Twitter hashtag #Ferguson a moment ago. The first tweet I read inspired this post. Someone wrote that &amp;ldquo;being able to be thankful after #Fergson is a privilege itself.&amp;rdquo;
I understand how someone could feel that their &amp;ldquo;gratitude privilege&amp;rdquo; had been revoked. We lost our daughter just before Christmas in 1994, about four weeks after I got out of the Navy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Have Just One Chance for October Surprise</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 16:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/26/democrats-just-one-chance-october-surprise/</guid>
      <description>The White House and its corrupt Department of Justice has one chance to change the election&amp;rsquo;s outcome.According to Nate Silver&amp;rsquo;s FiveThirtyEight blog, the GOP has a 62.1 percent chance of a Senate majority. With nine days left until the election, and with President Obama&amp;rsquo;s approval and likability plunging, the Democrats face a huge loss.
Apathetic Democrats Many political observers blame Democrat voter apathy, particularly among African-Americans. The black vote that swelled in 2008 and 2012 with Obama on the ballot shows signs of deflating in 2014 as it did in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Create Hate and Discontent in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/17/create-hate-discontent-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 18:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/17/create-hate-discontent-america/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t written about Ferguson because I&amp;rsquo;ve known too little to add value. But ignorance hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped others from stirring up hate and discontent. For example, Missouri&amp;rsquo;s shakedown artist, Lacy Clay.
Lacy Clay, speaking from a private island in the Carribean, told the St. Louis Post-Dispatch that Michael Brown was murdered. Clay knew or should have known the effect of his words: more violence. Either Clay meant to incite violence or he has a casual disregard for the effect of his irresponsible speech.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>