<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jack Kemp on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jack-kemp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jack Kemp on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:36:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jack-kemp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Kemp Stood for Civil Rights . . . And America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</guid>
      <description>Jack Kemp is on the top of my wall of heroes. Literally. An autographed Kemp card sits on top of my bookshelf housing the works and images of my heroes.
As the NFL self-destructs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth reading about Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s work for civil rights. And for the Republican Party. And for conservatism.
Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s Activism Kemp did it all. And, thanks to Jeffrey Lord, we can remember Kemp&amp;rsquo;s finest moments of civil rights activism:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Misdirection Play</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/19/trumps-misdirection-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 22:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/19/trumps-misdirection-play/</guid>
      <description>Everybody loves misdirection. It makes magic shows and movies interesting. You think you know what happens next, then WHAM! the unexpected happens. Now you&amp;rsquo;re plugged in.
Trump gave a head fake. Everybody bought it. (Including me.) Then his legs went the other way, and we stand here flailing at the air. Some people&amp;rsquo;s heads exploded on CNN. BOOM! I&amp;rsquo;ll reveal the real misdirection in a moment. You&amp;rsquo;ll love it.
After declaring &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to change&amp;rdquo; and hiring Stephen K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatever Happened to the Party of Ideas?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</guid>
      <description>From about 1978 until the Monica Lewinsky fiasco, the GOP was called &amp;ldquo;the party of ideas.&amp;rdquo; I miss the ideas.
William F. Buckley helped. Buckley liked big ideas and smart people. He liked politicians who gave legs to great ideas and governors with the guts to experiment. Governor Ronald Reagan appeared on Buckley&amp;rsquo;s Firing Line shortly after the Gipper became California&amp;rsquo;s governor. Reagan talked about many ideas he was trying or hoping to try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s the One Thing Congress Should Push Right Now?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/03/whats-the-one-thing-congress-should-push-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/03/whats-the-one-thing-congress-should-push-right-now/</guid>
      <description>It’s not the Balanced Budget Amendment, though that’s a good second choice.
It’s certainly not senseless and impossible ideas like impeaching Obama or suing over birth certificates.
Instead, we should push an idea that’s ripe for quick passage. It’s an idea that cheers political moderates and conservatives. And it doesn’t immediately turn off liberals.
What is it?
It’s an old idea that Jack Kemp championed for decades. It’s an idea that I’ve written about many times before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sad News About Jack Kemp</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/07/sad-news-about-jack-kemp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 00:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/07/sad-news-about-jack-kemp/</guid>
      <description>The first time I met George W. Bush in person, I was campaigning for Jack Kemp for President. Kemp was running against Vice President George H. W. Bush (and 47 others) for the Republican nomination. This was 1987.
A wonderful, tough, and tireless local Republican organizer named Thelma Stuart recruited me and served as my mentor in Dixiecrat-style politics of South Carolina. My first gig was manning the Kemp booth at the Low Country Stump Days in Charleston.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>