<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jo Ann Emerson on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jo-ann-emerson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jo Ann Emerson on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 01:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jo-ann-emerson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is Exactly How The Special Election To Replace Jo Ann Emerson Will Be Conducted. (We Think)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/05/here-is-exactly-how-the-special-election-to-replace-jo-ann-emerson-will-be-conducted-we-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/05/here-is-exactly-how-the-special-election-to-replace-jo-ann-emerson-will-be-conducted-we-think/</guid>
      <description>I’ve gotten a lot of emails and comments asking for more information on the special election process in Missouri’s 8th Congressional District. So I went to the smartest person I know about this stuff: Frieda Keough.
Here’ what I learned:
 Eddie Justice, the Chair of the 8th Congressional District will call a meeting. Anyone wanting to be appointed to run for the 8th Congressional District shows up at the meeting and will be put before the committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Lloyd Smith and Jo Ann Emerson Plan This All Along?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</guid>
      <description>In an open Republican primary in Missouri’s 8th Congressional District, a solid conservative would beat an establishment &amp;ldquo;my turn&amp;rdquo; Republican, hands down. And the Missouri GOP would hate it.
That’s why I smell a rat. Would you be surprised to learn that Jo Ann Emerson and Lloyd Smith had this switcheroo planned months ago? You have to admit that the timing is suspicious:
 * Emerson wins a certain re-election * Smith announces he&#39;s stepping down as Missouri GOP Executive Director * Emerson announces she&#39;s resigning to become Queen of Lobbyists * Missouri&#39;s GOP Establishment breaks hips to tell reporters &amp;quot;Lloyd Smith&#39;s our man!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>