<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>global-warming on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/global-warming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in global-warming on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 17:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/global-warming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The UN Game</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/the-climate-agreement-from-game-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 17:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/the-climate-agreement-from-game-theory/</guid>
      <description>The UN is a game with many players.
The UN makes money by convincing member nations that the costs of funding the UN are less than the costs of not funding it.
The UN wants to grow as large as possible, like any organization or organism or rear end.
The UN is already very large. Its last budget was $5.4 billion, and that represented a 2.9 percent reduction from the previous two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the AP, Huffpo, and Business Insider Lie About Climate</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/22/ap-huffpo-business-insider-lie-climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 21:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/22/ap-huffpo-business-insider-lie-climate/</guid>
      <description>Dina Spector breathlessly reports that &amp;ldquo;December Heat Wave Smashes Temperature Records In New York City&amp;rdquo; on Business Insider. Her hysteria relies on a Huffington Post piece which relies on an AP story.
And they&amp;rsquo;re all wrong.
I checked with NOAA on record temperature maximums in the US on December 21, 2013. There were none.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14162&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;941&amp;rdquo;] NOAA Record Highs for 12/21/2013[/caption]
The &amp;ldquo;record&amp;rdquo; high temperature that Dina, HuffPo, and AP reported was from an unofficial thermometer in Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonishing Science: Sun May Cause Global Warming</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/astonishing-science-sun-may-cause-global-warming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 10:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/astonishing-science-sun-may-cause-global-warming/</guid>
      <description>Unbelievable! Scientists have discovered that the huge, glowing fireball in the sky may affect Earth’s temperature.
The latest evidence comes from . . . the Moon.
Back when we used to send astronauts to the Moon, we placed some temperature sensors on the Moon’s surface. We still monitor those sensors.
Guess what they show. Yep, you’re right! As temperatures rose on Earth, temperatures rose on the Moon.

Watts Up With That has all the details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Hansen Indicts Democracy; Can&#39;t Find His Rubber Duckies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/19/james-hansen-indicts-democracy-cant-find-his-rubber-duckies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 03:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/19/james-hansen-indicts-democracy-cant-find-his-rubber-duckies/</guid>
      <description>James Hansen told some idiots who are bored enough to listen to the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost global warming fraudster that democracy is destroying the planet. This is the James Hansen who&amp;rsquo;s been cooking NASA books for a decade to try to cover his 20-year-old error about CO2 and global warming.
Meanwhile, 90 rubber ducks that NASA dropped on Greenland glaciers to track the speed of melting have never made it to the sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Horrible Week for Global Warming Industry</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/30/another-horrible-week-for-global-warming-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 12:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/30/another-horrible-week-for-global-warming-industry/</guid>
      <description>The GDP might have contracted 5.4 percent annualized in 4Q08, but the AGW industry contracted about 50 percent in one week:
Hansen’s Boss: James Hansen, AGW’s Father of Lies, received an insulting, public rebuke from his old boss at NASA. In essence, Dr. John Theon of the Institute for Global Environmental Strategies, accused of Hansen of violating basic scientific principles, NASA’s scientific methodologies and policies, and of embarrassing the agency with his anti-scientific screeds on global warming.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>