<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Warning: The Volcanoes Are Coming</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-volcanoes-are-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 22:10:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-volcanoes-are-coming/</guid>
      <description>File this one under &amp;ldquo;As If We Don&amp;rsquo;t Have Enough to Worry About.&amp;rdquo;
We could be entering an age of revolution around the world, and I blame the sun.
Solar Maxima/Solar Minima The sun goes through ~11 year cycles of high activity (solar maxima with lots of solar flares and sunspots) and low activity (solar minima with few solar flares and sunspots). NASA projected April 2020 (+/- 6 months) as the trough of the current cycle, number 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leave the Gun Take the Cannolis</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/leave-the-gun-take-the-cannolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 20:10:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/leave-the-gun-take-the-cannolis/</guid>
      <description>Via WGEM:
 Illinois Gov. J.B. Pritzker responded Friday afternoon to President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s statement earlier in the day where Trump said he had deemed churches and other houses of worship &amp;ldquo;essential&amp;rdquo; and called on governors to allow them to reopen this weekend.
During his COVID-19 press briefing on Friday afternoon, Gov. Pritzker said Illinois would continue to operate on the basis of science and data.
 If JB Pritzker, governor of Illinois, took science and data seriously, he&amp;rsquo;d drop about 280 pounds fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The President&#39;s Authority to Open Churches Is the Constitution - VIDEO RANT</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/presidents-authority-to-open-churches-is-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 13:57:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/presidents-authority-to-open-churches-is-constitution/</guid>
      <description>The morons in the White House press corps spend most of today&amp;rsquo;s briefing screaming at press secretary Kayleigh McEnany about President Trump&amp;rsquo;s order to re-open all churches.
The oft-repeated (shouted) question: &amp;ldquo;What federal law is the president relying on to require states to allow church services?&amp;rdquo;
The question demonstrates the absolute ignorance and laziness, the besst-like stupidity, of most journalists.
  The president&amp;rsquo;s authority is the United States Constitution, you mouth-breathing swine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lyda Krewson and the Joy of Dictatoring</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/lyda-krewson-and-the-joy-of-dictatoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 08:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/lyda-krewson-and-the-joy-of-dictatoring/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis, Missouri, consistently makes everyone&amp;rsquo;s top 10 lists for worst cities in the United States. The reasons given include crime, lack of opportunity, and dilapidated neighborhoods. Having grown up in the city, and with most of my family still living there, I can add to that list unreliable city services, terrible roads, cronyism, and less than ideal weather.
[Cities People Can&amp;rsquo;t Flee Fast Enough: St. Louis Number 4]
Mayors can&amp;rsquo;t do anything about the weather, of course, but St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should I Wear a Mask</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/masks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 12:59:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/masks/</guid>
      <description>Go ahead and wear a mask, especially if a merchant requires you to, or if not wearing a mask will cause someone undue anxiety. It&amp;rsquo;s charitable.
Also, if you&amp;rsquo;re highly active (get out a lot), you should probably wear a mask and wash your hands if you&amp;rsquo;re going to be around people who are more likely to suffer severely from Coronavirus: the elderly, the obese, people with chronic conditions. While we&amp;rsquo;re at it, basic practices our grandmothers taught us should always apply:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>