<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Humane Approach to Coronavirus Is to Open Up Everything</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-humane-approach-to-coronavirus-open-up-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 10:04:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-humane-approach-to-coronavirus-open-up-everything/</guid>
      <description>The most human approach to Coronavirus is to let it spread without overwhelming the hospitals in any location. Mitigation orders, such as wearing masks, stay-at-home orders, and maintaining six feet of distance, while well-intentioned, actually prolong the agony except in places that are in danger of overwhelming the hospital system.
The idea that we can maintain this near-complete shutdown of society for as long as Coronavirus exists is a recipe for disaster on a Biblical scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Short Movie for Our Time</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/perfect-short-movie-for-our-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 20:47:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/perfect-short-movie-for-our-time/</guid>
      <description>No need for set-up. This is simply the perfect short movie for our time.
Please watch and share widely. Especially with your snitch friends.
  God bless Kevin James.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Reaches 48th Place on Genocide List</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/cuomo-reaches-48th-place-on-genocide-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 19:20:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/cuomo-reaches-48th-place-on-genocide-list/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK—New York Governor Andrew Cuomo&amp;rsquo;s nursing home genocide passed the Chittagong Hill Tracts genocide of 1977 to take sole possession of 48th place in the all-time genocide list, according to Genocide Watch International. Cuomo is now only 3,100 deaths away from overtaking Slobodan Milošević&amp;rsquo;s Bosnian genocide of 1992 to 1995 for 47th.
All-time list of Greatest Genocides via Wikipedia
  Over 5,200 nursing home residents in New York died to Coronavirus as a result of Cuomo&amp;rsquo;s policy of placing elderly Coronavirus patients in otherwise disease-free facilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today, Watergate Became the Second Worst Abuse of Power in American History</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/watergate-now-second-worst-abuse-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 15:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/watergate-now-second-worst-abuse-of-power/</guid>
      <description>Releasing national security intercepts to unauthorized persons is a federal felony punishable by 10 years in prison. And at least one of the names on this list of top Obama Administration officials is guilty beyond a reasonable doubt. 18 U.S. Code § 798(a)(4):
 Whoever knowingly and willfully communicates, furnishes, transmits, or otherwise makes available to an unauthorized person, or publishes, or uses in any manner prejudicial to the safety or interest of the United States or for the benefit of any foreign government to the detriment of the United States any classified information—obtained by the processes of communication intelligence from the communications of any foreign government, knowing the same to have been obtained by such processes—Shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than ten years, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Former Obama Officials Tired of His Drunken, Late-Night Calls</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/former-obama-officials-tired-of-his-drunken-late-night-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 20:12:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/former-obama-officials-tired-of-his-drunken-late-night-calls/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON — Members of the so-called &amp;ldquo;Obama Alumni Association&amp;rdquo; feel harassed and abused by the former president whose late-night, drunken conference calls have become annoying, frequent, and less coherent as time goes on.
Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View has learned that Obama began these occasional conference calls with a handful of former officials about six months after leaving office in 2017. Over time, the 44th president stopped following a semi-weekly schedule of planned calls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>