<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Livingcare on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/livingcare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Livingcare on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 15:08:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/livingcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Neediness</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/neediness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/neediness/</guid>
      <description>President Trump is teaching the world a huge lesson. That valuable lesson goes something like this:
Don&amp;rsquo;t be needy.
Jim Camp is a world-famous negotiation coach. Jim has led some enormous negotiations: labor disputes, huge multi-national buys, and mergers. This is is what Jim says about neediness in his book Start With No:
 It is absolutely imperative that you as a negotiator understand the importance of this point. You do NOT need this deal, because** to be needy is to lose control and make bad decisions**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Can Missouri Legislators Learn From 19th Century St. Louis Politicians?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/13/what-can-missouri-legislators-learn-from-19th-century-st-louis-politicians/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/13/what-can-missouri-legislators-learn-from-19th-century-st-louis-politicians/</guid>
      <description>I’ll let one of my favorite thinkers, St. Louis native Don Peppers, tell about St. Louis in 1850:
 My hometown of St. Louis, Missouri was the largest city west of the Mississippi River in 1850, and the second largest port city in the entire country. Only New York handled more tonnage than the riverboats that docked, often more than a hundred at a time, at the St. Louis levee. Among other things, the riverboats supplied equipment, people, horses, and other materials to a burgeoning population of pioneers who rode wagon trains out from St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why You Are Underemployed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</guid>
      <description>If you can’t find full-time work, blame Obamacare.

One reason the Middle Class has shriveled and wages shrunk over the the past four years is underemployment. People want full time work, but settle for anything. And anything is usually part time.
Most of the fantastic new jobs created since the 2009 have been part-time jobs.
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, 14.6% of Americans want a full-time job but settle for part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What’s Great About the Supreme Court’s Obamacare Decision</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</guid>
      <description>In the Ronald Reagan movie Kings Row, Reagan plays Drake McHugh, whose legs are sawn off by a sadistic, class-conscious doctor.

Everyone remembers the line “Where’s the rest of me?” No remembers what happens after that. I’ll fill you in.
McHugh’s best friend, a psychiatrist, decides to tell McHugh (Reagan) the truth: his legs were perfectly healthy, but the doctor cut them off to keep the lower class McHugh from pursuing the doctor’s debutante daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s One Way the Government&#39;s Making Medicine Worse in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 02:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</guid>
      <description>I had to go to the doctor today. The reason&amp;rsquo;s not important. Here&amp;rsquo;s what is:
It took my doctor 10 minutes to describe my symptoms into a government-mandated voice recognition system.   
In the old days, the doctor took notes. Now, he has to recite his observations into a Mad Men-era dictaphone. &amp;ldquo;Male, age 48, blood pressure one-twenty-one over seventy-three . . . &amp;quot;
The damn machine (government medical technology) couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand half the doctor&amp;rsquo;s words.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>