<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Livingcare on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/livingcare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Livingcare on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 15:08:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/livingcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Neediness</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/neediness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/neediness/</guid>
      <description>President Trump is teaching the world a huge lesson. That valuable lesson goes something like this:
Don&amp;rsquo;t be needy.
Jim Camp is a world-famous negotiation coach. Jim has led some enormous negotiations: labor disputes, huge multi-national buys, and mergers. This is is what Jim says about neediness in his book Start With No:
 It is absolutely imperative that you as a negotiator understand the importance of this point. You do NOT need this deal, because** to be needy is to lose control and make bad decisions**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Can Missouri Legislators Learn From 19th Century St. Louis Politicians?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/13/what-can-missouri-legislators-learn-from-19th-century-st-louis-politicians/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/13/what-can-missouri-legislators-learn-from-19th-century-st-louis-politicians/</guid>
      <description>I’ll let one of my favorite thinkers, St. Louis native Don Peppers, tell about St. Louis in 1850:
 My hometown of St. Louis, Missouri was the largest city west of the Mississippi River in 1850, and the second largest port city in the entire country. Only New York handled more tonnage than the riverboats that docked, often more than a hundred at a time, at the St. Louis levee. Among other things, the riverboats supplied equipment, people, horses, and other materials to a burgeoning population of pioneers who rode wagon trains out from St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why You Are Underemployed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</guid>
      <description>If you can’t find full-time work, blame Obamacare.

One reason the Middle Class has shriveled and wages shrunk over the the past four years is underemployment. People want full time work, but settle for anything. And anything is usually part time.
Most of the fantastic new jobs created since the 2009 have been part-time jobs.
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, 14.6% of Americans want a full-time job but settle for part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What’s Great About the Supreme Court’s Obamacare Decision</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</guid>
      <description>In the Ronald Reagan movie Kings Row, Reagan plays Drake McHugh, whose legs are sawn off by a sadistic, class-conscious doctor.

Everyone remembers the line “Where’s the rest of me?” No remembers what happens after that. I’ll fill you in.
McHugh’s best friend, a psychiatrist, decides to tell McHugh (Reagan) the truth: his legs were perfectly healthy, but the doctor cut them off to keep the lower class McHugh from pursuing the doctor’s debutante daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s One Way the Government&#39;s Making Medicine Worse in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 02:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</guid>
      <description>I had to go to the doctor today. The reason&amp;rsquo;s not important. Here&amp;rsquo;s what is:
**It took my doctor 10 minutes to describe my symptoms into a government-mandated voice recognition system. **
In the old days, the doctor took notes. Now, he has to recite his observations into a Mad Men-era dictaphone. &amp;ldquo;Male, age 48, blood pressure one-twenty-one over seventy-three . . . &amp;quot;
The damn machine (government medical technology) couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand half the doctor&amp;rsquo;s words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Health Insurance Solution that Some Smart State Should Try</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/a-health-insurance-solution-that-some-smart-state-should-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2012 15:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/29/a-health-insurance-solution-that-some-smart-state-should-try/</guid>
      <description>The term “United States” is both plural (many states united) and singular (the United States). The tag line “e pluribus unum” loses its meaning if we cease to be many, if we give up our identities as individual states. As states, we are as different from each other as the United States is from Canada.
The United States are most powerful pursuing opportunities and fixing problems in the plural but defending in the singular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of the GOP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-state-of-the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/the-state-of-the-gop/</guid>
      <description>by Bill Hennessy and Jim Durbin
John Knowles’s classic novel, A Separate Peace, begins memorably:
 I went back to the Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there fifteen years before . . . as if a coat of varnish had been put over everything for better preservation.
 I get precisely the opposite feel when I look at the Republican Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCOTUS Reality Tour</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/scotus-reality-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/scotus-reality-tour/</guid>
      <description>By now you’ve seen the sensational headlines:
* People Are Saying That Obama&#39;s Healthcare Law Got Massacred At The Supreme Court Today*  Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/politics#ixzz1qMjfnTtF** Here Is The Moment When Justice Alito Shredded Verrilli At The Obamacare Hearings* Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/politics#ixzz1qMjjQXFM** Skeptical Kennedy signals trouble for Obama&amp;rsquo;s healthcare law** Supreme Court Health Care Law: Justices Come Down Hard On The Mandate
And so it goes.
Before we start dancing in the streets, let’s face a little reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s War on Catholics Has Nothing To Do With Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Obama’s dictate that Catholic organizations must participate in contraception and abortion has nothing to do with healthcare or rights or contraception or anything of the sort. Not at all. Modern dictatorships don’t operate that way.
**Obama just destroyed the free practice clause of the First Amendment, and that’s exactly what he intended. **
 Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Are We For?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/what-are-we-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 17:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/what-are-we-for/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back, the Christian Science Monitor asked me to write an op-ed. The subject was, “If the Tea Party ran America, how would things change; and why do you think you’ll win?”
The call was my opportunity to break from the easy, unassailable position that things are bad and getting worse. It meant coming up with a solution or two. And solutions already find disagreement somewhere.
For over a year I’ve said that the Tea Party movement, begun out of anger, must shift its energy over time from anger to solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>