<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Victory Field House on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/victory-field-house/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Victory Field House on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/victory-field-house/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If We Don’t Flip Some Toss-Up States, Romney, Ryan, and the USA Are Screwed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</guid>
      <description>Choosing Paul Ryan as his running mate was a great Romney move. Looking ahead, Romney sees movement conservatives working hard right up to the election—even if he or his advisors continues to say stupid things. That was necessary.
SCROLL DOWN FOR TWO IMPORTANT EVENTS THIS WEEK
But it wasn’t enough to win the election and unseat America’s first anti-American president. To do that, we must find a way to win over the selfish middle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Candy Crowley: Tea Party Groups Resemble the 13 Colonies, Not the Balkans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</guid>
      <description>Analogies say more about the speaker than about the subject.
Candy Crowley told KMOX Radio listeners on Friday that Tea Party groups resemble the Balkans without guns.
Wrong. Crappy analogy, Candy. The diverse and autonomous, often quarrelsome,** Tea Party groups remind me of the original 13 colonies.**
The colonies were divided on just about every subject imaginable. The disagreed on slavery, on economics, on agraculture, manufacturing, cities, names &amp;ndash; name it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>