<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>export-import on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/export-import/</link>
    <description>Recent content in export-import on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:53:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/export-import/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: White House Shuffles Export Import Management (parody)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/28/breaking-white-house-shuffles-export-import-management-parody/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/28/breaking-white-house-shuffles-export-import-management-parody/</guid>
      <description>Washington (APP) —In a Rose Garden press conference today, President Barack Obama introduced Art Vandelay as his choice to head the troubled Export Import Bank for a five-year term, pending approval by the Senate.
The shake-up comes as Congress debates whether or not to extend the bank’s authorization amid heavy opposition from conservative and libertarian groups led by Heritage Action for America.
Mr. Vandelay brings almost 30 years of experience in the export-import business, where he traded in commodities as varied as potato chips, diapers, and matches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Export Import Bank Matters Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/18/why-the-export-import-bank-matters-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 01:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/18/why-the-export-import-bank-matters-now/</guid>
      <description>Start small&amp;ndash;end big.
Raise your hand if you know someone who woke one morning and ran a marathon having never so much as walked around the block.
No hands?
Of course not. A few freaks of nature might be able to go from zero to 26.2 in no time, but most people would hurt themselves trying. And never do it again.
When a sane sedentary person decides to run a marathon, he starts by walking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Ann Wagner Is Wrong to Attack Heritage Action</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 02:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</guid>
      <description>Accountability? We don&amp;rsquo;t need no stinking accountability.
 No, Ann Wagner didn&amp;rsquo;t actually say that. But her comments to a 2nd District Republican committee meeting on Tuesday gave at least one attendee the impression that Mrs. Wagner opposes the idea of conservatives holding Congress accountable.
Ann Wagner Attacks the Conservative Heritage Action Rep. Ann Wagner accused the conservative Heritage Action for America of &amp;ldquo;pitting Republican against Republican&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;never attacking Dems&amp;rdquo; at the Republican meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Export-Import Bank Story the Post-Dispatch Refused to Print</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/export-import-bank-story-post-dispatch-refused-print/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 21:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/export-import-bank-story-post-dispatch-refused-print/</guid>
      <description>Since the Post won&amp;rsquo;t run my reply a recent op-ed about the Ex-Im Bank, I&amp;rsquo;ll publish it here:
Huge multi-national corporations like to preach from the &amp;ldquo;small business&amp;rdquo; bible when it comes to the Export-Import bank. Unfortunately, most of the Ex-Im propaganda about how &amp;ldquo;small business&amp;rdquo; benefits crumbles under scrutiny.
Professor Stanford Levin of Southern Illinois University recently wrote an Op-Ed supporting reauthorization of the Export Import Bank. As the professor states, the Export-Import Bank provides cheap loans to foreign companies and governments with which to buy products sold by mostly large, multi-national companies with headquarters in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah Goldberg Perfectly Defines the GOP Establishment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 18:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</guid>
      <description>I hope you read Jonah Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s short article on National Review Online last week. If not, you missed the best definition of Establishment Republicans EVER!
Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s piece also exploded the myth of &amp;ldquo;pro-business&amp;rdquo; way too many conservatives believe. Conservatism isn&amp;rsquo;t pro-business, it&amp;rsquo;s pro-market. I&amp;rsquo;ll let Jonah explain:
 Just to clarify, the difference between being pro-business and pro-market is categorical. A politician who is a “friend of business” is exactly that, a guy who does favors for his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>