<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boston Marathon on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/boston-marathon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boston Marathon on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 18:06:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/boston-marathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thin-Slicing, Experts, and the Power of the Human Brain Help Capture Suspect Two Alive</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/20/thin-slicing-experts-and-the-power-of-the-human-brain-capture-suspect-two-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 18:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/20/thin-slicing-experts-and-the-power-of-the-human-brain-capture-suspect-two-alive/</guid>
      <description>The police in Watertown responded magnificently. But the most brilliant strategic move gets little notice from the press.

For about sixteen hours, hundreds of law officers, FBI agents, helicopters, and satellites scoured a relatively tiny area of Boston suburbs for one wounded terrorist. At the same time, they kept the public relatively safe, off the streets, and out of the way of their manhunt.
**But they didn’t find their man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Boston Marathon Bombing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/15/thoughts-on-boston-marathon-bombing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 02:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/15/thoughts-on-boston-marathon-bombing/</guid>
      <description>. . . What Your Definition of Terrorism Is I heard a lot of people giving their opinions of what constitutes “terrorism.” Here’s the United States Code:
 Definitions &amp;hellip; the term &amp;lsquo;terrorism&amp;rsquo; means premeditated, politically motivated violence perpetrated against noncombatant targets by subnational groups or clandestine agents;
 Let’s stick with that one. To be terrorism, all of these five elements must be present. You can use it as a checklist:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is What Evil Looks Like In Action **UPDATES**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/15/this-is-what-evil-looks-like-in-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 20:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/15/this-is-what-evil-looks-like-in-action/</guid>
      <description>This is a Vine clip of the first explosion at the Boston Marathon. Fox 25 in Boston reported moments ago that organizers confirmed that bombs caused the explosions. Clearly many casualties.
“For the sake of His sorrowful passion, have mercy on us and on the whole world.”
UPDATES
   Saudi National Suspected
   CNN&amp;rsquo;s Wolf Blitzer Implicates anti-tax conservatives
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>