<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2015 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2015 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Could Be a Very Bad Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/2016-bad-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 17:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/2016-bad-year/</guid>
      <description>People act according to what they expect.
And that, my friends, could be very bad news for the economy in 2016.
Social psychologists and usability experts both know that people&amp;rsquo;s words often conflict with their actions. This is especially true when asking people to predict their own behavior in a hypothetical.
For example, one study asked people to predict whether they would buy flowers for a charity. Eight-three percent of respondents said, &amp;ldquo;yes I would,&amp;rdquo; but only 43 percent actually did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missourians can access military bases after January 10</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/how-missourians-can-access-military-bases-after-january-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 16:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/how-missourians-can-access-military-bases-after-january-10/</guid>
      <description>Need to visit a federal building or military base after January 10? Your Missouri DL won&amp;rsquo;t work by itself.
If you have a Missouri drivers license or ID card but you do not have a passport or military ID, bring your Social Security card or your birth certificate.
That&amp;rsquo;s the word I got from Navy Recruit Training Command, Great Lakes.
The Department of Homeland Security informed Missouri last week that our state&amp;rsquo;s drivers licenses and ID cards will no longer serve as identification at federal agencies after January 10, 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why New York Drops the Ball at Midnight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/heres-why-new-york-drops-the-ball-at-midnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 13:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/heres-why-new-york-drops-the-ball-at-midnight/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, in the days of sundials and pendulum clocks, people needed a way to agree on the time. For instance, if my watch says 11:13 and your watch says 1:32, who&amp;rsquo;s right?
One way to coordinate time in a city or a sea port was a time ball placed somewhere highly visible. People could use the ball to set their pocket watches, and use their pocket watches to set their other clocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One thing the military teaches that business school doesn&#39;t</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/30/one-thing-the-military-teaches-that-business-school-doesnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 21:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/30/one-thing-the-military-teaches-that-business-school-doesnt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What was the biggest adjustment for you going from the military to the business world?&amp;rdquo;
Several people have asked me that question, and my answer always surprises them.
&amp;ldquo;In the military,&amp;rdquo; I say, &amp;ldquo;every individual has a lot more latitude and authority to act. In the business world, no one can do anything without explicit instructions.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Really? I thought it would be the other way around,&amp;rdquo; they say.
&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the popular culture, but the truth is one-hundred eighty degrees the other way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did the Pritzkers Donate to Greitens?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, the blog Progressives Today ran an attack piece on Eric Greitens for two of his donors (link). The piece generated of lot angst and fury on the right side of social media.
**Turns out the story was pretty shoddy journalism. **
Progressives Today didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to look at the Pritzkers&amp;rsquo; other donations or the military museum they founded. If they had, they&amp;rsquo;d know that Jennifer N. Pritzker (formerly James N.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>