<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2015 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2015 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Could Be a Very Bad Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/2016-bad-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 17:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/2016-bad-year/</guid>
      <description>People act according to what they expect.
And that, my friends, could be very bad news for the economy in 2016.
Social psychologists and usability experts both know that people&amp;rsquo;s words often conflict with their actions. This is especially true when asking people to predict their own behavior in a hypothetical.
For example, one study asked people to predict whether they would buy flowers for a charity. Eight-three percent of respondents said, &amp;ldquo;yes I would,&amp;rdquo; but only 43 percent actually did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Missourians can access military bases after January 10</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/how-missourians-can-access-military-bases-after-january-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 16:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/how-missourians-can-access-military-bases-after-january-10/</guid>
      <description>Need to visit a federal building or military base after January 10? Your Missouri DL won&amp;rsquo;t work by itself.
If you have a Missouri drivers license or ID card but you do not have a passport or military ID, bring your Social Security card or your birth certificate.
That&amp;rsquo;s the word I got from Navy Recruit Training Command, Great Lakes.
The Department of Homeland Security informed Missouri last week that our state&amp;rsquo;s drivers licenses and ID cards will no longer serve as identification at federal agencies after January 10, 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why New York Drops the Ball at Midnight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/heres-why-new-york-drops-the-ball-at-midnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 13:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/31/heres-why-new-york-drops-the-ball-at-midnight/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, in the days of sundials and pendulum clocks, people needed a way to agree on the time. For instance, if my watch says 11:13 and your watch says 1:32, who&amp;rsquo;s right?
One way to coordinate time in a city or a sea port was a time ball placed somewhere highly visible. People could use the ball to set their pocket watches, and use their pocket watches to set their other clocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One thing the military teaches that business school doesn&#39;t</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/30/one-thing-the-military-teaches-that-business-school-doesnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 21:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/30/one-thing-the-military-teaches-that-business-school-doesnt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What was the biggest adjustment for you going from the military to the business world?&amp;rdquo;
Several people have asked me that question, and my answer always surprises them.
&amp;ldquo;In the military,&amp;rdquo; I say, &amp;ldquo;every individual has a lot more latitude and authority to act. In the business world, no one can do anything without explicit instructions.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Really? I thought it would be the other way around,&amp;rdquo; they say.
&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the popular culture, but the truth is one-hundred eighty degrees the other way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did the Pritzkers Donate to Greitens?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, the blog Progressives Today ran an attack piece on Eric Greitens for two of his donors (link). The piece generated of lot angst and fury on the right side of social media.
**Turns out the story was pretty shoddy journalism. **
Progressives Today didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to look at the Pritzkers&amp;rsquo; other donations or the military museum they founded. If they had, they&amp;rsquo;d know that Jennifer N. Pritzker (formerly James N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Can Happen Again—The Big Short Movie</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/24/it-can-happen-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 10:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/24/it-can-happen-again/</guid>
      <description>“You know how when you walk into a post office you realize there is such a difference between a government employee and other people,” said Vinny. “The ratings agency people were all like government employees.”
 The Big Short: Inside the Doomsday Machine (movie tie-in) (Movie Tie-in Editions) (p. 156). W. W. Norton &amp;amp; Company. Kindle Edition.
I wanted to blame the government.
Like millions of American conservatives, I had developed a powerful narrative of the way the world works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Posts of 2015</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/23/top-10-posts-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/23/top-10-posts-2015/</guid>
      <description>With 2015 winding down, here are the most read posts on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View in the last year. Clearly, the governor&amp;rsquo;s race is the top story. In reverse order (most read on bottom).
The GOP&amp;rsquo;s Sad New Whisper Campaign View
Is Earth&amp;rsquo;s Axis Shifting? View
Can John Brunner&amp;rsquo;s Consultant Do His Duty? View
Paris Attacks Expose Narcissists of Mizzou View
Analysis of Governor Poll View
Providence and Hope in Missouri View</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party Like It&#39;s 1992</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/22/party-like-its-1992/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 20:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/22/party-like-its-1992/</guid>
      <description>Five for five.
The first five people who told me they supported Trump in 2015 also supported Ross Perot in 1992.
I realize it&amp;rsquo;s a tiny sample size. Still, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty clear that Donald Trump is the reincarnation of H. Ross Perot. Conservatives&amp;ndash;all conservatives and all center-right voters&amp;ndash;need to come to terms with that fact. We must also deal with the realities of the 2016 election and choose a strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri&#39;s 2016 Electorate Very Different from 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/21/missouris-2016-electorate-different-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/21/missouris-2016-electorate-different-2012/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to the number of potential voters, 2016 is shaping up to be a watershed year in Missouri politics.
Take at look at this chart of generational voters in 2008 and 2012:
(Source: Missouri Census Data Center)
Where Did the Millennials Come From? Leaving biology out of it, it&amp;rsquo;s simple: 2016 will be the first election in which the entire Millennial cohort is old enough to vote. Plus Millennial-aged immigrants have increased their numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to Choose</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/its-time-to-choose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 05:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/its-time-to-choose/</guid>
      <description>I am a mess.
I am a terrible father, a crappy husband (ask my ex-wives), and a difficult employee. I do a lot of things poorly. Most things, in fact. Especially the things I &amp;ldquo;have&amp;rdquo; to do. Authority irritates me.
While I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at following plans, I write a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of blogs on Saturday and Sunday mornings. The pattern keeps me sane. Or semi-sane. I supplement those when events warrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GOP Establishment Is a Cancer on America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/the-gop-establishment-is-a-cancer-on-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/20/the-gop-establishment-is-a-cancer-on-america/</guid>
      <description>Former Florida governor Jeb Bush, appearing Thursday on ABC’s “Good Morning America,” said that “of course” he would back Trump, should he emerge triumphant at next year’s GOP convention in Cleveland. “We need to be unified, we need to win,” Bush said.
 &amp;ndash;The Washington Post, September 3, 2015
The Republican Establishment has exposed itself as a political disease willing to kill its host. Unless we seek treatment and remove the tumor first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Short</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/19/the-big-short/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 17:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/19/the-big-short/</guid>
      <description>The Big Short: Inside the Doomsday Machine by Michael Lewis My rating: 5 of 5 stars
Capitalists are like children and free marketers are like their parents.
If the free marketers neglect their duties to feed, protect, teach, and discipline capitalists, some well-meaning but inept government agency will impose itself into the parenting role, destroying the lives of everyone involved and wasting trillions of tax dollars (borrowed from future generations) in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest Post: My Night With the Klan, Part 3</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/16/guest-post-my-night-with-the-klan-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 23:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/16/guest-post-my-night-with-the-klan-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s Note: This article from 1992 tells a remarkable story of one man&amp;rsquo;s brave visit to a KKK rally. The stories Lee present serve a cautionary tale: human nature abhors a vacuum. When leaders fail to lead, humanity cries out. And, to paraphrase Steven King, who knows what dread thing will answer.
Bear in mind that this rally took place in 1992. George H.W. Bush was president, and the Golden Age of Ronald Reagan was only 3 years in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Strangedebate (or how I learned to stop worrying and love the GOP)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/16/dr-strangedebate-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 06:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/16/dr-strangedebate-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-the-gop/</guid>
      <description>“I’ll build a wall . . . and I’ll make Donald Trump pay for it.” — Ted Cruz
Line of the night in the last GOP Presidential debate of the year of our Lord two thousand and fifteen.
This was the most telling debate of all. And it shouldn’t have happened.
The more you know about anything, the less you like it. That’s a scientific fact.
That’s why the &amp;ldquo;love of your life&amp;rdquo; when you were dating is the &amp;ldquo;lump on the couch&amp;rdquo; 20 years later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest Post: My Night With the Klan, Part 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/15/guest-post-my-night-with-the-klan-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/15/guest-post-my-night-with-the-klan-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s Note: This article from 1992 tells a remarkable story of one man&amp;rsquo;s brave visit to a KKK rally. The stories Lee present serve a cautionary tale: human nature abhors a vacuum. When leaders fail to lead, humanity cries out. And, to paraphrase Steven King, who knows what dread thing will answer.
Bear in mind that this rally took place in 1992. George H.W. Bush was president, and the Golden Age of Ronald Reagan was only 3 years in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest Post: My Night With the Klan, Part 1</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/14/guest-post-my-night-with-the-klan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 23:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/14/guest-post-my-night-with-the-klan/</guid>
      <description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s Note: This article from 1992 tells a remarkable story of one man&amp;rsquo;s brave visit to a KKK rally. The stories Lee present serve a cautionary tale: human nature abhors a vacuum. When leaders fail to lead, humanity cries out. And, to paraphrase Steven King, who knows what dread thing will answer.
Bear in mind that this rally took place in 1992. George H.W. Bush was president, and the Golden Age of Ronald Reagan was only 3 years in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The UN Game</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/the-climate-agreement-from-game-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 17:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/the-climate-agreement-from-game-theory/</guid>
      <description>The UN is a game with many players.
The UN makes money by convincing member nations that the costs of funding the UN are less than the costs of not funding it.
The UN wants to grow as large as possible, like any organization or organism or rear end.
The UN is already very large. Its last budget was $5.4 billion, and that represented a 2.9 percent reduction from the previous two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the Cardinals’ Reign Over?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/is-the-cardinals-reign-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 06:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/is-the-cardinals-reign-over/</guid>
      <description>Imagine a world in which the Cardinals are not perennial champions. Major league baseball could be working on that scenario right now.
The 1970s in Southwest St. Louis The Red Bird Express ran from Ivanhoe to Busch Stadium along Arsenal Street. For about seven dollars, I could get to a game and back, including bus fare, a bleacher ticket, and a hotdog and soda. My mom didn’t know how many times I made that trip, often for day games while she worked at St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America is for Americans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/09/america-is-for-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 01:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/09/america-is-for-americans/</guid>
      <description>Dave: You hear from your folks, Mooch? Moocher: Yeah, my dad called. He wanted to know if the house was sold. He could use the money something fierce. Dave: Well, you can come and live with me when it&amp;rsquo;s sold. In Italy, everybody lives together. Moocher: [laughs] Since you won that Italian bike, man, you&amp;rsquo;ve been acting weird. You&amp;rsquo;re really getting to think you&amp;rsquo;re Italian, aren&amp;rsquo;t you? Cyril: I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind thinking I was someone myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unbearable Lightness of Being There</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/the-unbearable-lightness-of-being-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 03:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/the-unbearable-lightness-of-being-there/</guid>
      <description>Eve: May I ask your name? Chance: Chance. Eve: Chance? Chance: Chance, the gardener. Eve: Chauncey Gardiner? Mr. Chauncey Gardiner. Are you related to Basil and Perdita Gardiner?
 &amp;ndash; Being There, 1979
 People tell us who they are, but we ignore it. Because we want them to be what we we want them to be.
 &amp;ndash;Don Draper, Mad Men
President Obama used his third Oval Office address in seven years to say &amp;ldquo;Honey, I shrunk the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loretta Lynch Mob **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/i-could-go-to-jail-for-this-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 18:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/i-could-go-to-jail-for-this-post/</guid>
      <description>“I think it’s important that as we again talk about the importance of free speech we make it clear that actions predicated on violent talk are not America,&amp;rdquo; said Lynch. &amp;ldquo;They are not who we are, they are not what we do, and they will be prosecuted.” (source: Daily Wire)
 Take a slide on the slippery slope.
Yesterday I warned that thePC Police will soon call for summary incarceration of anyone who violates the rules of their nationwide “safe space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police LT Mike Madden Paints Picture of Jihadi Death</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/police-lt-mike-madden-paints-picture-of-jihadi-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 16:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/police-lt-mike-madden-paints-picture-of-jihadi-death/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/siLsflWdhz8
Remarkable account of massacre by a police lieutenant who arrived first on the scene in San Bernardino.
Notice the difference between his reaction and the reactions of the left.
H/T Lee Presser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up From Political Correctness</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/05/up-from-political-correctness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 18:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/05/up-from-political-correctness/</guid>
      <description>I won’t blame the neighbors, but the neighbors knew.
Syed Farook and four or five others worked long hours in Farook’s San Bernardino garage for months leading up to a deadly Islamic terror attack last week.
Neighbors knew. They knew Farook and his Pakistani wife, Tashfeen Malik, were up to no good. But the neighbors said nothing until after the massacre at a center for the developmentally disabled.
**The suspicious neighbors were afraid, not of the Muslim terrorists, but of political correctness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Conversion Odyssey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/01/the-conversion-odyssey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 05:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/01/the-conversion-odyssey/</guid>
      <description>John Dos Passos has a mesmerizing name.
The &amp;ldquo;John&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t fit the &amp;ldquo;Dos Passos,&amp;rdquo; does it? Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be Juan Dos Passos?
But John Dos Passos was one of the Four Horsemen of American literature in the first half of the 20th century. And all four horsemen were Nomads, according to generational historians Howe and Strauss.
The Nomads Wander Left to Right I&amp;rsquo;m a Nomad, too. Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m drawn to Hemingway, Faulkner, Fitzgerald, and Dos Passos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I know it was you, Fredo</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/29/fredo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 23:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/29/fredo/</guid>
      <description>Fredo Corleone: I&amp;rsquo;m your older brother, Mike, and I was stepped over! Michael Corleone: That&amp;rsquo;s the way Pop wanted it. Fredo Corleone: It ain&amp;rsquo;t the way I wanted it! I can handle things! I&amp;rsquo;m smart! Not like everybody says&amp;hellip; like dumb&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m smart and I want respect!
 —The Godfather: Part II
I&amp;rsquo;m sure John Brunner never saw himself as Fredo Corleone.
A Burning Question Did you ever ask yourself why John Brunner would release a surreptitious recording of a phone call with an opponent?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Story of Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/26/the-real-story-of-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 17:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/26/the-real-story-of-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>Thanksgiving celebrates the Pilgrims&amp;rsquo; break from socialism.
Schools and textbooks avoid the topic, but it&amp;rsquo;s worth remembering. The Plymouth and Jamestown plantations were dying under &amp;ldquo;common store&amp;rdquo; approach. Only by establishing a free market did the settlers thrive.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the beginning of Kent Dillon&amp;rsquo;s excellent story of Thanksgiving, which you can continue reading in its entirety at The Mises Institute:
By Kent Dillon
 The celebration of Thanksgiving is a celebration of plenty and appreciation of the abundance that has characterized the free enterprise, individualistic, capitalistic systems of the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John “The Weasel” Brunner</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/24/john-the-weasel-brunner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 05:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/24/john-the-weasel-brunner/</guid>
      <description>RADAR: Did you lose something, sir? HAWKEYE: Hi, Stinky. RADAR: Uh, sir, that&amp;rsquo;s the sort of name that kind of sticks with a fella. I&amp;rsquo;d appreciate it if you&amp;rsquo;d just call me by my given nickname.
 —MAS*H
Some names stick with a fella.
A friend emailed the link and this note:
 Brunner is indeed a weasel
 John Brunner, candidate for governor, surreptitiously recorded a phone conversation with his opponent Eric Greitens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slay Poverty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/24/francis-slay-is-a-terrible-host/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 01:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/24/francis-slay-is-a-terrible-host/</guid>
      <description>Paul Berry III made me laugh out loud. “Francis Slay hung out the vacancy sign but he’s running the Bates Motel.&amp;quot;
We were talking about the Syrian refugees and Francis Slay’s insistence that hosting a lot of them is in the city’s vital interest.
Leaving aside the question of security and vetting for the refugees, why does Francis Slay want so desperately to host more people who have no jobs, no language, and little hope of flourishing in a city that, on most measures, is failing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our military leaders are no Pattons</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/our-leaders-are-no-pattons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 23:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/our-leaders-are-no-pattons/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, Lee Presser made a great point in this guest post, The Only Rule of Engagement Will Be Victory. As one commenter noted:
 This is the best analysis of the war on terror that I have read. If we do not fight to win, we shouldn’t be in the fight. Winning the war on terror starts with 1) admitting there is a war on terror, 2) being willing to confront the enemy with force, 3) fighting to win the war rather than appease the enemy, and 4) do whatever it takes to protect Americans and their homeland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mizzou Protests Were About Abortion All Along</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/mizzou-protests-abortion-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 12:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/mizzou-protests-abortion-along/</guid>
      <description>I hate to say &amp;ldquo;I told you so.&amp;rdquo;
But the St. Louis Post Dispatch has found that I may have been right on November 8. That&amp;rsquo;s when I made the outlandish comment that the whole race issue at Mizzou is actually an abortion issue. I suspected that Planned Parenthood&amp;rsquo;s vast lobbyist network is agitating leaders of left-leaning organizations trying to create general unrest.
**The manipulators would use campus racial unrest to demand restored privileges for Planned Parenthood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Only Rule of Engagement Will Be Victory</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/21/the-only-rule-of-engagement-will-be-victory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2015 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/21/the-only-rule-of-engagement-will-be-victory/</guid>
      <description>Guest Post by Lee Presser
When FDR sent the troops to fight World War 2, he sent them to win. Since 1945, the political class has not given America’s military that clear instruction when being sent to war. Political considerations have modified the goal of winning. In Korea, it was fight but do not anger the Chinese. In Viet Nam, it was fight but do not attack the enemy if they are standing on the other side of line drawn on a map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The torch has been passed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/18/the-torch-has-been-passed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 01:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/18/the-torch-has-been-passed/</guid>
      <description>I feel old.
It’s not my knees or my eyes. Nothing physical. It’s bigger than that.
Be Kind to Him, World My mom framed a column she read in the St. Louis Globe Democrat in about 1969, just about the time I started kindergarten. The Globe title was “Be Kind To Him, World,” but Dan Valentine’s orginal title was “Dear World.”
That column moved from place to place in our house most of the time I lived at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s time for Democrats to abandon Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/18/its-time-for-democrats-to-abandon-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/18/its-time-for-democrats-to-abandon-obama/</guid>
      <description>In the war on terror, you’re on our side or theirs.
Barack Obama announced that he will veto any attempt by Congress to require background checks of Syrian refugees in an attempt to weed out ISIS terrorists. The President&amp;rsquo;s allegiances are now clear.
I heard Senator Dick Durbin (D-IL) say that we must ensure proper screening in the wake of last Friday’s Islamic terrorist attack in Paris.
The House of Representatives is working on legislation to do just that: increase the likelihood that we will catch terrorist infiltraters before they reach American soil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week: November 15, 2015</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/15/the-week-november-15-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/15/the-week-november-15-2015/</guid>
      <description>Viva la France This week, let&amp;rsquo;s say a special prayer for the people of France. And the whole world.
Mayor Slay About to Change Tune on Refugees On September 11, St. Louis Mayor Francis Slay announced plans to accept 10,000 non-Christian Syrian refugees to St. Louis. After the coordinated attacks by ISIS terrorists in Paris on Friday, expect the mayor come under intense pressure to change plans. News that at least one of the Paris attackers entered France from Serbia as a Syrian war refugee will only intensify the pressure on Slay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paris Attacks Expose The Narcissists of Mizzou</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/14/paris-attacks-expose-the-narcissists-of-mizzou/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/14/paris-attacks-expose-the-narcissists-of-mizzou/</guid>
      <description>People tell us who they are, but we ignore it. Because we want them to be what we want them to be.
 &amp;ndash;Mad Men
You can&amp;rsquo;t make this stuff up.
Concerned Student 1950, the group that seized public ground for private use at the University of Missouri has a new concern today. It seems the kiddos are upset that ISIS deigned to steal the headlines by killing 120 to 150 people in Paris, wounding 200 others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we need in America is more Irish</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/10/what-we-need-in-america-is-more-irish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 23:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/10/what-we-need-in-america-is-more-irish/</guid>
      <description>Disclosure: I am Irish.
I know the politically correct way to say it is Irish-American. The accurate way to say it is American of Irish descent.
But I grew up in South St. Louis where we were just Irish. And the Italians were Italian and the Germans were German. (That&amp;rsquo;s about all we had in my neighborhood, plus a few Jewish converts to Catholicism, but they caucused with the Germans.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hysterical Yale student embarrasses herself on video</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/09/hysterical-yale-student-embarrasses-herself-on-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 02:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/09/hysterical-yale-student-embarrasses-herself-on-video/</guid>
      <description>Nicholas Christakis is a giant in social psychology.
And social psychology is only part of his resume. He&amp;rsquo;s also a medical doctor.
Christakis wrote one of the most important books on social networks (the real kind, not Facebook), Connected: The Surprising Power of Our Social Networks. He holds distinguished positions at both Yale and Harvard and has appeared on Time Magazine&amp;rsquo;s list of 100 Most Influential People in the World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/09/the-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 12:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/09/the-week/</guid>
      <description>Ben Carson The press can&amp;rsquo;t find people who will corroborate Ben Carson&amp;rsquo;s low opinion of himself as a young man. And somehow we&amp;rsquo;re supposed to believe that reflect poorly on Dr. Carson. It reflects poorly on journalism, for sure, but it actually shows that people who knew Dr. Carson won&amp;rsquo;t speak ill of him. Nice problem to have.
Weather Was the weather wonderful this weekend, or what? I hope you got out, even if just to do some yard work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are abortionists manipulating Mizzou&#39;s black athletes?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/08/are-abortionists-manipulating-mizzous-black-athletes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 18:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/08/are-abortionists-manipulating-mizzous-black-athletes/</guid>
      <description>A few Mizzou football players announced they&amp;rsquo;re boycotting all sports activities until University of Missouri system president Tim Wolfe quits or is fired. Considering the football team&amp;rsquo;s dismal performance, the cynic in me wonders if sitting out might help the players&amp;rsquo; chances of getting an NFL draft.
The players and other African-American students at Mizzou believe they are victims of &amp;ldquo;systematic oppression&amp;rdquo; and they want Tim Wolfe to fix it simply by resigning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to be wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/07/learning-to-be-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 16:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/07/learning-to-be-wrong/</guid>
      <description>I am wrong a lot.
When I was 25, I was wrong a lot, too.
The difference between 1988 and 2015 is not that I&amp;rsquo;m particularly smarter now, but that I&amp;rsquo;m used to being wrong. Somewhere along life&amp;rsquo;s journey, I realized two things:
*1. Being wrong isn&amp;rsquo;t the end of the world. *2. Being wrong is the beginning of learning.
When I was 25, I refused to admit being wrong about anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Debate for Bad Journalists</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/28/the-debate-for-bad-journalists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 03:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/28/the-debate-for-bad-journalists/</guid>
      <description>When Jim Cramer asks a question, you know everything&amp;rsquo;s all boogered up.
The first hour of the GOP Presidential Debate from Colorado will go down as the first official event of the post-journalism world. The debate ended with John Harwood lying about the debate&amp;rsquo;s length. Having been an occasional guest of Larry Kudlow, I&amp;rsquo;m being nice. But the CNBC reporters couldn&amp;rsquo;t write a story for my high school newspaper.
On the substance of what the candidates said, this was the best debate so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservatism Is The New Black</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/15/conservatism-is-the-new-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 02:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/15/conservatism-is-the-new-black/</guid>
      <description>What has 50 years of loyalty to Democrats won for African-Americans?
If you answered &amp;ldquo;civil rights legislation,&amp;rdquo; you better look at who voted for the laws and who opposed. (Hint: Republicans yea, Democrats nay.)
Welfare? In 1967 the poverty rate was 14 percent. In 2014, the poverty rate was 14 percent. In the interim, we pissed away $22 trillion on bureaucratic sex junkets to Costa Rica and massive government office buildings in every major city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is What Democracy Looks Like</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/14/this-is-what-democracy-looks-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 03:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/14/this-is-what-democracy-looks-like/</guid>
      <description>The headline is a play on the oft-chanted slogan from OWS protests. Please, no &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s not a democracy&amp;rdquo; emails.
That&amp;rsquo;s a threat.
A couple years ago on a Saturday night, I wrote about 2,000 words on the meaning of &amp;ldquo;democracy&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;republic.&amp;rdquo; I never posted it out of pity for you. I&amp;rsquo;m telling you, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of Montesquieu in it, so if you don&amp;rsquo;t like superfluous vowels, don&amp;rsquo;t make me post it now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whip It. Whip It Good.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/11/whip-it-whip-it-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/11/whip-it-whip-it-good/</guid>
      <description>Maybe Ann Wagner&amp;rsquo;s the problem.
Rep. Ann Wagner (HA-64) is the House Majority Whip. Her job is to know how every GOP member will vote on bills and to cut deals until House leadership gets the numbers it wants.
It&amp;rsquo;s unfathomable that a majority whip would not have seen the Kevin McCarthy meltdown coming long before the House Republican caucus met to nominate a candidate for speaker. But many accounts suggest that the Republican House leadership thought McCarthy had the votes up to the moment he withdrew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Send Dan Hyatt to Jefferson City</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/27/send-dan-hyatt-to-jefferson-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 04:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/27/send-dan-hyatt-to-jefferson-city/</guid>
      <description>**On Tuesday, September 29th at 7:00 p.m., please join Dan Hyatt as he formally announces his candidacy for the Missouri House of Representatives, 72nd District at the Maryland Heights Community Center, 2344 McKelvey Rd., Maryland Heights, MO 63043. **
Suggested donation is $25. Gold donor $100.
RSVP danhyatt4missouri@gmail.com
We got to know Dan Hyatt at an After Party at Sky Music Lounge back in about 2011.
Dan quickly chose a mission for himself: red light and speed cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The MTC&#39;s Newest Fight Is For Its Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/22/the-mtcs-newest-fight-is-for-its-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 11:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/22/the-mtcs-newest-fight-is-for-its-life/</guid>
      <description>Uber X St. Louis rolled into existence on Friday.
No, Uber did not win the Metropolitan Taxicab Commission&amp;rsquo;s permission to operate. Instead, the ride-sharing service filed a federal anti-trade suit against the MTC.
In the first weekend, Uber X provided over 5,000 rides, mostly from people leaving bars between 10 p.m. and 3 a.m. In other words, by defying the MTC, Uber X kept 5,000 drunk drivers off the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why can&#39;t presidential candidates talk like this?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/17/why-cant-presidential-candidates-talk-like-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 14:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/17/why-cant-presidential-candidates-talk-like-this/</guid>
      <description>Called upon to undertake the duties of the first executive office of our country, I avail myself of the presence of that portion of my fellow-citizens which is here assembled to express my grateful thanks for the favor with which they have been pleased to look toward me,** to declare a sincere consciousness that the task is above my talents, and that I approach it with those anxious and awful presentiments which the greatness of the charge and the weakness of my powers so justly inspire**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate writing this post</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-hate-writing-this-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 03:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-hate-writing-this-post/</guid>
      <description>I like to say I hate electoral politics.
Maybe I just want people to think I&amp;rsquo;m the kind of person who hates electoral politics. (We are all capable of being wrong about ourselves.)
I have to say, briefly, that this was the most encouraging Republican debate since . . . 1980? These are all serious people, and I&amp;rsquo;m including Trump. They all love America, and not just what they might get from America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am honored to question the GOP candidates for you and Heritage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-am-honored-to-question-the-gop-candidates-for-you-and-heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 12:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-am-honored-to-question-the-gop-candidates-for-you-and-heritage/</guid>
      <description>This is pretty cool and a little unnerving.
Heritage Action has extended the honor to be one of three Heritage Action Sentinels to question Republican Presidential candidates on Friday, September 17 in Greenville, South Carolina. So far, 12 candidates have confirmed, including Donald Trump, Jeb Bush, Ben Carson, Carly Fiorina, Ted Cruz, Scott Walker, Rick Santorum, Bobby Jindal, Rand Paul, Chris Christie, and Marco Rubio. (Maybe Trump will make fun of my tie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Is No Liberty Without Pursuit of Happiness</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/15/there-is-no-liberty-without-pursuit-of-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/15/there-is-no-liberty-without-pursuit-of-happiness/</guid>
      <description>What did Jefferson mean by “pursuit of happiness” as an unalienable right?
If you’ve heard it was a substitute for “property” because Jefferson feared Southerners would equate property with slaves, you heard wrong.
For weeks I have repeated a foundational belief of conservatism: every person deserves the dignity of meaningful work and the freedom to pursue happiness.
But what does it mean to pursue happiness? What did Jefferson mean? And why did Locke consider pursuit of happiness essential to liberty?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get to Westport Plaza on September 26 at 11:00 a.m.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/14/get-to-westport-plaza-on-september-26-at-1100-a-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 02:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/14/get-to-westport-plaza-on-september-26-at-1100-a-m/</guid>
      <description>If you read this blog, you have a mile-wide curiosity streak.
Many of you want to know more about Eric Greitens.
You have a great chance to learn more on Saturday, September 26 at 11:00 a.m.
Eric Greitens will have some things to say. Perhaps he won&amp;rsquo;t say everything you want to hear. (It&amp;rsquo;s still 11 months until the primary.) But he&amp;rsquo;ll say things you need to hear.
And that&amp;rsquo;s my favorite thing about Eric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump: The final nail in the conservative coffin?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/10/trump-the-final-nail-in-the-conservative-coffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 22:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/10/trump-the-final-nail-in-the-conservative-coffin/</guid>
      <description>So many battles are fought in war and in civilian life, and nothing is gained by their victory. Every battle we fight will result in a gain for us or we will not fight . . . There is no great gain in merely being right. To be right about some unimportant subject is not important.
 &amp;ndash;General George S. Patton
Jonah Goldberg explains the problem of Trump better than anyone:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Welfare Reform Must Continue</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/09/why-welfare-reform-must-continue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 22:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/09/why-welfare-reform-must-continue/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I missed this.
It&amp;rsquo;s the story of Marienthal Austria.
Marienthal was a town in Austria that thrived thanks to a single employer. When the flax mill went out of business in 1932, Marienthal&amp;rsquo;s population became mostly unemployed.
Thanks to Austria&amp;rsquo;s liberal unemployment programs that replaced up to 90 percent of income, no one in Marienthal plunged into economic poverty as a result of the mill&amp;rsquo;s closing. But spiritual poverty was another story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why poverty is a conservative issue</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/08/why-poverty-is-a-conservative-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/08/why-poverty-is-a-conservative-issue/</guid>
      <description>Oh but now old friends they&amp;rsquo;re acting strange, They shake their heads, they say I&amp;rsquo;ve changed Well something&amp;rsquo;s lost, but something&amp;rsquo;s gained In living every day. &amp;ndash;Joni Mitchell, Both Sides Now
 I&amp;rsquo;ve looked at poor from both sides now.
I get a lot of grief for pushing poverty solutions. And service. Many conservatives believe Mitt Romney was right when he uttered his infamous 47 percent line.
In case you forgot:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Same-Sex Marriage Is a Tax Problem</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/07/same-sex-marriage-is-tax-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 16:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/07/same-sex-marriage-is-tax-problem/</guid>
      <description>Why is government involved in marriage at all? Taxes.
Brian Bollmann makes an excellent point about same-sex marriage.
Brian points out in this post that marriage is not a matter for government; contract law is. Government&amp;rsquo;s only concern in the case of a marriage is with its contractual implications:
 At some point in the short history of the United States (and certainly after the Civil War), state governments stepped onto the wall of separation and began getting involved in the religious institution of marriage in the appropriate area of protecting the rights to property – especially that of women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Out What I&#39;ve Been Up To</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/02/find-out-what-ive-been-up-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 04:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/02/find-out-what-ive-been-up-to/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for the dearth of posts.
You know I have a day job. Sometimes that day job becomes a night job. And a weekend job, too.
That&amp;rsquo;s happened.
I&amp;rsquo;m still keeping up on what&amp;rsquo;s going on in the world, but travel and software launches and strategic plans have me spinning.
I like to write when I have a long periods of uninterrupted time. Well, those blocks of time have been few and far between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Worst-Case Scenario?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/26/republicans-worst-case-scenario/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 00:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/26/republicans-worst-case-scenario/</guid>
      <description>Things are getting bad for Hillary.
I hear she&amp;rsquo;s losing a lot of support from Democrat Party insiders, at least in private. The DNC is meeting this week, and talk will likely surround an alternative Democrats can vote for.
While Republicans enjoy the Clinton meltdown, we might want to be careful what we wish for.
One of the GOP&amp;rsquo;s best hopes for the White House is voter enthusiasm. Republicans can&amp;rsquo;t wait to vote, Democrats dread it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Correction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/25/correction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 01:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/25/correction/</guid>
      <description>Something weird happened in the stock market today.
Yesterday I blogged about the stock markets. I&amp;rsquo;d been up early to see what was going on in Europe and Asia. I was watching US futures, too.
I decided to write about what might happen. And I told you about Ben Hunt, my favorite economics writer. Ben combines remarkable knowledge of game theory and psychology with his genius in finance and economics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Good, Bad, and Ugly</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/24/trump-good-bad-and-ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 21:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/24/trump-good-bad-and-ugly/</guid>
      <description>There seems to be a certain air of inevitability that Trump will win the GOP nomination for President. According to a new poll, 57 percent of Republican voters expect that Trump will be the party&amp;rsquo;s candidate next year. Why is that important?
Expectations Beat Preferences It&amp;rsquo;s important because expectations are far better predictors of actual winners than preference polls. From a 2012 NY Times story by David Leonhardt:
 Over the last 60 years, poll questions that asked people which candidate they expected to win have been a better guide to the outcome of the presidential race than questions asking people whom they planned to vote for, the study found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Note on Market</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/24/quick-note-on-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/24/quick-note-on-market/</guid>
      <description>I was up early this morning sifting through the market stories.
** Asia: crash ** Middle East: crash ** Europe: crash ** USA: set to open
There&amp;rsquo;s good news in all this loss. First, stocks were overpriced. At some point, they will bottom out and it will be time to start buying. Second, the Golden Age of the Central Banker seems to be over. And that is very good news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results of the Cabinet Matching Game</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/23/results-of-the-cabinet-matching-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 17:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/23/results-of-the-cabinet-matching-game/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, I published a simple game for political nerds. Assuming the next president must build a cabinet from current candidates for the Republican nomination for president, how would you assign candidates to cabinet positions.
This was meant to be a fun exercise for people who spend too much time thinking about politics. Like the leaders-eat-last poll, this required hide, often dissatisfying choices. As a result, only six people completed the exercise which took up to a half hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Immigration Fans Need to Read Wong Kim Ark</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 04:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/trumps-immigration-fans-need-to-read-wong-kim-ark/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s sad that Donald Trump has inspired so many good conservatives to promote fantasies about the 14th Amendment.
The Supreme Court addressed the issue of birthright citizenship directly, and Mark Levin and Laura Ingram know it. They are Constitutional lawyers.
Both Levin and Ingraham are familiar with United States v. Wong Kim Ark (1898) which established, thoroughly, that citizenship by birth has been the law of the land since before the Declaration of Independence and was codified by the 14th Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fascinating Results from Leaders Eat Last Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</guid>
      <description>This is the story of hard choices and how people resist making them.
Last week&amp;rsquo;s poll asked you to watch a video by Simon Sinek before answering two, simple, two-part questions: which Republican candidate for President and Missouri Governor is most likely and least likely to eat last?
I intended the poll to be hard. Not complicated, not long, but emotionally challenging.
Why the Poll Was Emotionally Challenging For several weeks, I have built a case for the importance of leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Really Left in the GOP Field?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/18/whos-really-left-in-the-gop-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 23:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/18/whos-really-left-in-the-gop-field/</guid>
      <description>If you lack a unique, differentiating value, your only play is price.
In business, you command the price play by being very, very big and very, very efficient. In presidential politics, you&amp;rsquo;re unique or you close up shop and go home. Commodities don&amp;rsquo;t win executive offices. Usually.
Even though it&amp;rsquo;s early, only four Republican candidates for president have differentiating value propositions:
** Ben Carson ** Donald Trump ** Carly Fiorina ** Ted Cruz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Question for Carly Fiorina</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/18/one-question-for-carly-fiorina/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 10:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/18/one-question-for-carly-fiorina/</guid>
      <description>The next US President must be a great communicator.
Distilling complex and controversial problems into mental models accessible to large numbers of people is not deception&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s brilliance. The reason we hang onto sound bites isn&amp;rsquo;t because we&amp;rsquo;re stupid&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s because we&amp;rsquo;re busy. We all don&amp;rsquo;t have time to earn masters-degree understanding of every issue facing society and government. Honest, accurate distillations of the complex ideas allow us to choose and act quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is The Difference Between Leadership and Service?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/16/what-is-the-difference-between-leadership-and-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 01:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/16/what-is-the-difference-between-leadership-and-service/</guid>
      <description>Marine Corps officers eat last.
That simple insight inspired the title of Simon Sinek&amp;rsquo;s latest book, &amp;ldquo;Leaders Eat Last.&amp;rdquo; If I could influence high school or college curricula, no one would graduate without successfully completing a semester course on that principle.
Below is another remarkable video of Simon Sinek discussing how circumstances can override our desire to lead and serve and how leadership and service can fix almost any problem. But first, I&amp;rsquo;d like you think a bit more about these two critical needs: leadership and service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Have a New Son, America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/15/you-have-a-new-son-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/15/you-have-a-new-son-america/</guid>
      <description>My son Patrick (closest to the camera at a civilian’s idea of parade rest) listens to the instructions of the enlisting officer among 9 young men and women preparing to swear an oath to the Constitution of the United States. They were here to make their first commitment to the armed forces.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_16700&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;711&amp;rdquo;]Patrick Hennessy takes the oath of enlistment at the Federal Building in St. Louis August 14, 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Leadership?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/14/what-is-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 16:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/14/what-is-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Many of you loved Simon Sinek’s Start With Why TEDx talk.
I love the way Simon Sinek thinks. It’s no surprise, then, that his TED Talk on leadership could be the greatest definition of leadership I’ve ever heard.
Please watch and share. I have some thoughts and a poll following. [ted id=1998]
Contrasts give greater clarity. Sinek’s contrast between military leadership and business leadership says a lot about the state of American business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were Once the Party of Ideas and Optimism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/13/we-were-once-the-party-of-ideas-and-optimism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 04:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/13/we-were-once-the-party-of-ideas-and-optimism/</guid>
      <description>On my desk is a book titled &amp;ldquo;Grinning With the Gipper.&amp;rdquo;
It&amp;rsquo;s 117 pages of Ronald Reagan&amp;rsquo;s humor.Think of that. A US president who could fill a book with jokes.
My cursory review shows that about 60 percent of the jokes are on Reagan himself. And another 20 percent are on Republicans.
Ronald Reagan knew that life is too short and too precious to waste it on anger and pride. Better to spend your days getting laughs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Smart Phones Are More Popular Than the Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/why-smart-phones-are-more-popular-than-the-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/why-smart-phones-are-more-popular-than-the-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Does it bother you that people would give up essential freedoms before they’d give up their iPhone?
 While 26 percent of Americans report that they can’t live without their smartphone, only 20 percent of Americans say they can’t live without sex, according to this infographic compiled by FinancesOnline.com, a personal finance website.
 Seriously.
It should bother you. [olympus_highlight color=&#39;yellow]Without essential freedoms, smart phones can be taken away or banned[/olympus_highlight].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Compassionate Alternative to Raising the Minimum Wage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/we-can-do-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 10:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/we-can-do-better/</guid>
      <description>The headline is depressing, but I&amp;rsquo;m going to write it anyway:
America&amp;rsquo;s Slums Are Exploding
The story is in the Atlantic, a progressive publication. But they admit what so many Americans know: the welfare state has failed those who needed it most. And it&amp;rsquo;s failing those never needed it but were sucked into it nonetheless.
 Half a century after President Lyndon B. Johnson declared a war on poverty, the number of Americans living in slums is rising at an extraordinary pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Sell Conservative Principles</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/how-to-sell-conservative-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 21:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/how-to-sell-conservative-principles/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re still asking &amp;ldquo;why bother?&amp;rdquo; read this.
If you still believe conservatism is an economic theory, read this.
If you&amp;rsquo;re ready to [olympus_highlight color=&amp;quot;yellow&amp;rdquo;]create a transformational social movement that improves lives[/olympus_highlight] by providing every America with the dignity of meaningful work and the freedom to pursue happiness, watch this video. It&amp;rsquo;s Simon Sinek&amp;rsquo;s TEDx talk about his then-new book, Start With Why, and it&amp;rsquo;s the most powerful idea I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request for Interview: Police Foot Patrol</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/request-for-interview-police-foot-patrol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 16:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/request-for-interview-police-foot-patrol/</guid>
      <description>If you have walked a neighborhood foot beat as a police officer, I&amp;rsquo;d like to talk to you.
I am working on a story on policing, and I would like to hear stories from men and women who have both walked neighborhoods as police officers and driven patrols in cruisers.
If interested, please contact me with this form:
[contact-form to=&#39;billhennessy@me.com&amp;rsquo; subject=&#39;Police Foot Patrol Response&amp;rsquo;][contact-field label=&#39;Name&amp;rsquo; type=&#39;name&amp;rsquo; required=&#39;1&amp;rsquo;/][contact-field label=&#39;Email&amp;rsquo; type=&#39;email&amp;rsquo; required=&#39;1&amp;rsquo;/][contact-field label=&#39;Comment&amp;rsquo; type=&#39;textarea&amp;rsquo;/][contact-field label=&#39;Police Department&amp;rsquo; type=&#39;text&amp;rsquo; required=&#39;1&amp;rsquo;/][/contact-form]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Has a Job To Do</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</guid>
      <description>We believe that meaningful work dignifies and enriches human lives.
[olympus_highlight color=&amp;quot;yellow&amp;rdquo;]Every person who wants to work should find a choice of occupations to pursue. And every occupation improves the life of the person doing the work, the people the work is done for, and the family and community in which the worker lives.[/olympus_highlight]
The more workers engaged in meaningful work, the better our country becomes.
The opposite of work is not idleness but dependency, and dependency degrades human lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day of Hope, Prayer, and Clean-up in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/a-day-of-hope-prayer-and-clean-up-in-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 23:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/a-day-of-hope-prayer-and-clean-up-in-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Dellena Jones’s 911 Hair Salon was attacked at about 11:15 PM by a small band of young men. The break-in and robbery occurred close to the time of the first shooting. The hair salon is less than 100 yards from the scene of the shooting.
But that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop volunteers from St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and friends from helping.
[caption width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;quot;attachment_16631&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo;]Volunteers pose for a picture after helping clean and repair 911 Hair Salon in Ferguson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>911 Beauty Salon Targeted by Looters. Please Help</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/911-beauty-salon-targeted-by-looters-please-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 12:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/911-beauty-salon-targeted-by-looters-please-help/</guid>
      <description>Our adopted Ferguson business, the 911 Beauty Salon, appears to have been a target of looters tonight according to KTVI 2.
[olympus_cta button_text=&amp;quot;Donate Now&amp;rdquo; button_color=&amp;quot;red&amp;rdquo; button_url=&amp;quot;https://www.gofundme.com/911hairsalonferg&amp;rdquo;]Don&amp;rsquo;t Let the Looters Win! Save 911[/olympus_cta]
Dellena Jones&amp;rsquo;s business was already struggling. She didn&amp;rsquo;t need this.
Let&amp;rsquo;s prove that we believe in free enterprise entrepreneurship. That we can help our neighbors.
You can donate to help Dellena on this GoFundMe project
[olympus_cta button_text=&amp;quot;Donate Now&amp;rdquo; button_color=&amp;quot;red&amp;rdquo; button_url=&amp;quot;https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Really Want Your Principles to Win?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/do-you-really-want-your-principles-to-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 10:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/do-you-really-want-your-principles-to-win/</guid>
      <description>in a democratic system, the minority is by definition the opposition. Their de facto position is fighting against the ideas of the other side. Political minorities fight against something that’s more powerful than they are. And over time, their entire self-identity can become utterly reliant on acting like the principled underdog. &amp;ndash;Arthur C Brooks, The Conservative Heart
 My developmental psychology professor told a story of a female patient. The woman came to him for help with dating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overnight in Ferguson: &#34;A remarkable amount of gunfire out there&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/overnight-in-ferguson-a-remarkable-amount-of-gunfire-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 08:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/overnight-in-ferguson-a-remarkable-amount-of-gunfire-out-there/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis County Police Chief Jon Belmar told reporters &amp;ldquo;there was a remarkable amount of gunfire out there,&amp;rdquo; describing the scene on W. Florissant last night.
A shooter confronted plain-clothes officers and opened fire. Officers returned fire, striking the suspect. The suspect is in critical, unstable condition in a local hospital. One officer was treated, but the severity and cause of his injury is unknown.
The shooting and at least one break-in of a business marred what had been peaceful commemorations of the death of Michael Brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible video of shooting in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/incredible-video-of-shooting-in-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 07:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/incredible-video-of-shooting-in-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Watch. You can see the shooter in a white t-shirt.
https://youtu.be/fZmpmVdIfJU
We can make a difference.
If you want to make the world better, like this, then we have to change the way talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Bother?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/09/why-bother/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 10:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/09/why-bother/</guid>
      <description>Note: This was written in August, 2015, during the Obama administration. Lamentations about the current state of affairs pertain to an era now past. Hope for the future, though, burns eternal.
 We yearn for civic character but satisfy ourselves with symbolic gestures and celebrity circuses. We perceive no greatness in our leaders, a new meanness in ourselves. Small wonder that each new election brings a new jolt, its aftermath a new disappointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fill the Cabinet</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/fill-the-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 23:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/fill-the-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>My friend Scott Oppelt mentioned his complaint that the GOP has so many great candidates all at once. Why can&amp;rsquo;t they be spread out over 20 years?
Great question. History being what it is, we can&amp;rsquo;t spread them across time, only across government. So this week&amp;rsquo;s poll is a little fun.
The rules:
You must fill the next White House cabinet using only the current candidates for President. You do not know who the President or Vice President is, so assume it&amp;rsquo;s none of the current candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Good Issued From the Candidate Debate?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/what-good-issued-from-the-candidate-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 10:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/what-good-issued-from-the-candidate-debate/</guid>
      <description>Did you hear about the ratings?
Over 24 million people watched the first Republican debate Thursday. That&amp;rsquo;s the largest audience ever for a cable program, save for sports.
Everybody knows why so many watched: people wanted to see a fight break out between Chris Christie and Rand Paul.
Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s presence probably didn&amp;rsquo;t hurt. Let me clarify that. Trump&amp;rsquo;s appearance helped rating. His performance might have ended his campaign.
Donald Trump comported himself with all the dignity and gravitas of a George W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Deserve Better</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/we-deserve-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 07:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/we-deserve-better/</guid>
      <description>I should have gone to bed.
I wanted to finish a great book called The Conservative Heart by Arthur C. Brooks of the American Enterprise Institute. The book left me feeling happy, proud, and inspired.
I should have gone to bed as soon as I finished the book. But the feeling of having read something wonderful wanted to linger, so I sat with it for a bit. Then I really screwed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enjoy Your Weekend More</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/07/enjoy-your-weekend-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 21:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/07/enjoy-your-weekend-more/</guid>
      <description>Conservatism blesses the world.
Our principles dignify people with work that** produces value**. We leave them **free to pursue happiness**, which includes their work, their leisure, their learning, and their families.
Our cause is moral and spiritual, not economic. We want everyone to experience and benefit from meaningful work because work provides people with self-esteem and satisfaction. Work is not punishment; it&amp;rsquo;s a blessing.
We do oppose things, but only those things that threaten to degrade human beings by denying them the dignity and benefits of working and living their own lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Readers Overwhelmingly Believe in a Service Ethic</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/readers-overwhelming-believe-in-a-service-ethic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 14:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/readers-overwhelming-believe-in-a-service-ethic/</guid>
      <description>Readers of this blog believe a stronger service ethic would make America a stronger country, but no one wants the federal government involved. And 95 percent of respondents agree that performing service benefits the volunteer as much or more as it benefits the recipients of the work.
Those are the key finding from last week’s poll on service. Specifically, 82 percent agree with the statement “A strong service ethic would make America stronger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Pissed That I’m Pissed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/im-pissed-that-im-pissed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/im-pissed-that-im-pissed/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of being angry?
Did you know that a lot of other people are tired of your anger?
Did you know that 70 percent of Americans don’t like politics?
Did you know that the 70 percent of Americans who don’t like politics won’t vote for anything an angry person tells them to vote for?
Go look it up. It’s totally true.
So many conservatives want another Reagan, but they want an angry, vengeful, belligerent Reagan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poll: Which Candidate Qualities Matter Most?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/05/poll-which-candidate-qualities-matter-most/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 10:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/05/poll-which-candidate-qualities-matter-most/</guid>
      <description>Powered by Typeform
Voting ends Saturday at midnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farewell, Joe LeGrand</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/farewell-joe-legrand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/farewell-joe-legrand/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time I didn&amp;rsquo;t like Joe LeGrand.
It was 3rd grade. I was in the Epiphany Toppers Drum and Bugle Corps, and Joe was a bugler who stood right in front of me. He kept turning around and giving me dirty looks. So I decided right then and there that I didn&amp;rsquo;t like him.
Joe was a year ahead of me in school. While our lives intersected a lot, we weren&amp;rsquo;t really close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Partiers in St. Louis See Things a Bit Differently</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/tea-partiers-in-st-louis-see-things-a-bit-differently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/tea-partiers-in-st-louis-see-things-a-bit-differently/</guid>
      <description>There’s a huge, important fiinding in a new poll—one I believe will affect a lot of elections nationally and in Missouri in 2016. In fact, 2016 will come down to one word.
Write down what you think that word is before reading on.
STLTPC vs. USA on President First, let’s look at some polls.
St. Louis Tea Party members see the GOP Presidential race a little differently than the country at large.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I was an immigrant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/31/i-was-an-immigrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 01:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/31/i-was-an-immigrant/</guid>
      <description>Maybe I’m remembering this wrong. Maybe not.
I met my best high school friends at the lunch table. Scott Oppelt, John Clancy, Christian Saller, Tom Newport, and . . . and dude with curly blond hair who was in Scott Oppelt’s band. John. John Martin.
I met them early in my junior year. We had just one thing in common: we were all transferees. We were not native DuBourgers. We transferred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to kill a movement</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/30/how-to-kill-a-movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 03:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/30/how-to-kill-a-movement/</guid>
      <description>Did you ever see a movement grow?
Did you see the way it starts?
Did you feel it spread around you?
Did you hear it rustling the leaves and scraping the sidewalk?
Did you want to kill it?
The weird thing about movements is that opposition tends to strengthen them. Movements feed on hostility the way rats feed on garbage.
The way you kill a movement is infiltration and fragmentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissolve the Empty See (MTC)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/29/dissolve-the-empty-see-mtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 04:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/29/dissolve-the-empty-see-mtc/</guid>
      <description>The Holy See is in Rome.
The Empty See is in St. Louis.
The Metropolitan Taxicab Commission (MTC) is a racket to protect incumbent taxicab companies. They use their power to keep St. Louis in the stone age of transportation.
It’s time to dissolve the MTC. It has served its purpose and outlived its usefulness. Like the riverboat commission of the 1850s.
Until then, I will do everything in my power to avoid taxis in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep Missouri Money in Missouri with TEA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/28/keep-missouri-money-in-missouri-with-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 01:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/28/keep-missouri-money-in-missouri-with-tea/</guid>
      <description>The Transportation Empowerment Act gives states control and funding for their roads. It is a far superior to the Highway Trust Fund, which is slush fund for pork projects.
Transportation Empowerment Act (TEA) from Senator Mike Lee would gradually shift federal gasoline taxes from Washington back to the states where they were collected without a Washington DC handling fee and without strings attached.
TEA embodies an idea I first heard from Ronald Reaganwhen he was governor of California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Donald Trump Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/27/analysis-of-donald-trump-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 10:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/27/analysis-of-donald-trump-poll/</guid>
      <description>Last week&amp;rsquo;s poll asked for your degree of support for Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy. This poll received far less attention than the Missouri GOP Governor poll of the previous week, as only 60 people responded.
On the plus side, there was no detectable cheating on the Trump poll.
One Word: Polarization [caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_16313&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;600&amp;rdquo;]Histogram of Trump Poll[/caption]
Respondents had choices from 0 to 5 to indicate their degree of support for Trump, with 0 = No Support and 5 = Total Support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poll: What Do You Think About Service?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/26/poll-what-do-you-think-about-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/26/poll-what-do-you-think-about-service/</guid>
      <description>Last week, we posted a 5-part series on national service. This week, we&amp;rsquo;d like to see what you think.
Be heard
The poll closes Saturday, August 1 at Midnight. Please vote only once.
Last Week&amp;rsquo;s Poll: Trump Here&amp;rsquo;s my analysis of last week&amp;rsquo;s poll on Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free eBook of National Service Posts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/free-ebook-of-national-service-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 23:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/free-ebook-of-national-service-posts/</guid>
      <description>My series on National Service is important. Maybe not urgent, but important. (See Eisenhower Square.) So I turned it into an eBook:

DOWNLOAD FREE E-BOOK
Be warned: I did not edit the posts, so the ebook contains all the links to previous posts in the series. If there&amp;rsquo;s interest, I&amp;rsquo;ll go back and clean it up. This is just for convenience.
Thanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Conservative Missouri Service Program--Part 5</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/a-conservative-missouri-service-program-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 10:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/a-conservative-missouri-service-program-part-5/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve reached the end.
On Monday, we corrected disinformation about The Franklin Project.
Next, we looked at the historical conservative framework for national service.
Wednesday was a dissection of The Franklin Project&amp;rsquo;s Plan of Action (as distinguished from the group&amp;rsquo;s vision.)
Yesterday, we examined the consequences of ignoring the call for national service.
Today, we offer an oversimplified proposal for Missouri&amp;rsquo;s version of a national-service program. While inadequate, it is a start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Conservatives Should Get Involved—Part 4</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/23/why-conservatives-should-get-involved-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 10:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/23/why-conservatives-should-get-involved-part-4/</guid>
      <description>In part 1 of this series, we clarified some misconceptions and falsehoods about the Franklin Project.
In part 2, we examined the debate on the right from 1990 with William F. Buckley and Milton Friedman.
Part 3 was a critique of the Franklin Project&amp;rsquo;s Plan of Action.
Today, we will look at the consequences should conservatives turn their backs on the concept of developing a service ethos in America.
Generations: Saying “No” Won’t Work  Do you remember when Roosevelt died?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Wrong With The Franklin Project? – Part 3</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/22/whats-wrong-with-the-franklin-project-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 10:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/22/whats-wrong-with-the-franklin-project-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This is part three of a five-part series on national service. Part 1 introduced the controversy and corrected a major misconception. Part 2 looked at national service through the eyes of conservative giants, Milton Friedman, William F. Buckley, and Ronald Reagan.
So, what’s wrong with the Franklin Project? Plenty.
The Franklin Project promotes the idea of a renewed ethos of national service in America. It’s mission:
 The Franklin Project envisions a future in which a year of full-time national service—a service year—is a cultural expectation, a common opportunity, and a civic rite of passage for every young American.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buckley vs. Friedman on Service-Part 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 10:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</guid>
      <description>This is part 2 of a series on national service and the Franklin Project. Read part 1 here.
First, answer this for yourself: would you vote for William F. Buckley Jr?
Milton Friedman on National Service My friend Lloyd Sloan points out that Milton Friedman disagreed with Buckley’s call for national service. It seems appropriate, then, to view the idea of a service ethos through the eyes of two champions of conservatism of the 20th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fact and Fiction of the Franklin Project--Part 1</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/20/fact-and-fiction-of-the-franklin-project-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 10:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/20/fact-and-fiction-of-the-franklin-project-part-1/</guid>
      <description>You know how to tell when a political camp has nothing on an opponent?
It begins making stuff up.
That “making stuff up” has become the chief form of amusement among those who oppose Eric Greitens for Governor.
The current fiction they advance has to do with an organization called The Franklin Project. The fiction advanced by a few Facebook warriors goes something like this: “The Franklin Project wants mandatory national service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of 2016 GOP Governor Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/19/analysis-of-2016-gop-governor-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 20:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/19/analysis-of-2016-gop-governor-poll/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I launched anonline poll of declared and likely candidates for governor.
This was not a controlled survey, so be careful what you read into it. Instead of using the poll as a measure of breadth, I recommend looking at from a few other angles.
Suspicious Voting Yes, there was a lot of suspicious voting. At least one candidate received his or her strongest support from a single data center in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/19/donald-trump-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 14:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/19/donald-trump-poll/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump is back in the news. This time for attacking John McCain&amp;rsquo;s service record. But he&amp;rsquo;s dominating the polls.
Given what you know of Donald Trump, rate your own support for Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy for president on a scale of 0 to 5 with 0 meaning &amp;ldquo;no support&amp;rdquo; and 5 meaning &amp;ldquo;full support.&amp;rdquo;
[yop_poll id=&amp;quot;3&amp;rdquo;]
This poll closes at Midnight on Saturday, July 25.
Please vote only once.
Last Week&amp;rsquo;s Poll Results</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transportation in the 21st Century Event</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/18/transportation-in-the-21st-century-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 23:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/18/transportation-in-the-21st-century-event/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;rsquo;t get there from here.
 The way people get from here to there&amp;ndash;and how they pay for the privilege&amp;ndash;is about to change. We want you to have a say in the future of transportation.
To help, Heritage Action for America is teaming up with St. Louis Tea Party Coalition to put on a Transportation Empowerment night on Saturday, July 25, 2015 at 6:30 p.m.
Speakers Include:
[gallery ids=&amp;quot;16213,16214,16215&amp;rdquo;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can John Brunner&#39;s Consultant Do His Duty?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/18/can-john-brunners-consultant-do-his-duty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 10:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/18/can-john-brunners-consultant-do-his-duty/</guid>
      <description>Republican consultant David Barklage is in a weird place.
Barklage grew up in Cape Girardeau, Missouri, along with Peter Kinder. Barklage has been Kinder’s campaign consultant for years—all of Kinder’s races, as far as I know. They were a team. David Barlage was Peter Kinder’s chief of staff when Kinder was president pro tem of the Missouri Senate in 2002.
And a loyal consultant is a great tool for a politician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Entire World Is a Sick Joke</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/16/the-entire-world-is-a-sick-joke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 10:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/16/the-entire-world-is-a-sick-joke/</guid>
      <description>Greece&amp;rsquo;s parliament just signed its surrender to Germany. The country signed over virtually all of its national assets and all its future income for 30 years. No one believes Greece will make good on the agreement, and Greece didn&amp;rsquo;t want the deal. Germany demanded it, and Greece surrendered. But Greece will default at some point. Then what? Will Germany send its army? Probably.
In Washington, Barack Obama berated a skeptical press for questioning the agreement he reached with the world&amp;rsquo;s largest exporter of Islamic terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics Is War By Other Means</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/15/politics-is-war-by-other-means/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 10:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/15/politics-is-war-by-other-means/</guid>
      <description>WAR IS A MERE CONTINUATION OF POLICY BY OTHER MEANS.
 Good old Clausewitz. Best book on war ever written. (The Art of War was about something else.)
But the 21st century has reversed his famous line. Politics has become war by other means.
Germany has a history of waging wars of conquest. World War I. World War II. The Greek bailout. As Stratfor&amp;rsquo;s George Friedman explains:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Wrong--Evil</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/not-just-wrong-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/not-just-wrong-evil/</guid>
      <description>Today was a particularly busy day for me.
I had a series of meetings. Like every hour, another meeting. From 9:00 on.
I saw the text from my wife. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to click on a video. I was in a room full of people. Important business. Major client and all that. And I completely misunderstood the &amp;ldquo;H/T Gina L.&amp;rdquo; thing. For some reason, I thought Angela was mad at Gina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric Greitens’ Shocking Revelation Could Shatter People’s Faith</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/eric-greitens-shocking-revelation-could-shatter-peoples-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/eric-greitens-shocking-revelation-could-shatter-peoples-faith/</guid>
      <description>Were you shocked when you learned that Navy SEAL, author, humanitarian, and charity founder, Eric Greitens, was born and raised and voted Democrat?
I was.
Sure, I’d heard the rumors. The whispers spread by some Republican campaign operatives. But I’ve learned to trust those campaign operatives about as far as I fund the national debt.
Then, Senator John Lamping sent me a link to this Fox News story:
Former Navy SEAL: Why I am no longer a Democrat So, the rumors were true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chili Palmer</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/13/chili-palmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/13/chili-palmer/</guid>
      <description>The greatest mob movie of all time was Get Shorty. (Please, don’t argue.) The whole movie revolved around this exchange:
 Ronnie Wingate: Excuse me bro&amp;rsquo;, but who the fuck are you? Chili Palmer: I&amp;rsquo;m the one tellin&amp;rsquo; you how it is&amp;hellip;
 Last Sunday, Greece was Chili Palmer. A few days later, Angela Merkel is.

Funny how things change.
You probably heard that Greece’s Prime Minister called for a referendum on the troika’s terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republican Governor Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/12/republican-governor-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 18:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/12/republican-governor-poll/</guid>
      <description>Read my analysis of the poll here.
[yop_poll id=&amp;quot;2&amp;rdquo;]
You may vote only once.
Poll closes at midnight on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jefferson’s Greatest Idea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/10/jeffersons-greatest-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/10/jeffersons-greatest-idea/</guid>
      <description>Down in my former state of South Carolina, the legislature hastily voted to remove the Confederate flag from the state capitol building. That is their prerogative, and I take no offense at their move.
What I do worry about is the haste.
South Carolina’s action on the flag reflected a spasm instigated by the horrible deeds of a horrible man—an unthinkable crime and grave sin. I can understand how the murderer’s association with the flag would lead people to connect the flag to the murders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RANT: Metropolitan Taxicab Commission Is Killing Capitalism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/08/rant-metropolitan-taxicab-commission-is-killing-capitalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 02:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/08/rant-metropolitan-taxicab-commission-is-killing-capitalism/</guid>
      <description>So how to reenergize the innovation diffusion machine? This is key: “A level playing field that does not favour incumbents over entrants. Many policy measures, from environmental to fiscal measures, are designed to favour incumbents.” More entry through startups and more exit by uncompetitive incumbents.
 &amp;ndash;JAMES PETHOKOUKIS, AMERICAN ENTERPRISE INSTITUTE
The Metropolitan Taxicab Commission is a crony club for taxi company executives and their hospitality friends, and its primary purpose is to kill transportation innovation and thwart price competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Is Crashing and Greece Is Spinning Out of Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/07/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/07/f/</guid>
      <description>The world is even more fragile than it was in 2007. The big banks are bigger. Aggregate bank assets are concentrated in fewer hands. The bank derivatives books are much larger. Market liquidity is worse.
 —James Rickards, The Daily Reckoning
Well, ain’t that just dandy?
And it’s undeniably true. We were told that the 2008 financial meltdown was caused by entities that had grown too large: banks, insurance companies, corporations, derivitives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dangerous Misunderstanding of Debt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/06/a-dangerous-misunderstanding-of-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/06/a-dangerous-misunderstanding-of-debt/</guid>
      <description>Debt is not a guarantee of future payments in full. Rather, it is a risk that creditors take, in hopes of maybe being paid tomorrow.
 The key word there is &amp;ldquo;risk.&amp;rdquo;
If you&amp;rsquo;re willing to take the risk, you&amp;rsquo;ll get a premium — in the form of interest.
But the downside of that risk is that you lose your money. And Greece just called Germany&amp;rsquo;s bluff.
Jim Edwards nailed a major problem with modern finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greece Rejects Central Banksters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/greece-rejects-central-banksters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/greece-rejects-central-banksters/</guid>
      <description>Greece has voted to reject the “troika&amp;rsquo;s” bailout terms. The people of Greece said “no” to the central banksters who encourage sovereigns to enslave themselves under mountains of debt.
The Greeks showed remarkable courage and resiliency, and their example could disrupt the entire international banking system. Tyler Durden at Zero Hedge:
 The Greek people have spoken and they said &amp;ldquo;OXI&amp;rdquo;! So congratulations Greece: for the first time you had the chance to tell the Troika, the unelected eurocrats, and the entire status quo establishment, not to mention all the banks, how you really felt and based on the most recent results, some 61% of you told it to go fuck itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Uber Nada</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/st-louis-uber-nada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/st-louis-uber-nada/</guid>
      <description>About this time, a variety of railroads began trying to build their own networks to the West, but the St. Louis city government refused to grant the permits required for constructing railroad bridges across the river at their location, even though St. Louis was the logical choice and would have been a perfect place for a rail hub. Apparently, the politicians in St. Louis felt their duty was to protect the riverboat industry, at that time their life and blood, from any and all competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Corner Prosperity Is Just Around Is Miles From Where We’re Standing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/02/the-corner-prosperity-is-just-around-is-miles-from-where-youre-standing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/02/the-corner-prosperity-is-just-around-is-miles-from-where-youre-standing/</guid>
      <description>William Hennessy: Psychopomps are carriers of the dead, but they carry them to their afterlife.
Dottie Bailey: Cool!!
William Hennessy: We are in that phase of history. The 20th century is dying, or dead
Dottie Bailey: Makes me sad though.
William Hennessy: Everything that we called “normal” for all our lives lies listless in the beaks of sparrows—psychopomps—on their way to a new birth.
That rebirth won’t happen for another 5 to 10 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are In Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/30/you-are-in-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/30/you-are-in-control/</guid>
      <description>This post is about the control you have.
And the control you don’t have.
Last week was tough on a lot of us. The Supreme Court limited your freedom. The same-sex marriage case was very similar to Roe v. Wade in judicial legislation. States lost the power to regulate marriage. (There’s a deep theological discussion around whether the state ever had any say in marriage, but that’s for another post.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charleston, South Carolina</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/22/why-we-believe-not-just-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 04:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/22/why-we-believe-not-just-what/</guid>
      <description>Limited government, fiscal responsibility, and the other tea party principles are not ends. They were never ends. Tea party principles are merely the most effective and efficient means to nobler ends
Those ends include a society and a nation that respects and protects life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness.
Without life, of what use are the others?
Just as we speak out when &amp;ldquo;government becomes destructive of these ends,&amp;rdquo; so we must speak out when misguided and deranged individuals pervert those principles—or any principles—to their own illegitimate and murderous ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Rambling Now?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/18/whos-rambling-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 21:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/18/whos-rambling-now/</guid>
      <description>Someone who met Bill Clinton told me, &amp;ldquo;I rambled. He probably thought I was an idiot.&amp;rdquo;
No. Bill Clinton wanted you to ramble. He wanted to make you the most important person in the room for two minutes. He listened for a nugget of information&amp;ndash;a story&amp;ndash;he could use in his next speech.
If you&amp;rsquo;re running for office remember: the most important person in every room is the voter you&amp;rsquo;re talking with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Walk on the Hedonic Treadmill</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/17/take-a-walk-on-the-hedonic-treadmill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 21:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/17/take-a-walk-on-the-hedonic-treadmill/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s what happens when you raise the minimum wage to $15 an hour, according to scientists:
Nothing.
Well, not nothing. All kinds of bad things happen to the economy. But nothing happens for two groups of people central to the whole debate: workers who get a bump to $15 and employers who have to bump to $15 an hour.
Most cities and states that have raised their minimum wage laws to $15 will phase in the increase over five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypocrisy of the Left on Self-Identification</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/16/hypocrisy-of-the-left-on-self-identification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 23:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/16/hypocrisy-of-the-left-on-self-identification/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll make this brief.
If we must respect (revere?) the erstwhile Bruce Jenner for self-identifying as a woman, we have to respect Rachel Dolezal for self-identifying as black.
Both voluntarily left the world of privilege, as it were, to join an underclass&amp;ndash;an identifiable minority. Jenner left manhood; Dolezal left whitehood.
The left doesn&amp;rsquo;t see it that way, though. Apparently, rejecting one&amp;rsquo;s biological sex is okay, but rejecting one&amp;rsquo;s biological race isn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activist Ron Calzone Sues Missouri Over Omnibus Bill</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/31/activist-ron-calzone-sues-missouri-over-omnibus-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 14:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/31/activist-ron-calzone-sues-missouri-over-omnibus-bill/</guid>
      <description>Without comment . . .
 Jefferson City, MO, May 29, 2015 - A lawsuit challenging the constitutionality of Senate Bill 672, passed by the Missouri General Assembly in 2014, was filed in Cole County circuit court on May 29th.
 The lawsuit claims that the General Assembly ignored the constitutional limits to their legislative authority. The Missouri Constitution includes clauses that prohibit legislators from changing the purpose of a bill, including multiple subjects in one bill, or passing a “special law” that fails to treat everyone equally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: White House Shuffles Export Import Management (parody)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/28/breaking-white-house-shuffles-export-import-management-parody/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/28/breaking-white-house-shuffles-export-import-management-parody/</guid>
      <description>Washington (APP) —In a Rose Garden press conference today, President Barack Obama introduced Art Vandelay as his choice to head the troubled Export Import Bank for a five-year term, pending approval by the Senate.
The shake-up comes as Congress debates whether or not to extend the bank’s authorization amid heavy opposition from conservative and libertarian groups led by Heritage Action for America.
Mr. Vandelay brings almost 30 years of experience in the export-import business, where he traded in commodities as varied as potato chips, diapers, and matches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come to Export Import Speaking and Gathering This Saturday at Paddy O&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/27/come-to-export-import-speaking-and-gathering-this-saturday-at-paddy-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 23:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/27/come-to-export-import-speaking-and-gathering-this-saturday-at-paddy-os/</guid>
      <description>With Opportunity for All; With Favoritism Toward None Join Us Paddy O&amp;rsquo;s&amp;ndash;618 S. 7th Street, St. Louis, MO 4:15 PM Saturday, May 30 RSVP on Facebook
They say the Export Import Bank is a tiny agency that creates jobs for small business while producing a profit for the Treasury. And rescues baby rabbits from dangerous predators. And it’s gluten free.
Call us skeptics.
We saw the news that Goldman Sachs used the Export Import Bank to secure funding for a financially unstable buyer—after paying the Secretary of State’s husband $200,000 for a fifteen-minute speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I finally finished reading Resilience by Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/19/i-finally-finished-reading-resilience-by-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 21:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/19/i-finally-finished-reading-resilience-by-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>I usually breeze through books.
I read Thinking, Fast and Slow by Daniel Kahneman in four days. And it has math.
I read Eric Greitens&amp;rsquo;s book The Heart and the Fist in two days.
Why did it take me over a month to finish Resilience?
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure, but here&amp;rsquo;s what I think.
First, the book compels action. How could I read this paragraph without writing a blog post?
  If we are trapped in a life where everything is provided for us, our minds fail to grow, our relationships atrophy, and our spirits deteriorate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Export Import Bank Matters Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/18/why-the-export-import-bank-matters-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 01:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/18/why-the-export-import-bank-matters-now/</guid>
      <description>Start small&amp;ndash;end big.
Raise your hand if you know someone who woke one morning and ran a marathon having never so much as walked around the block.
No hands?
Of course not. A few freaks of nature might be able to go from zero to 26.2 in no time, but most people would hurt themselves trying. And never do it again.
When a sane sedentary person decides to run a marathon, he starts by walking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Home</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/17/going-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 14:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/17/going-home/</guid>
      <description>A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.
But if that step is in the wrong direction, you might end up 2,000 miles from your goal.
Many believe America took a step in the wrong direction long ago&amp;ndash;about the time &amp;ldquo;progressivism&amp;rdquo; became popular among political, business, and academic elites in the early 20th century.
If progressivism was a step in the wrong direction, it&amp;rsquo;s led us at least 2,000 miles from our target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lazy Person&#39;s Cure for Herpes Ex-Im</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/07/the-lazy-persons-cure-for-herpes-ex-im/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 22:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/07/the-lazy-persons-cure-for-herpes-ex-im/</guid>
      <description>Every six months.
Just when you can you least afford it.
It happens.
A breakout.
It&amp;rsquo;s Herpes Ex-Im, a cronyism disease that can make the prettiest economic system look sick.
Herpes Ex-Im is a virus that attacks your economy&amp;rsquo;s competitive system, resulting ugly blemishes. Even your lover won&amp;rsquo;t want to kiss you.
But there&amp;rsquo;s a cure.
**Left untreated by Congress, Herpes Ex-Im will die. **
The free-market system has built-in defenses against crony diseases like Herpes Ex-Im.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There&#39;s One Person to Blame if Blues Disappointed You</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/26/theres-one-person-to-blame-if-blues-disappointed-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/26/theres-one-person-to-blame-if-blues-disappointed-you/</guid>
      <description>Harsh, I know.
The St. Louis Blues disappeared from the NHL Stanley Cup Playoffs in a 4-2, first-round collapse for the third consecutive season.
And this year was supposed to be different. So different. With off-season pickups like Jori Lehtera and Paul Stastny, we expected St. Louis to shut down for a parade in June, not in the 3rd period of game six.
Instead, we&amp;rsquo;re wondering how soon will T.J. Oshie sweaters go on the clearance rack at Dick&amp;rsquo;s?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approaching Excellence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/21/approaching-excellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 21:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/21/approaching-excellence/</guid>
      <description>Could it be?
Am I reading this right?
Has anyone ever surprised you with a wish? A wish that defied logic?
Yesterday, a friend wrote of his concerns about Eric Greitens, the Navy SEAL, humanitarian, Rhodes Scholar, charity founder, and former boxer who’s considering a run for Missouri Governor.
His concern began: “Most all GOP candidates proudly trumpet their positions . . . “
He was right, of course. Almost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a Beautiful Spring Day, And Dellena Struggles to Stay In Business</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/18/its-a-beautiful-spring-day-and-dellena-struggles-to-stay-in-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 17:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/18/its-a-beautiful-spring-day-and-dellena-struggles-to-stay-in-business/</guid>
      <description>We metDellena Jones during our first Ferguson BUYcott in August. Since then, St. Louis Tea Partier, Dottie Bailey, has made it her mission to help Dellena&amp;rsquo;s business survive and flourish.
https://youtu.be/r-ye3nSe2Vk
Dellena&amp;rsquo;s business has fallen 60 percent since the first riots. She&amp;rsquo;s repaired the damage to her salon, but business is slow.
Despite all her challenges, Dellena still found the time and energy to host Center for Self-Governance training in her shop on a Saturday, foregoing that day&amp;rsquo;s revenue to learn about freedom and responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We All Need a Drink</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/15/we-all-need-a-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 14:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/15/we-all-need-a-drink/</guid>
      <description>Ever come across a text you know, but forgot?
I did recently. This gem of a paragraph leapt off the page and into my mind:
 I believe this nation hungers for a spiritual revival; hungers to once again see honor placed above political expediency; to see government once again the protector of our liberties, not the distributor of gifts and privilege. Government should uphold and not undermine those institutions which are custodians of the very values upon which civilization is founded &amp;ndash; Faith, education and, above all, family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Know You&#39;re Doing the Right Thing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/14/how-to-know-youre-doing-the-right-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 21:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/14/how-to-know-youre-doing-the-right-thing/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What if everything goes wrong?&amp;rdquo;
I remember asking myself that on the morning of Friday, February 27, 2009.
I was driving on I-44 headed to the Arch to host a Tea Party. My co-hosts were people I&amp;rsquo;d never met: Dana Loesch, Gina Loudon, Ed Martin, Michelle Moore. Those were the three to offered to help. Others offered to speak: Jim Lembke, Shamed Dogan, and a few others. Others helped organize sign-making, food, sign-in sheets, and music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s In Your Medicine Cabinet?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/13/whats-in-your-medicine-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 21:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/13/whats-in-your-medicine-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>Missouri is the only state that doesn&amp;rsquo;t track your medical prescriptions.
People say it like it&amp;rsquo;s a bad thing.
What&amp;rsquo;s wrong with the government not knowing that one bit of information about your private medical life? Can&amp;rsquo;t government keep out of at least this one, extremely personal matter?
The do-gooders and busy-bodies want Missouri to maintain a database (tied into similar databases in all other states) that keeps a permanent record of every prescription a doctor or dentist writes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Interest Rates Hid True Cost of Increasing Debt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/12/low-interest-rates-hid-true-cost-of-increasing-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/12/low-interest-rates-hid-true-cost-of-increasing-debt/</guid>
      <description>House mortgage-type instrument suggested as means to pay off national debt
Guest Post By Lee A. Presser
Interest rates have been held artificially low by the Federal Reserve since 2008. This has had the effect of hiding the true cost of increasing debt. As interest rates rise back toward 4%, the U.S. Treasury will have less money to spend on discretionary governmental functions.
The FY 2015 budget is approximately $3,900,000,000,000.00. Another way to look at that number is about $12,187.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The SEAL, the Race, and the CEO</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/10/the-seal-the-race-and-the-ceo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/10/the-seal-the-race-and-the-ceo/</guid>
      <description>In its entire history, who was the safest CEO for Apple?
In other words, if you were a corporate recruiter hired by Apple&amp;rsquo;s board to find a chief executive, whom would hire?
I&amp;rsquo;ll answer this later, but first here&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m asking.
Who Would You Recruit? In response to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post on Brunner vs. Greitens, someone asked me a similar question about Eric Greitens. The inquisitor seems to question my judgment for preferring Greitens over John Brunner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greater of Two Goods</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/09/the-greater-of-two-goods/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 21:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/09/the-greater-of-two-goods/</guid>
      <description>You know the feeling.
You support someone for office. Call this person Candidate A. You&amp;rsquo;re all in. You&amp;rsquo;ve told your friends about this great person.
Then another candidate jumps in to oppose your candidate. Let&amp;rsquo;s call this person Candidate B. This insurgent has great qualifications. You campaigned for Candidate B in another race a few years ago. You&amp;rsquo;ve talked him up. In the past, told your friends to vote for Candidate B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering One&#39;s Domain</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/04/mastering-ones-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 01:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/04/mastering-ones-domain/</guid>
      <description>I own a ton of domain names.
Most of them I&amp;rsquo;ll never use. I bought them&amp;ndash;and pay for them&amp;ndash;because I don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone else to have them. Many contain &amp;ldquo;teabaggers.&amp;rdquo; Many contain &amp;ldquo;teaparty.&amp;rdquo; Many contain &amp;ldquo;Hennessy,&amp;rdquo; although the cognac people had sucked up quite a few of those already.
Everyone should invest in domains containing their surname. Anyone who is even mildly famous should own the domains containing their full name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Guy Puts People to Work</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/31/eric-greitens-puts-people-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 05:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/31/eric-greitens-puts-people-to-work/</guid>
      <description>Brett wanted to know more about Eric Greitens.
Ben deferred to me to tell the Greitens story. I went through the usual, remarkable life of a man, eleven years my junior, a century my senior. I told him about Duke, boxing, Bosnia, Rwanda, Mother Teresa. I told him about boxing at Oxford and becoming a SEAL.
Nothing from Brett.
&amp;ldquo;Really,&amp;rdquo; I thought. &amp;ldquo;How stuck-up is this guy?&amp;rdquo;
But we didn&amp;rsquo;t give up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am a Coward (but I&#39;m trying to get better)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/26/i-am-coward/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 21:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/26/i-am-coward/</guid>
      <description>A critic is someone who enters the battlefield after the war is over and shoots the wounded.
 ― Murray Kempton
Great leaders inspire thought and action.
But their real value? Great leaders inspire action. Hard action. Uncomfortable action.
I&amp;rsquo;m reading Resilience by Eric Greitens. I have already bought six copies of the book, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll buy more. I want everyone to read it. The book changes people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Flynn for Congress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/25/mike-flynn-for-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 21:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/25/mike-flynn-for-congress/</guid>
      <description>I was hungover.
I sat in a booth at the Holiday Inn in Quincy, Illinois, with my wife and two friends from St. Louis. The day before was my wife&amp;rsquo;s birthday, which she graciously spent waiting for me to speak at a tea party in Quincy.
Angela and I sat with Jim Durbin and Ben Evans. About four feet away, sitting at the bar, were Andrew Breitbart and editor-in-chief of Andrew&amp;rsquo;s BigGovernment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Don&#39;t Need More Technology--They Need Less</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</guid>
      <description>I was on my high school&amp;rsquo;s board of education for a year. It was quite an honor, honestly, but I screwed it up.
At the time, I was a software architect. They put me on the board as the technology guy. I was supposed to make the case for more funding for smart boards and other tech stuff.
But I said kids really don&amp;rsquo;t need more technology in school. Technology, I said, was like sex education: they&amp;rsquo;ll get more than they can handle on the streets or watching TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are Entitled to Nothing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/22/you-are-entitled-to-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 17:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/22/you-are-entitled-to-nothing/</guid>
      <description>I know &amp;ldquo;House of Cards&amp;rdquo; character Frank Underwood is fictitious, malicious, and evil.
But even an evil fictitious character can hit the nail on its head occasionally.
https://youtu.be/QgTIhT5aLCg
We might not like his prescription, but he diagnoses America&amp;rsquo;s chief problem more concretely, more accurately, and more honestly than any American politician ever has. Ever.
 We’ve been crippled by Social Security, Medicare, Medicaid, by welfare, by entitlements. And that is the root of the problem: entitlements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GOP&#39;s Sad New Whisper Campaign **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/21/the-gops-sad-new-whisper-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2015 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/21/the-gops-sad-new-whisper-campaign/</guid>
      <description>Note: Updated to remove reference to Jeff Roe
Poor Catherine Hanaway.
Her shadowy operatives worked so hard to defeat Tom Schweich, but a new threat to Hanaway&amp;rsquo;s coronation emerged: Eric Greitens. (You can read all about Eric Greitens, here.)
The GOP establishment&amp;rsquo;s inept, new whisper campaign against Greitens is so amateurish and sad it evokes the kind of sympathy one feels toward the ignorance of animals (to paraphrase William F. Buckley).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will the Left Fund a Campaign to &#34;Fix&#34; Missouri? **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/19/will-the-left-fund-a-campaign-to-fix-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 01:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/19/will-the-left-fund-a-campaign-to-fix-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Updated with new information
Leftist donors flooded Texas with money for two years.
Wendy Davis was the poster-child in 2014, but she was only a candidate of convenience. Leftists know that turning Texas purple would mean leftist domination in America. In 2013 &amp;ldquo;purple Texas&amp;rdquo; was all the talk. From Huffington Post:
 Last week, Politico reported that national Democrats are creating a &amp;ldquo;large-scale independent group&amp;rdquo; aimed at turning Texas into a legitimate electoral battleground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Recruit Better Political Candidates</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/12/how-to-recruit-better-political-candidates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 21:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/12/how-to-recruit-better-political-candidates/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s accept that people are lazy.
I noticed no one rose to argue, so universal laziness is a given.
When political consultants and parties recruit candidates, they do the lazy thing. They look for candidates who are easily electable. They want people who look good, speak well, shake hands like they&amp;rsquo;re still alive, and never made the papers for slapping their spouse.
Actually, they want people who are squeaky clean. Boring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ridiculous Thing I Gave Up for Lent</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/11/the-ridiculous-thing-i-gave-up-for-lent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 21:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/11/the-ridiculous-thing-i-gave-up-for-lent/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What did you give up for Lent?&amp;rdquo;
Ever get that one? Like it&amp;rsquo;s something you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to post on your Facebook page.
A very good priest I knew, Dom Oppenheimer, warned against revealing one&amp;rsquo;s Lenten sacrifice.
&amp;ldquo;When you tell others what you gave up for Lent, you&amp;rsquo;re likely to feel some pride,&amp;rdquo; he explained. &amp;ldquo;But pride is the worst sin.&amp;rdquo;
That actually makes a lot of sense when you think about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Questions. And I want some damn answers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/10/3-questions-and-i-want-some-damn-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 04:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/10/3-questions-and-i-want-some-damn-answers/</guid>
      <description>What would happen if we if worked on:
 stuff we could actually fix stuff no one could complain about fixing stuff we didn&amp;rsquo;t care who got credit for fixing?  Next question:
 Name one thing that needs fixing that meets all three criteria (and think of people you hate when answering question 2)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Two Industries Suck Most at Customer Service?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/10/which-two-industries-suck-most-at-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 19:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/10/which-two-industries-suck-most-at-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Want to know why Net Neutrality is dangerous?
Forget the Constitutional stuff. That&amp;rsquo;s important, but most people don&amp;rsquo;t care. Seriously. As soon as you mention the Constitution or mercantilism, the 99% walk away.
And the remaining 1% already agree with you.
No, the way to scare people about Net Neutrality is this chart from Statista:

You will find more statistics at Statista
The only thing worse than Comcast&amp;rsquo;s customer service?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why It&#39;s Good To Be Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/09/why-its-good-to-be-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 21:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/09/why-its-good-to-be-wrong/</guid>
      <description>Well, a redneck nerd in a bowling shirt was a-guzzlin&amp;rsquo; lone star beer Talking religion and-uh politics for all the world to hear.
 &amp;ndash;Kinky Friedman, They Aint&amp;rsquo; Makin&amp;rsquo; Jews Like Jesus Anymore
I used to hate to be wrong.
In fact, most of my life, I&amp;rsquo;d deny being wrong long after all doubt had left the room.
I&amp;rsquo;d get angry when I was wrong, too. More accurately, I&amp;rsquo;d get angry when someone found out I was wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Emphasis on Race Hurts Efforts to Reform Municipal Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/08/how-race-hurts-efforts-to-reform-municipal-courts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 22:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/08/how-race-hurts-efforts-to-reform-municipal-courts/</guid>
      <description>My story on the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s Ferguson report addressed race early. .
So let&amp;rsquo;s have a little blunt talk about race from a West County white guy&amp;rsquo;s point of view (which is alway helpful).
Faction A and Faction B Whenever race comes up, two large factions shut down. They shut down intellectually because &amp;lsquo;race&amp;rsquo; touches an irrational, emotional nerve.
Faction A views every issue as a race problem. They see rain at a picnic as racist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Do With the DOJ Report on Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/what-to-do-with-the-doj-report-on-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 17:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/what-to-do-with-the-doj-report-on-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>The will of man is not shattered, but softened, bent, and guided; men are seldom forced by it to act, but they are constantly restrained from acting. Such a power does not destroy, but it prevents existence; it does not tyrannize, but it compresses, enervates, extinguishes, and stupefies a people, till each nation is reduced to nothing better than a flock of timid and industrious animals, of which the government is the shepherd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Hope Beats Anger</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/why-hope-beats-anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 06:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/why-hope-beats-anger/</guid>
      <description>The human brain is three times as sensitive to pain as it is to gain.
That’s a gross over-simplification, but it’s basically true. In other words, you’ll work three-times harder to save a dollar you have than to earn one you don’t.
Put another way, you won’t bet a dollar with even odds unless you stand to gain three dollars for a win.
That’s not a flaw. It keeps you alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providence and Hope in Missouri</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/providence-and-hope-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 23:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/providence-and-hope-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Fate moves in mysterious ways.
Just days before State Auditor and Republican gubernatorial candidate Tom Schweich died, Eric Greitens announced an exploratory committee. Greitens wants to test the water of a possible run for Missouri Governor as a Republican.
Greitens would be, perhaps, the most remarkable human being ever to pursue the office of Governor of Missouri. Here’s a sampling of Greitens’s achievements:
 Humanitarian who’s worked in Rwanda, Bosnia, Central America, India and other disaster zones—usually man-made disaster zones Boxer who won championships in England Rhodes Scholar who completed the program at Oxford Navy SEAL who earned the Bronze Star among other accolades in four tours in Iraq Founder of The Mission Continues to give wounded veterans a mission and a purpose in life Time Magazine’s 100 most influential people in the world Forbes’ Magazine’s 50 greatest leaders in the world  Purpose Over Party Greitens is no ideologue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri Deserves Better</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/missouri-deserves-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 10:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/missouri-deserves-better/</guid>
      <description>Hancock, who is a political consultant, said he held meetings last fall with prospective donors for a project to register Catholic voters. Hancock said that if he had mentioned that Schweich was Jewish, it would have been in the context that Hanaway was Catholic but that was no indication of how Catholics were likely to vote.
 Those circling the wagons around John Hancock: woe betide you. God forgive you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allman in the Mourning</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/allman-in-the-mourning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 08:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/allman-in-the-mourning/</guid>
      <description>I hear that Jamie Allman ripped into Senator John Danforth yesterday.
Allman called Danforth a failure and a thug. According to Allman, Danforth&amp;rsquo;s sin was defending a friend against lies, defending a people against centuries-old hate.
I guess Jamie Allman and his handlers like lies and hate.
I&amp;rsquo;d hate to be Jamie Allman on judgement day.
Just sayin&amp;rsquo;.
Mourning for Jamie&amp;rsquo;s soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/02/doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 22:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/02/doing/</guid>
      <description>Ben Evans worked hard to host a joint event with St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and Heritage Foundation a couple years ago.
Because of Ben&amp;rsquo;s hard work, we met Dottie.
Then the trouble in Ferguson happened last August. Fearless Dottie joined our band of BUYcotters who went to Ferguson to shop while the city still smoldered.
We met Dellena.
Dottie cultivated a relationship with Dellena.
Saturday, February 28, Dellena hosted Level One training in Self-Governance at her 911 Beauty Salon on W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Success?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/01/what-is-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 21:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/01/what-is-success/</guid>
      <description>Could I ask you to answer a couple of questions. You can do this offline or in the comments of this post.
*1. Name 3 people you consider wildly successful. *2. For each person you named, what is the number one criterion for establishing his or her success?
Please do that before continuing.
Done?
Okay. I’m going to guess that, when all the answers are tabulated, wealth and income will be the top criteria for success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Thoughts on Tom Schweich</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/27/some-thoughts-on-tom-schweich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 13:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/27/some-thoughts-on-tom-schweich/</guid>
      <description>Excerpts from past posts on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View about Tom Schweich
&amp;ldquo;Integrity&amp;rdquo; is the first word I think of when trying to describe Tom Schweich.
Rock n Roll Lunch We met for lunch on a hot day in April 2010. I expected a typical GOP establishment hack: smooth, overly friendly, defensive, and forgettable. I expected the man others told me to expect. But I met someone very different.
How different? That lunch ended listening to his band&amp;rsquo;s recording of their original rock song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Schweich, RIP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/26/tom-schweich-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 20:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/26/tom-schweich-rip/</guid>
      <description>News of Auditor Tom Schweich&amp;rsquo;s death hit me hard. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard, St. Louis Post-Dispatch reported to day that my friend Tom Schweich died of a gunshot wound today. Tom was 54.
I am saddened by this news. I pray for Tom&amp;rsquo;s family and for his rapid entry to eternal happiness.
May perpetual light shine on him, and may his soul and all the souls of all the faithful departed rest in peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the hell got me involved in politics to begin with?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/26/what-the-hell-got-me-involved-in-politics-to-begin-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 14:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/26/what-the-hell-got-me-involved-in-politics-to-begin-with/</guid>
      <description>Paul Hamby asked a question last month.
I was only one of the many he asked, and, being the rude bastard I am sometimes, I took a month to reply. And being lazy, I figured I should get a blog post out of it.
So here&amp;rsquo;s my answer to the question &amp;ldquo;who inspired you to get involved in politics?&amp;rdquo;
In the Summer of 74, I was between 3rd and 4th grade (I think).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Seems Like a Really Big Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/this-seems-like-a-really-big-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 04:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/this-seems-like-a-really-big-win/</guid>
      <description>I am so embarrassed.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know that Fred Sauer, Gretchen Logue, and Anne Gassel were suing Missouri over Common Core.
Did you know that?
(I probably knew it and forgot. Sorry.)
But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: THEY WON!!!!
Wait. YOU won. You won because Fred, Gretchen, and Anne stuck their necks out for you. And for me.
So Thank You! to Fred, Gretchen, and Anne. And this case seems really, really big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Russian Empire</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</guid>
      <description>The last two years of Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s presidency will see the rise of a new Russian empire.
This new empire will resemble the Soviet Union in shape, the Czars in style.
We looked at this subject over the summer (here and here). To summarize those blogs:
 The US-led coup of Ukraine convinced Putin to reassert safer borders Russia wants to build a buffer between itself and NATO Putin wants to re-establish a Russian Empire to revitalize Russian pride and influence Western debt and war-weariness make NATO impotent Putin knows the next US president might be more of a man than Obama, even if its Hillary Putin will want to complete his expansion by January 20, 2017 Ukraine is as good as done and Poland will fall under Russian influence  I still believe all of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The tangled web of net neutrality</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/24/tangled-web-net-neutrality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 02:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/24/tangled-web-net-neutrality/</guid>
      <description>A friend asked my thoughts on net neutrality.
I hemmed and hawed and told her a story she probably didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hear. The best I could come up with was:
 I don&amp;rsquo;t trust the FCC or the Obama Administration to do anything honest I don&amp;rsquo;t trust the Republican establishment to do anything right  First, the Obama Administration would love to get control of internet content. They can already read every message, every keystroke anyone types anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Might Abandon the GOP in 2016</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/17/i-might-abandon-the-gop-in-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/17/i-might-abandon-the-gop-in-2016/</guid>
      <description>Why have conservatives and right-leaning libertarians made so little progress since 2009?
Consider that the GOP was written off for dead following the 2008 election. Republicans disappeared from the press. When a Republican popped up on a Sunday talk show, he was talking about compromise and getting along.
Then the Tea Party happened, and all of a sudden the GOP&amp;rsquo;s testes descended. But after two off-year wave elections that gave the GOP their largest majorities since Hoover, the GOP seems poised to double down on the crony capitalist, elitist policies and candidates that got them tossed out of Washington in 2006 and 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>34 to 0: Good Ideas Are Hard to Fight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/13/34-0-good-ideas-hard-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 03:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/13/34-0-good-ideas-hard-fight/</guid>
      <description>I was scared. Not afraid to say it.
And some friends turned hostile. They had good reasons. And I was probably a little cavalier. And I talked way too long.
But last September I wanted to start something that would help real people in our neighborhood while advancing liberty and upsetting abusive government. Sure, I&amp;rsquo;d rather upset the federal government in Washington, but my arms are little short to box with Harry Reid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe Police Officers Would Rather Be Tax Collectors</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/01/maybe-police-officers-rather-tax-collectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 05:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/01/maybe-police-officers-rather-tax-collectors/</guid>
      <description>Do people become cops just so they can write speeding tickets?
According to the National Sheriffs’ Association, writing speeding tickets is a police officer’s noblest calling. People and technologies that help drivers drive more safely and obey the law interfere with that noble mission of revenue generation, and the NSA is out to stop it.
According to the Associated Press,the National Sheriffs’ Association wants to crack down on the popular traffic navigation app Waze™ so that people will drive faster and cops can write more tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do the Speed-Trap Mayors Want You To Drive Dangerously?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/22/speed-trap-mayors-want-drive-dangerously/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 02:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/22/speed-trap-mayors-want-drive-dangerously/</guid>
      <description>I had the rare honor of testifying before the Missouri Senate committee on Economic Development. The hearing&amp;rsquo;s subject was Senator Eric Schmitt&amp;rsquo;s Senate Bill 5 to reign in traffic court abuses in Missouri.
Here&amp;rsquo;s some perspective:
 St. Louis County accounts for 22 percent of Missouri&amp;rsquo;s population and over 50 percent of traffic tickets St. Ann&amp;rsquo;s traffic court revenue exploded from about $500,000 in 2009 to over $3.5 million last year Traffic court generates 90 percent of the total revenue for one Missouri city Ferguson, Missouri, has three outstanding traffic ticket warrants for every citizen The mayor of Edmundson in North St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Define Tom Schweich With One Word</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/18/define-tom-schweich-one-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 22:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/18/define-tom-schweich-one-word/</guid>
      <description>Work screwed up my plans.
Our annual St. Louis Tea Party / Heritage Action Christmas Party started at 6:00 in the evening on December 17. I knew Auditor Tom Schweich planned to attend, and I looked forward to seeing him.
About 3:00 the problems started. People scurrying to wrap up projects before the Christmas break led to errors, questions, and never-ending email threads.
I finally made it out of the office about 7:30 and arrived at Scarecrow in Chesterfield a little after 8:00.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boehner&#39;s Purge</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/06/boehners-purge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 04:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/06/boehners-purge/</guid>
      <description>You might have noticed that my report on the Speaker election process lacked enthusiasm.
Now you know why.
Boehner is moving quickly to purge conservatives from all committees of meaning. He has vowed to cooperate with the White House and Democrats. He has vowed never to shut down government again, no matter how evil, onerous, or destructive of liberty government becomes.
Boehner has gone full native.
That&amp;rsquo;s a predictable outcome of a failed coup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s How a Mere Mortal Becomes Speaker of the House</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/05/heres-mere-mortal-becomes-speaker-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/05/heres-mere-mortal-becomes-speaker-house/</guid>
      <description>The geniuses at Heritage Action put together a fantastic brief explaining everything you need to know about the Speaker election process.
Check this out: Speaker Election Procedural Facts
For the record, I&amp;rsquo;d love to see the election go to a second, third, fourth, or ninety-fifth ballot. But I don&amp;rsquo;t expect Boehner to lose. And if Boehner should lose, Gohmert might not win. The winner will need a LOT of Republican votes, and Boehner supporters won&amp;rsquo;t vote for the guy who inserted himself into the race.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>