<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>game theory on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/game-theory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in game theory on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 15:57:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/game-theory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How a Strategist Looks at the Supreme Court Nomination Battle</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/02/strategist-looks-supreme-court-nomination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 15:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/02/strategist-looks-supreme-court-nomination/</guid>
      <description>In a moment, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look the Supreme Court nomination of Merrick Garland and find the best strategy for Senate Republicans. In a moment. First, let&amp;rsquo;s just relax and think about a party. And pretend you&amp;rsquo;re a paid strategist.
Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View Podcast: [soundcloud url=&amp;quot;https://api.soundcloud.com/tracks/256943967&amp;rdquo; params=&amp;quot;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;100%&amp;rdquo; height=&amp;quot;450&amp;rdquo; iframe=&amp;quot;true&amp;rdquo; /]
Party Now or Party Later?  Tim and Mary Johnson want to have a party for their friends. They&amp;rsquo;ve been talking about it since spring, and now it&amp;rsquo;s nearly winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Correction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/25/correction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 01:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/25/correction/</guid>
      <description>Something weird happened in the stock market today.
Yesterday I blogged about the stock markets. I&amp;rsquo;d been up early to see what was going on in Europe and Asia. I was watching US futures, too.
I decided to write about what might happen. And I told you about Ben Hunt, my favorite economics writer. Ben combines remarkable knowledge of game theory and psychology with his genius in finance and economics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Expect Boehner To Play The Black Knight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</guid>
      <description>The GOP didn’t really have a plan in place in case it lost. It certainly didn’t have a plan for getting snotclobbered. And if you try to spin Tuesday’s results as anything less than a good old-fashioned ass-kicking, you’re deluding yourself.

**Republicans Got Creamed ** I know Michelle Malkin found 20 things that went right on election night, but there about 60 million things that went wrong. Let’s take a look:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Theory and the Ryan Pick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/game-theory-and-the-ryan-pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 21:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/game-theory-and-the-ryan-pick/</guid>
      <description>If Mitt Romney applied game theory in choosing Paul Ryan, I have renewed respect for him. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain why, but first a bit of background on game theory.
Game theory is a branch of social science concerned with strategic decision-making. It is most closely associated with economics. Professor John Nash, the subject of the movie A Beautiful Mind, won a Nobel Prize in Economics for his work in game theory. (For a great primer on the subject, read Thinking Strategically: the competitive advantage in business, politics, and everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>