<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prayer on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/prayer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prayer on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:00:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/prayer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret to a Better Life and Less Political Violence Is Here</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</guid>
      <description>If you read a lot of business and personal improvement blogs, you know they feed a lot of tips for living a better life. By &amp;ldquo;better&amp;rdquo; they mean making more money, getting a promotion, being more productive, whatever.
Are those things really what makes life better? If so, why do so many successful people burn out? John Belushi, River Phoenix, Amy Winehouse, Janice Joplin, Michael Jackson. Is it show business? Well, look what&amp;rsquo;s happening to Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosary Coast-to-Coast October 7—Pray for America! *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/18/rosary-coast-to-coast-october-7-pray-for-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 02:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/18/rosary-coast-to-coast-october-7-pray-for-america/</guid>
      <description>The holy Rosary is a powerful weapon!
St. Josemaria Escriva
 On Sunday, October 7 at 3:30 p.m. Central (and simultaneously across the USA and the whole world), millions will say the Rosary in unison. Will you join us?
 We are at war. A war without borders, where no man is exempt but where most haven’t recognized, let alone been trained, to fight. Casualties often go unseen, but very few are left unwounded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>40 Days of Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/40-days-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 20:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/40-days-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Forty Days of Life is a peaceful, prayerful response the poverty of abortion.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x-AfLO6Oevo]
The Coalition for Life is a community based Christian pro-life organization made up of over 90 churches and thousands of individuals who are working to end abortion in St. Louis, peacefully and prayerfully. ____
 The 40 Days for Life St. Louis Adopt-A-Day program is for Churches and/or Organizations that feel God is calling them to a day of prayer at our vigil location near Planned Parenthood on Forest Park Avenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poll: Tim Burns Can Take Murtha’s Seat</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/poll-tim-burns-can-take-murthas-seat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 03:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/poll-tim-burns-can-take-murthas-seat/</guid>
      <description>The final poll before Tuesday’s special election to fill Jack Murtha’s unexpired seat in the U.S. House shows that Republican Tim Burns is neck and neck with Democrat and pork barrel specialist Mark Critz. (Yes, Critz’s campaign is funded by lobbyists and special interests.)

PPP has it 48 to 47 Burns.
That means GOTV will determine the winner.
If you want to make a difference, here’s the four step plan:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>