<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prayer on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/prayer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prayer on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 07:40:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/prayer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Put on the Armor of God</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/put-on-the-armor-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 07:40:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/put-on-the-armor-of-god/</guid>
      <description>St. Paul warned us of times like these.
Ephesians 6:10-20 warns us that we lack the strength, wisdom, courage, and intellect to fight the forces of darkness alone. That&amp;rsquo;s not to say we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t fight or that we should leave it to others. It means the only weapons that work are spiritual.
Mere humans cannot forever defend monuments against other humans bent on their destruction. The defilers and destroyers need to get it right only once, while the defenders&amp;rsquo; vigilance must be perfect at all times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Prayed at the Statue of St. Louis IX, King of France</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/why-we-prayed-at-statue-of-st-louis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 15:04:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/why-we-prayed-at-statue-of-st-louis/</guid>
      <description>Our purpose in holding this Rosary event at the statue of St. Louis was to satisfy the two greatest commandments: to love God and to love our neighbor as ourselves. To that end, we prayed equally for everyone present at the event:
 For those who attacked us and called us names For those who falsely accused us of being in the KKK For those on both sides of the issues who came to provoke the other side For those police officers who donned riot gear on a hot, humid day to keep us all safe For those who came out to pray  For all of them, we prayed to God that He softens our hearts and fills our souls with gifts of the Holy Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Us Pray at the Statue of St. Louis in Forest Park Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/let-us-pray-at-the-statue-of-st-louis-in-forest-park-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 06:24:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/let-us-pray-at-the-statue-of-st-louis-in-forest-park-saturday/</guid>
      <description>By the grace of God, Jim Hoft, the Gateway Pundit, has called all Catholic Christian men to pray the Rosary at the statue of St. Louis IX, King of France, on Art Hill in Forest Park at Noon on Saturday, June 28, 2020. Please join us. If you cannot join us, please pray for us.
Pray that our intentions align with the will of God, that we do nothing out of vainglory or pride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret to a Better Life and Less Political Violence Is Here</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</guid>
      <description>If you read a lot of business and personal improvement blogs, you know they feed a lot of tips for living a better life. By &amp;ldquo;better&amp;rdquo; they mean making more money, getting a promotion, being more productive, whatever.
Are those things really what makes life better? If so, why do so many successful people burn out? John Belushi, River Phoenix, Amy Winehouse, Janice Joplin, Michael Jackson. Is it show business? Well, look what&amp;rsquo;s happening to Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosary Coast-to-Coast October 7—Pray for America! *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/18/rosary-coast-to-coast-october-7-pray-for-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 02:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/18/rosary-coast-to-coast-october-7-pray-for-america/</guid>
      <description>The holy Rosary is a powerful weapon!
St. Josemaria Escriva
 On Sunday, October 7 at 3:30 p.m. Central (and simultaneously across the USA and the whole world), millions will say the Rosary in unison. Will you join us?
 We are at war. A war without borders, where no man is exempt but where most haven’t recognized, let alone been trained, to fight. Casualties often go unseen, but very few are left unwounded.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>