<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>trust on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/trust/</link>
    <description>Recent content in trust on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:31:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/trust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Hard to Deny North County Has Problems with Police and Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>What did you think when you first heard reports of violence in Ferguson? I mean, after the shooting death of Michael Brown?
Did you ever for a moment think, &amp;ldquo;this is about more than just Michael Brown?&amp;rdquo;
I hate to say that. It&amp;rsquo;s embarrassing to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m so jaded as to think &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;rdquo; when a young man dies. Sorry. I&amp;rsquo;m just being honest.
I understand community grief and anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust Is a Bigger Problem for GOP Than Marketing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/trust-is-a-bigger-problem-for-gop-than-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 16:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/trust-is-a-bigger-problem-for-gop-than-marketing/</guid>
      <description>The GOP’s self-examination on the 2012 election debacle rightly identifies marketing and messaging and lack of a ground game as contributors to that mess.

But the GOP’s self-exam missed a potentially fatal problem for the party: the American people simply do not trust Republicans on the budget.
Read this paragraph from The Hill carefully. Read all of it. It should tell you everything you need to know.
 More voters trust the Democratic Party than the Republican Party on budgetary issues, according to the results of a new poll for The Hill — even though a strong majority actually prefer Republican fiscal policies [emphases added].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did You See the Crisis Coming?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/07/did-you-see-the-crisis-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/07/did-you-see-the-crisis-coming/</guid>
      <description>Can you guess the year?
** Scottish scientists cloned a sheep named Dolly ** President Clinton signed a bill barring federal funds for human cloning ** Bank robbers in Kevlar suits staged an epic gun battle with Los Angeles police ** The English Patient wins Best Picture Oscar ** Tony Blair becomes Prime Minister of England ** Timothy McVeigh convicted of pure evil ** Titanic bounced off the iceberg and hit the box office</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>