<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>grassroots on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/grassroots/</link>
    <description>Recent content in grassroots on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 14:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/grassroots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Condorcet Method Could Save The GOP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/20/how-the-condorcet-method-could-save-the-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/20/how-the-condorcet-method-could-save-the-gop/</guid>
      <description>The RNC’s Autopsy report wants to do away with caucuses and conventions, replacing them with regional primaries. But I’ll propose a different reform that will make candidate selection more interesting, whether in a caucus or a primary.
A Word About The Autopsy The idea of compacting the primary season and eliminating caucuses has some merit, but also a lot of downside. On the plus side are splashier events to showcase the party, fewer Tuesdays littered with politics, and, believe it or not, some economies as candidates can focus on one geographical region at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin’s Grit Overwhelms Establishment’s Power</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/05/ed-martins-grit-overwhelms-establishments-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 02:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/05/ed-martins-grit-overwhelms-establishments-power/</guid>
      <description>In a blow to the old guard establishment,** the Missouri Republican State Committee elected Ed Martin Jr. as its new party chairman**.

Roy Blunt and all six Republican members of Congress from Missouri lobbied the new state committee over the past few weeks to block Ed and retain the establishment’s choice, David Cole. Jo Mannies of the St. Louis Beacon wrote:
 Cole’s loss appears to be a setback for Missouri’s GOP establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Two People in West County About The After Party This Thursday at Sky Music Lounge</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/tell-two-people-in-west-county-about-the-after-party-this-thursday-at-sky-music-lounge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/tell-two-people-in-west-county-about-the-after-party-this-thursday-at-sky-music-lounge/</guid>
      <description>A friend from Dallas just called me. He said he met two conservatives from Ballwin who’d love to be involved in movement conservatism . . . but don’t know how.
I was shocked. And a little embarrassed. ** How can someone in West County not know about St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and The After Party?** &#39;

Clearly, I’ve done something wrong. I’m sorry. But I can’t just throw my hands up and walk away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Candy Crowley: Tea Party Groups Resemble the 13 Colonies, Not the Balkans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</guid>
      <description>Analogies say more about the speaker than about the subject.
Candy Crowley told KMOX Radio listeners on Friday that Tea Party groups resemble the Balkans without guns.
Wrong. Crappy analogy, Candy. The diverse and autonomous, often quarrelsome,** Tea Party groups remind me of the original 13 colonies.**
The colonies were divided on just about every subject imaginable. The disagreed on slavery, on economics, on agraculture, manufacturing, cities, names &amp;ndash; name it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>