<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>first amendment on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/first-amendment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in first amendment on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 13:57:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/first-amendment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The President&#39;s Authority to Open Churches Is the Constitution - VIDEO RANT</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/presidents-authority-to-open-churches-is-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 13:57:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/presidents-authority-to-open-churches-is-constitution/</guid>
      <description>The morons in the White House press corps spend most of today&amp;rsquo;s briefing screaming at press secretary Kayleigh McEnany about President Trump&amp;rsquo;s order to re-open all churches.
The oft-repeated (shouted) question: &amp;ldquo;What federal law is the president relying on to require states to allow church services?&amp;rdquo;
The question demonstrates the absolute ignorance and laziness, the besst-like stupidity, of most journalists.
  The president&amp;rsquo;s authority is the United States Constitution, you mouth-breathing swine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, the Government Should Fear the People</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/government-create-free-speech-zones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 14:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/government-create-free-speech-zones/</guid>
      <description>Every inch of US territory is a Constitutionally guaranteed free-speech zone. I am all for arresting and prosecuting without mercy any government employee&amp;ndash;including military&amp;ndash;who attempt to limit the size or scope of this zone.

During the Bundy Ranch standoff in Nevada, the Bureau of Land Management set up &amp;ldquo;free-speech zones.&amp;rdquo; I prefer to call them &amp;ldquo;First Amendment pens.&amp;rdquo;
The government uses these pens to segregate people. The US government says, &amp;ldquo;If you want to speak your mind, you may do so only within the pen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Government’s Surrender to Cliven Bundy Destroys Taleb’s Weak Argument for Gun Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</guid>
      <description>Events of the past week show the power of the Second Amendment to challenge government tyranny, regardless of the government’s firepower advantage. Let me back up, though.
A Smart Man’s Stupid Argument for Gun Control A year ago, the gun control lobby pumped a Facebook post by Nassim Nicholas Taleb, one of my favorite thinkers.
In his post, Taleb argued that the Second Amendment means nothing because the federal government has massively superior firepower:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Suffocate Free Speech</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 15:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</guid>
      <description>Colleges in the United States are systematically destroying free speech, free thought, and creative writing. Sixty-five percent of colleges and universities censor students, even in creative writing classes.
[youtube=https://youtu.be/Z3vgGqlZGGE] Hillsdale or nothing.
Related articles  * [GREG LUKIANOFF IN THE NEW YORK TIMES: Feigning Free Speech on Campus. &amp;quot;Colleges and universities a...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/155479/) (pjmedia.com) * [ONE WAY FREE SPEECH: The progressive vision of free speech is decidedly one-way, excluding any s...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/154514/) (pjmedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Save Religious Freedom in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/13/how-you-can-save-religious-freedom-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/13/how-you-can-save-religious-freedom-in-america/</guid>
      <description>When Barack Obama declared that Catholics must either violate their consciences or face government persecution, he wasn’t going after just Catholics. Nor was he promoting healthcare.
Barack Obama and his myrmidon Kathleen Sebelius tried to erase the First Amendment. They tried to erase religious freedom. They tried to take away yet another foundational liberty that made America America.
And they will try again  &#34;
Unless you stop them.
But how are you going to stop them alone?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>