<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anthony Kennedy on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/anthony-kennedy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in anthony Kennedy on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:05:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/anthony-kennedy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Votes on Obamacare Today</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</guid>
      <description>We won’t know the result until late June, most likely. And the results of today’s vote could change by then.

Still, it’s sort of weird that after three years of public, wildly emotional and stupifyingly complex arguments, the fate of the republic comes down to a short meeting in Washington involving nine people in a paneled room.
Mark Sherman of AP describes the cloistered scene:
 After months of anticipation, thousands of pages of briefs and more than six hours of arguments, the justices will vote on the fate of President Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s health care overhaul in under an hour Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCOTUS Reality Tour</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/scotus-reality-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/scotus-reality-tour/</guid>
      <description>By now you’ve seen the sensational headlines:
* People Are Saying That Obama&#39;s Healthcare Law Got Massacred At The Supreme Court Today*  Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/politics#ixzz1qMjfnTtF** Here Is The Moment When Justice Alito Shredded Verrilli At The Obamacare Hearings* Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/politics#ixzz1qMjjQXFM** Skeptical Kennedy signals trouble for Obama&amp;rsquo;s healthcare law** Supreme Court Health Care Law: Justices Come Down Hard On The Mandate
And so it goes.
Before we start dancing in the streets, let’s face a little reality.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>