<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2016 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2016/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2016 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed: Coup Attempt Is Under Way In America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/14/confirmed-coup-attempt-is-under-way-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 13:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/14/confirmed-coup-attempt-is-under-way-in-america/</guid>
      <description>You might have thought I was paranoid for wondering if some people in the CIA and the Deep State are plotting a coup to overturn our recent election.
The Wall Street Journal seems to agree with my conclusion: a coup attempt is going on in America. Rogue actors within the CIA, all of the major leftist media (New York Times, Washington Post, CNN, NBC, ABC, CBS), and probably major defense contractors seem to be involved, though the Wall Street Journal stops short of accusing advertisers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Trump Might Never Become President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/12/why-trump-might-never-become-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 01:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/12/why-trump-might-never-become-president/</guid>
      <description>Call me paranoid, but it seems Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s chances of taking the oath of office for President are diminishing every day.
You might find yourself wondering why the CIA would plot a coup against Trump and his supporters. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t wondered about a CIA coup, you should.** Focus your awareness for a moment on what Trump means to the people of the Deep State.**
The Deep State involves those people and institutions that have insulated themselves from the consequences of elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the CIA Plotting a Coup? *UPDATE* FBI Disputes CIA Allegation - VIDEOS</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/11/is-the-cia-plotting-a-coup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/11/is-the-cia-plotting-a-coup/</guid>
      <description>Many powerful interests around the world loathe Donald Trump and the people who elected him. There&amp;rsquo;s no disputing that.
One of those powerful interests is the Central Intelligence Agency. One of the CIA&amp;rsquo;s own, Evan McMullin, attempted to disrupt the election. Like Bay of Pigs and Saddam&amp;rsquo;s weapons of mass destruction, that CIA plot failed. Even George Will admits the CIA makes some horrible, deadly mistakes. And sometimes those mistakes come from seeing the results they want to see, not the results presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump: The Greatest President-elect in History</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/08/donald-trump-the-greatest-president-elect-in-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 03:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/08/donald-trump-the-greatest-president-elect-in-history/</guid>
      <description>No one saw this coming.
In the month since the election on November 8, America burst out of the longest economic malaise since the Great Depression. Historians will credit the election of Donald Trump as the 45th President of the United States. Those historians will be right, of course, but how can that be? President Trump won&amp;rsquo;t take office until Friday, January 20, 2017. Today is December 8, 2016. Yet Trump has already transformed America more in four weeks than Barack Obama did in eight years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapter Twelve</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/03/civil-war-chapter-twelve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/03/civil-war-chapter-twelve/</guid>
      <description>Roger crashed into his office. His sanctuary. It was only two fifteen, but he wanted a drink. Calls first.
He pulled out is cell phone and decided to call the cop again. But the phone buzzed in his hand before he could find the number.
“Hello,” Roger said.
“Hi, Mr. Thompson? This is Amanda Mateo, one of David’s teachers.”
“Hi. Ms. Mateo. Yeah, we met in August.”
“Oh, yeah, right. Parents’ Night.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>