<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics 2012 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics 2012 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop The Crazy Talk: Vote Fraud Didn’t Cost Romney The Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</guid>
      <description>I wrote yesterday that if you need someone to blame, blame me. Don’t blame bogeymen.

Yes, vote fraud is real. Voter rolls in most states need to be cleaned up. Voter intimidation should be harshly prosecuted.
You can sign up at True the Vote or Missouri Precinct Project to take effective, useful action. These organizations do vital work, and they both need more volunteers.
Using vote fraud, however, as an excuse for secession or for blocking the Electoral College vote is neither effective nor useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is How To Spend Election Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/this-is-how-to-spend-election-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/this-is-how-to-spend-election-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives take great pride in working, and for good reason. Work gives shape to life. Work is the poles of a tent, the bones of a body, the beams in the ceiling.

But work isn’t why we live. We live to pursue happiness.
For some, the pursuit of happiness involves acquiring property. Land, clothes, cars, plastic surgery. All examples of the pursuit of happiness.
Voting is another pursuit. People vote for minor candidates representing strange parties who have no chance of winning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney’s Cleaning Up in Early Voting, but It’s Confused the Hell Out of Politico</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/30/mitt-romneys-cleaning-up-in-early-voting-but-its-confused-the-hell-out-of-politico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/30/mitt-romneys-cleaning-up-in-early-voting-but-its-confused-the-hell-out-of-politico/</guid>
      <description>Gallup released its early voting poll today, and it shows Mitt Romney winning 52% to 45%—right in line with their Likely Voter poll numbers. Here’s the chart.

Politico Reporter Can’t Read But Gallup’s section on early voting by party ID completely lost Politico’s Kevin Robillard.
Robillard looked at the chart that shows when voters intend to vote by party and candidate and mistook it for voting results. This poll question shows that those who support Obama as as likely to vote early as are those who support Romney.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignoramus Rex</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/30/ignoramus-rex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 17:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/30/ignoramus-rex/</guid>
      <description>Arguably, the most important battles for economic liberty in the next four years will be between states and the government in Washington. The progressives in Washington want to consolidate power and money to feed the insatiable appetite of parasites in the USA and the world.

Rex Sinquefield, the billionaire Bishop DuBourg alum who masquerades as a libertarian-ish Republican, lifted his mask this week to help Washington’s progressives steal Missouri’s autonomy and treasures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Write Yourself Into the Great American Novel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/24/how-to-write-yourself-into-the-great-american-novel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/24/how-to-write-yourself-into-the-great-american-novel/</guid>
      <description>A couple years ago, a lot of folks believed that victory in 2010 would be a cakewalk. Led by Tea Party activists, the GOP picked up over 800 legislative seats, state and federal, in the 2010 off-year election. Rumors of the Republican Party&amp;rsquo;s death had been greatly exaggerated.
  
Or so it seemed.
Novels and action movies involve a hero&amp;rsquo;s quest. The main character hopes to accomplish something. Dorothy wants to return to Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin’s AG Race Makes 3rd Anniversary Tea Party Even More Important</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/27/ed-martins-ag-race-makes-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-even-more-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 01:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/27/ed-martins-ag-race-makes-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-even-more-important/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago, weeks ago, how many Missouri statewide offices did you expect to flip? Be honest.
Yes, there are great people running for Governor, Secretary of State, and Treasurer. And we already have a fine Lieutenant Governor Kinder running for re-election.
But numerous factors, like name recognition, experience, and Jay Nixon’s weird relationship with Republican House leadership, made a major upset unlikely. And no Republicans had stepped up to challenge Chris Koster for Attorney General.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Ed Martin Running for Attorney General in Missouri *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin Jr. of St. Louis has redirected his fire to the Attorney General race, and this is great news for everyone except Chris Koster.
Back when Ed Martin was talking about running for the Republican nod to take on Claire McCaskill, I had another thought. Well, a bunch of people had another thought: Ed would make an outstanding Attorney General.
UPDATE
HUGE list of endorsements on Ed’s official press release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire Exposes GOP’s Diverse Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</guid>
      <description>Okay, Santorum and Gingrich didn’t get a bump out of their debates over the weekend. More like the bump got them.
And Ron Paul did way better than I expected. Congratulations to Dr. Paul and Mitt. 
I still think my Saturday night post accurately reflected the national impressions, though. That’s backed up by this CBS News poll that shows Republicans believe Santorum most closely shares their values, but—and this is a J Lo but—they believe Romney is more electable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Moves for Herman Cain Supporters Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</guid>
      <description>Herman Cain is riding a wave of popularity because of his upset win in the Florida straw poll on Saturday. He’s helped by Rick Perry’s free-fall and Mitt Romney’s establishmentarianism. But Cain is a huge underdog.
That’s okay because **America loves an underdog. **
Here’s what must happen right now for Herman Cain to win:
1. Social Media avalanche. Get @THEHermanCain trending on Twitter, and keep it there for five consecutive days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>