<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/authors/bill-hennessy/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 09:28:33 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/authors/bill-hennessy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It Begins: Isolation, Fear, and Masks Make People Mean</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/it-begins-isolation-fear-and-masks-make-us-mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 09:28:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/it-begins-isolation-fear-and-masks-make-us-mean/</guid>
      <description>An ice cream parlor in Massachusetts closed one day after re-opening because customers treated his employees like dirt.
Owner Mark Lawrence told Fox25 Boston, via Fox News:
 “People have forgotten how to treat other human beings in the six or seven weeks that they’ve been confined to their homes,” he told the station. “They have no clue how to respect other human beings.”
 After just one day, Lawrence closed his shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Efficiency Caused Food and Toilet Paper Shortages</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/how-efficiency-caused-food-shortages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 09:08:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/how-efficiency-caused-food-shortages/</guid>
      <description>If you work for corporation, you&amp;rsquo;ve undoubtedly heard about the virtues of efficiency. And, if you&amp;rsquo;re living in America, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably noticed shortages of stables like meat, packaged food, cleaning supplies, toilet paper, and more.
What you probably don&amp;rsquo;t realize is that business&amp;rsquo;s pathological concerns for efficiency caused the shortages. And, what&amp;rsquo;s worse, most of the &amp;ldquo;expert&amp;rdquo; recommendations for dealing with pandemics will put us all at risk for precisely the same reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Secrets of Coronavirus Data Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:21:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>Nate Silver let the cat out of the bag.
In case you don&amp;rsquo;t recognize his name, Nate Silver is the data analyst who launched Five Thirty-Eight, orignally in the New York Times. He was famous for not predicting an election a few years ago.
Today, Nate unloaded on the media for just one aspect of their narrative-driven Coronavirus coverage. In short, noted the same thing Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View pointed out a month ago: positive tests is meaningless unless it&amp;rsquo;s indexed to the number of tests administered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Triumphant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 04:56:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump just had another one of those weeks for which he&amp;rsquo;s become famous.
 There was the week hit bombed Syria while dining with President Xi of China at Mar a Lago. There was Easter Week 2019 when the Mueller Report exonerated and the economy hit new highs. There was the week of the State of the Union Address that included his exoneration in the Senate.  But, this week&amp;rsquo;s outbreak of liberty and its commensurate exposure of Trump&amp;rsquo;s enemies as pure scum is the best so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Andrew Cuomo Intentionally Kill the Elderly of New York?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:50:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</guid>
      <description>It would be the most sinister murder plot in US history. Imagine a governor conspiring to thin the population of elderly people, using a pandemic as both cover and weapon.
As unimaginable as it would be, evidence is mounting New York Governor Andrew Cuomo did just that: culled the herd in nursing homes by weaponizing Coronavirus.
Dumped Off With Their Own Body Bags New York Governor Andrew Cuomo implemented an emergency declaration that required nursing homes to accept active Coronavirus patients regardless of their ability to care for or isolate the infected patients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>