<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/authors/bill-hennessy/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 16:32:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/authors/bill-hennessy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New CDC Office Guidelines Ignore Science</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/cdc-office-guidelines-ignore-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 16:32:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/cdc-office-guidelines-ignore-science/</guid>
      <description>The CDC, today, issued guidelines for reopening offices that ignore medical guidance regarding masks.
The latest medical guidance, according to May 21 article in the New England Journal of Medicine reported here, says:
 Public health authorities define a significant exposure to Covid-19 as face-to-face contact within 6 feet with a patient with symptomatic Covid-19 that is sustained for at least a few minutes (and some say more than 10 minutes or even 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Masks Are Symbolic,&#39; say Dr Fauci and The New England Journal of Medicine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/masks-are-symbolic-dr-fauci/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 07:41:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/masks-are-symbolic-dr-fauci/</guid>
      <description>In the past week, Dr. Anthony Fauci and the New England Journal of Medicine have admitted that masks are little more than symbols. Virtue signaling.
For those of you who shout &amp;ldquo;science&amp;rdquo; like it&amp;rsquo;s a Tourette tick, this is from the New England Journal of Medicine on May 21, 2020:
 We know that wearing a mask outside health care facilities offers little, if any, protection from infection. Public health authorities define a significant exposure to Covid-19 as face-to-face contact within 6 feet with a patient with symptomatic Covid-19 that is sustained for at least a few minutes (and some say more than 10 minutes or even 30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Should Christians Prepare for and Respond to New World Order</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/how-should-christians-prepare-for-and-respond-to-new-world-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 12:11:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/how-should-christians-prepare-for-and-respond-to-new-world-order/</guid>
      <description>A recurring theme in the Old Testament went something like this: the people of God (Jews) face a temporal crisis. The people of God surrender to a pagan nation, paying tribute to both the foreigners and to their gods.
Most of the chosen people assimilate with their earthly masters. During the Babylonian Exile, they largely abandoned circumcision and most of the Mosaic laws. The Temple was given over to orgies and terrible sacrilege.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Priests Gamble With Your Soul, and What You can Do About It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/water-gun-baptism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 15:07:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/water-gun-baptism/</guid>
      <description>Could anything be more entertaining than watching a &amp;ldquo;woke&amp;rdquo; priest mock his own religion and its sacraments by spraying an infant with a water gun in the sanctuary?
        Yet, this is where the &amp;ldquo;reforms&amp;rdquo; of Vatican II have landed us. Satan himself has more respect for God than these vested buffoons who use Coronavirus as an excuse to mock God, mock His Church, and mock the seven Holy Sacraments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Turn Nursing Homes Into Death Camps</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</guid>
      <description>When I wrote this post on May 6, I worried how it would be received. Accusing a governor of intentionally killing nursing home residents in order to save money is a serious charge. And, with only circumstantial evidence, difficult to prove.
Since then, Andrew Cuomo&amp;rsquo;s behavior has been consistent with guilt. The latest example is deflection. He&amp;rsquo;s trying, now, to blame federal guidelines for his order to force uninfected nursing homes to treat confirmed COVID-19 patients even if they lacked the facilities and skills to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>