<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/authors/bill-hennessy/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 06:24:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/authors/bill-hennessy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Us Pray at the Statue of St. Louis in Forest Park Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/let-us-pray-at-the-statue-of-st-louis-in-forest-park-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 06:24:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/let-us-pray-at-the-statue-of-st-louis-in-forest-park-saturday/</guid>
      <description>By the grace of God, Jim Hoft, the Gateway Pundit, has called all Catholic Christian men to pray the Rosary at the statue of St. Louis IX, King of France, on Art Hill in Forest Park at Noon on Saturday, June 28, 2020. Please join us. If you cannot join us, please pray for us.
Pray that our intentions align with the will of God, that we do nothing out of vainglory or pride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Confederate Army</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-new-confederate-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 11:22:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-new-confederate-army/</guid>
      <description>Five hundred West Point Military Academy graduates became the ideological heirs of Robert E. Lee this week. I bet they didn&amp;rsquo;t even realize it. The Gateway Pundit reports that 500 former West Point grads denounce &amp;ldquo;politicization&amp;rdquo; of the military and refuse to defend America against domestic enemies.
Oath of Commissioned Officers  I [state your name], do solemnly swear (or affirm) that I will support and defend the Constitution of the United States against all enemies, foreign and domestic; that I will bear true faith and allegiance to the same; that I take this obligation freely, without any mental reservation or purpose of evasion; and that I will well and faithfully discharge the duties of the office on which I am about to enter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War Chapter 14</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/civil-war-chapter-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 11:18:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/civil-war-chapter-14/</guid>
      <description>(Previously, on Civil War&amp;hellip;)
Amanda Mateo&amp;rsquo;s door did indeed have balloons on it. A big plastic wreath with fake balloons. As if Martha Stewart went to work for Fischer-Price.
&amp;ldquo;Hello, again,&amp;rdquo; Amanda said as she opened the door.
&amp;ldquo;How did you know it was safe to open the door?&amp;rdquo; Mike asked.
&amp;ldquo;I looked through the hole, silly. I&amp;rsquo;m not stupid.&amp;rdquo;
Amanda stepped back, and Mike walked into her apartment. Brand new everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapter 13</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/civil-war-chapter-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 18:53:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/civil-war-chapter-13/</guid>
      <description>(Previously, in Civil War&amp;hellip;)
Michael Francis Franklin walked into his San Jose home at six thirty-seven on November 18, 2016. In his hands were a dozen envelopes and ads from his mailbox. On his mind was Amanda Mateo.
Franklin was married from 1999 to 2006. He could remember about an hour and a half of being happily married. The rest was torture. In the decade since his divorce, Mike had come to accept that he was meant to be alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Crazy Democrat Idea That Doesn&#39;t Go Far Enough</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/qualified-immunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 07:57:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/qualified-immunity/</guid>
      <description>House Democrats last week introduced a federal police reform bill. As usual, the bill is terrible, even in concept. Policing is a local issue.
But, like a broken clock, the Democrat bill is right on one matter: their bill makes qualified immunity a legislative issue instead of a judicial concern.
What Is &amp;lsquo;Qualified Immunity&amp;rsquo; Qualified immunity bars lawsuits against public officials whose actions cause actual damages unless those actions violate the law.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>