<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Political Psychology on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/political-psychology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Political Psychology on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 14:06:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/political-psychology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Declare Independence from Social Media. Do This Instead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/04/declare-independence-from-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 14:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/04/declare-independence-from-social-media/</guid>
      <description>The American Revolution started in a tavern.
Actually, it started in many taverns. But taverns they were.
J.R.R. Tolkien and C.S. Lewis hatched their greatest novels in The Eagle and Child tavern in Oxford.
If you want to be as great as the founding fathers or as prolific as Tolkien and Lewis, get off social media and get to a bar. I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you why.
#1: Social Media Breed Depression and Anxiety The more time you spend on Facebook, the more likely you are to suffer depression, attempt suicide, and feel overwhelmed by life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s what will happen in 2018 election (POLL)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/30/heres-what-will-happen-in-2018-election-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 16:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/30/heres-what-will-happen-in-2018-election-poll/</guid>
      <description>Do you think Democrats will retake the House, the Senate, or both in the 2018 election?
[socialpoll id=&amp;quot;2479812&amp;rdquo;]
Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve answered, let&amp;rsquo;s consider the limits of data science in 2018.
The best data scientists in the world agreed with nearly absolute certainty. These scientists determined, beyond a reasonable doubt, that Hillary Clinton would be the 45th President of the United States. That was in 2016.
Those scientists were wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Washington Post Radicalizes Murderers (video)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/14/how-the-washington-post-radicalizes-murderers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 01:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/14/how-the-washington-post-radicalizes-murderers/</guid>
      <description>To liberals, the murder of a Republican is like the swatting of a mosquito. They oppose violence in theory, but they also want the pest dead. They&amp;rsquo;re just too lazy to get out of their easy chairs to do it themselves.
Cass Sunstein, a leftist who&amp;rsquo;s happy whenever a conservative dies early, wrote a book called Nudge. It&amp;rsquo;s a good psychology book. Nudge is about persuasion, which is my chief interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>False Flag or Not</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/08/false-flag-or-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/08/false-flag-or-not/</guid>
      <description>The contemporary term false flag describes covert operations that are designed to deceive in such a way that activities appear as though they are being carried out by entities, groups, or nations other than those who actually planned and executed them. [Wikipedia]
 Think of a time when you acted on false information. You knew it might be false, but you acted as if it was true. Why did you do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do I Mean By &#34;Narrative&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/07/what-do-i-mean-by-narrative/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 22:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/07/what-do-i-mean-by-narrative/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t agree.&amp;rdquo;
Some folks disagreed with my instant assessment of the Syrian strike. My assessment: Trump&amp;rsquo;s surprise military attack will shift four narratives in Trump&amp;rsquo;s favor:
** Trump is Hitler: dead ** Trump is a Russian agent: dead ** Trump is incompetent: dying ** Trump is a lightweight among world leaders: dead
In other words, it took 59 cruise missiles to blow up the left&amp;rsquo;s anti-Trump narratives.
But my friends disagree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BACKFIRE: Psychological Tricks Used to Advance Russian Conspiracy Theory</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/07/how-newspapers-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 18:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/07/how-newspapers-lie/</guid>
      <description>Newspapers lie. And by &amp;ldquo;newspapers,&amp;rdquo; I mean the whole mainstream media.
Yesterday I told you how Donald Trump punked the media by pulling a Crazy Ivan maneuver. A critic on Twitter thinks I&amp;rsquo;m lying. He thinks I&amp;rsquo;m lying because he read a news article. He read it in the New York Times.
This Twitter critic thinks it&amp;rsquo;s okay for the New York Times to lie (&amp;ldquo;Wiretapped Data Used In Inquiry of Trump Aides&amp;rdquo;), as long as they only lie in their headlines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How ObamaCare Benefits from the Scarcity Heuristic</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/23/obamacare-benefits-from-scarcity-heuristic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 13:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/23/obamacare-benefits-from-scarcity-heuristic/</guid>
      <description>The Concorde was a supersonic passenger plane. It shuttled people between New York and Paris very quickly.
When commercial Concorde flights began in 1976, the novelty and excitement of flying at twice the speed of sound led people to line up to take the flights. But after 27 years and several safety mishaps, the Concorde&amp;rsquo;s popularity waned. Flights were often less than half full, so British Airways, the operator, was losing money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Landslide Tipping Point Is Breathing Down Your Neck</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/19/trumps-landslide-tipping-point-is-breathing-down-your-neck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/19/trumps-landslide-tipping-point-is-breathing-down-your-neck/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re getting close, folks. So close you can feel it. Close your eyes and feel the soft, warm breath on the back of your neck. (Now open your eyes and continue reading. You&amp;rsquo;re such a good reader.)
As you watch the polls shift rapidly toward Trump, you might wonder what&amp;rsquo;s happening. What&amp;rsquo;s happening is completely natural, but it&amp;rsquo;s not normal. Elections don&amp;rsquo;t usually go this way. And two psychological phenomena are working to deliver the Trump landslide I predicted long ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Election Unlike Any Other</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/08/an-election-unlike-any-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 03:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/08/an-election-unlike-any-other/</guid>
      <description>France’s population had changed considerably since 1614. The non-aristocratic members of the Third Estate now represented 98 percent of the people but could still be outvoted by the other two bodies. In the lead-up to the May 5 meeting, the Third Estate began to mobilize support for equal representation and the abolishment of the noble veto–in other words, they wanted voting by head and not by status. While all of the orders shared a common desire for fiscal and judicial reform as well as a more representative form of government, the nobles in particular were loath to give up the privileges they enjoyed under the traditional system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purpose Trumps Policy and Principles—Video</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/05/purpose-trumps-policy-and-principles-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 13:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/05/purpose-trumps-policy-and-principles-video/</guid>
      <description>Why did Trump beat Ted Cruz? Probably the biggest reason is that Trump talks purpose while Cruz talks policy and principles.
When people hear Trump, they hear a purpose that aligns with their purpose. I know I do. And it&amp;rsquo;s similar to the purpose Arthur C. Brooks explained in his great book, The Conservative Heart.
Ted Cruz never seemed to have a purpose, just policies and principles. Cruz spoke of abstract principles and left it to the people to figure out if those principles would make their lives better or worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being the Oddball Sucks</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/how-leaders-decide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 10:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/how-leaders-decide/</guid>
      <description>Could you stand by a &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; answer?
Let&amp;rsquo;s pretend you&amp;rsquo;re in a room with 10 people about your age and background. You&amp;rsquo;ve been talking for a while, and you&amp;rsquo;ve gotten to know the others. Then the task begins. It&amp;rsquo;s straightforward.
On a large TV, you see a line drawing of a face. The instructor calls out people by name and asks if the face is a happy face, a sad face, or neutral face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caution: Identifying as &#39;NeverTrump&#39; Changes Your Brain</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/what-happens-you-identify-as-nevertrump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/what-happens-you-identify-as-nevertrump/</guid>
      <description>When a person declares himself &amp;ldquo;NeverTrump,&amp;rdquo; he thinks he&amp;rsquo;s making a political statement. Or a moral one. But he&amp;rsquo;s not. He&amp;rsquo;s making a psychological commitment that&amp;rsquo;s very difficult and painful to break.
Identity is the highest, most powerful form of persuasion. Identity also drives our decisions in parts of the brain we don&amp;rsquo;t really have conscious control over. I realize many conservatives reject brain science, but, for those of you who are open to learning, I&amp;rsquo;ll explain as best I can in a moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You&#39;re Mad At Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/06/why-youre-mad-at-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 02:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/06/why-youre-mad-at-trump/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people seem to be mad at Trump. You might be one of them.
You probably think you know why you’re mad at him. For instance, you might not like what he said about the judge in a lawsuit he’s involved with. Or maybe you didn’t like what he said about Rosie O’Donnell. You might even be mad that he said Saddam Hussein was a bad man who was good at killing terrorists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Predict Trump&#39;s Landslide Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/13/how-to-predict-trumps-landslide-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 20:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/13/how-to-predict-trumps-landslide-win/</guid>
      <description>You might have noticed that my predictions have been remarkably accurate lately, have you not?
For example, on Sunday, May 1, I predicted Ted Cruz would suspend his campaign after getting trounced in Indiana. Two days later, Cruz lost the Indiana primary to Donald Trump 53 to 36. At the time I wrote, many pundits and pollster still believed Cruz could win that Indiana race, and everyone believed Cruz was telling the truth when he said repeatedly he was staying in the race to Cleveland unless Trump reached 1,237 delegates before then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Is Conservative?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/08/who-is-conservative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 22:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/08/who-is-conservative/</guid>
      <description>People think they&amp;rsquo;re rational, but we&amp;rsquo;re not. For example, on many issues,** Trump&amp;rsquo;s positions are almost identical to Ronald Reagan&amp;rsquo;s.** When it comes to abortion, trade, taxes, foreign policy and the military, and entitlements like Social Security, you can&amp;rsquo;t fit a dime between Reagan and Trump.
So why do people see Trump as far to the left of Reagan?
Contrasts and comparisons.
Reagan ran against George Bush and John B. Anderson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Psychology of The Inevitable</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/01/the-psychology-of-the-inevitable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 16:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/01/the-psychology-of-the-inevitable/</guid>
      <description>I have no idea who will win the Indiana primary 72 hours from the time I write. But the people inside Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s campaign seem to have an idea. And it&amp;rsquo;s not good for them. Cruz&amp;rsquo;s top team expects their candidate to lose. And Senator Cruz seems to have accepted that outcome.
Expectations Matter More Than Preferences Regular readers know that polls that ask &amp;ldquo;who do you think will win&amp;rdquo; trump polls that ask &amp;ldquo;who do you intend to vote for&amp;rdquo; or even &amp;ldquo;who did you vote for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fascinating Results from Leaders Eat Last Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</guid>
      <description>This is the story of hard choices and how people resist making them.
Last week&amp;rsquo;s poll asked you to watch a video by Simon Sinek before answering two, simple, two-part questions: which Republican candidate for President and Missouri Governor is most likely and least likely to eat last?
I intended the poll to be hard. Not complicated, not long, but emotionally challenging.
Why the Poll Was Emotionally Challenging For several weeks, I have built a case for the importance of leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to kill a movement</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/30/how-to-kill-a-movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 03:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/30/how-to-kill-a-movement/</guid>
      <description>Did you ever see a movement grow?
Did you see the way it starts?
Did you feel it spread around you?
Did you hear it rustling the leaves and scraping the sidewalk?
Did you want to kill it?
The weird thing about movements is that opposition tends to strengthen them. Movements feed on hostility the way rats feed on garbage.
The way you kill a movement is infiltration and fragmentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Rambling Now?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/18/whos-rambling-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 21:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/18/whos-rambling-now/</guid>
      <description>Someone who met Bill Clinton told me, &amp;ldquo;I rambled. He probably thought I was an idiot.&amp;rdquo;
No. Bill Clinton wanted you to ramble. He wanted to make you the most important person in the room for two minutes. He listened for a nugget of information&amp;ndash;a story&amp;ndash;he could use in his next speech.
If you&amp;rsquo;re running for office remember: the most important person in every room is the voter you&amp;rsquo;re talking with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Walk on the Hedonic Treadmill</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/17/take-a-walk-on-the-hedonic-treadmill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 21:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/06/17/take-a-walk-on-the-hedonic-treadmill/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s what happens when you raise the minimum wage to $15 an hour, according to scientists:
Nothing.
Well, not nothing. All kinds of bad things happen to the economy. But nothing happens for two groups of people central to the whole debate: workers who get a bump to $15 and employers who have to bump to $15 an hour.
Most cities and states that have raised their minimum wage laws to $15 will phase in the increase over five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Secrets Politicians Don&#39;t Want You to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/20/5-secrets-politicians-dont-want-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 14:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/20/5-secrets-politicians-dont-want-know/</guid>
      <description>How long has it been since you said, &amp;ldquo;they just don&amp;rsquo;t listen to us?&amp;rdquo;
By &amp;ldquo;they,&amp;rdquo; you mean politicians, of course. Maybe you feel they listen to lobbyists and big corporations and banksters, but they don&amp;rsquo;t listen to their constituents.
I have to agree with you. Politicians don&amp;rsquo;t listen to their constituents. They don&amp;rsquo;t even know who their constituents are.
They know demographics and statistics about their constituents, but that&amp;rsquo;s like saying you know how a banana tastes because you read a chemical assay report of its contents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Messages Backfire?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/04/why-do-messages-backfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/04/why-do-messages-backfire/</guid>
      <description>In the 1970s, a magazine ad for Benson &amp;amp; Hedges cigarettes portrayed a hockey fight. Two players slug it out. Sticks and gloves litter the ice.
The point of view is on-ice, in the midst of the scrum. The crowd is on its feet, banging the glass. You&amp;rsquo;re right there with linesmen trying to break it up.
The hockey gloves are Coopers. Every hockey player knows the name. In the photo, one of the gloves has been doctored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Roy Blunt Needs a Psychologist</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/03/can-roy-blunt-save-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/03/can-roy-blunt-save-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>Senator Roy Blunt (HA-57) proposed that all Obamacare ads contain a disclaimer: &amp;ldquo;Paid for by the American Taxpayer.&amp;rdquo;
I get the idea. I can&amp;rsquo;t stand it when my tax dollars buy ads intended to raise my taxes. It means I&amp;rsquo;m fighting against myself.
Still, I don&amp;rsquo;t like Senator Blunt&amp;rsquo;s plan because I think it could backfire.
The Psychology of Ownership Right now, few people have a sense of ownership of Obamacare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s the Most Encouraging Thing John Boehner Ever Said</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</guid>
      <description>Today on ABC&amp;rsquo;s This Week, Speaker of the House John Boehner spoke very powerful words about himself. They reveal his motivation. And it&amp;rsquo;s very encouraging.
 &amp;ldquo;I’m a reasonable guy. But I didn’t come to Washington to be a congressman. I came to do something for my country.&amp;rdquo;
 Write that down. That statement echos.
Research shows thatpeople motivated by doing, by getting better, by learning, will work harder and stay truer to their principles than people motivated by demonstrating how good they are&amp;ndash;being something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Happens When You Count Your Blessings?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/18/what-happens-when-you-count-your-blessings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/18/what-happens-when-you-count-your-blessings/</guid>
      <description>I think I was upset about losing a baseball game. I don’t remember. I’m better now, but when I was a kid, everybody knew when I was upset. I made sure of it.
And I hated when someone tried to break those foul moods.
Wouldn’t you know it. My mom said, “count your blessings.”
Yeah. What blessings? We lost! Wasn’t she listening?
I was a real peach.
It turns out, my mom was right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Strong Leader Can Keep Congress In Line</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/11/one-strong-leader-can-keep-congress-in-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/11/one-strong-leader-can-keep-congress-in-line/</guid>
      <description>Why do our members of Congress disappoint us?
Why do they seem to put their personal interests ahead of the mission we elected them to do?
More importantly, how we can we deter Republicans or bring them back to the fold?
Study Shows How Communities Keep Members In Line New research by University of Oxford and the ETH Zurich could provide an answer: one strong leader.
When non-cheating members of a community empowered a strong member to challenge the anti-social cheater, the cheating stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use This One Word Because It Makes You More Influential</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/use-this-one-word-because-it-makes-you-more-influential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/use-this-one-word-because-it-makes-you-more-influential/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me to explain why the human brain works the way it does. And don&amp;rsquo;t ask me how scientists get the idea for some experiments.
Instead, take note of the most influential work in the English language, because I want you to be more influential.
What&amp;rsquo;s that one word?
It&amp;rsquo;s not &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;instantly&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;new.&amp;rdquo; They&amp;rsquo;re very powerful words, as every copywriter knows. But they&amp;rsquo;re not the most influential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Want Fewer Abortions, Stop Talking About How Many There Are</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/19/if-you-want-fewer-abortions-stop-talking-about-how-many-there-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/19/if-you-want-fewer-abortions-stop-talking-about-how-many-there-are/</guid>
      <description>I’m using abortion as an example, but this bit of science applies to all political messaging.
What’s wrong with this headline?

I’ll tell you what’s wrong with it. It shouts: “Everybody’s getting an abortion!” Even if connected with messages that say abortion is wrong.
In numerous studies, messages intended to discourage a behavior by promoting the number of people engaged in the behavior (called negative social proof) actually caused the behavior to increase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss The Brain Study That Tells You How to Influence Democrats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/01/dont-miss-the-brain-study-that-tells-you-how-to-influence-democrats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/01/dont-miss-the-brain-study-that-tells-you-how-to-influence-democrats/</guid>
      <description>One of the most powerful tools of influence is fear.
Decades of research shows that fear of loss is about three times as motivating as hope for gain. (This changes under certain situations, like conditions of certain loss, but that’s for another time.)
So political message writers often use negative messages to influence voters to take a chance on a cause or a candidate.
This tactic works well with Republican voters, and less well with Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ambition Comes In Good and Bad Flavors</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/28/ambition-comes-in-good-and-bad-flavors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/28/ambition-comes-in-good-and-bad-flavors/</guid>
      <description>When I was in high school I wanted to be a US Senator.
Wait, that wasn’t the punch line.
That ambition changed, and I&amp;rsquo;m glad it did. It was a bad ambition.
Steve Jobs wanted to build an enduring company that made insanely great products that people loved. Thank God he pursued and achieved his ambition, because it was good and noble.
What’s the difference? It’s not that one ambition was personal and one involved others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why The Sequester Is Worse Now Than It Will Be After It Happens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/why-the-sequester-is-worse-now-than-it-will-be-after-it-happens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/why-the-sequester-is-worse-now-than-it-will-be-after-it-happens/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Dr. Gina Show Listeners!
Republicans should announce “the sequester won’t be so bad” and shut up, and science tells us why.
Obama, the Dems, liberal pundits, the press, and even John Boehner are running around yelling about how horrible the sequester will be.
In some deep recesses of our minds, we agree. “Oh, my God! We’re all going to do die!”
Fear-mongering only works in the future because, in short, nothing is as bad (or as good) as we think it will be when we think about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>