<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Political Psychology on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/political-psychology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Political Psychology on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 14:06:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/political-psychology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Declare Independence from Social Media. Do This Instead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/04/declare-independence-from-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 14:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/04/declare-independence-from-social-media/</guid>
      <description>The American Revolution started in a tavern.
Actually, it started in many taverns. But taverns they were.
J.R.R. Tolkien and C.S. Lewis hatched their greatest novels in The Eagle and Child tavern in Oxford.
If you want to be as great as the founding fathers or as prolific as Tolkien and Lewis, get off social media and get to a bar. I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you why.
#1: Social Media Breed Depression and Anxiety The more time you spend on Facebook, the more likely you are to suffer depression, attempt suicide, and feel overwhelmed by life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s what will happen in 2018 election (POLL)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/30/heres-what-will-happen-in-2018-election-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 16:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/30/heres-what-will-happen-in-2018-election-poll/</guid>
      <description>Do you think Democrats will retake the House, the Senate, or both in the 2018 election?
[socialpoll id=&amp;quot;2479812&amp;rdquo;]
Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve answered, let&amp;rsquo;s consider the limits of data science in 2018.
The best data scientists in the world agreed with nearly absolute certainty. These scientists determined, beyond a reasonable doubt, that Hillary Clinton would be the 45th President of the United States. That was in 2016.
Those scientists were wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Washington Post Radicalizes Murderers (video)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/14/how-the-washington-post-radicalizes-murderers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 01:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/14/how-the-washington-post-radicalizes-murderers/</guid>
      <description>To liberals, the murder of a Republican is like the swatting of a mosquito. They oppose violence in theory, but they also want the pest dead. They&amp;rsquo;re just too lazy to get out of their easy chairs to do it themselves.
Cass Sunstein, a leftist who&amp;rsquo;s happy whenever a conservative dies early, wrote a book called Nudge. It&amp;rsquo;s a good psychology book. Nudge is about persuasion, which is my chief interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>False Flag or Not</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/08/false-flag-or-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/08/false-flag-or-not/</guid>
      <description>The contemporary term false flag describes covert operations that are designed to deceive in such a way that activities appear as though they are being carried out by entities, groups, or nations other than those who actually planned and executed them. [Wikipedia]
 Think of a time when you acted on false information. You knew it might be false, but you acted as if it was true. Why did you do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do I Mean By &#34;Narrative&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/07/what-do-i-mean-by-narrative/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 22:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/07/what-do-i-mean-by-narrative/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t agree.&amp;rdquo;
Some folks disagreed with my instant assessment of the Syrian strike. My assessment: Trump&amp;rsquo;s surprise military attack will shift four narratives in Trump&amp;rsquo;s favor:
** Trump is Hitler: dead ** Trump is a Russian agent: dead ** Trump is incompetent: dying ** Trump is a lightweight among world leaders: dead
In other words, it took 59 cruise missiles to blow up the left&amp;rsquo;s anti-Trump narratives.
But my friends disagree.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>