<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Activism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/activism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Activism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 11:35:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/activism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Descend on Jefferson City</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/17/descend-on-jefferson-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 11:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/17/descend-on-jefferson-city/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time. Powerful and corrupt people want to undo the 2016 election. In Washington. In Missouri.
Win or lose, Americans deal with the results of elections. Our commitment to open, public government, of the people, by, the people, for people, has sustained this nation. And made it the greatest nation in the history of humanity.
But dark forces in Missouri want to turn your government into their private club. A club managed by corrupt business who rely on tax dollars to keep their failed enterprises afloat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Governance Is the Best Kept Secret in the Fight for Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/02/best-kept-secret-fight-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 03:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/02/best-kept-secret-fight-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to MOPP for this fantastic summary for Center for Self-Governance training opportunities in the show me state. Includes links to enroll in class.
  FYI&amp;hellip;
TO: MOPP SUPPORTERS
 MOPP COUNTY COORDINATORS
(please help spread this message by forwarding to your Missouri contacts/networks/thanks!)
**_ _**
**_ _**
**_ _**  Citizen involvement is “snowballing” across the State of Missouri as the Center for Self Governance adds more classes to its schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss A Rising Conservative Star</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/dont-miss-a-rising-conservative-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 23:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/dont-miss-a-rising-conservative-star/</guid>
      <description>I met Raz Shaver in 2010. Even though he’s many years my junior, Raz has been an insightful, patient, and indispensible to mentor in grassroots activism.

Raz continues to help me and St. Louis Tea Party Coalition from his bunker in Texas. He also helps groups like St. Louis Tea Party all around the country. Victories and 2010, those to come in 2012, owe, in a large degree, to Raz Shafer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Two People in West County About The After Party This Thursday at Sky Music Lounge</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/tell-two-people-in-west-county-about-the-after-party-this-thursday-at-sky-music-lounge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/tell-two-people-in-west-county-about-the-after-party-this-thursday-at-sky-music-lounge/</guid>
      <description>A friend from Dallas just called me. He said he met two conservatives from Ballwin who’d love to be involved in movement conservatism . . . but don’t know how.
I was shocked. And a little embarrassed. ** How can someone in West County not know about St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and The After Party?** &#39;

Clearly, I’ve done something wrong. I’m sorry. But I can’t just throw my hands up and walk away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare Ruling Comes Down This Week, and We’re Having a Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/24/obamacare-ruling-comes-down-this-week-and-were-having-a-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 18:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/24/obamacare-ruling-comes-down-this-week-and-were-having-a-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Pack clothes, flags, and signs for an Obamacare Tea Party at Forest Park on Art Hill this week. The rally will begin at 7:00 PM on the day the Supreme Court rules.

We don’t know the day, but we do know the time: 7:00 pm in Forest Park on Art Hill (map below). The most likely days are Monday or Thursday, but because of the magnitude of this case, it could be any day of the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTION:  Steve Tilley and Kevin Engler Want to Implement Obamacare. Stop Them.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/03/action-steve-tilley-and-kevin-engler-want-to-implement-obamacare-stop-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 02:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/03/action-steve-tilley-and-kevin-engler-want-to-implement-obamacare-stop-them/</guid>
      <description>Missouri House Speaker Steve Tilley and Senate Leader Kevin Engler never tire of implementing Obama’s totalitarian agenda.

This time, Tilley and Engler are shoving HB 1193 through to passage. This bill is designed to score brownie points with Sibelius and Obama by creating a prescription spy network that monitors the prescription drug purchases of every Missouri resident.
If Tilley and Engler get their way, every time your doctor writes a prescription, your pharmacist will be required to inform Jefferson City and Washington bureaucrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party Activist Calls for Stampede</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/frieda-responds-to-the-lake-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 10:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/frieda-responds-to-the-lake-post/</guid>
      <description>I blogged aboutthe battle of the Tea Party&amp;rsquo;s future going on around the Lake of the Ozarks recently.
I received this response from Freida Keough, St. Louis County Director ofMissouri Precinct Project:
 My answer: We have 56 positions for committeemen and women in 28 Townships for St.Louis County. Did you know that 35 new individuals filed for these positions in addition to the incumbents. Coincidence? I don&amp;rsquo;t think this happened because people felt they have nothing else to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You a Superhero?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/06/are-you-a-superhero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/06/are-you-a-superhero/</guid>
      <description>This is a challenge.
I want you to grab a pen and paper (or open your favorite note app). Now write down a list of characteristic you’d expect a **superhero_ _**to display. Write as many or as few as you’d like.
Don’t continue until you’ve written down the characteristics of a superhero.

Welcome back.
Here’s the next step. I want you to look over your list of superhero traits. As you do, think about the amount of that trait you have in you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTION: Melt the Phones</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/27/action-melt-the-phones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/27/action-melt-the-phones/</guid>
      <description>I’m going to ask you to melt phones in Jefferson City, UMSL, UMKC, and Mizzou. I’m asking you to do this today and tomorrow. I’m following up with an email to you.
It’s sad that our state’s premier University System has fallen so far.
Follow the #mounion hash tag on twitter
Jay Nixon just asked the legislature to transfer $400 million from the taxpayers to the University of Missouri System. Unless the Governor or the Legislature acts at your request, some of that money will go to put you out of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell UMSL to Stop Teaching Industrial Sabotage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/25/tell-umsl-to-stop-teaching-industrial-sabotage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 01:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/25/tell-umsl-to-stop-teaching-industrial-sabotage/</guid>
      <description>[ ](https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/UofMCommie.png)Contact UofM President Steve Owens and demand an immediate end to the communist-led industrial sabotage courses that he’s shoving down your kids’ throats
That’s right, UMSL and UMKC are teaching kids how to destroy business in America. They want your job to go overseas. And the guy leading the class is a proud communist.
No employer in his right might would hire a graduate of the University of Missouri-St. Louis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTION:  Jefferson City February 26  *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/25/action-jefferson-city-february-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 03:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/25/action-jefferson-city-february-26/</guid>
      <description>Your country needs you today—Saturday, February 26—in Jefferson City, MO. Radical unions threatening a Wisconsin-style hatefest at the State Capitol. But some great Americans like Phil Todd and Elizabeth and Paul Couture have secured a permit for
Tea Party on the
Capitol Steps beginning at
10:30 a.m. Saturday, Feb. 26 Please pass the word. If you can’t be there at 10:30, come later. We’ll need people there ALL DAY.
RSVP Right Now</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>