<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hillary-Clinton on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/hillary-clinton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hillary-Clinton on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 20:46:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/hillary-clinton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: State Department releases Huma Abedin emails found on Weiner&#39;s hard drive</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/breaking-state-department-releases-huma-abedin-emails-found-on-weiners-hard-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 20:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/breaking-state-department-releases-huma-abedin-emails-found-on-weiners-hard-drive/</guid>
      <description>The US Department of State released 2,800 emails involving Hillary aid Huma Abedin that were found on Anthony Weiner&amp;rsquo;s hard drive last year, Judicial Watch reports. You can read all the emails here: FOIA Abedin Emails
In a statement, Judicial Watch, which forced the release through lawsuits, said this:
 This is a major victory. After years of hard work in federal court, Judicial Watch has forced the State Department to finally allow Americans to see these public documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graceless</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/14/graceless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 01:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/14/graceless/</guid>
      <description>Not often does a person or an event fit every definition of a single word. But Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s life after the election fits perfectly all three definitions of graceless.
__
Graceless.
Graceless Hillary.
Why didn&amp;rsquo;t Donald Trump think of that one during the campaign. &amp;ldquo;Graceless Hillary…&amp;rdquo;
Not a single rational being could challenge the accuracy of that monicker. Graceless Hillary.
Clumsy.
No sense of propriety or decency.
Inferior or clumsy in treatment or performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glad to See Trump Focusing on Working People Instead of Worrying About Hillary Clinton</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/23/glad-to-see-trump-focusing-on-working-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 15:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/23/glad-to-see-trump-focusing-on-working-people/</guid>
      <description>You might have heard that President-elect Trump has said he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to waste time and attention on Hillary&amp;rsquo;s email server. You also might have heard that some people are upset about that. I&amp;rsquo;m not one of them.
Months ago I was telling people Trump should announce that, if elected, he will pardon Hillary Clinton for all crimes related to her email scandal. I had two reasons for promoting this strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Looks Like I Was Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/01/breaking-looks-like-i-was-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 19:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/01/breaking-looks-like-i-was-right/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I speculated that Barack Obama had grown sick of Hillary&amp;rsquo;s corruption, lies, and criminal disregard for the rule of law.
A lot of people thought I was nuts, that I was reading too much into the White House statement that discredited Hillary&amp;rsquo;s primary talking point about James Comey.
But today the Gateway Pundit reports that Michelle Obama has scrubbed all references** to Hillary Clinton from both of her Twitter timelines**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killing Ron Brown: A Clinton Crime Family Story</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/02/killing-ron-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 16:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/02/killing-ron-brown/</guid>
      <description>Your life is in danger. At this moment, a Chinese nuclear warhead sits in a missile silo. Its guidance, if launched, instructs the warhead to detonate a mile or two above your home. And this was all made possible by extortion, murder, and illegal campaign contributions to Bill and Hillary Clinton.
Remember Ron Brown? Brown was Clinton&amp;rsquo;s Secretary of Commerce.
Ron Brown ran the Clintons&amp;rsquo; extortion racket in the 1990s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>