<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hillary-Clinton on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/hillary-clinton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hillary-Clinton on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 20:46:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/hillary-clinton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: State Department releases Huma Abedin emails found on Weiner&#39;s hard drive</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/breaking-state-department-releases-huma-abedin-emails-found-on-weiners-hard-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 20:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/breaking-state-department-releases-huma-abedin-emails-found-on-weiners-hard-drive/</guid>
      <description>The US Department of State released 2,800 emails involving Hillary aid Huma Abedin that were found on Anthony Weiner&amp;rsquo;s hard drive last year, Judicial Watch reports. You can read all the emails here: FOIA Abedin Emails
In a statement, Judicial Watch, which forced the release through lawsuits, said this:
 This is a major victory. After years of hard work in federal court, Judicial Watch has forced the State Department to finally allow Americans to see these public documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graceless</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/14/graceless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 01:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/14/graceless/</guid>
      <description>Not often does a person or an event fit every definition of a single word. But Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s life after the election fits perfectly all three definitions of graceless.
__
Graceless.
Graceless Hillary.
Why didn&amp;rsquo;t Donald Trump think of that one during the campaign. &amp;ldquo;Graceless Hillary…&amp;rdquo;
Not a single rational being could challenge the accuracy of that monicker. Graceless Hillary.
Clumsy.
No sense of propriety or decency.
Inferior or clumsy in treatment or performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glad to See Trump Focusing on Working People Instead of Worrying About Hillary Clinton</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/23/glad-to-see-trump-focusing-on-working-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 15:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/23/glad-to-see-trump-focusing-on-working-people/</guid>
      <description>You might have heard that President-elect Trump has said he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to waste time and attention on Hillary&amp;rsquo;s email server. You also might have heard that some people are upset about that. I&amp;rsquo;m not one of them.
Months ago I was telling people Trump should announce that, if elected, he will pardon Hillary Clinton for all crimes related to her email scandal. I had two reasons for promoting this strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Looks Like I Was Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/01/breaking-looks-like-i-was-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 19:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/01/breaking-looks-like-i-was-right/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I speculated that Barack Obama had grown sick of Hillary&amp;rsquo;s corruption, lies, and criminal disregard for the rule of law.
A lot of people thought I was nuts, that I was reading too much into the White House statement that discredited Hillary&amp;rsquo;s primary talking point about James Comey.
But today the Gateway Pundit reports that Michelle Obama has scrubbed all references** to Hillary Clinton from both of her Twitter timelines**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killing Ron Brown: A Clinton Crime Family Story</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/02/killing-ron-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 16:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/02/killing-ron-brown/</guid>
      <description>Your life is in danger. At this moment, a Chinese nuclear warhead sits in a missile silo. Its guidance, if launched, instructs the warhead to detonate a mile or two above your home. And this was all made possible by extortion, murder, and illegal campaign contributions to Bill and Hillary Clinton.
Remember Ron Brown? Brown was Clinton&amp;rsquo;s Secretary of Commerce.
Ron Brown ran the Clintons&amp;rsquo; extortion racket in the 1990s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Jake Tapper Great Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/18/make-jake-tapper-great-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/18/make-jake-tapper-great-again/</guid>
      <description>I am making an honest man out of Jake Tapper. This twitter thread tells it all.
   @whennessy i never made an issue of Trump&amp;rsquo;s use of the word bomb. so the whole premise of this is nonsense.
 — Jake Tapper (@jaketapper) September 18, 2016
The controversy began when Hillary Clinton attacked Donald Trump for calling terrorist bombings in New Jersey and New York &amp;ldquo;bombs.&amp;rdquo; But in the same interview, Hillary called the bombings &amp;ldquo;bombing,&amp;rdquo; making her look like an idiot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only the &#39;64 Phillies Rival Hillary Clinton&#39;s Brutal September Collapse</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/16/only-the-64-phillies-rival-hillary-clintons-brutal-september-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 22:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/16/only-the-64-phillies-rival-hillary-clintons-brutal-september-collapse/</guid>
      <description>After the Phillies beat the Dodgers on September 20, they owned a 6.5-game lead over the Reds and Cardinals, who were tied for second place. Philadelphia then hosted Cincinnati for three games, and the visiting Reds won all three. Then the Phillies hosted Milwaukee for four, and the visiting Braves won all four. At the end of that series, the Reds were in first place, a game ahead of the Phillies and 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Takes While Donald Gives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/26/hillary-takes-while-donald-gives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 13:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/26/hillary-takes-while-donald-gives/</guid>
      <description>Contrasts.
Two Politico stories, just weeks apart, demonstrate the remarkable contrasts between the two candidates for president.
The headline of the Trump story tells it all:
 Trump raised $32 million with RNC, but kept only a fraction.
 And the Hillary story:
 Leaked emails show officials tried to obscure the fact that Clinton allowed states to keep only a tiny fraction of proceeds from joint fundraising.
 Trump is on Team America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama &amp; Hillary Have Lost Control of Cop Killer Rhetoric</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/17/cop-killer-hillary-has-lost-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/17/cop-killer-hillary-has-lost-control/</guid>
      <description>Hillary, Obama, and much of the Democrat Party have fomented race hatred for years. They&amp;rsquo;ve ratcheted up their lies in recent months, hoping to turn race hatred into votes. They are that cynical and self-serving.
Now, Hillary and Obama have lost control of the fire they started. Crazed, racist murderers all across the country have declared war on police officers. From Dallas, Texas, to Ballwin, Missouri, to Baton Rouge, Louisianna, Hillary has sent a message that says it&amp;rsquo;s okay to kill a cop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convict Hillary</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/10/convict-hillary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 15:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/10/convict-hillary/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people are mad at FBI Director James Comey. Comey read a list of crimes committed by Hillary Clinton, then announced he couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend prosecution for those crimes. On its face, it sounds like Comey caved.
Let&amp;rsquo;s play the imagine game. Imagine Comey decided to refer Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s crimes to the Department of Justice for prosecution. What would happen?
First, you&amp;rsquo;d never hear about it. The FBI and the DOJ don&amp;rsquo;t discuss active criminal investigations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Left the Gate Open and Laughed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/05/hillary-left-the-gate-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 23:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/05/hillary-left-the-gate-open/</guid>
      <description>Many people grew up with dogs and backyards. If you are such a person, you probably remember being to told to make sure the gate&amp;rsquo;s shut and locked. Or maybe you were told not to use the gate at all because the dog might get out.
A lot of people who grew up with dogs suffered emotional trauma when something bad happened to their dog. Imagine how you&amp;rsquo;d feel if you were seven or eight and you left the gate open and the dog got out and got hit by a car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hookers By The Dozens and Booze Galore--So Where Was BILL Clinton In All This? *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/hookers-by-the-dozens-and-booze-galore-so-where-was-bill-clinton-in-all-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 01:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/17/hookers-by-the-dozens-and-booze-galore-so-where-was-bill-clinton-in-all-this/</guid>
      <description>Let me get this straight. Secret Service Agents and some military guys brought more than 20 &amp;ndash; count &amp;lsquo;em, _twenty _&amp;ndash; hookers to a hotel in Cartagena, Columbia. The Americans were drinking&amp;ndash;a lot, according to hotel staff. When the girls were ready to leave, apparently, the Americans refused to pay.
I guess these soldier or sailors or Marines don&amp;rsquo;t watch enough movies. They&amp;rsquo;d know how hookers act when they don&amp;rsquo;t get paid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reason TV Destroys Hillary Clinton’s Tax Theories</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/reason-tv-destroys-hillary-clintons-tax-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 21:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/reason-tv-destroys-hillary-clintons-tax-theories/</guid>
      <description>Hillary Clinton opened her mouth this week—the same mouth that she insisted on opening during the campaign, resulting in our most corrupt and juvenile president ever.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wzg0dGrfP60&amp;amp;color1;=0xb1b1b1&amp;amp;color2;=0xd0d0d0&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;feature;=player_embedded&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Post-Palin Electoral College Map</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/06/the-post-palin-electoral-college-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 18:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/06/the-post-palin-electoral-college-map/</guid>
      <description>Sarah Palin will push 9 toss-up states into McCain&amp;rsquo;s camp (from left to right):
 * Nevada * Colorado * New Mexico * [Michigan](https://www.politico.com/news/stories/0908/13198.html) * New Hampshire * Indiana * Ohio * Virginia * [Florida](https://www.surveyusa.com/client/PollReportEmail.aspx?g=e3a24829-6f3f-4928-b30f-cb21804091f0)  This will give McCain the Electoral College victory in November, 300 to 238. The Palin-Effect works two different ways: Rough Rider Admiration and Strong Woman Identification. This estimate and projection is based on analysis of detailed polling data from Gallup and Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First They Come After Obama . . .</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/12/first-they-come-after-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 00:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/12/first-they-come-after-obama/</guid>
      <description>The incestuous relationship between the Democrat party and the MSM may be the Dem&amp;rsquo;s weakest link.
Big media are good two things: creating celebrities and destroying them. Think of Cindy Sheehan, Michael Jackson, Howard Dean. The evening news, the New York Times and Washington Post, the entertainment columns and television shows all contributed mightily to the rise and fall of these celebrities.
When Barack Obama threw into the presidential race, the media provided millions of dollars in free advertising.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>