<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John Roberts on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/john-roberts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in John Roberts on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 07:06:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/john-roberts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Am Skipping Independence Day This Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/04/im-skipping-independence-day-because-we-gave-our-independence-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/04/im-skipping-independence-day-because-we-gave-our-independence-back/</guid>
      <description>July 4th became my favorite holiday in 1981, replacing Christmas. Maybe it was a sign of my maturity.

It was also a sign of the times. After a ten-year hiatus, patriotism was chic again, thanks to Ronald Reagan. Here’s a few other things that made me fall in love with Independence Day:
 * Fireworks—who doesn’t love blowing stuff up? * Parties * VP Fair (tragically renamed to Fair St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Roberts Switched His Vote Under Outside Pressure</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/01/john-roberts-switched-his-vote-under-outside-pressure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 23:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/01/john-roberts-switched-his-vote-under-outside-pressure/</guid>
      <description>It won’t look like decay to many. John Roberts will be the toast of the political class for years to come. He’ll attend all the prettiest events with the prettiest people. Barbara Streisand will have him out to her massively carbon-releasing Hollywood mansion. The Washington Post intelligentsia will place his bust in its pantheon of The Evolved. He might even golf with Bill and Obama.

But beneath the black robe grows a dark stain on his soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court Votes on Obamacare Today</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/30/the-supreme-court-votes-on-obamacare-today/</guid>
      <description>We won’t know the result until late June, most likely. And the results of today’s vote could change by then.

Still, it’s sort of weird that after three years of public, wildly emotional and stupifyingly complex arguments, the fate of the republic comes down to a short meeting in Washington involving nine people in a paneled room.
Mark Sherman of AP describes the cloistered scene:
 After months of anticipation, thousands of pages of briefs and more than six hours of arguments, the justices will vote on the fate of President Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s health care overhaul in under an hour Friday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>