<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 07:36:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Secrets of Coronavirus Data Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:21:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>Nate Silver let the cat out of the bag.
In case you don&amp;rsquo;t recognize his name, Nate Silver is the data analyst who launched Five Thirty-Eight, orignally in the New York Times. He was famous for not predicting an election a few years ago.
Today, Nate unloaded on the media for just one aspect of their narrative-driven Coronavirus coverage. In short, noted the same thing Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View pointed out a month ago: positive tests is meaningless unless it&amp;rsquo;s indexed to the number of tests administered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Andrew Cuomo Intentionally Kill the Elderly of New York?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 11:50:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/did-cuomo-use-intentionally-kill-the-elderly/</guid>
      <description>It would be the most sinister murder plot in US history. Imagine a governor conspiring to thin the population of elderly people, using a pandemic as both cover and weapon.
As unimaginable as it would be, evidence is mounting New York Governor Andrew Cuomo did just that: culled the herd in nursing homes by weaponizing Coronavirus.
Dumped Off With Their Own Body Bags New York Governor Andrew Cuomo implemented an emergency declaration that required nursing homes to accept active Coronavirus patients regardless of their ability to care for or isolate the infected patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doomsday Doctors Make the Best Case for Opening the Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/doomsday-doctors-make-best-case-for-opening-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 12:12:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/doomsday-doctors-make-best-case-for-opening-economy/</guid>
      <description>A lot of doctors seem to derive much pleasure from convincing people that Coronavirus will kill us all very soon. Very soon. These are the Doomsday Doctors. And if they&amp;rsquo;re right, we need to eliminate all behavior restrictions immediately and enjoy our final days.
The latest tactic of the Doomsday Doctors is to report (non-peer reviewed) that the Coronavirus has mutated into a weapons-grade killer that no one can avoid or resist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shock Therapy: Scott Adams Scooped Me</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/shock-therapy-scott-adams-scooped-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 06:30:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/shock-therapy-scott-adams-scooped-me/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing &amp;ldquo;around&amp;rdquo; this topic for weeks, now. But I have to post this today, because Scott Adams scooped me. Tonight on his Coffee with Scott Adams Periscope he exposed the secret I&amp;rsquo;ve been leading up to. No reason to be subtle any longer. So, here we go.
Watch Scott Adams&amp;rsquo; rant. (Begins about 9:30 mark.)
There will be extra cussing tonight. Put the kids to bed. Close your windows and get under the covers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Was China All Along</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/it-was-china-all-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 06:05:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/it-was-china-all-along/</guid>
      <description>The leaked Five Eyes dossier on China&amp;rsquo;s nefarious Coronavirus pandemic provides all the pieces to figure out what happened and why. The dossier doesn&amp;rsquo;t connect the dots for you, but they&amp;rsquo;re now easy to connect. So easy, even I can do it. The story goes something like this.
 China was playing around with dangerous natural microbes in order to prove that it was as good as the USA at studying and neutralizing infectious diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>