<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>humility on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/humility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in humility on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 07:05:57 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/humility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s About the Destination, Not the Journey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/destination-not-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 07:05:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/destination-not-journey/</guid>
      <description>Jerry Garcia Was Wrong
Jerry Garcia of Grateful Dead was famous for saying &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s about the journey, not the destination.&amp;rdquo;
Garcia was wrong.
There are two possible destinations:
 Eternal perfection. Eternal misery.  It&amp;rsquo;s all about the destination. The destination is all that matters.
The journey matters only insofar as it determines the destination. If you know and pursue the right destination, the journey will be difficult, often painful, often lonely, often frustrating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret to a Better Life and Less Political Violence Is Here</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</guid>
      <description>If you read a lot of business and personal improvement blogs, you know they feed a lot of tips for living a better life. By &amp;ldquo;better&amp;rdquo; they mean making more money, getting a promotion, being more productive, whatever.
Are those things really what makes life better? If so, why do so many successful people burn out? John Belushi, River Phoenix, Amy Winehouse, Janice Joplin, Michael Jackson. Is it show business? Well, look what&amp;rsquo;s happening to Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unto Dust We Shall Return</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/22/unto-dust-we-shall-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/22/unto-dust-we-shall-return/</guid>
      <description>Today begins Lent.

Lent prepares us for the cycle of mortality and resurrection, perfected by Christ, without which life has no meaning. It’s a time of humility. We call to mind our human brokenness in hopes of making ourselves better imitators of Christ.
On Ash Wednesday, we mark ourselves with the sign of the cross in ashes. **“Remember, man, that you are dust and unto dust you shall return (Genesis 3:19).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas-2/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is the holiday about humility.
The humility of the immortal and all powerful and all knowing stooping to become a mere human being.
The humility of God and king to live among the humblest and poorest&amp;ndash;a carpenter&amp;rsquo;s son.
The humility of belonging to a race so broken that our Creator sent his only Son to redeem us.
For me, the humblest part of this season is what I&amp;rsquo;m doing right now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>