<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tcot on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tcot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tcot on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 01:07:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tcot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the America of Our Dreams</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/19/welcome-to-the-america-of-our-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 01:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/19/welcome-to-the-america-of-our-dreams/</guid>
      <description>Jim Durbin called me this evening. &amp;ldquo;Are you excited?&amp;rdquo; he asked.
Jim was in the crowd at the very first Tea Party in St. Louis, February 27, 2009. A cold Friday. He and more than a thousand other folks took off work and school to see what this protest was all about. Like so many others, Jim knew America needed a change. A big one. A change built on the hopes and dreams and fierce independence of ordinary people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Herbert Hoover Launched Cardinal Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals were the major league team farthest west and farthest south until the 1950s. But that’s not the only reason the Redbirds built a massive flock of fans from the Alleghenies to the Rockies, and from Canada to the Gulf of Mexico.
The St. Louis Cardinals owe big government statism and technological innovation a big thanks, in addition to geography and great teams. The technology was radio. The big government statist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Ed Martin Running for Attorney General in Missouri *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin Jr. of St. Louis has redirected his fire to the Attorney General race, and this is great news for everyone except Chris Koster.
Back when Ed Martin was talking about running for the Republican nod to take on Claire McCaskill, I had another thought. Well, a bunch of people had another thought: Ed would make an outstanding Attorney General.
UPDATE
HUGE list of endorsements on Ed’s official press release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: 2nd Federal Judge Rules HealthControl Unconstitutional—No One Surprised</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/31/breaking-2nd-federal-judge-rules-healthcontrol-unconstitutionalno-one-surprised/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/31/breaking-2nd-federal-judge-rules-healthcontrol-unconstitutionalno-one-surprised/</guid>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Roger Vinson today ruled Obamacare directly violates the Constitution by mandating that citizens buy health insurance.
This ruling goes further than the previous Virginia ruling. Judge Vinson declared the entire Obamacare bill unconstitutional because the individual mandate portion is not severable from the rest of the law.
Third, Judge Vinson granted the plaintiffs “declaratory relief,” the functional equivalent of an injunction, freeing them from the burden of compliance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video of St. Louis Event--Almost as Good as Being There *update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/video-of-st-louis-event-almost-as-good-as-being-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 23:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/video-of-st-louis-event-almost-as-good-as-being-there/</guid>
      <description>My hat&amp;rsquo;s off to Bob Anders and the crew from Creative Video Services for this 3-part series of the St. Louis Nationwide Chicago Tea Party protest held February 27, 2009. If you need videography, you can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with Creative Video.
Part I: https://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=3408578&amp;amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;amp;show_title=1&amp;amp;show_byline=1&amp;amp;show_portrait=0&amp;amp;color=&amp;amp;fullscreen=1 St. Louis Tea Party (Part 1) from CR8VDO on Vimeo.
Click here for Parts 2 and 3.
Dana has lots of great links. UPDATES
   It was a 3-part, not 4-part video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>