<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>History on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in History on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 22:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s A Great Way To Connect to America’s Founding: 1776</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/06/17/heres-a-great-way-to-connect-to-americas-founding-1776/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/06/17/heres-a-great-way-to-connect-to-americas-founding-1776/</guid>
      <description>Get into the spirit of ‘76 with a great live musical You probably didn’t know that I was a theatre guy in high school and college. In fact, I was a theatre major for a couple of years. I think the right’s neglect of the arts is one of our biggest failings. The arts reach people at an emotional level. Intellectual arguments cannot change emotional attachments.
So here’s a chance to rev up your American patriotic spirits while connecting with the arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe It’s the New Season of Mad Men</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/08/maybe-its-the-new-season-of-mad-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 07:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/08/maybe-its-the-new-season-of-mad-men/</guid>
      <description>This post is a bit unusual for me.
Strange and disturbing thoughts crowded my mind tonight—Sunday, March 7.
These thoughts interrupted my television viewing. I couldn’t really focus. Then, I couldn’t sleep. The thoughts won’t rest, and they won’t give me rest. So I write.
I’m bewildered by the world’s stock markets. Someone told the Wall Street Journal that, sure, the US economy seems to be tanking, manufacturing’s falling, the labor rate’s in the toilet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday, Jack Hennessy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/02/happy-birthday-jack-hennessy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/02/happy-birthday-jack-hennessy/</guid>
      <description>I don’t get into town to visit my dad often enough. That’s my loss.
Jack Hennessy, my dad, epitomizes what we call The Greatest Generation.
He helped raise his younger brothers and sister after their mother passed away. Jack was ten. His youngest sibling, my uncle Jim, was a newborn.
Jack Hennessy answered the call of World War II. He was a Machinist’s Mate in the Navy. He answered, again, when North Korea crossed the 34th Parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Herbert Hoover Launched Cardinal Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals were the major league team farthest west and farthest south until the 1950s. But that’s not the only reason the Redbirds built a massive flock of fans from the Alleghenies to the Rockies, and from Canada to the Gulf of Mexico.
The St. Louis Cardinals owe big government statism and technological innovation a big thanks, in addition to geography and great teams. The technology was radio. The big government statist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peering Into the Future from the Past</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/23/peering-into-the-future-from-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 05:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/23/peering-into-the-future-from-the-past/</guid>
      <description>Check this out:
 As far as the market drop and the comeback of the market, I&amp;rsquo;d just like to pass along the following information. I stand in the Ten-Year Treasury-Note pit in the Chicago Board of Trade. The name of the room I trade in is the Financial Room. We trade the commodities that represent most of our national debt. When the gov., sells debt, the buyers of that debt have to hedge somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Much for the Experts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/08/so-much-for-the-experts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 04:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/08/so-much-for-the-experts/</guid>
      <description>Rule by the cleverest brute dominated most of human history. Then came the bizarre notion – in Greece and Rome to degrees, but mostly in the USA – of rule by the governed.
Rule by the governed gave way in 20th century to rule by experts.
Many so called “conservatives” warned against the expert thing. Eventually, conservatives believed, the experts would either fall prey to the clever brutes or to a world too complex for a small group to manage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>