<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peter Kinder on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/peter-kinder/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Peter Kinder on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 17:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/peter-kinder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fascinating Results from Leaders Eat Last Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</guid>
      <description>This is the story of hard choices and how people resist making them.
Last week&amp;rsquo;s poll asked you to watch a video by Simon Sinek before answering two, simple, two-part questions: which Republican candidate for President and Missouri Governor is most likely and least likely to eat last?
I intended the poll to be hard. Not complicated, not long, but emotionally challenging.
Why the Poll Was Emotionally Challenging For several weeks, I have built a case for the importance of leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Grades</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/10/primary-grades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 01:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/10/primary-grades/</guid>
      <description>I was surprised to learn that Sarah Steelman conceded the GOP Senate race at 10:00. I&amp;rsquo;d talked to Todd Akin at my polling place on Tuesday morning, and he confirmed my suspicion the [Missouri](https://maps.google.com/maps?ll=38.5,-92.5&amp;amp;spn=3.0,3.0&amp;amp;q=38.5,-92.5 (Missouri)&amp;amp;t=h) Republican race for US Senate would be close. It really wasn&amp;rsquo;t.
Mr. Akin won handily, considering the 3-way race. John Brunner&amp;rsquo;s remarkably negative, nasty, angry campaign should have made the race much closer. It didn&amp;rsquo;t. Sarah Palin&amp;lsquo;s endorsement of Ms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Updates on University of Missouri Story</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/28/3-updates-on-university-of-missouri-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/28/3-updates-on-university-of-missouri-story/</guid>
      <description>Big news day in the advance of liberty in our battle against collectivists.
First, KMOX is reporting that an UMSL professor has resigned** over the controversy**. For the life of me, I cannot find who the professor is. I thought that everyone involved was either an instructor or a guest lecturer. If you know the answer to the riddle, please use the comment form.
Second, University of Kansas City refuses to accept responsibility for what goes on in its classroom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>