<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RNC Rules Committee on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/rnc-rules-committee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in RNC Rules Committee on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 11:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/rnc-rules-committee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s How the RNC Rules Committee Fiasco Really Went Down</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/25/heres-how-the-rnc-rules-committee-fiasco-really-went-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/25/heres-how-the-rnc-rules-committee-fiasco-really-went-down/</guid>
      <description>First, I understand that some Republicans who don’t regularly read my blog were confused (and unhappy) about my “Prostitutes in Business Suits” slogan for the Missouri Chamber of Commerce (and other business organizations that stop being conservatives when government money’s dangled before their eyes). Well, grow up, Republicans. (Have you ever listened to Rush Limbaugh?)
Now to the meat of the story.
On Friday, two people contacted me. Urgent stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Republican Party Seems Bent On Self-Destruction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/the-republican-party-seems-bent-on-destruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 13:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/the-republican-party-seems-bent-on-destruction/</guid>
      <description>Every election cycle millions of reliable Republican voters die and even more millions of Democrat voters get the vote. Messaging and pandering won’t fix the problem. Reforming the party might.
Libertarian reforms offer the best hope, because all the other conservative factions – evangelicals, Second Amendment, home schoolers, fiscal &amp;ndash; have hit their high-water marks. We saw that in 2012. Liberty, however, sells with the kids. Or it might, if Republicans would try it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>