<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hillary_clinton on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/hillary_clinton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hillary_clinton on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2007 04:38:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/hillary_clinton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinton on Iraq:  Victory is Not an Option</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/21/clinton-on-iraq-victory-is-not-an-option/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2007 04:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/21/clinton-on-iraq-victory-is-not-an-option/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis, MO&amp;ndash;Campaiging in Mooseknuckles, MO, today, Democrat Hillary Clinton gave supporters her strongest argument to date for an immediate, unconditional pull-out from Iraq.
&amp;ldquo;You read the news,&amp;rdquo; she shrilled to the largely silent crowd. &amp;ldquo;You read the reports the coming out of Iraq. You know what&amp;rsquo;s happened during George Bush&amp;rsquo;s war!&amp;rdquo;
The audience&amp;rsquo;s polite but blank silence indicated that they didn&amp;rsquo;t.
&amp;ldquo;You have seen Senator Durbin and several Brookings Institute scholars report from the field that the surge is pushing back the insurgents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presidential Campaign Roundup</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/presidential-campaign-roundup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2007 17:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/presidential-campaign-roundup/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re still 15 months away from the next general election. Remember that. Getting groceries and taking the kids to hockey practice are more important. Two World Series separate us from the election, not to mention a season and a half of football, more than a year of school. A child born today will be talking and walking before the election.
That said, Fred Thompson spoke to CNN yesterday, and his remarks make interesting reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YearlyKos Review</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/05/yearlykos-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2007 16:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/05/yearlykos-review/</guid>
      <description>The YearlyKos could be the last hurrah of this new hard left, the way Woodstock was the final note of the song of the Sixties.
YearlyKos is a get-together of hard left bloggers organized by DailyKos founder Markos Moulitsas. DailyKos claimed, perhaps rightly, responsibility for the Democrat Congressional victory in 2006&amp;ndash;much the way Hammas might claim victory for blowing up an Israeli schoolhouse.
The Kos and Democratic Underground people who filled attendee list are the kind of folks who giggle at Dick Cheney&amp;rsquo;s heart problems, wish al Qaeda victory in its war against the West, and popped bottles of bubbly upon hearing of Chief Justice Roberts&amp;rsquo; seizure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Weird Chess Game</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/02/obamas-weird-chess-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2007 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/02/obamas-weird-chess-game/</guid>
      <description>Democrat candidate for president Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s bizarre chess game with foreign policy took another twist today.
In remarks to a report, Obama seemed to formulate his nuclear policy as he went along:
 &amp;ldquo;I think it would be a profound mistake for us to use nuclear weapons in any circumstance,&amp;rdquo; Obama said, with a pause, &amp;ldquo;involving civilians.&amp;rdquo; Then he quickly added, &amp;ldquo;Let me scratch that. There&amp;rsquo;s been no discussion of nuclear weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MichelleMalkin.com Called &#34;Hate Site&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/michellemalkincom-called-hate-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2007 01:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/michellemalkincom-called-hate-site/</guid>
      <description>Michelle Malkin responds to that unnecessary race of humans known as liberals. The liberals, it seems, have gone about calling her web site, michellemalkin.com, a &amp;ldquo;hate-site.&amp;rdquo;
Other bloggers are jumping in to defend Michelle. I won&amp;rsquo;t. I think she has one of the best blogs in the business, but she doesn&amp;rsquo;t need my defense.
First, liberals are evil little creatures&amp;ndash;more little than evil, in the small, petty sense. Their self-righteous slander is not really meant to hurt its target as to aggrandize the speaker or writer in his own small mind and among his own petty peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Hysterium</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/20/hillary-hysterium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2007 05:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/20/hillary-hysterium/</guid>
      <description>Senator Clinton asked the Pentagon to describe its plans to withdraw from Iraq. The Pentagon—specifically, undersecretary of defense, Eric Edelman—replied in the most appropriate manner imaginable:
 Premature and public discussion of the withdrawal of U.S. forces from Iraq reinforces enemy propaganda that the United States will abandon its allies in Iraq, much as we are perceived to have done in Vietnam, Lebanon and Somalia
 In response, Ms. Clinton displayed the kind of hysterium one associates with under-medicated paranoid schizophrenics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>