<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crooked Hillary on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/crooked-hillary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crooked Hillary on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 22:14:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/crooked-hillary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Donna Brazile&#39;s Corrupt Silent Partner</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/31/donna-braziles-corrupt-silent-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 22:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/31/donna-braziles-corrupt-silent-partner/</guid>
      <description>Since its revelation in WikiLeaks two weeks ago, Donna Brazile has been justly excoriated for cheating on behalf of Hillary Clinton by passing along a debate question.
However, an important aspect to this story has been overlooked. As the saying goes, it takes two to tango. Yes, Donna Brazile sent a critically beneficial piece of information - but Hillary Clinton accepted it.
Mrs. Clinton accepted it (stealing), used it (cheating), and said nothing (lying).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have Voters Priced In Clinton&#39;s Criminality?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/31/have-voters-priced-in-clintons-criminality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 17:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/31/have-voters-priced-in-clintons-criminality/</guid>
      <description>You never expect a candidate&amp;rsquo;s surrogates to tell you their candidate is a crook. But that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what Hillary&amp;rsquo;s surrogates are telling you now.
From Bill Richardson to Robby Mook, Clinton surrogates are reciting a strange and disturbing talking point: Voters have &amp;ldquo;baked in&amp;rdquo; Clinton&amp;rsquo;s life of crime.
[FLASHBACK: I gave James Comey the benefit of the doubt in July]
The talking point seems meant to keep Democrats from panicking over the FBI&amp;rsquo;s re-opened criminal investigation of Hillary Clinton and the Clinton Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Administration Revives Watergate—In Living Color!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/30/obama-administration-revives-watergate-in-living-color/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 15:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/30/obama-administration-revives-watergate-in-living-color/</guid>
      <description>Everyone knows that the White House is interfering with the FBI&amp;rsquo;s investigation of Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s criminal conspiracies. We know this because the Justice Department is stonewalling the FBI&amp;rsquo;s request for a warrant to search the hard drive Huma Abedin shared with her ex-husband Anthony Weiner.
For those of us too young to remember those black-and-white days of Watergate, here&amp;rsquo;s a brief timeline via Watergate.info:
** July 13, 1973: Alexander Butterfield, former presidential appointments secretary, reveals in congressional testimony that since 1971 Nixon had recorded all conversations and telephone calls in his offices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: FBI Report Confirms Hillary&#39;s Guilty Mental Problems</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/02/fib-confirms-clinton-guild-mental-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 18:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/02/fib-confirms-clinton-guild-mental-problems/</guid>
      <description>The FBI dumped its Clinton criminal investigation report today, and it&amp;rsquo;s full of bombshells. Bombs are exploding like the 4th of July, especially the way Clinton lied about Gen. Colin Powell.
Clinton has maintained that Powell advised her to use a private email and cell phone instead of using secure systems provided by the US government.
Hillary lied.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the FBI found:
 Clinton contacted former Secretary of State Colin Powell via e-mail to inquire about his use of a BlackBerry while he was Secretary of State .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Takes While Donald Gives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/26/hillary-takes-while-donald-gives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 13:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/26/hillary-takes-while-donald-gives/</guid>
      <description>Contrasts.
Two Politico stories, just weeks apart, demonstrate the remarkable contrasts between the two candidates for president.
The headline of the Trump story tells it all:
 Trump raised $32 million with RNC, but kept only a fraction.
 And the Hillary story:
 Leaked emails show officials tried to obscure the fact that Clinton allowed states to keep only a tiny fraction of proceeds from joint fundraising.
 Trump is on Team America.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>