<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>William F. Buckley on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/william-f.-buckley/</link>
    <description>Recent content in William F. Buckley on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 10:55:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/william-f.-buckley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Wrong With The Franklin Project? – Part 3</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/22/whats-wrong-with-the-franklin-project-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 10:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/22/whats-wrong-with-the-franklin-project-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This is part three of a five-part series on national service. Part 1 introduced the controversy and corrected a major misconception. Part 2 looked at national service through the eyes of conservative giants, Milton Friedman, William F. Buckley, and Ronald Reagan.
So, what’s wrong with the Franklin Project? Plenty.
The Franklin Project promotes the idea of a renewed ethos of national service in America. It’s mission:
 The Franklin Project envisions a future in which a year of full-time national service—a service year—is a cultural expectation, a common opportunity, and a civic rite of passage for every young American.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fact and Fiction of the Franklin Project--Part 1</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/20/fact-and-fiction-of-the-franklin-project-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 10:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/20/fact-and-fiction-of-the-franklin-project-part-1/</guid>
      <description>You know how to tell when a political camp has nothing on an opponent?
It begins making stuff up.
That “making stuff up” has become the chief form of amusement among those who oppose Eric Greitens for Governor.
The current fiction they advance has to do with an organization called The Franklin Project. The fiction advanced by a few Facebook warriors goes something like this: “The Franklin Project wants mandatory national service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: Ronald Reagan Wants the Transportation Empowerment Act</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/13/ronald-reagan-wants-transportation-empowerment-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 13:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/13/ronald-reagan-wants-transportation-empowerment-act/</guid>
      <description>Want to fix Missouri&amp;rsquo;s roads and cut taxes at the same time? Well, two American conservative icons showed us the way almost 50 years ago.
The Establishment likes to attack grassroots conservatives by claiming Reagan would have opposed the Tea Party. They&amp;rsquo;re wrong, of course, and the Transportation Empowerment Act tells us why.
In 1967, shortly after Ronald Reagan became governor of California, William F. Buckley Jr. asked Governor Reagan if was even possible to be an effective governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Would Buckley Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/upon-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 09:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/08/upon-time/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to be William F. Buckley Jr. All I lacked was his intellect, education, and unique experiences.
Well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be him. I wanted to be the next one.
Every day, I wrote a 750-word piece. Poorly. I believed that practice would improve my writing.
It didn&amp;rsquo;t.
One day, I realized, as long as I tried to be the next William F. Buckley, I was destined for frustration and failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Tax Code: The Fustercluck From Which Everything Rancid Crawls</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/02/our-tax-code-the-fustercluck-from-which-everything-rancid-crawls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 01:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/02/our-tax-code-the-fustercluck-from-which-everything-rancid-crawls/</guid>
      <description>William F. Buckley proposed a simple tax reform in 1973. The language barrier that separates people like Buckley from that odd species we call Congress prevented his thoughts from finding fertile soil. And in the 40 years between, the tax code has become only murkier and more dangerous.

“Our tax laws were,” Buckley wrote in _Four Reforms: A Guide for the Seventies, “_designed historically to raise revenue for the operations of government.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>