<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>presidential debate on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/presidential-debate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in presidential debate on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 10:55:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/presidential-debate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Good Issued From the Candidate Debate?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/what-good-issued-from-the-candidate-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 10:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/08/what-good-issued-from-the-candidate-debate/</guid>
      <description>Did you hear about the ratings?
Over 24 million people watched the first Republican debate Thursday. That&amp;rsquo;s the largest audience ever for a cable program, save for sports.
Everybody knows why so many watched: people wanted to see a fight break out between Chris Christie and Rand Paul.
Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s presence probably didn&amp;rsquo;t hurt. Let me clarify that. Trump&amp;rsquo;s appearance helped rating. His performance might have ended his campaign.
Donald Trump comported himself with all the dignity and gravitas of a George W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will KMOX Drop Candy Crowley Or Lose Its Credibility?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/will-kmox-drop-candy-crowley-or-lose-its-credibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 04:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/will-kmox-drop-candy-crowley-or-lose-its-credibility/</guid>
      <description>CNN’s Candy Crowley talks politics during KMOX’s Total Information AM every Friday. KMOX Presents Crowley as a credible source of political information.
But Crowley’s credibility is gone.
On Tuesday, Crowley jumped into the Presidential Debate by claiming Barack Obama called the Benghazi attack “an act of terror” in the Rose Garden on September 12. In hockey, she’d have earned a game misconduct for being the third player into a fight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now We Know Why Mitt Romney Has Been Wildly Successful In Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 00:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama’s performance was not nearly as bad as Romney’s performance was good.

Not good—terrific.
I’m not talking about his politics and policies; I’m talking Romney’s remarkable presence. Here are the four principles of presence that Romney knocked out of the park.
Command of the Facts When it came to facts—and to how those facts matter to the listeners—Mitt Romney seemed more prepared for the office of President than the President.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>