<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>peggy noonan on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/peggy-noonan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in peggy noonan on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 14:43:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/peggy-noonan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Makes It Worse</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/06/03/obama-makes-it-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 14:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/06/03/obama-makes-it-worse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rdquo; could refer to anything. Anything at all.
In this case, though, I&amp;rsquo;m referring to unemployment. Well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;m referring to the economy overall.
Unemployment rate rises to 9.1%, 54K jobs added « Hot Air
Obama has increased regulation, seized entire industries (auto, student loans, commercial banking, medicine), and borrowed more money faster than all previous presidents combined.
Obama is a one-dictator disaster. And an incompetent one at that.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a job, Obama made it worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Good Candidates. Start Now.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/19/get-good-candidates-start-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/19/get-good-candidates-start-now/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives (tea party, et al) and Republicans better learn to get along. Quickly. Just as quickly, the two need to recruit, vet, and prep some A-list candidates. Candidates for offices from President down to school boards.
That’s because the winners in 2012 will either belong to a conservative coalition or the most radical elements of the Democrat Party. Here’s why.
Pollster Frank Luntz points out in today’s Washington Post that the largest ideological faction in the United States is the combination of GOP plus tea partiers:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Decay in the Age of Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/human-decay-in-the-age-of-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/human-decay-in-the-age-of-obama/</guid>
      <description>In 47BC, Julius Caesar assumed dictatorial power in Rome. He instituted “reforms” that transformed the Republic into the Empire. In the process, he became a dictator. Rome’s decent into oblivion began. In 44BC, seeing the damage Caesar’s tyranny and reforms, three men removed Caesar from power by the method of the day.
History moves faster now than it did 2,000 years ago. A megalomaniacal leaders bent on fundamentally transforming a nation can do remarkable damage in the blink of an eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/1-do-the-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 02:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/1-do-the-math/</guid>
      <description>Have you noticed few people call Barack Obama “The One” anymore? “The Golfer” or “The Vacationer” is more like it. Something less than One, by any measure.

Still, with each passing day and each new, permanent crisis, it seems like BO just ain’t up to the job of President. Nothing new. When Jimmy Carter’s incompetence became obvious, the lefty press developed a theory that the job had simply grown too complex for one man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We&#39;ve Made a Difference</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 18:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</guid>
      <description>When you give over most of your private time to a cause, you need some feedback. We got some from former Reagan speechwriter Peggy Noonan on Friday: The Summer of the Angry Mob
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;521&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Dana&amp;rsquo;s Famous &amp;lsquo;Meet the Mob&amp;rsquo; Blog&amp;rdquo;][/caption]
Ms. Noonan reflected on the Townhall Revolt which began in St. Louis one year ago. Writes Noonan:
 When Rep. Russ Carnahan held a town hall meeting at a community college in Missouri on July 20, he tried patiently to explain that ObamaCare not only would be deficit-neutral, it would save money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Failure of Leadership *UPDATES*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/total-failure-of-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 17:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/total-failure-of-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama’s incompetent, confused, and contradictory handling of the Gulf oil spill reveals a man unfit for any position of authority.
As Peggy Noonan pointed out in a painfully honest Wall Street Journal column on May 28, we know now that Barack Obama is an empty suit, a child playing grown-up.
 I wonder if the president knows what a disaster this is not only for him but for his political assumptions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>