<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nancy-pelosi on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/nancy-pelosi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nancy-pelosi on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 13:16:10 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/nancy-pelosi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Is a Styrofoam Bird</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/impeachment-and-styrofoam-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 13:16:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/impeachment-and-styrofoam-bird/</guid>
      <description>This post is about impeachment. But, first, you need to hear about a toy bird from the 1970s.
Disappointing Toys When I was seven or eight, I just had to have a Zorr: The Mighty Eagle.
Zorr could soar on the wind for hours, just like a real eagle. The TV commercials left me certain that Zorr would make the most popular kid on my block—maybe the whole parish. I&amp;rsquo;d have a pet eagle, really.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leftists Turn Against Nancy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/18/leftist-turn-against-nancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 23:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/18/leftist-turn-against-nancy/</guid>
      <description>Nancy Pelosi is paying a price for statesmanship.
Remember when this blog wrote about liberals saving us from Antifa?
 But one group can save us from the Antifa caliphate. An unlikely group. A group you’d never believe could be the heroes of this terrifying story.
 Who’s this group? Who will save America? Who will preserve Western Civilization? Christendom? Judaism?
Not the Right.
Not the Center.
Not the Great “Undecided” Voter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Left&#39;s Gamble Lost</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/11/04/lefts-gamble-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 23:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/11/04/lefts-gamble-lost/</guid>
      <description>From 2004 through about September 12, the American and European left bet the farm on terrorists.
Here&amp;rsquo;s Dick Durbin, the anti-American from Illinois, in September:
 In a speech Friday at the Center for National Policy, Sen. Dick Durbin, D-Ill., said, &amp;ldquo;President Bush is preparing to tell the nation, once again, that his strategy in Iraq is succeeding. We know what the Bush-Petraeus report will say: The surge is working. Be patient.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>