<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>buycott on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/buycott/</link>
    <description>Recent content in buycott on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 22:35:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/buycott/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Ideas to Save Christmas in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Nixon buck-passed while Ferguson burned. With the city’s main business district laid to rubble, buycotts won’t have much effect. And Christmas is around the corner.
Who got hurt last night?
*1. People who own businesses *2. People who work at businesses *3. People who rely on businesses
Time is short. The people affected by last night’s riots need help rebuilding and jobs right now. While I don’t have complete plans, I can throw out eight ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where I&#39;m Kicking Off My Ferguson BUYcott Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/29/im-kicking-ferguson-buycott-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 23:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/29/im-kicking-ferguson-buycott-saturday/</guid>
      <description>At 1:00 PM, I&amp;rsquo;ll be at 911 Beauty Salon: 9193 W Florissant Ave, St Louis, MO 63136, Cross Streets: Between Ferguson Ave and Canfield Dr. Let us knowyour story here. Upload photos, reciepts, and stories. People love stories.
You are welcome to join me there at 1:00, or shop and dine on your own.

This Ferguson BUYcott is getting massive national attention. Big thanks to everyone who took part last week and who&amp;rsquo;s joining in this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why St. Louis Tea Party Went to Ferguson To Shop</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/why-st-louis-tea-party-went-to-ferguson-to-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 04:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/why-st-louis-tea-party-went-to-ferguson-to-shop/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;rsquo;t change the world in your living room.
That&amp;rsquo;s why a small band of (mostly) white people from (mostly) West County drove to Ferguson (and Dellwood) to shop tonight.
We targeted the small businesses that were hit hard by violence&amp;ndash;violence committed (mostly) by out of town agitators, criminals, vandals, and hooligans.
We drove to Ferguson to make two statements with our actons: 1) Ferguson is OUR community, and 2) Ferguson is open for business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferguson Shopping Ideas</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/ferguson-shopping-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/21/ferguson-shopping-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Here are some businesses people should frequent:
Eat at Sweetie Pies on W. Florrisant, or head to Paul’s Market on Elizabeth, Drive down N./S. Florrisant for Shop-n-Save, Chinese Food, local eats, bakeries, dollar tree, etc. Ferguson also extends to New Halls Ferry and 270, where there is a Home Depot, another Shop-n-Save, Party store, UPS store, and more. https://livewellferguson.com/main/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/FergusonMap5-1.jpg
Also, there is Ferguson Bike shop, The Whistle Stop, and Sportsprint (where you might find an I heart Ferguson shirt).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are there any courageous business executives alive today?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/09/are-there-any-courageous-business-executives-alive-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/09/are-there-any-courageous-business-executives-alive-today/</guid>
      <description>The most disappointing thing about leaving the military is that it usually means leaving the last bastion of leadership in America. If you open your own business or freelance, you probably don’t notice the cowardly bastards populating corner offices in most American enterprises. You’d puke, as Holden Caulfield might say.
John Mackey of Whole Foods had the courage to oppose socialized medicine AND to defend his position and his right to say it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>