<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rex sinquefield on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/rex-sinquefield/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rex sinquefield on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 13:32:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/rex-sinquefield/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rex the Libertarian Tyrant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-the-libertarian-tyrrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 13:32:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-the-libertarian-tyrrant/</guid>
      <description>I want to take over the world and leave everybody alone
 &amp;ndash;Libertarian Motto
Rex Sinquefield graduated from Bishop DuBourg High School and he&amp;rsquo;s supposedly something of a libertarian. That&amp;rsquo;s about all we have in common.
Rex left St. Louis and became a billionaire by inventing stock market indexing or something. I went the Navy and still thank God every day that I have roof over my head.
Rex is a brilliant chess strategist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elitists Want to Make St. Louis County More Like Failing City #DontMergeUs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-sinquefields-plan-to-strand-you-on-i-44-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 08:56:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-sinquefields-plan-to-strand-you-on-i-44-forever/</guid>
      <description>This blog post will probably destroy my property value.
Snowstorm Humanitarian Crisis on I-44 Last night, hundreds of people (maybe thousands) were trapped in their cars on I-44 eastbound near Eureka, Missouri for 7, 9, 12 hours. Some even longer. According to police scanners, a baby was born on the highway. It was a humanitarian crisis.
Now, St. Louis billionaire Rex Sinquefield wants to make every aspect of your St. Louis County life a humanitarian crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Police Department Is Crumbling, But You Can Vote to Save It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</guid>
      <description>You get the feeling that Rex Sinquefield holds a grudge against his home state, and he’s using some of his fortune to punish us.
Rex gave a quarter million dollars to Obama’s Lawyer, Chris Koster. But that wasn’t his first assault on us. Rex’s war against the St. Louis Police Department is older and far more bitter.
Rex wants to force the state to surrender the Board of Police Commissioners for St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>