<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Claire McCaskill on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/claire-mccaskill/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Claire McCaskill on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 03:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/claire-mccaskill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Tell a Lie</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/02/how-to-tell-a-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 03:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/02/how-to-tell-a-lie/</guid>
      <description>You had to laugh. Claire McCaskill jumped on Twitter to announce she&amp;rsquo;d never met the Russian ambassador to the US. Before that, she jumped on Twitter to brag about being so damned important and vital that the Russian ambassador sought her oracle-like guidance.
After people mocked and scorned her silly lie, Claire McCaskill made up more lies to cover the first lie. You know, like a liar.
Senator McCaskill believes Jeff Sessions should resign for not telling a lie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Are the Ex-Im Facts Ann Wagner and Claire McCaskill Don&#39;t Want You to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/10/heres-ex-im-facts-ann-wagner-claire-mccaskill-wont-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 23:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/10/heres-ex-im-facts-ann-wagner-claire-mccaskill-wont-tell/</guid>
      <description>Rep. Ann Wagner&amp;rsquo;s Heritage Action Score is a disappointing 59. It&amp;rsquo;s about to drop even lower.
Last week, the Republican from Missouri&amp;rsquo;s 2nd Congressional District came out strongly in support of cronyism by endorsing and vowing to fight for extending the Export-Import Bank.
From Wagner&amp;rsquo;s interview with National Public Radio:
 “There is some talk about a short-term reauthorization, perhaps six or seven months on Ex-Im,” she said. “I’d like it to be longer than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Karl Rove School of Sanctimony</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/03/the-karl-rove-school-of-sanctimony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 23:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/03/the-karl-rove-school-of-sanctimony/</guid>
      <description>When I read about Todd Akin&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate comments to Charles Jaco, my first thought was uncharitable. &amp;ldquo;I could just kill him.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I could kill him,&amp;rdquo; is an idiom. Its cousins include &amp;ldquo;wring his neck&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;poke his eyes out.&amp;rdquo; Idioms hyperbolize our emotional reaction to an event.
I was angry because Todd Akin gave the left a great talking point in the infamous interview. I like Todd Akin. I voted for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3:  Todd Akin Needs to Lead or Get Out of the Way</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] Todd Akin: member of the United States House of Representatives. (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
Part 3 of 3 | Read Part 1 | Read Part 2
Before we get too far down the Akin rally road, let&amp;rsquo;s get some solid advice to Mr. Akin.
His principles, his spine, his grassroots do no good if Missouri turns blue. He cannot advance his causes from his house in Wildwood. Failure to take the Senate makes Obamacare permanent, at least in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preserving the Republic Is Paramount in 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/20/preserving-the-republic-is-paramount-in-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/20/preserving-the-republic-is-paramount-in-2012/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I blogged about loyalty to people and loyalty to principles. Both are important. Loyalty to people is an honorable principle.
Sometimes, the ideal is paramount. In 2012, we simply must take the US Senate. We must put Claire McCaskill out of office. And we must send a strong conservative to the US House of Representatives from Missouri’s 2nd Congressional district.
Missouri’s 2nd Congressional District has been well served by Todd Akin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>