<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Claire McCaskill on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/claire-mccaskill/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Claire McCaskill on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 03:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/claire-mccaskill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Tell a Lie</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/02/how-to-tell-a-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 03:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/02/how-to-tell-a-lie/</guid>
      <description>You had to laugh. Claire McCaskill jumped on Twitter to announce she&amp;rsquo;d never met the Russian ambassador to the US. Before that, she jumped on Twitter to brag about being so damned important and vital that the Russian ambassador sought her oracle-like guidance.
After people mocked and scorned her silly lie, Claire McCaskill made up more lies to cover the first lie. You know, like a liar.
Senator McCaskill believes Jeff Sessions should resign for not telling a lie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Are the Ex-Im Facts Ann Wagner and Claire McCaskill Don&#39;t Want You to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/10/heres-ex-im-facts-ann-wagner-claire-mccaskill-wont-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 23:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/10/heres-ex-im-facts-ann-wagner-claire-mccaskill-wont-tell/</guid>
      <description>Rep. Ann Wagner&amp;rsquo;s Heritage Action Score is a disappointing 59. It&amp;rsquo;s about to drop even lower.
Last week, the Republican from Missouri&amp;rsquo;s 2nd Congressional District came out strongly in support of cronyism by endorsing and vowing to fight for extending the Export-Import Bank.
From Wagner&amp;rsquo;s interview with National Public Radio:
 “There is some talk about a short-term reauthorization, perhaps six or seven months on Ex-Im,” she said. “I’d like it to be longer than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Karl Rove School of Sanctimony</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/03/the-karl-rove-school-of-sanctimony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 23:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/03/the-karl-rove-school-of-sanctimony/</guid>
      <description>When I read about Todd Akin&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate comments to Charles Jaco, my first thought was uncharitable. &amp;ldquo;I could just kill him.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I could kill him,&amp;rdquo; is an idiom. Its cousins include &amp;ldquo;wring his neck&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;poke his eyes out.&amp;rdquo; Idioms hyperbolize our emotional reaction to an event.
I was angry because Todd Akin gave the left a great talking point in the infamous interview. I like Todd Akin. I voted for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3:  Todd Akin Needs to Lead or Get Out of the Way</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] Todd Akin: member of the United States House of Representatives. (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
Part 3 of 3 | Read Part 1 | Read Part 2
Before we get too far down the Akin rally road, let&amp;rsquo;s get some solid advice to Mr. Akin.
His principles, his spine, his grassroots do no good if Missouri turns blue. He cannot advance his causes from his house in Wildwood. Failure to take the Senate makes Obamacare permanent, at least in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preserving the Republic Is Paramount in 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/20/preserving-the-republic-is-paramount-in-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/20/preserving-the-republic-is-paramount-in-2012/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I blogged about loyalty to people and loyalty to principles. Both are important. Loyalty to people is an honorable principle.
Sometimes, the ideal is paramount. In 2012, we simply must take the US Senate. We must put Claire McCaskill out of office. And we must send a strong conservative to the US House of Representatives from Missouri’s 2nd Congressional district.
Missouri’s 2nd Congressional District has been well served by Todd Akin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCaskillPAC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/25/mccaskillpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 03:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/25/mccaskillpac/</guid>
      <description>What I find so funny about Claire McCaskill&amp;rsquo;s war on super pacs is that her husband is a super PAC.
For the record, I have formally endorsed Senator McCaskill in her race to return to private life.
Zimmerman Update Having declared George Zimmerman guilty of first degree, racially motivated murder, the MSM are now investigating the case.
What they&amp;rsquo;re finding:
 The George Zimmerman that Francescani describes is quite different from the &amp;ldquo;delusional racist vigilante&amp;rdquo; that many have made him out to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Taxes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/24/a-tale-of-two-taxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/24/a-tale-of-two-taxes/</guid>
      <description>On Monday, we learned that US Senator Claire McCaskill failed to pay property taxes on her personal luxury jet for three years. Previously, she had charged taxpayers some of the cost of operating her private plane. Before that, it seems, she registered the plane in property tax-free Delaware.
On Monday, Claire wrote a $287,000 check without batting an eye. Now, St. Louis County says she owes them another $33,000 in interest and penalties, for a total bill of $320,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pujols or Politics?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/06/pujols-or-politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 18:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/06/pujols-or-politics/</guid>
      <description>I’m torn.
  Yesterday, I took part in a demonstration outside Senator Claire McCaskill’s St. Louis office on Delmar. The future of the republic is important. We are concerned that Senator McCaskill put her re-election before Missouri jobs by lobbying the DNC to hold its 2012 convention in Charlotte, NC, instead of St. Louis, MO.
Down the road, a group of Cardinals fans held a demonstration outside Busch Stadium. The future of future Hall of Famer Albert Pujols is important, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Orwell Write This Weekend?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/did-orwell-write-this-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/did-orwell-write-this-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Democrats—from Jane Fonda to Senator Bob Brady of Pennsylvania—are pushing to ban words, phrases, and images they don’t like, as P/Od Patriot points out.
Yes, we are living in very dangerous times. And the danger comes almost exclusively from the left.
* Democrat [McCaskill calls for Americans to take up arms](https://gatewaypundit.rightnetwork.com/2010/12/claire-mccaskill-promotes-violence-if-dems-dont-get-their-historic-tax-hikes-it-really-is-time-for-americans-to-take-up-pitchforks-video/) if Democrat tax increase fails. (It did. And Gabrielle Giffords helped it fail.)** Democrat [Joe Biden threatened to strangle Republicans](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A National Day of Shame</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/a-national-day-of-shame/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/a-national-day-of-shame/</guid>
      <description>It’s bad enough that five people died, including a wonderful nine-year-old girl.
It’s bad enough that a dozen or more people were shot.
It’s bad enough that a deranged man attacked our American system.
But America’s liberal elite turned the tragedy into a national day of shame. They accomplished this by callously and capriciously blaming innocent political opponents for the violence. When confronted with facts to the contrary, liberals, including Paul Krugman, CBS News, the New York Times, CNN, MSNBC, Jane Fonda, Sheriff Dupnick of Pima County Arizona, and others, continued to lie, slander, and libel the tea party, Rush Limbaugh, Sarah Palin, Glenn Beck, and conservatives in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We&#39;ve Made a Difference</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 18:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</guid>
      <description>When you give over most of your private time to a cause, you need some feedback. We got some from former Reagan speechwriter Peggy Noonan on Friday: The Summer of the Angry Mob
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;521&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Dana&amp;rsquo;s Famous &amp;lsquo;Meet the Mob&amp;rsquo; Blog&amp;rdquo;][/caption]
Ms. Noonan reflected on the Townhall Revolt which began in St. Louis one year ago. Writes Noonan:
 When Rep. Russ Carnahan held a town hall meeting at a community college in Missouri on July 20, he tried patiently to explain that ObamaCare not only would be deficit-neutral, it would save money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junk Bond</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 01:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond-2/</guid>
      <description>John is a Vietnam veteran and retired business executive. He loves America and hates to see what’s happened in Washington the past few years. He believes in liberty and Constitutional limitations on government growth.
He called the Tea Party just to vent and to see if it’s just him.
Recently, John had called Senator Kit Bond’s (R-MO) office in Washington. He wanted to know whether stories that Bond had signed off a $659 million earmark for soy bean farmers were true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junk Bond</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 01:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond/</guid>
      <description>John is a Vietnam veteran and retired business executive. He loves America and hates to see what’s happened in Washington the past few years. He believes in liberty and Constitutional limitations on government growth.
He called the Tea Party just to vent and to see if it’s just him.
Recently, John had called Senator Kit Bond’s (R-MO) office in Washington. He wanted to know whether stories that Bond had signed off a $659 million earmark for soy bean farmers were true.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>