<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stoicism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/stoicism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stoicism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 19:29:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/stoicism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea, Meet Stoicism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/chelsea-meet-stoicism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 19:29:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/chelsea-meet-stoicism/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s triumph in the 2016 election drove Chelsea Handler into a depraved descent. Weed and depression. Psychiatrists. Broken.
Not because of anything that happened to her. She didn&amp;rsquo;t lose her home. No one close to her died because of the election.
Chelsea Handler lost her mind because reality violated her expectations.
I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Ms. Handler doesn&amp;rsquo;t read Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View, but you do. So, for you, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how to avoid losing your mind when reality violates your expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do Stoics and Catholics Have in Common?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/11/01/what-do-stoics-and-catholics-have-in-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/11/01/what-do-stoics-and-catholics-have-in-common/</guid>
      <description>Lots, actually. But one Stoic practice that&amp;rsquo;s central to Christianity seems pertinent on All Hallow&amp;rsquo;s Eve: memento mori.
Remember your death. Remember, you will die. We all die. All the tech billionaires spending their fortunes trying to live forever will die. No matter how young and healthy you are, time is running through your hourglass. It will run out. And you probably won&amp;rsquo;t know when. For over a year I&amp;rsquo;ve carried a challenge coin that reminds me of my death:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Deal With Events</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/06/03/how-to-deal-with-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 16:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/06/03/how-to-deal-with-events/</guid>
      <description>Governor Eric Greitens resigned. Friend of the lobbyists, Mike Parson, became Missouri&amp;rsquo;s governor. In the words of someone who knows the new governor well, Mike Parson will &amp;ldquo;sell everything that isn&amp;rsquo;t nailed down.&amp;rdquo;
For those of us who believe in limited government that doesn&amp;rsquo;t put its thumb on the scale of achievement, it&amp;rsquo;s time to panic and despair, right?
Wrong. It&amp;rsquo;s never time to panic or despair. And we know this from two of the greatest philosophers of all time, Epictetus and Seneca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Character?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/what-is-character/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/what-is-character/</guid>
      <description>Worry about your character, not your reputation. Reputation is what people think of you. Character is who you are.
 —John Wooden, legendary coach of basketball and character
Everyone admits that President Trump cares more about his character than about his reputation. Only a man concerned with his character would tell the truth.
Reputation is what people think of you. Character is who you are.
The Stoics teach us that reputation is beyond our control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Was Good About Charlottesville</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/13/what-was-good-about-charlottesville/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 14:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/13/what-was-good-about-charlottesville/</guid>
      <description>Charlottesville used to be a place. Now, it&amp;rsquo;s a thing.
On Friday, Charlottesville was a city in Virginia.
Today, Charlottesville is an event. A thing.
In our hyper-emotional world of 2017, we are told to explore our emotions. Then act upon those emotions. Like poorly trained animals. Like half-wits. Like narcissists and spoiled brats. Like lower primates.
Like the KKK and BLM and Antifa thugs who turned that place into a thing yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>