<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>National Service on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/national-service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in National Service on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 01:11:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/national-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is The Difference Between Leadership and Service?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/16/what-is-the-difference-between-leadership-and-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 01:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/16/what-is-the-difference-between-leadership-and-service/</guid>
      <description>Marine Corps officers eat last.
That simple insight inspired the title of Simon Sinek&amp;rsquo;s latest book, &amp;ldquo;Leaders Eat Last.&amp;rdquo; If I could influence high school or college curricula, no one would graduate without successfully completing a semester course on that principle.
Below is another remarkable video of Simon Sinek discussing how circumstances can override our desire to lead and serve and how leadership and service can fix almost any problem. But first, I&amp;rsquo;d like you think a bit more about these two critical needs: leadership and service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Have a New Son, America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/15/you-have-a-new-son-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/15/you-have-a-new-son-america/</guid>
      <description>My son Patrick (closest to the camera at a civilian’s idea of parade rest) listens to the instructions of the enlisting officer among 9 young men and women preparing to swear an oath to the Constitution of the United States. They were here to make their first commitment to the armed forces.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_16700&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;711&amp;rdquo;]Patrick Hennessy takes the oath of enlistment at the Federal Building in St. Louis August 14, 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poll: What Do You Think About Service?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/26/poll-what-do-you-think-about-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/26/poll-what-do-you-think-about-service/</guid>
      <description>Last week, we posted a 5-part series on national service. This week, we&amp;rsquo;d like to see what you think.
Be heard
The poll closes Saturday, August 1 at Midnight. Please vote only once.
Last Week&amp;rsquo;s Poll: Trump Here&amp;rsquo;s my analysis of last week&amp;rsquo;s poll on Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free eBook of National Service Posts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/free-ebook-of-national-service-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 23:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/free-ebook-of-national-service-posts/</guid>
      <description>My series on National Service is important. Maybe not urgent, but important. (See Eisenhower Square.) So I turned it into an eBook:

DOWNLOAD FREE E-BOOK
Be warned: I did not edit the posts, so the ebook contains all the links to previous posts in the series. If there&amp;rsquo;s interest, I&amp;rsquo;ll go back and clean it up. This is just for convenience.
Thanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Conservative Missouri Service Program--Part 5</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/a-conservative-missouri-service-program-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 10:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/a-conservative-missouri-service-program-part-5/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve reached the end.
On Monday, we corrected disinformation about The Franklin Project.
Next, we looked at the historical conservative framework for national service.
Wednesday was a dissection of The Franklin Project&amp;rsquo;s Plan of Action (as distinguished from the group&amp;rsquo;s vision.)
Yesterday, we examined the consequences of ignoring the call for national service.
Today, we offer an oversimplified proposal for Missouri&amp;rsquo;s version of a national-service program. While inadequate, it is a start.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>