<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mitt Romney on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mitt-romney/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mitt Romney on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mitt-romney/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Character?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/what-is-character/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/what-is-character/</guid>
      <description>Worry about your character, not your reputation. Reputation is what people think of you. Character is who you are.
 —John Wooden, legendary coach of basketball and character
Everyone admits that President Trump cares more about his character than about his reputation. Only a man concerned with his character would tell the truth.
Reputation is what people think of you. Character is who you are.
The Stoics teach us that reputation is beyond our control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is The Infographic That The Whole Republican Party Is Freaking Out About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</guid>
      <description>The 3 million McCain voters who didn’t vote for Romney?
They’re dead.

[Click image to view full size. Please forward, download, and print. This is important.]
To survive, the GOP needs to stop being afraid of Millennials and tell them truth: they can move out of mom and dad’s house, they can drop out of school, they can quit their dead-end job with the idiot supervisor. But they can’t get away from government and debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Lloyd Smith and Jo Ann Emerson Plan This All Along?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</guid>
      <description>In an open Republican primary in Missouri’s 8th Congressional District, a solid conservative would beat an establishment &amp;ldquo;my turn&amp;rdquo; Republican, hands down. And the Missouri GOP would hate it.
That’s why I smell a rat. Would you be surprised to learn that Jo Ann Emerson and Lloyd Smith had this switcheroo planned months ago? You have to admit that the timing is suspicious:
 * Emerson wins a certain re-election * Smith announces he&#39;s stepping down as Missouri GOP Executive Director * Emerson announces she&#39;s resigning to become Queen of Lobbyists * Missouri&#39;s GOP Establishment breaks hips to tell reporters &amp;quot;Lloyd Smith&#39;s our man!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop The Crazy Talk: Vote Fraud Didn’t Cost Romney The Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</guid>
      <description>I wrote yesterday that if you need someone to blame, blame me. Don’t blame bogeymen.

Yes, vote fraud is real. Voter rolls in most states need to be cleaned up. Voter intimidation should be harshly prosecuted.
You can sign up at True the Vote or Missouri Precinct Project to take effective, useful action. These organizations do vital work, and they both need more volunteers.
Using vote fraud, however, as an excuse for secession or for blocking the Electoral College vote is neither effective nor useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Expect Boehner To Play The Black Knight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</guid>
      <description>The GOP didn’t really have a plan in place in case it lost. It certainly didn’t have a plan for getting snotclobbered. And if you try to spin Tuesday’s results as anything less than a good old-fashioned ass-kicking, you’re deluding yourself.

**Republicans Got Creamed ** I know Michelle Malkin found 20 things that went right on election night, but there about 60 million things that went wrong. Let’s take a look:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s My Electoral Map Prediction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I’m feeling a wave toward Romney.

My gut tells me this year is a lot like 1980.
1980 Was A Dead Heat
The final Gallup poll that year had a dead heat. Time Magazine’s November 3, 1980, called the race a dead heat. So did Newsweek.
The press was hoping John B. Anderson, a former Republican Congressman running for president as an independent, would siphon votes from Reagan. He did siphon votes from Reagan, but not nearly enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Shuts Down Another Small Business</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 01:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</guid>
      <description>200,000 That&amp;rsquo;s the number of** small businesses lost during the Obama Administration**.
If re-elected, Obama promises to accelerate the policies that destroyed American jobs, investments, and companies.
https://youtu.be/NlFHrLeeJIU
Voting isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. We need your help at 9966 Lin Ferry Drive, St. Louis, MO 63123.
Pick you day to work the phones and get out the vote:
 * Friday, November 2 Noon to 8 p.m. * Saturday, November 3 Noon to 5 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now We Know Why Mitt Romney Has Been Wildly Successful In Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 00:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama’s performance was not nearly as bad as Romney’s performance was good.

Not good—terrific.
I’m not talking about his politics and policies; I’m talking Romney’s remarkable presence. Here are the four principles of presence that Romney knocked out of the park.
Command of the Facts When it came to facts—and to how those facts matter to the listeners—Mitt Romney seemed more prepared for the office of President than the President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Sums Up Everything I Believe Better Than I Ever Could</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/14/this-sums-up-everything-i-believe-better-than-i-ever-could/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 06:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/14/this-sums-up-everything-i-believe-better-than-i-ever-could/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;463&amp;rdquo;] Buckley (right) and L. Brent Bozell Jr. promote their book McCarthy and His Enemies, 1954 (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
The Liberal Kirsten Powers (my favorite liberal at times) described the leftist media&amp;rsquo;s mania as &amp;ldquo;absolutely, utterly insane.&amp;rdquo;
What triggered the maniacal insanity from MSNBC and The New York Times (among others) was Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s public dismay over the way Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s State Department responded to terror attacks on US embassies in Egypt and Libya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the Romney Campaign Serious About Winning?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/11/is-the-romney-campaign-serious-about-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 10:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/11/is-the-romney-campaign-serious-about-winning/</guid>
      <description>The Romney Campaign today reminded me of the McCain Campaign of 2008.
I&amp;rsquo;m pretty good at ignoring bogus, fraudulent polls like the one CNN released tonight. In that poll, CNN announced a massive 52-46 national lead for Obama. If true, the race would be all but over.
CNN, of course, cooked the books on this one.
About one-third of voters describe themselves as independents, CNN sampled only 3% independents for its latest poll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Warning Signs That Obama’s Imploding</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/02/7-warning-signs-that-obamas-imploding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 21:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/02/7-warning-signs-that-obamas-imploding/</guid>
      <description>Hurricane Isaac smiled on the Republicans in Tampa and delivered more misery to New Orleans and its surroundings. That was just one of the ominous signs that 2012 is shaping up to be a forgettable year for Democrats, especially for Barack Obama.

Here’s seven more warning signs that Obama’s 6-year campaign is about to implode:
1. Torrential Rains Wipe the Face of Mount Obamamore
Not that weather plays favorites, but you have wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If We Don’t Flip Some Toss-Up States, Romney, Ryan, and the USA Are Screwed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</guid>
      <description>Choosing Paul Ryan as his running mate was a great Romney move. Looking ahead, Romney sees movement conservatives working hard right up to the election—even if he or his advisors continues to say stupid things. That was necessary.
SCROLL DOWN FOR TWO IMPORTANT EVENTS THIS WEEK
But it wasn’t enough to win the election and unseat America’s first anti-American president. To do that, we must find a way to win over the selfish middle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romney-Ryan Have a Vision They Can Talk About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/11/obamas-surrounded-by-really-nasty-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 02:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/11/obamas-surrounded-by-really-nasty-people/</guid>
      <description>Why did murder skyrocket in Chicago as soon as Rahm Emanuel became mayor? Why have Americans become nastier and meaner since Barack Obama became president?

As Michael Dukakis told us, a fish rots from the head down. Obama surrounds himself with people who thrive on decay and death.
After four years, Obama has nothing to say for himself. Nothing. He can only cut and attack and lie and sneer and mock like a high school bully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If the election were held today, there’d be a lot of crying and gnashing of teeth</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/17/gnashing-of-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/17/gnashing-of-teeth/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a screen grab from RealClearPolitics.com’s presidential tracking poll:

RCP aggregates dozens of polls to produce its RCP average. The method has been remarkably accurate, especially at the state level.
It’s time to focus on preventing the unmitigated disaster of a second Obama term.
In 112 days, Americans will vote on whether or not to continue our experiment in self-government. If the election were held today, that experiment would be aborted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney Shut Down a Company Over a Young Woman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/24/mitt-romney-shut-down-a-company-over-a-young-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/24/mitt-romney-shut-down-a-company-over-a-young-woman/</guid>
      <description>There are many stories about Mitt Romney’s evil-doings when he ran Bain Capital, a $1 billion company famous for buying troubled companies and making money off them.

Some of the stories involve Bain laying off workers to make companies profitable, then selling them off.
Some of the stories involve Bain and Romney chopping companies to bits and selling off the parts.
This story is about Romney shutting down a thriving business over a woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santorum Surging Because People Like Him</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/santorum-surging-because-people-like-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 01:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/santorum-surging-because-people-like-him/</guid>
      <description>The latest Public Policy Poll shows Santorum surging—big time.

**Santorum is most appealing to conservatives—from Evangelicals to Tea Partiers: **
 Santorum is now completely dominating with several key segments of the electorate, especially the most right leaning parts of the party. With those describing themselves as &amp;lsquo;very conservative,&amp;rsquo; he&amp;rsquo;s now winning a majority of voters at 53% to 20% for Gingrich and 15% for Romney. Santorum gets a majority with Tea Party voters as well at 51% to 24% for Gingrich and 12% for Romney.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relate to This, Mitt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/relate-to-this-mitt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/relate-to-this-mitt-2/</guid>
      <description>The liberal press cannot issue a story about the Republican presidential race that does not refer to Mitt Romney’s need (and inability) to “relate to” conservatives. Puke.
Relate to this: if Mitt Romney’s a conservative, I’m a Hottentot.

By “relate to,” the media and Romney’s handlers actually mean “hoodwink.” While Romney might secure the GOP nomination without conservative support, his campaign will go down in flames without conservative grassroots boots on the ground from Labor Day to Election Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bain of Newt’s Existence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/17/the-bain-of-newts-existence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/17/the-bain-of-newts-existence/</guid>
      <description>Truth is, not all companies, not all business ideas, can make it on their own.
It’s easy to say that a good idea will automatically lead to a successful business. But it’s a lie.
Apple did not become Apple without investors. Sure, there are some examples of businesses that flourished without financial help. But not many. We’ll never know the wonderful ideas that died in their owner’s garage for lack of financing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where’s Bob Dole?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/20/wheres-bob-dole/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/20/wheres-bob-dole/</guid>
      <description>The middle of the road is fine until you have to get somewhere.
I voted for Bob Dole in 1996. Yet his nomination drove me away from political activism for years.

I got out of the Navy in the fall of 1994. I watched the GOP reclaim the House with my nephew, Scott. I expected the Republicans to nominate a solid conservative who deliver a knock-out blow to the Clinton era two years later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Moves for Herman Cain Supporters Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</guid>
      <description>Herman Cain is riding a wave of popularity because of his upset win in the Florida straw poll on Saturday. He’s helped by Rick Perry’s free-fall and Mitt Romney’s establishmentarianism. But Cain is a huge underdog.
That’s okay because **America loves an underdog. **
Here’s what must happen right now for Herman Cain to win:
1. Social Media avalanche. Get @THEHermanCain trending on Twitter, and keep it there for five consecutive days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>