<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mitt Romney on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mitt-romney/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mitt Romney on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mitt-romney/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Character?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/what-is-character/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/what-is-character/</guid>
      <description>Worry about your character, not your reputation. Reputation is what people think of you. Character is who you are.
 —John Wooden, legendary coach of basketball and character
Everyone admits that President Trump cares more about his character than about his reputation. Only a man concerned with his character would tell the truth.
Reputation is what people think of you. Character is who you are.
The Stoics teach us that reputation is beyond our control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is The Infographic That The Whole Republican Party Is Freaking Out About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</guid>
      <description>The 3 million McCain voters who didn’t vote for Romney?
They’re dead.

[Click image to view full size. Please forward, download, and print. This is important.]
To survive, the GOP needs to stop being afraid of Millennials and tell them truth: they can move out of mom and dad’s house, they can drop out of school, they can quit their dead-end job with the idiot supervisor. But they can’t get away from government and debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Lloyd Smith and Jo Ann Emerson Plan This All Along?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</guid>
      <description>In an open Republican primary in Missouri’s 8th Congressional District, a solid conservative would beat an establishment &amp;ldquo;my turn&amp;rdquo; Republican, hands down. And the Missouri GOP would hate it.
That’s why I smell a rat. Would you be surprised to learn that Jo Ann Emerson and Lloyd Smith had this switcheroo planned months ago? You have to admit that the timing is suspicious:
 * Emerson wins a certain re-election * Smith announces he&#39;s stepping down as Missouri GOP Executive Director * Emerson announces she&#39;s resigning to become Queen of Lobbyists * Missouri&#39;s GOP Establishment breaks hips to tell reporters &amp;quot;Lloyd Smith&#39;s our man!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop The Crazy Talk: Vote Fraud Didn’t Cost Romney The Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</guid>
      <description>I wrote yesterday that if you need someone to blame, blame me. Don’t blame bogeymen.

Yes, vote fraud is real. Voter rolls in most states need to be cleaned up. Voter intimidation should be harshly prosecuted.
You can sign up at True the Vote or Missouri Precinct Project to take effective, useful action. These organizations do vital work, and they both need more volunteers.
Using vote fraud, however, as an excuse for secession or for blocking the Electoral College vote is neither effective nor useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Expect Boehner To Play The Black Knight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/12/dont-expect-boehner-to-play-the-black-knight/</guid>
      <description>The GOP didn’t really have a plan in place in case it lost. It certainly didn’t have a plan for getting snotclobbered. And if you try to spin Tuesday’s results as anything less than a good old-fashioned ass-kicking, you’re deluding yourself.

**Republicans Got Creamed ** I know Michelle Malkin found 20 things that went right on election night, but there about 60 million things that went wrong. Let’s take a look:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>