<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Millennials on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/millennials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Millennials on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 22:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/millennials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri&#39;s 2016 Electorate Very Different from 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/21/missouris-2016-electorate-different-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/21/missouris-2016-electorate-different-2012/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to the number of potential voters, 2016 is shaping up to be a watershed year in Missouri politics.
Take at look at this chart of generational voters in 2008 and 2012:
(Source: Missouri Census Data Center)
Where Did the Millennials Come From? Leaving biology out of it, it&amp;rsquo;s simple: 2016 will be the first election in which the entire Millennial cohort is old enough to vote. Plus Millennial-aged immigrants have increased their numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Pissed That I’m Pissed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/im-pissed-that-im-pissed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/im-pissed-that-im-pissed/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of being angry?
Did you know that a lot of other people are tired of your anger?
Did you know that 70 percent of Americans don’t like politics?
Did you know that the 70 percent of Americans who don’t like politics won’t vote for anything an angry person tells them to vote for?
Go look it up. It’s totally true.
So many conservatives want another Reagan, but they want an angry, vengeful, belligerent Reagan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thad Cochran&#39;s Pyrrhic Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/06/thad-cochran-mortally-wound-gop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 21:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/06/thad-cochran-mortally-wound-gop/</guid>
      <description>A Pyrrhic victory is a victory with such a devastating cost that it is tantamount to defeat. Someone who wins a Pyrrhic victory has been victorious in some way; however, the heavy toll negates any sense of achievement or profit (another term for this would be &amp;ldquo;hollow victory&amp;rdquo;).
 — from Wikipedia
I keep some things in a little box in my bedroom. Some Navy and submarine mementos, some letters, favorite photos of the kids that mean things only to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is The Infographic That The Whole Republican Party Is Freaking Out About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</guid>
      <description>The 3 million McCain voters who didn’t vote for Romney?
They’re dead.

[Click image to view full size. Please forward, download, and print. This is important.]
To survive, the GOP needs to stop being afraid of Millennials and tell them truth: they can move out of mom and dad’s house, they can drop out of school, they can quit their dead-end job with the idiot supervisor. But they can’t get away from government and debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Conservatives: We Are Already Losing 2016</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/18/dear-conservatives-we-are-already-losing-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/18/dear-conservatives-we-are-already-losing-2016/</guid>
      <description>If you need to blame someone for our election losses, blame me.

I Let You Down I could have done more. I could have spoken up sooner. I could have been more honest with you about the mistakes we made and the opportunities we ignored. I could have worked harder on what I saw as the most important work we could do.
I let you down. I focused on petty issues of the day, too, instead of working on a different future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials About To Bite Obama’s Crap Sandwich . . . with Relish</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/05/millennials-about-to-bite-obamas-crap-sandwich-with-relish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/05/millennials-about-to-bite-obamas-crap-sandwich-with-relish/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the folks at Business Insider get fairly simple ideas ass backwards. Take their Winners and Losers story on the Supreme Court’s Obamacare decision. It’s dead wrong about Millennials (born after 1982):
 Young people can also count themselves winners in the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s decision to uphold the Affordable Care Act, which allows children to stay on their parents&amp;rsquo; insurance plan until their 26th birthday. Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/winners-losers-affordable-care-act-supreme-court-obamacare-ruling-2012-6?op=1#ixzz1zP2AiaCO
 [continued after image]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday (Infographic)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</guid>
      <description>The world&amp;rsquo;s economy&amp;ndash;including BRICs&amp;ndash;is collapsing. The problem is debt, and the youth will set us free. Even if that&amp;rsquo;s a very painful liberation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Never Guess Who&#39;s About to Become Obama&#39;s Biggest Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>In 2008, we heard all about the youth movement for Obama. We heard that the enormous Millennial Generation, born between 1982 and 2001, would destroy the GOP and everything America once stood for&amp;ndash;like jobs, family, faith, and hard work. And when Obama won, many believed the tales of the Obama Youth.
  
But many were wrong. Voters under 30 have had it with vague promises and glittering bullshit from that punk from Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Scrooge Teaches Millennials</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/28/what-scrooge-teaches-millennials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/28/what-scrooge-teaches-millennials/</guid>
      <description>_This is the fourth in a series. If you haven’t, please read part 1, part 2, and part 3. _
Because so many school systems have driven great English literature out of students’ hands and minds, it’s possible that some kids never read Charles Dickens’s A Christmas Carol. If you’ve never read this classic, please do so now. You need it.

Back? Good. Fascinating stuff, isn’t it? And so much more accessible than David Copperfield, which was my introduction to Dickens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peering Into the Future from the Past</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/23/peering-into-the-future-from-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 05:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/23/peering-into-the-future-from-the-past/</guid>
      <description>Check this out:
 As far as the market drop and the comeback of the market, I&amp;rsquo;d just like to pass along the following information. I stand in the Ten-Year Treasury-Note pit in the Chicago Board of Trade. The name of the room I trade in is the Financial Room. We trade the commodities that represent most of our national debt. When the gov., sells debt, the buyers of that debt have to hedge somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Your FICA Score?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/20/whats-your-fica-score/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 08:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/20/whats-your-fica-score/</guid>
      <description>Your FICO score is a number between 380 and 820 (or something like that) that banks use to determine your credit worthiness. The higher your FICO score, the better.
But that’s not what I’m talking about here.
I’m talking about your FICA score.

Your FICA score is the minimum payment on your federal loan.
You didn’t know you had a federal loan? You do.
If you’re 18 years old, you owe the federal government about $46,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Look for Quick Fixes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/14/dont-look-for-quick-fixes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 01:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/14/dont-look-for-quick-fixes/</guid>
      <description>According to a book by historians Neil Howe and William Strauss, history follows a fairly predictable pattern, rotating in cycles equal to a long human life. The book, The Fourth Turning, was written in 1997.
Read it.
If Howe and Strauss are right—and so far, they’re dead on—then we recently entered a Fourth Turning in the current saeculum which they named “millennium.”
What is a Fourth Turning?
 The Fourth Turning is a Crisis, a decisive era of secular upheaval, when the values regime propels the replacement of the old civic order with a new one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Happy Hour for March 11, 2011</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/11/friday-happy-hour-for-march-11-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 18:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/11/friday-happy-hour-for-march-11-2011/</guid>
      <description>Every senior generation decries the banal idiocy of its junior generations. Remember how critical Boomers were of Generation X?
Turns out Gen X was one of the most productive generations in a long while. Then Gen Y just went off and fought two wars for us.
Historian Neil Howe points us to today’s Happy Hour: a Millennial elected to Michigan’s state assembly last November.
https://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&amp;amp;isUI=1
As Howe points out:
 Many positive Millennial (born 1982-200?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>