<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ronald_reagan on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/ronald_reagan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ronald_reagan on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 02:04:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/ronald_reagan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/1-do-the-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 02:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/1-do-the-math/</guid>
      <description>Have you noticed few people call Barack Obama “The One” anymore? “The Golfer” or “The Vacationer” is more like it. Something less than One, by any measure.

Still, with each passing day and each new, permanent crisis, it seems like BO just ain’t up to the job of President. Nothing new. When Jimmy Carter’s incompetence became obvious, the lefty press developed a theory that the job had simply grown too complex for one man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe We Need a Lazy President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/09/03/maybe-we-need-a-lazy-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2007 13:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/09/03/maybe-we-need-a-lazy-president/</guid>
      <description>The MSM are tripping over themselves to publish stories about Fred Thompson&amp;rsquo;s supposed laziness. Newsweek decided to make the accusation head on (from CNN.com):
 [A]s he prepares to formally begin his campaign for the White House this week, after months of &amp;ldquo;testing the waters,&amp;rdquo; the conventional wisdom in Washington is that Thompson doesn&amp;rsquo;t want it badly enough, isn&amp;rsquo;t willing to work hard enough-put bluntly, that he is lazy. Newsweek: Grin and Bear It</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Take Down Iran</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/time-to-take-down-iran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 02:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/time-to-take-down-iran/</guid>
      <description>I was lying in the bathtub after a rare Sunday afternoon football practice when the Big Red post-game show was interrupted:
 We interrupt this program for a CBS Radio News special report.  I&amp;rsquo;m Morton Dean. The US State Department has announced that a group of students under control of the Ayatollah Khomeini of Iran have siezed the American Embassy in Tehran, taking more than 100 Americans hostage.
or something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thompson Gaining Social Conservatives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/leftist-attacks-on-thompson-not-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2007 23:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/leftist-attacks-on-thompson-not-working/</guid>
      <description>Boston.com reports that social conservatives are &amp;ldquo;coalescing&amp;rdquo; around Fred Thompson as their choice for Republican nominee for President in 2008.
 &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s a consensus developing around him that&amp;rsquo;s pretty clear and pretty profound,&amp;rdquo; said John Stemberger, president of the Florida Family Policy Council, an Orlando-based conservative group. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen anything like it in 25 years in politics.&amp;rdquo;
 I agree. In 1979, as a high school sophomore with a National Review subscription, I became dissatisfied (for a short time) with the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peggy Noonan: Turning Coats Softly With Her Song</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/17/peggy-noonan-turning-coats-softly-with-her-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2007 04:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/17/peggy-noonan-turning-coats-softly-with-her-song/</guid>
      <description>Peggy Noonan is a great ally and a doubtful foe. She turned, mildly, on Reagan. She has turned on Bush. So what. Her human insights are wonderful, her writing , usually, excellent. She is setting up her pick for 2008 awkwardly.
Bush supporters and detractors, alike, have made much of Ms. Noonan&amp;rsquo;s Friday Opinion Journal column about President Bush. As a fan Peggy&amp;rsquo;s, I was disappointed. One of the hallmarks of conservatism—something that should distinguish us from them—is that we don&amp;rsquo;t eat our own in public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>