<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MoGov on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mogov/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MoGov on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 02:39:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mogov/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Voting for Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/01/why-im-voting-for-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 02:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/01/why-im-voting-for-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>This was supposed to be a longer post, so I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you why I&amp;rsquo;m voting for Eric Greitens in a minute. First, why I have to cut it short.
I got home from door knocking for Eric at about 6:30 and walked straight to my laptop to write. Just as I sat down, my wife called me to dinner. She&amp;rsquo;d already eaten, but she heated up my dinner, called to me, then walked into our living room and shrieked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Choice for President Just Endorsed Eric Greitens for Governor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/30/my-first-choice-for-president-just-endorsed-eric-greitens-for-governor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 18:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/30/my-first-choice-for-president-just-endorsed-eric-greitens-for-governor/</guid>
      <description>From Dr. Ben Carson:
   President Obama and his allies are trying to hijack the Republican primary in Missouri by attacking my good friend Eric Greitens.
    Like me, Eric is a conservative outsider, and that means the political establishment is terrified of him. Obama and his allies are now spending a million dollars falsely attacking Eric Greitens and trying to fool the people of Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did the Pritzkers Donate to Greitens?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, the blog Progressives Today ran an attack piece on Eric Greitens for two of his donors (link). The piece generated of lot angst and fury on the right side of social media.
**Turns out the story was pretty shoddy journalism. **
Progressives Today didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to look at the Pritzkers&amp;rsquo; other donations or the military museum they founded. If they had, they&amp;rsquo;d know that Jennifer N. Pritzker (formerly James N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John “The Weasel” Brunner</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/24/john-the-weasel-brunner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 05:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/24/john-the-weasel-brunner/</guid>
      <description>RADAR: Did you lose something, sir? HAWKEYE: Hi, Stinky. RADAR: Uh, sir, that&amp;rsquo;s the sort of name that kind of sticks with a fella. I&amp;rsquo;d appreciate it if you&amp;rsquo;d just call me by my given nickname.
 —MAS*H
Some names stick with a fella.
A friend emailed the link and this note:
 Brunner is indeed a weasel
 John Brunner, candidate for governor, surreptitiously recorded a phone conversation with his opponent Eric Greitens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>