<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scott Adams on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/scott-adams/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scott Adams on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:18:05 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/scott-adams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Your President Trump: Season Six</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-season-six/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:18:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-season-six/</guid>
      <description>Scott Adams says Donald Trump lives his life like a movie or television series. (See Looking Ahead to Season Four of Trump for a complete explanation.) Being New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, it&amp;rsquo;s time to look back on Season Five (2019) and, then, look ahead to season six (2020) of Trump.
Season Five: Mueller Report and Ukraine Hoax Going into 2019, the Fed had slowed the incredible Trump Economy with aggressive interest rate hikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking ahead to season four of Trump: The President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/looking-ahead-to-season-four-of-trump-the-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 18:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/looking-ahead-to-season-four-of-trump-the-president/</guid>
      <description>Scott Adams first identified Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s greatest strength. What do you think that might be?
It&amp;rsquo;s not his money or his business experience. Those are strengths, sure, but they&amp;rsquo;re not THE strength.
Scott Adams believes Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign was a movie script. Here&amp;rsquo;s what Adams wrote way, way back when Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy was still just a PR stunt because he had zero chance of winning even a single primary:
 A movie script is almost always arranged in what the professionals call a three-act form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In 3 Minutes You&#39;ll Be Able Fend Off Any Verbal Attack About Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/23/in-3-minutes-youll-be-able-fend-off-any-verbal-attack-about-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 04:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/23/in-3-minutes-youll-be-able-fend-off-any-verbal-attack-about-trump/</guid>
      <description>You probably don&amp;rsquo;t believe it. You&amp;rsquo;re probably reading just to argue. But three minutes from now, you&amp;rsquo;ll be armed.
Armed and ready to do verbal combat.
Armed and ready to defend your Trump vote.
Armed and read to win any intellectual confrontation.
Think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible? Keep reading. You&amp;rsquo;ll find out defending your vote for Trump is easier than you could imagine. Your opponent will be standing there, jaw moving, lips quivering, voice lost, brain scrambled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Destroy Radical Islam Without Firing a Shot</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/29/how-to-destroy-radical-islam-without-firing-a-shot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 04:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/29/how-to-destroy-radical-islam-without-firing-a-shot/</guid>
      <description>You probably know that I admire Scott Adams quite a bit. He&amp;rsquo;s brilliantly predicted everything Trump has done. And he&amp;rsquo;s not finished dazzling us with his prediction skills.
Yesterday he made a prediction of how we&amp;rsquo;ll kill ISIS. It isn&amp;rsquo;t pretty. He&amp;rsquo;s not advocating what will happen. He&amp;rsquo;s just telling us what will happen.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to offer an alternative end to ISIS. It&amp;rsquo;s one I&amp;rsquo;ve advocated for attacking radical Islam since 2001.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dethroning the Pointy-Haired Bosses of the Universe</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/26/dethroning-the-pointy-haired-bosses-of-the-universe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/26/dethroning-the-pointy-haired-bosses-of-the-universe/</guid>
      <description>Okay, let me explain this in the simplest possible way&amp;hellip;
 you&amp;hellip;are&amp;hellip;an&amp;hellip;idiot.
&amp;ndash;Scott Adams, Dilbert
 Lately&amp;hellip;the Peter Principle has given way to the &amp;ldquo;Dilbert Principle.&amp;rdquo; The basic concept of the Dilbert Principle is that the most ineffective workers are systematically moved to the place where they can do the least damage: management.
 ― Scott Adams, The Dilbert Principle: A Cubicle&amp;rsquo;s-Eye View of Bosses, Meetings, Management Fads &amp;amp; Other Workplace Afflictions</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>