<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>global-warming on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/global-warming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in global-warming on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:42:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/global-warming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Weinstein and His Call to Jail Global Warming Skeptics</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Yet, in holding scientific research and discovery in respect, as we should, we must also be alert to the equal and opposite danger that public policy could itself become the captive of a scientific-technological elite.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ndash;President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Farewell Address, 1961
A young man named Adam Weinstein recently called for incarceration of disbelievers in the cult of catastrophic anthropogenic global warming (CAGW). His argument mirrors the argument Goebbels used in 1930s to quash dissent from eugenics and to take immediate policy actions for the betterment of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Climate Scientists Aren’t Telling You About Global Warming</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/10/what-climate-scientists-arent-telling-you-about-global-warming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/10/what-climate-scientists-arent-telling-you-about-global-warming/</guid>
      <description>Allan Savory caused the slaughter of 40,000 elephants in a vain attempt to save the planet by stopping desertification.
It turns out that he succeeded only in turning lush grasslands into desert. And, of course, killing 40,000 elephants.
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;1134&amp;rdquo;] Biologist Allan Savory lobbied for the slaughter of 40,000 elephants in a vain attempt to save grasslands. Instead, the grasslands died even faster. Savory devoted his life to finding out why he and other scientists were so wrong about desertification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As the World Cools</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/02/as-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/02/as-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Two quick global warming notes.
Arctic Sea Ice Extend Growing
Not too long ago, Al Gore told German school kids that the North Pole, Santa, Polar Bears, and puppies would all be dead and rotting hunks of diseased fleshed in barren, desserts that were once the Arctic Sea by the time they entered high school. Turns out that the Arctic Sea Ice Extent for 2007-08 and 2008-09 is pretty much in the average for entire history of measured sea ice extent (1979 to present).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Video of 2008</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/25/best-video-of-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 04:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/25/best-video-of-2008/</guid>
      <description>OMG, this is golden: [youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JmPSUMBrJoI&amp;amp;w;=425&amp;amp;h;=344]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More on Hansen&#39;s Fraud</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/27/more-on-hansens-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 12:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/27/more-on-hansens-fraud/</guid>
      <description>While my flaming headline (&amp;quot;Dr. James Hansen of GISS is a Liar and Fraud&amp;quot;) received a fair amount of attention, people a lot smarter than I are carefully documenting the facts that led to my unavoidable conclusion.
One such appears on the Telegraph today. Christopher Booker (corrected link) notes that Dr. Hansen&amp;rsquo;s GISS center is alone in seeing continued warming throughout the world. Pointing out that laws supported by Hansen, Al Gore, and others will cost tens of trillions of dollars and severely limit freedoms throughout the world for the generations, Booker rightly contends that those proposing such a retreat from liberty be damn well sure they&amp;rsquo;re right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Caught Lying Like a Hansen on Climate Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/26/obama-caught-lying-like-a-hansen-on-climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 23:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/26/obama-caught-lying-like-a-hansen-on-climate-change/</guid>
      <description>TigerHawk decided to fact-check Obama&amp;rsquo;s pontifical address to his German subjects concerning the messiah&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;facts&amp;rdquo; about global warming (h/t Hackbarth). Like Hansen and Gore, Obama enjoys lying to the people. TigerHawk shows academic research that report sea levels falling, not rising, and Kansas not in a drought, but normal to exceptionally moist.
I&amp;rsquo;m not surprised to catch Obama in a lie; I am surprised that people continue to lie about global warming despite all scientific evidence (not doctored byJames Hansen) to the contrary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. James Hansen of GISS is a Liar and a Fraud</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/23/dr-james-hansen-of-giss-is-a-liar-and-a-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 05:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/23/dr-james-hansen-of-giss-is-a-liar-and-a-fraud/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Hansen purposely and with malice aforethought manipulates actual temperature observations in order to perpetuate a global warming hoax.
If I&amp;rsquo;m wrong, he can sue me. But he won&amp;rsquo;t, because he&amp;rsquo;s a fraud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Evidence That Al Gore&#39;s A Liar</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/30/more-evidence-that-al-gores-a-liar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2007 23:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/30/more-evidence-that-al-gores-a-liar/</guid>
      <description>This gem of bad news for environmentalist wackos comes from the U. S. Senate Committee on Environment &amp;amp; Public Works via Drudge: Fewer than half of all peer-reviewed scientists who have written on global warming endorse the idea of man-made global warming.
 Of 528 total papers on climate change, only 38 (7%) gave an explicit endorsement of the consensus. If one considers &amp;ldquo;implicit&amp;rdquo; endorsement (accepting the consensus without explicit statement), the figure rises to 45%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>