<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politico on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/politico/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politico on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 23:29:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/politico/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN Liars Slither to New All-Time Low as Politico Hits Rock Bottom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/17/cnn-liars-slither-to-new-all-time-low-as-politico-hits-rock-bottom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 23:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/17/cnn-liars-slither-to-new-all-time-low-as-politico-hits-rock-bottom/</guid>
      <description>CNN is so afraid people will find out they&amp;rsquo;ve been lied to that CNN is lying harder than ever.
It is perfectly legal to visit the Wikileaks.com website. You can even copy information found on the site. Yet CNN&amp;rsquo;s paid liars are telling viewers it&amp;rsquo;s against the law. Plus, they&amp;rsquo;re saying the only way you are allowed to learn the content of the Wikileaks documents is to have it filtered through CNN&amp;rsquo;s official state-sponsored Department of Truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to be wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/07/learning-to-be-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 16:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/07/learning-to-be-wrong/</guid>
      <description>I am wrong a lot.
When I was 25, I was wrong a lot, too.
The difference between 1988 and 2015 is not that I&amp;rsquo;m particularly smarter now, but that I&amp;rsquo;m used to being wrong. Somewhere along life&amp;rsquo;s journey, I realized two things:
*1. Being wrong isn&amp;rsquo;t the end of the world. *2. Being wrong is the beginning of learning.
When I was 25, I refused to admit being wrong about anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Lose Because They Don’t Attract Enough Conservatives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/04/republicans-lose-because-they-dont-attract-enough-conservatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/04/republicans-lose-because-they-dont-attract-enough-conservatives/</guid>
      <description>For 20 years, the Battleground Poll of States (now the Politico/GW Battleground Poll) showed a freakish consistency about ideology.
2009: 59% Conservative 
 2012: 57% Conservative 
With almost 60% calling themselves somewhat or very conservative, how could Barack Obama get re-elected? How could Republicans fail to gain the Senate in 2010 and 2012? Come to think of it, how do Democrats win at all?
The answer is simple: being conservative doesn’t make you Republican, but being Democrat makes you a liberal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Conspire to Suppress Republican Turnout</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/media-conspire-to-suppress-republican-turnout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 23:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/media-conspire-to-suppress-republican-turnout/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s KSDK.com is doing its fair share to suppress the Republican voter turnout. They&amp;rsquo;re pumping a handful of counted votes to give the impression that Obama is walking away with the national popular vote:
  Here&amp;rsquo;s the scam. Only 42 votes have been counted in a country of 150 million registered voters. In other words, it&amp;rsquo;s crap. No responsible news organization would post such misleading nonsense&amp;ndash;except in hopes of discouraging Romney voters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney’s Cleaning Up in Early Voting, but It’s Confused the Hell Out of Politico</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/30/mitt-romneys-cleaning-up-in-early-voting-but-its-confused-the-hell-out-of-politico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 22:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/30/mitt-romneys-cleaning-up-in-early-voting-but-its-confused-the-hell-out-of-politico/</guid>
      <description>Gallup released its early voting poll today, and it shows Mitt Romney winning 52% to 45%—right in line with their Likely Voter poll numbers. Here’s the chart.

Politico Reporter Can’t Read But Gallup’s section on early voting by party ID completely lost Politico’s Kevin Robillard.
Robillard looked at the chart that shows when voters intend to vote by party and candidate and mistook it for voting results. This poll question shows that those who support Obama as as likely to vote early as are those who support Romney.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Turning Tide Swamps All Lefties</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/a-turning-tide-swamps-all-lefties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/12/a-turning-tide-swamps-all-lefties/</guid>
      <description>For three consecutive days the hard left of American politics executed a prepared battle plan:
 * Personify the Enemy (Sarah Palin, Rush Limbaugh, Glenn Beck) * Isolate him or her (Rightwing vitriol, conservative talk radio, “crosshairs”) * Vilify without mercy (Hate, violence, accessory to murder)  Democrat Mark Penn showed us the left’s cards in November when he said that Obama needs an Oklahoma bombing to help him “reconnect” with the American people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>