<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clinton on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/clinton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clinton on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 01:41:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/clinton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Killing Scalia: The Clinton Crime Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/13/killing-scalia-the-clinton-crime-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/13/killing-scalia-the-clinton-crime-family/</guid>
      <description>Do you think the Clinton Crime Family whacked Antonin Scalia? You will soon if you let yourself read this and all the links. But first, a strange call I had last week.
Something Unrelated At the end of our talk, the reporter said, &amp;ldquo;do you mind if I ask you about something else? It has nothing to do with my article, and I won&amp;rsquo;t write about it.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Uh, sure,&amp;rdquo; I said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Heard From Ann Wagner. Now Let&#39;s Hear From the Clintons&#39; Victims</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/08/lets-hear-from-the-clintons-victims/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 20:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/08/lets-hear-from-the-clintons-victims/</guid>
      <description>Today, Rep. Ann Wagner (R-MO) abandoned her party&amp;rsquo;s nominee to support a rape accomplice for President. Ann Wagner has lost her moral authority on all matters outside of her own home. I call on Mrs. Wagner to resign from the House of Representatives and to retire gracefully from public life.
Mrs. Wagner seems to believe that being a woman gives her some unique moral vantage point. She forgets that she&amp;rsquo;s not the only woman in America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinton vs. Trump on Women</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/08/clinton-vs-trump-on-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 15:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/08/clinton-vs-trump-on-women/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Access Hollywood audio has a lot of people cringing. Especially a lot of men who remember the things they&amp;rsquo;ve said about women around other men. And I&amp;rsquo;m talking about men you respect and admire like husbands and dads and brothers. Comedians know what I &amp;lsquo;m talking about.
I won&amp;rsquo;t bore you with the biology of it all, but you probably realize that men and women are fundamentally different. Especially when it comes to reproductive success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Are Back in School And Jihadists Are Killing Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/21/kids-are-back-in-school-and-jihadists-killing-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/21/kids-are-back-in-school-and-jihadists-killing-again/</guid>
      <description>If you thought the government never made a mistake, this story might surprise (via Breitbart)
 WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. government has mistakenly granted citizenship to at least 858 immigrants who had pending deportation orders from countries of concern to national security or with high rates of immigration fraud, according to an internal Homeland Security audit released Monday.
 The Homeland Security Department’s inspector general found that the immigrants used different names or birthdates to apply for citizenship with U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>