<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>senate on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/senate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in senate on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 18:00:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/senate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3:  Todd Akin Needs to Lead or Get Out of the Way</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] Todd Akin: member of the United States House of Representatives. (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
Part 3 of 3 | Read Part 1 | Read Part 2
Before we get too far down the Akin rally road, let&amp;rsquo;s get some solid advice to Mr. Akin.
His principles, his spine, his grassroots do no good if Missouri turns blue. He cannot advance his causes from his house in Wildwood. Failure to take the Senate makes Obamacare permanent, at least in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Were You When Obama Nullified the Constitution?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>Most Americans know more about forensic evidence in the Casey Anthony case than they do about the Constitution. That ignorance gave Barack Obama the hubris to end constitutional government in the United States. He did it, and you probably didn’t even notice.
Over the course of a week, Barack Obama made a series of so-called recess appointments. In the process, he and his henchmen in Eric Holder’s Justice Department effectively nullified the US Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Favor Terrorists Over Constituents</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/21/democrats-favor-terrorists-over-constituents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 01:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/21/democrats-favor-terrorists-over-constituents/</guid>
      <description>I hyperbolize now and then, but not this time.
Democrats in the House and Senate voted to encourage criminal prosecution of Americans who report suspicious activity (Gateway Pundit). Do you know how difficult it is to formulate a more dramatic representation of that fact than the fact itself (Discerning Texan)?
I hate Democrats. Yeah, I know, you&amp;rsquo;re not supposed to &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; anyone. But Democrats are anti-American ass hats. They breed socialism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>