<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FBI on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/fbi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FBI on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 18:34:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/fbi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Note That Killed the FBI</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/the-note-that-killed-the-fbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 18:34:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/the-note-that-killed-the-fbi/</guid>
      <description>Agents of the FBI plotted to frame and destroy General James Flynn for politic purposes according to handwritten notes released today.
General Flynn, a 30-year Army veteran and 3-star General, pled guilty to false charges in order to protect his family from further harassment by the FBI in 2017.
Now, the law firm that once represented Flynn has release thousands of documents it previously illegally refused to turn over. One of those documents is a handwritten note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the New York Times blackmailing FBI and CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 01:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</guid>
      <description>Sounds ridiculous, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
How could a reporter at New York Times blackmail an FBI or CIA agent?
Easily. And everyone who ever went through counter-espionage training knows it.
What Went Down This morning, British Prime Minister Theresa May chastised the US government. The UK freely shares anti-terrorism intelligence with the US. The US is expected to keep secrets secret.
But the US intel community is one gigantic sieve these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Are Back in School And Jihadists Are Killing Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/21/kids-are-back-in-school-and-jihadists-killing-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/21/kids-are-back-in-school-and-jihadists-killing-again/</guid>
      <description>If you thought the government never made a mistake, this story might surprise (via Breitbart)
 WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. government has mistakenly granted citizenship to at least 858 immigrants who had pending deportation orders from countries of concern to national security or with high rates of immigration fraud, according to an internal Homeland Security audit released Monday.
 The Homeland Security Department’s inspector general found that the immigrants used different names or birthdates to apply for citizenship with U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: FBI Report Confirms Hillary&#39;s Guilty Mental Problems</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/02/fib-confirms-clinton-guild-mental-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 18:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/02/fib-confirms-clinton-guild-mental-problems/</guid>
      <description>The FBI dumped its Clinton criminal investigation report today, and it&amp;rsquo;s full of bombshells. Bombs are exploding like the 4th of July, especially the way Clinton lied about Gen. Colin Powell.
Clinton has maintained that Powell advised her to use a private email and cell phone instead of using secure systems provided by the US government.
Hillary lied.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the FBI found:
 Clinton contacted former Secretary of State Colin Powell via e-mail to inquire about his use of a BlackBerry while he was Secretary of State .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Left the Gate Open and Laughed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/05/hillary-left-the-gate-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 23:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/05/hillary-left-the-gate-open/</guid>
      <description>Many people grew up with dogs and backyards. If you are such a person, you probably remember being to told to make sure the gate&amp;rsquo;s shut and locked. Or maybe you were told not to use the gate at all because the dog might get out.
A lot of people who grew up with dogs suffered emotional trauma when something bad happened to their dog. Imagine how you&amp;rsquo;d feel if you were seven or eight and you left the gate open and the dog got out and got hit by a car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m with Apple</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/19/im-with-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 22:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/19/im-with-apple/</guid>
      <description>The government wants Apple to build a back door into the iPhone. Apple has refused.
I’m with Apple on this one.
This back door would allow the FBI to access the content of the San Bernardino terrorists’ phone, possibly exposing more terrorists. That would be a good thing.
But Apple never built a back door to the iPhone because no one can control the keys to such portals. If Apple builds it, every government spy agency in the world will be able to read your texts, see where you’ve been, and listen to your phone calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Water/Black Ops</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/12/white-waterblack-ops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/12/white-waterblack-ops/</guid>
      <description>When I was a kid (thought I felt kind of old at the time) disaster movies were the thing.
Before Star Wars, the 1970s were about killer sharks, towering infernos, earthquakes, and capsized cruise ships.
Psychologists and sociologists attributed the genre&amp;rsquo;s popularity to the people&amp;rsquo;s need to assimilate nuclear holocaust.
I think the movies were just good, cathartic entertainment.
 Nonnie Parry: [Deck behind the group is flooding rapidly] How long will we stay afloat?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>