<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eric Schmitt on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/eric-schmitt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eric Schmitt on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 22:05:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/eric-schmitt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Republican Primary Key Races</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/30/2016-republican-primary-key-races/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 22:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/30/2016-republican-primary-key-races/</guid>
      <description>Some people have a loud opinion on each and every Republican Primary race.
I have a lot of opinions, but I like to focus on a few key races. Here are my major concerns for the 2016 Republican Primary on August 2.
[os-widget path=&amp;rdquo;/billhennessy/2016-republican-primary-key-races1&amp;rdquo; of=&amp;quot;billhennessy&amp;rdquo; comments=&amp;quot;false&amp;rdquo;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continue Your Support of Good Local Government</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/09/continue-your-support-of-good-local-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 19:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/09/continue-your-support-of-good-local-government/</guid>
      <description>You have another chance to improve government and fight petty tyranny by supporting Senator Eric Schmitt&amp;rsquo;s latest bill to hold local government accountable.
Last year, Senator Schmitt became the champion of responsible local government with SB-5, a bill designed to end &amp;ldquo;taxation by citation&amp;rdquo; in local governments.
This year, Senator Schmitt is back to close a loophole that some cities are exploiting to suck more money out of residents who can least afford it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>34 to 0: Good Ideas Are Hard to Fight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/13/34-0-good-ideas-hard-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 03:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/13/34-0-good-ideas-hard-fight/</guid>
      <description>I was scared. Not afraid to say it.
And some friends turned hostile. They had good reasons. And I was probably a little cavalier. And I talked way too long.
But last September I wanted to start something that would help real people in our neighborhood while advancing liberty and upsetting abusive government. Sure, I&amp;rsquo;d rather upset the federal government in Washington, but my arms are little short to box with Harry Reid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do the Speed-Trap Mayors Want You To Drive Dangerously?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/22/speed-trap-mayors-want-drive-dangerously/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 02:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/22/speed-trap-mayors-want-drive-dangerously/</guid>
      <description>I had the rare honor of testifying before the Missouri Senate committee on Economic Development. The hearing&amp;rsquo;s subject was Senator Eric Schmitt&amp;rsquo;s Senate Bill 5 to reign in traffic court abuses in Missouri.
Here&amp;rsquo;s some perspective:
 St. Louis County accounts for 22 percent of Missouri&amp;rsquo;s population and over 50 percent of traffic tickets St. Ann&amp;rsquo;s traffic court revenue exploded from about $500,000 in 2009 to over $3.5 million last year Traffic court generates 90 percent of the total revenue for one Missouri city Ferguson, Missouri, has three outstanding traffic ticket warrants for every citizen The mayor of Edmundson in North St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What&#39;s Happening on the Muni Courts Front</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 02:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</guid>
      <description>He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harrass our people, and eat out their substance.
 &amp;ndash; The Declaration of Independence
Back in August, I asked for your help in pushing for municipal court reform.
Cities that abuse their police and courts destroy liberty:
** Abusive citiesturn citizens against their police forces ** Abusive cities sponge off the poor ** Abusive cities operate debtor prisons ** Abusive cities subvert respect for the law and the courts ** Abusive citiesdemean and demoralize their citizens ** Abusive cities repel business and jobs ** Abusive cities condition people to bow down to government</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri’s Crap Sandwich Servers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/31/missouris-crap-sandwich-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/31/missouris-crap-sandwich-servers/</guid>
      <description>I have a question for State Senator Eric Schmitt: Who says that St. Louis’s 18 million square feet of vacant warehouse space isn’t good enough for Chinese goods?

I heard Senator Schmidt on KMOX a couple of weeks ago. He scoffed at the Show-Me Institute’s analysis of available warehouse space for China Hub saying that to use existing space would be like building F-16s in the Wright Brothers’ hangar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CORRECTED* You Can Help Right a Massive Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/01/you-can-help-right-a-massive-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2011 02:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/01/you-can-help-right-a-massive-wrong/</guid>
      <description>CORRECTION &amp;amp; APOLOGY_ I am so sorry to you and to Senator Eric Schmitt for misrepresenting his position on HB466. Senator Schmitt’s office tells me that he has no intention of filibustering this bill. He went on to say that he agrees in principle with the bill’s intent and may actually support it, depending on the language. _
Please accept my apology and help me make it right. Please call or write Senator Schmitt’s office (below) and tell him Thank You.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>