<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>truth on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/truth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in truth on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:12:51 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/truth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quid Est Veritas</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/quid-est-veritas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 12:12:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/quid-est-veritas/</guid>
      <description>Quid Est Veritas?
Sometimes I think Pontius Pilate gets a bad rap.
Sure, he was ultimately the slithery politician who sentenced Jesus to death, but he was also the only person on earth who offered Jesus something of a defense.
When the Jews first presented Jesus to Pilate, Pilate told them to try Jesus themselves. But the Jews argued that they could not lawfully put Him to death (John 18:31).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Truths of Republicans and Race</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/07/forbidden-truths-of-republicans-and-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/07/forbidden-truths-of-republicans-and-race/</guid>
      <description>Republicans hate race. Race has been bad for the GOP ever since Republicans passed the Civil Rights Act of 1964. See, Lyndon Johnson was a Democrat, and he proposed the Civil Rights Act of 1964. Most Democrats violently opposed the bill. But most Republicans supported it. The bill passed, of course, and it survived many Supreme Court challenges.
The Civil Rights Act&amp;rsquo;s aim was to wring racist behavior out of American life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m trying to write the truth</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/27/im-trying-to-write-the-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/27/im-trying-to-write-the-truth/</guid>
      <description>I was a pretender.
In 2012, I pretended I believed Mitt Romney would win. But I knew better. I just didn&amp;rsquo;t have the heart to tell the truth to the volunteers banging doors and working call lists from our election office in South County.
But I knew Romney would lose. I suspected the GOP would not regain the Senate.
When some of our hardest workers showed up to help break down the office and move our belongings, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t look at them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>