<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>heritage foundation on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/heritage-foundation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in heritage foundation on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 12:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/heritage-foundation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I am honored to question the GOP candidates for you and Heritage</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-am-honored-to-question-the-gop-candidates-for-you-and-heritage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 12:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/16/i-am-honored-to-question-the-gop-candidates-for-you-and-heritage/</guid>
      <description>This is pretty cool and a little unnerving.
Heritage Action has extended the honor to be one of three Heritage Action Sentinels to question Republican Presidential candidates on Friday, September 17 in Greenville, South Carolina. So far, 12 candidates have confirmed, including Donald Trump, Jeb Bush, Ben Carson, Carly Fiorina, Ted Cruz, Scott Walker, Rick Santorum, Bobby Jindal, Rand Paul, Chris Christie, and Marco Rubio. (Maybe Trump will make fun of my tie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatever Happened to the Party of Ideas?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/10/16/whatever-happened-party-ideas/</guid>
      <description>From about 1978 until the Monica Lewinsky fiasco, the GOP was called &amp;ldquo;the party of ideas.&amp;rdquo; I miss the ideas.
William F. Buckley helped. Buckley liked big ideas and smart people. He liked politicians who gave legs to great ideas and governors with the guts to experiment. Governor Ronald Reagan appeared on Buckley&amp;rsquo;s Firing Line shortly after the Gipper became California&amp;rsquo;s governor. Reagan talked about many ideas he was trying or hoping to try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Ann Wagner Is Wrong to Attack Heritage Action</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 02:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/24/ann-wagner-wrong-attack-heritage-action/</guid>
      <description>Accountability? We don&amp;rsquo;t need no stinking accountability.
 No, Ann Wagner didn&amp;rsquo;t actually say that. But her comments to a 2nd District Republican committee meeting on Tuesday gave at least one attendee the impression that Mrs. Wagner opposes the idea of conservatives holding Congress accountable.
Ann Wagner Attacks the Conservative Heritage Action Rep. Ann Wagner accused the conservative Heritage Action for America of &amp;ldquo;pitting Republican against Republican&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;never attacking Dems&amp;rdquo; at the Republican meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 15 Is The Next After Party with Heritage Tavern</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/12/august-15-is-the-next-after-party-with-heritage-tavern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/12/august-15-is-the-next-after-party-with-heritage-tavern/</guid>
      <description>**PLEASE MARK YOUR CALENDAR____**
OUR NEXT BIG AFTER PARTY EVENT!____
 It is Thursday, August 15, at 7:00 P.M. at Hacienda Mexican Restaurant____
https://www.haciendastl.com/____
____
 **Hacienda Mexican Restaurant____**
**9748 Manchester RD____**
**St Louis, MO 63119____**
314-962-7100****____
  Russ Vought, Political Director at Heritage Action, will be our guest speaker on Thursday, August 15. He will discuss his role with Heritage Action. ____
From 7pm-8pm, Russ will talk about the Scorecard &amp;amp; what our team does in DC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seducing the States</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/08/seducing-the-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/08/seducing-the-states/</guid>
      <description>You can’t call yourself a conservative and ask for education money from Washington.
Republicans dominate both houses of the Missouri legislature. You’d think they’d act like republicans (lower case). But when it comes to education bribes from Washington, many of our Republican legislators show little resistance to political seduction. We can help them.
On BigGovernment. com, Bob McCarty highlights the hypocrisy of blasting ObamaCare from one side of the mouth while begging for federal cash out of the other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>