<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hyperinflation on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/hyperinflation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hyperinflation on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 03:18:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/hyperinflation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Russian Empire</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/the-new-russian-empire/</guid>
      <description>The last two years of Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s presidency will see the rise of a new Russian empire.
This new empire will resemble the Soviet Union in shape, the Czars in style.
We looked at this subject over the summer (here and here). To summarize those blogs:
 The US-led coup of Ukraine convinced Putin to reassert safer borders Russia wants to build a buffer between itself and NATO Putin wants to re-establish a Russian Empire to revitalize Russian pride and influence Western debt and war-weariness make NATO impotent Putin knows the next US president might be more of a man than Obama, even if its Hillary Putin will want to complete his expansion by January 20, 2017 Ukraine is as good as done and Poland will fall under Russian influence  I still believe all of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Other Shoe Drops</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/08/the-other-shoe-drops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 12:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/08/the-other-shoe-drops/</guid>
      <description>For months I&amp;rsquo;ve been echoing the warnings of Peter Schiff and others: when China stops buying American debt, we&amp;rsquo;re in deep, deep trouble. The possibility for hyperflation, prices rise by double-digits on daily or weekly measures, becomes palpably high.
Even though this article from IHT failed to suprised me, I have a sick, frightened gnawing in my stomach:
 China has bought more than $1 trillion in American debt, but as the global downturn has intensified, Beijing is starting to keep more of its money at home - a shift that could pose some challenges to the U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>