<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ted Cruz on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/ted-cruz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ted Cruz on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 02:50:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/ted-cruz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz: Mensch!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/27/ted-cruz-mensch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 02:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/27/ted-cruz-mensch/</guid>
      <description>If you read my blog, you know I&amp;rsquo;ve had differences with Senator Ted Cruz. But the Senator has stepped up. Bigly! Only a gentleman would do what Cruz just did with his El Chapo bill.
Remember the GOP race? Cruz and Trump went at each other like nobody&amp;rsquo;s business. Wives and all. While Cruz couldn&amp;rsquo;t bring himself to endorse Trump at the convention, Ted has stepped up a lot since the election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#NeverTrump Self Immolation Over Trusty Ted Cruz</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/24/nevertrump-self-immolation-over-trusty-ted-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 17:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/24/nevertrump-self-immolation-over-trusty-ted-cruz/</guid>
      <description>This is for the people, like me, who realized sometime between June 2015 and June 2016 that Donald Trump is at least better than Hillary and possibly a transformational character who can reverse America&amp;rsquo;s descent into chaos.
 “A leader is a man who can adapt principles to circumstances.” – General George Patton Jr
 You might think this post is an attempt to reach #NeverTrumpers and bring them on board the Trump Train.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why does Ted Cruz&#39;s Speech Bother Me So Much?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/22/why-does-ted-cruzs-speech-bother-me-so-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 13:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/22/why-does-ted-cruzs-speech-bother-me-so-much/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m trying to put my finger on exactly why I found Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s remarks Wednesday night so incredibly distasteful.
The Pledge thing is a goodly part of it.
Simply put, the parties to the Pledge Ted Cruz signed were only Ted Cruz and the RNC (by extension, you can probably include the delegates and voters, too).
The Pledge promised support, including data, from the RNC in exchange for Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s endorsement of the eventual nominee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What If Ted Cruz Said This Instead?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/21/what-if-ted-cruz-said-this-instead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 21:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/21/what-if-ted-cruz-said-this-instead/</guid>
      <description>Parts pulled from comments to this post:
Today Cruz proved himself to be Lyin&amp;rsquo; Ted again.
After swearing that his non-endorsement was all about &amp;ldquo;freedom and the Constitution,&amp;rdquo; he admitted today that he broke his oath of support solely because Trump insulted his wife and his father. For Ted, this was personal, not business.
Ted could have told us it was personal last night. But he lied instead. He could have said something else, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Donald Trump Destroyed Ted Cruz</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/21/how-donald-trump-destroyed-ted-cruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/21/how-donald-trump-destroyed-ted-cruz/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re probably thinking that Ted Cruz made Donald Trump look bad last night. And he did. Ted Cruz had a prime time speaking slot and he failed to endorse his party&amp;rsquo;s nominee for president. Hillary Clinton will use it.
A lot of people are saying Trump shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have invited him to speak unless Cruz agreed to endorse Trump. But Trump didn&amp;rsquo;t even ask for Cruz&amp;rsquo;s endorsement. Trump just offered Ted the prime time spot, and Ted took it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>