<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>conservatives on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/conservatives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in conservatives on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 08:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/conservatives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners Proves Government Can’t Get Anything Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/04/st-louis-board-of-police-commissioners-proves-government-cant-get-anything-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/04/st-louis-board-of-police-commissioners-proves-government-cant-get-anything-right/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives love cracking on government and its unintended consequences. How often does a government initiative give us backassward results?
Exhibit A: Obama hands Solyndra millions in tax dollars to promote green energy. Solyndra (and numerous other green energy grant recipients) goes bankrupt.
Another example is the St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners.
In 1861, Missouri’s legislature created a board of commissioners to oversee the St. Louis Police Department. Why? Because Missouri was a slave state, but St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCaskillPAC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/25/mccaskillpac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 03:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/25/mccaskillpac/</guid>
      <description>What I find so funny about Claire McCaskill&amp;rsquo;s war on super pacs is that her husband is a super PAC.
For the record, I have formally endorsed Senator McCaskill in her race to return to private life.
Zimmerman Update Having declared George Zimmerman guilty of first degree, racially motivated murder, the MSM are now investigating the case.
What they&amp;rsquo;re finding:
 The George Zimmerman that Francescani describes is quite different from the &amp;ldquo;delusional racist vigilante&amp;rdquo; that many have made him out to be.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>