<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chip Wood on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/chip-wood/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chip Wood on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 18:34:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/chip-wood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Party, Not a Club</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/08/a-party-not-a-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 18:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/08/a-party-not-a-club/</guid>
      <description>Let’s face it: the Missouri GOP has become a club to advance the careers of a select few favorites. It is not a party to advance conservative principles.
And that needs to change here and now.
And that means some old names need to retire.
Here’s just one example of the ideological impotence of the Missouri Republican Party: The St. Louis County Assessor.
The GOP created the St. Louis County Assessor’s office because of corruption and incompetence in the political patronage version of the office under Democrats Buzz Westfall and Charlie Dooley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Taxes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/24/a-tale-of-two-taxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/24/a-tale-of-two-taxes/</guid>
      <description>On Monday, we learned that US Senator Claire McCaskill failed to pay property taxes on her personal luxury jet for three years. Previously, she had charged taxpayers some of the cost of operating her private plane. Before that, it seems, she registered the plane in property tax-free Delaware.
On Monday, Claire wrote a $287,000 check without batting an eye. Now, St. Louis County says she owes them another $33,000 in interest and penalties, for a total bill of $320,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>L.K. Wood Makes His Case</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/23/l-k-wood-makes-his-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 23:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/23/l-k-wood-makes-his-case/</guid>
      <description>You can help get these TV ads on the air. I will tell you how shortly.
Don’t in live in St. Louis County? You still have a horse in this race. I’ll tell you why after you watch this commercial.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LtcLdxad-3k&amp;amp;hl;=en&amp;amp;hd;=1]
Vote L. K. Wood, as everyone should, on April 5
Why should you care about this race if you don’t live in St. Louis County?
Because Chip’s opponent is a Harvard lawyer who’s being groomed for much bigger things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Top Ways to Clean Up St. Louis County Government</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/20/3-top-ways-to-clean-up-st-louis-county-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 20:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/20/3-top-ways-to-clean-up-st-louis-county-government/</guid>
      <description>Meet Chip Tuesday, March 22 from 5:30 to 7:00. Details below.
You can help clean up St. Louis County government. And you can have a good time doing it. Here’s how.
  Like L. K. “Chip” Wood’s Facebook page. It’ll take only a second, and you’ll feel more connected and productive just by doing it.
  Visit Chip Wood for Assessor and enter your email address in the email sign-up box on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crooked as a Dog’s Hind Leg</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/19/crooked-as-a-dogs-hind-leg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/19/crooked-as-a-dogs-hind-leg/</guid>
      <description>That’s St. Louis County Executive Charlie Dooley.
It’s bad enough that corruption, nepotism, and Machiavellian favoritism runs rampant in St. Louis County. What’s worse is that Dooley doesn’t seem to care what anyone thinks.
 St. Louis County in the third year of a hiring and pay freeze, Mike Temporiti landed a $70,000 county job.
. . .
The job was never posted, and Temporiti did not have to interview for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>L. K. “Chip” Wood for County Assessor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/09/l-k-chip-wood-for-county-assessor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 02:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/09/l-k-chip-wood-for-county-assessor/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that there’s an election on April 5? And it’s just as important an election as last November’s historic election.
https://www.facebook.com/v/10150106903825886
https://www.chipwoodforassessor.com/index1.html
This time, you and I have the job to elect Chip Wood for County Assessor.* Here’s why.
In 2010, voters created an elected assessor’s office in St. Louis County. The Republicans pushed for this new office because of corruption, abuse, and waste in the County Assessor’s office under Charlie Dooley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Election Counts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/08/every-election-counts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/08/every-election-counts/</guid>
      <description>Next Election: 4 weeks from today. I need a favor. This will only take you a minute (tops), but it’s very important that you do it right now.
I will step you through it.
  Get a pen or pencil and something to write on—preferably a journal or appointment calendar.
  Go to April 5, 2011, or write April 5, 2011, if not using a calendar or dated journal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>