<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>August 5 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/august-5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in August 5 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 21:31:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/august-5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is The Tea Party Suffering From Republican Fatigue Syndrome?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/11/tea-party-republican-fatigue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 21:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/11/tea-party-republican-fatigue/</guid>
      <description>Maybe the chickens are coming home to roost for the GOP in St. Louis County.
In my day job, I focus on two subjects: strategic behavioral science and analytics. Really smart people do most of the heavy analytics work. I deal with the human behavior (neuroeconomics, psychology, etc.). In our narrow field of loyalty and motivation, I think we&amp;rsquo;re the best in the business. Not me, but the people I work with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are the Missouri August Primary results a fluke or the beginning of a trend?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/10/missouri-august-primary-results-fluke-beginning-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 21:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/10/missouri-august-primary-results-fluke-beginning-trend/</guid>
      <description>Many Republican voters pulled a Democrat ballot August 5th, in St. Louis County. Having crossed over once, how many will do it again in November? It is no secret that the Republican legislature in Jefferson City has exhibited minimal leadership on major issues while spending most of a short legislative calendar talking about issues invented by lobbyists.
Republican voters expected more.
Many St. Louis County Republican voters are baffled by the absence of political ‘guts’ displayed in Jefferson City.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>