<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zen to Done on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/zen-to-done/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zen to Done on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 03:53:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/zen-to-done/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen to Done:  Learning the Dream</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/02/zen-to-done-learning-the-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 03:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/02/zen-to-done-learning-the-dream/</guid>
      <description>Feeling confident, relaxed, and complete is a dream. Many people believe it&amp;rsquo;s an impossible dream. I&amp;rsquo;m learning otherwise.
I&amp;rsquo;m into my third month of acquiring positive habits with Leo Babauta&amp;rsquo;sZen to Done method. At the same time, I&amp;rsquo;m working the 30 day challenge. What I&amp;rsquo;ve learned so far is that I hold onto too much.
 * I carried around anger and frustration over missed goals and failed or abandoned projects * I vilified good people (in my mind) because I wanted to get my way all the time about everything * I sabotaged myself by trying to do everything anyone asked of me * I was afraid to look weak, and that fear weakened me  The faultering economy, no doubt, led me toZen Habits, which led me to Zen to Done, which led me to &amp;ldquo;The Power of Less,&amp;rdquo; which led me to theSedona Method, which led me here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen to Done:  The Next Challenges</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/zen-to-done-the-next-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 05:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/zen-to-done-the-next-challenges/</guid>
      <description>Several weeks ago, I posted about Leo Babauta&amp;rsquo;s Zen to Done method for Getting Things Done. I apologize for not keeping up my blogging on my progress. But one habit at a time. Habit One: Capturing Everything
More than a month later, I can proudly say I&amp;rsquo;ve mastered the first step in the program. I still record everything on Jott, either on the web or by voice messaging Jott.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>