<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Hampshire on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/new-hampshire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New Hampshire on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/new-hampshire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If We Don’t Flip Some Toss-Up States, Romney, Ryan, and the USA Are Screwed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</guid>
      <description>Choosing Paul Ryan as his running mate was a great Romney move. Looking ahead, Romney sees movement conservatives working hard right up to the election—even if he or his advisors continues to say stupid things. That was necessary.
SCROLL DOWN FOR TWO IMPORTANT EVENTS THIS WEEK
But it wasn’t enough to win the election and unseat America’s first anti-American president. To do that, we must find a way to win over the selfish middle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire Exposes GOP’s Diverse Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/11/new-hampshire-exposes-gops-diverse-base/</guid>
      <description>Okay, Santorum and Gingrich didn’t get a bump out of their debates over the weekend. More like the bump got them.
And Ron Paul did way better than I expected. Congratulations to Dr. Paul and Mitt. 
I still think my Saturday night post accurately reflected the national impressions, though. That’s backed up by this CBS News poll that shows Republicans believe Santorum most closely shares their values, but—and this is a J Lo but—they believe Romney is more electable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Won the New Hampshire Republican Debate?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/07/who-won-the-new-hampshire-republican-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 05:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/07/who-won-the-new-hampshire-republican-debate/</guid>
      <description>It depends on how you score. 
I see three scoring scenarios: 1. Best conservative performance 2. Best electability performance 3. Best positional performance
Conservative performance is pretty clear: whose answers appeal to conservatives? (Does not mean conservatives believed the candidate meant what he said.) This is not Tea Party scoring, either. I’m not limiting my evaluation to the 3 core Tea Party principles of Constitutionally limited government, free markets, and fiscal responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>