<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tea Party News on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tea-party-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tea Party News on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 01:07:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tea-party-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Junk Bond</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 01:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond-2/</guid>
      <description>John is a Vietnam veteran and retired business executive. He loves America and hates to see what’s happened in Washington the past few years. He believes in liberty and Constitutional limitations on government growth.
He called the Tea Party just to vent and to see if it’s just him.
Recently, John had called Senator Kit Bond’s (R-MO) office in Washington. He wanted to know whether stories that Bond had signed off a $659 million earmark for soy bean farmers were true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junk Bond</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 01:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/12/11/junk-bond/</guid>
      <description>John is a Vietnam veteran and retired business executive. He loves America and hates to see what’s happened in Washington the past few years. He believes in liberty and Constitutional limitations on government growth.
He called the Tea Party just to vent and to see if it’s just him.
Recently, John had called Senator Kit Bond’s (R-MO) office in Washington. He wanted to know whether stories that Bond had signed off a $659 million earmark for soy bean farmers were true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consent of the Governed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/consent-of-the-governed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/consent-of-the-governed/</guid>
      <description>In the battle between conservatives and statists, a fundamental difference seems to lie in the meaning of a concept found in the Declaration of Independence:
 Governments are instituted among Men, deriving their just powers from the consent of the governed[.]
 The dispute is how men convey consensual powers to their government.
Conservatives believe that governmental power is conveyed exclusively through the Constitution; statists believe power is conveyed through elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Days of Free Markets Numbered</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/days-of-free-markets-numbered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/days-of-free-markets-numbered/</guid>
      <description>The statists are moving faster through the Constitution than Hitler moved through France. Today, Democrats in the House of Representatives voted to advance a bill to socialize medicine without debate.
 House Democrats went on record again in favor of advancing the legislation while allowing only limited debate, which would hobble the ability of Republicans to wrest concessions on one of Obama&amp;rsquo;s top domestic priorities.
 **Accelerating the **Banana Republic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another one bites the dust</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/18/another-one-bites-the-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 17:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/18/another-one-bites-the-dust/</guid>
      <description>This is my last post on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View, at least for some time. My work for the St. Louis Tea Party movement is very important to me and, in my opinion, to you. Our government is moving quickly to obliterate all vestiges of the free market republic that America once was. With the Republican party in disarray and the Democrat party in the hands of statist despots, the tea partiers are the only thing standing between liberty and tyranny.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>