<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Impeachment on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/impeachment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Impeachment on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 04:56:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/impeachment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Triumphant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 04:56:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump just had another one of those weeks for which he&amp;rsquo;s become famous.
 There was the week hit bombed Syria while dining with President Xi of China at Mar a Lago. There was Easter Week 2019 when the Mueller Report exonerated and the economy hit new highs. There was the week of the State of the Union Address that included his exoneration in the Senate.  But, this week&amp;rsquo;s outbreak of liberty and its commensurate exposure of Trump&amp;rsquo;s enemies as pure scum is the best so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Is a Styrofoam Bird</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/impeachment-and-styrofoam-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 13:16:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/impeachment-and-styrofoam-bird/</guid>
      <description>This post is about impeachment. But, first, you need to hear about a toy bird from the 1970s.
Disappointing Toys When I was seven or eight, I just had to have a Zorr: The Mighty Eagle.
Zorr could soar on the wind for hours, just like a real eagle. The TV commercials left me certain that Zorr would make the most popular kid on my block—maybe the whole parish. I&amp;rsquo;d have a pet eagle, really.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do Democrats Expect?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/what-do-democrats-expect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 18:50:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/what-do-democrats-expect/</guid>
      <description>If Democrats cross the Rubicon by impeaching President Trump, they will be sending a strong signal: no Republican president will ever survive his first term.
How do you expect people to respond? I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the people President Obama derisively labeled &amp;ldquo;bitter clingers.&amp;rdquo;
  The people RealPolitics data analyst Sean Trende identified as &amp;ldquo;downscale, Northern, rural &amp;hellip; H. Ross Perot voters.&amp;rdquo;
Or, to put it another way, Tea Partiers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;ve Never Been Closer to Totalitarianism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/30/weve-never-been-closer-to-totalitarianism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 13:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/30/weve-never-been-closer-to-totalitarianism/</guid>
      <description>Very scary thought: If the Democrats take over the House and Senate in January, they could impeach both Trump and Pence and try them in the Senate at the same time making Nancy Pelosi president.
You&amp;rsquo;ve Never Lived in a Time Like This One I&amp;rsquo;m almost old enough to remember the Democrat National Convention of 1968. Almost. What a show. Hippies and Yippies marching, tear gas, Mayor Daley, Buckley threatening to punch Gore Vidal on live TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Obama Using SEIU to Terrorize Citizens?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/22/is-obama-using-seiu-to-terrorize-citizens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/22/is-obama-using-seiu-to-terrorize-citizens/</guid>
      <description>Interesting. Mounting evidence suggests [the White House may have been complicit](If so, even Democrats in Congress would be forced to open impeachment investigations) in SEIU’s terrorism (as defined by U.S. Patriot Act) of a banker’s teenage son.

Quit the SEIU. No decent person would belong to an organization that openly, and with the federal government’s approval, uses terrorism to get its way.
Quit the DC Metro Police Force. The President is using you to promote domestic terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>