<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>roy blunt on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/roy-blunt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in roy blunt on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:16:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/roy-blunt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Win Consistently</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/06/how-to-win-consistently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/06/how-to-win-consistently/</guid>
      <description>If your favorite player hits a home run or scores a goal, but your favorite team loses, what have you accomplished?
If an athlete you despise makes a horrible error but the hated team he plays for wins the championship, how do you feel?
In several races across Missouri, some people seem willing to lose the war if it means they can win their private battles. That’s pretty sad, isn’t it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you want Mike Lee on the Supreme Court, you have to vote for Roy Blunt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/25/if-you-want-mike-lee-on-the-supreme-court-you-have-to-vote-for-roy-blunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/25/if-you-want-mike-lee-on-the-supreme-court-you-have-to-vote-for-roy-blunt/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll make this short. I have been highly critical of Senator Roy Blunt for a long time. You can search my blog and find many things that bother me about the Blunts, but that&amp;rsquo;s not what this is about.
This post is about whether the US Constitution survives.
This post is about whether that government of the people, by the people, and for the people will perish from the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strangest Governor Race Ever</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/05/the-strangest-governor-race-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/05/the-strangest-governor-race-ever/</guid>
      <description>You might be wondering why the Missouri Farm Bureau endorsed Democrat Chris Koster instead of Republican Eric Greitens. The Farm Bureau endorses Republicans about 99% of the time.
If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking it had to do with policy or personality, you&amp;rsquo;re thinking wrong. (And, no, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t because of Koster&amp;rsquo;s hair, Mark Reardon.) This was all about the establishment vs. the people. It&amp;rsquo;s about power and control. Greitens threatens the establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Expect Much More of Republicans on Obamacare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/25/expect-much-republicans-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 05:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/25/expect-much-republicans-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>Sam Adams and friends risked their lives in the commission of a felony in their outrage over government overreach.
That was the Boston Tea Party.
Look at us now! People furious with me for going after Senator Roy Blunt. I went after him because he announced he will vote for cloture knowing full well that cloture give Harry Reid his only chance to strip the House&amp;rsquo;s Obamacare defund language from the continuing resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork For Me But Not For Thee</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/31/pork-for-me-but-not-for-thee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/31/pork-for-me-but-not-for-thee/</guid>
      <description>Some St. Louis area conservatives cheered Roy Blunt’s (R-MO) elevation to the Number 5 leadership position in the Senate Republican caucus.

I didn’t. At least not politically. I like Senator Blunt personally, so I’m happy in that respect. But I’m not happy for the reasons some others are.
First, as I told Jo Mannies of the St. Louis Beacon, internal party stuff isn’t really a Tea Party matter. Leadership in the Senate’s GOP caucus is for Republican Senators to worry about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rah Rah Roy Blunt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/07/rah-rah-roy-blunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/07/rah-rah-roy-blunt/</guid>
      <description>Roy Blunt has not given an inch in thebattle over the debt ceiling. He deserves high praise for his resolve.
During the 2010 Republican primary, many on the right questioned Blunt&amp;rsquo;s fiscal conservative credentials. As a member of the House, Blunt had helped craft some and pass unpopular spending bills, including TARP. On theissue of debt and responsibility, though, he shows no sign of cracking.
  Government debt is the defining issue of our time, perhaps of the American experiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Tilley vs. Fiscal Responsibility</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/14/steve-tilley-vs-fiscal-responsibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/14/steve-tilley-vs-fiscal-responsibility/</guid>
      <description>Four men risked their political lives to help solve the problem of our lifetimes, but they forgot to massage Steve Tilley’s monstrous ego.
  When John McCain (R-AZ) and Roy Blunt (R-MO) agree with Michele Bachmann and Rush Limbaugh, you can bet the issue is beyond debate.
In this case, the issue is the massive U.S. debt and what that debt is about to do to America.
McCain compared the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes a Morris is Just a Morris</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/sometimes-a-morris-is-just-a-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 05:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/sometimes-a-morris-is-just-a-morris/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch invited Dick Morris onto her radio show today. Dana expected to discuss START with Mr. Morris. But Dick has a mind of his own.
Morris decided, about a minute and a half into a five-minute segment, that he wanted to talk about the 2012 US Senate race in Missouri instead. Specifically, he wanted spend the segment campaigning for Sarah Steelman for the the Republican nomination.
Decide for yourself: here’s the link to Dana’s show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Courage of Roy Blunt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/13/the-courage-of-roy-blunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 18:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/13/the-courage-of-roy-blunt/</guid>
      <description>When you vote for a candidate for high office, sometimes you do so with fingers crossed. You just don’t know how they’ll handle the new responsibilities. Will they succumb to pressure and influence? Or will they remain true?
Luckily for us, Senator-elect Roy Blunt showed his courage in a recent Wall Street Journal article about the Tea Party and the GOP.
In a year when voters overwhelming demanded changes to business as usual in Washington, Roy Blunt showed he has the rectitude to stand strong for the tried and true practices of obfuscation, political double-speak, and deflection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On to November</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/on-to-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/on-to-november/</guid>
      <description>The primaries are over.
I honestly believe that in the St. Louis area, the rightward-most, viable candidate won each of the key votes. The people of Missouri are in a position to make historical shifts in our Washington representation. And those shifts are just the first step and restoring America’s First Principles.

View Full Album
Roy Blunt is a conservative. He will be a big step up for conservatism in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Missouri US Senate Race Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/02/latest-missouri-us-senate-race-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 21:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/02/latest-missouri-us-senate-race-poll/</guid>
      <description>Rasmussen Report has the latest numbers from the Missouri Senate race.
The poll does not include any mention of Republican candidate Chuck Purgason. Purgason seems to be enjoying something of a surge. He’s doffed his toupee and traded the Bolo tie for a regular one. And Purgason’s released a radio commercial in key areas around the state.
Rasmussen finds strong support for Roy Blunt among those who consider themselves tea partyers:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>