<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>roy blunt on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/roy-blunt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in roy blunt on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:16:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/roy-blunt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Win Consistently</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/06/how-to-win-consistently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/06/how-to-win-consistently/</guid>
      <description>If your favorite player hits a home run or scores a goal, but your favorite team loses, what have you accomplished?
If an athlete you despise makes a horrible error but the hated team he plays for wins the championship, how do you feel?
In several races across Missouri, some people seem willing to lose the war if it means they can win their private battles. That’s pretty sad, isn’t it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you want Mike Lee on the Supreme Court, you have to vote for Roy Blunt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/25/if-you-want-mike-lee-on-the-supreme-court-you-have-to-vote-for-roy-blunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/25/if-you-want-mike-lee-on-the-supreme-court-you-have-to-vote-for-roy-blunt/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll make this short. I have been highly critical of Senator Roy Blunt for a long time. You can search my blog and find many things that bother me about the Blunts, but that&amp;rsquo;s not what this is about.
This post is about whether the US Constitution survives.
This post is about whether that government of the people, by the people, and for the people will perish from the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strangest Governor Race Ever</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/05/the-strangest-governor-race-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 02:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/05/the-strangest-governor-race-ever/</guid>
      <description>You might be wondering why the Missouri Farm Bureau endorsed Democrat Chris Koster instead of Republican Eric Greitens. The Farm Bureau endorses Republicans about 99% of the time.
If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking it had to do with policy or personality, you&amp;rsquo;re thinking wrong. (And, no, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t because of Koster&amp;rsquo;s hair, Mark Reardon.) This was all about the establishment vs. the people. It&amp;rsquo;s about power and control. Greitens threatens the establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Expect Much More of Republicans on Obamacare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/25/expect-much-republicans-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 05:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/25/expect-much-republicans-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>Sam Adams and friends risked their lives in the commission of a felony in their outrage over government overreach.
That was the Boston Tea Party.
Look at us now! People furious with me for going after Senator Roy Blunt. I went after him because he announced he will vote for cloture knowing full well that cloture give Harry Reid his only chance to strip the House&amp;rsquo;s Obamacare defund language from the continuing resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork For Me But Not For Thee</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/31/pork-for-me-but-not-for-thee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/31/pork-for-me-but-not-for-thee/</guid>
      <description>Some St. Louis area conservatives cheered Roy Blunt’s (R-MO) elevation to the Number 5 leadership position in the Senate Republican caucus.

I didn’t. At least not politically. I like Senator Blunt personally, so I’m happy in that respect. But I’m not happy for the reasons some others are.
First, as I told Jo Mannies of the St. Louis Beacon, internal party stuff isn’t really a Tea Party matter. Leadership in the Senate’s GOP caucus is for Republican Senators to worry about.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>