<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Jones on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tim-jones/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tim Jones on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:46:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tim-jones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Party Thursday!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/29/party-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 12:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/29/party-thursday/</guid>
      <description>A great State Rep decides to give up his seat. The seat previously held by the Speaker of the House and a conservative legend. A seat in, perhaps, the most reliably conservative House district in St. Louis County.
Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a battle for that seat. A battle between a left-leaning Establishment Republican and a grassroots Conservative activist. An activist whose work for the right causes earned a star on Heritage Action&amp;rsquo;s Wall of Honor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**DOH!** ACTION: Tell Missouri Legislature Jay Nixon to Pass Tax Holiday for Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 20:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>****UPDATE
Tim Jones let me know that I&amp;rsquo;m giving the legislature more power than it actually has.
Veto sessions are limited to overriding vetos. Thus the name. BUT the governor can call a Special Session to vote on a Ferguson Tax Holiday. That session can run concurrent with the Veto Session, saving taxpayer dollars.
SO &amp;gt; &amp;gt; &amp;gt; New Action: Ask Jay Nixon (via Twitter and Facebook) to call a Special Session concurrent with the Veto Session to create a Tax Holiday for Ferguson/Dellwood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DESE: The original box of rocks that nothing is dumber than</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/24/dese-the-original-box-of-rocks-that-nothing-is-dumber-than/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/24/dese-the-original-box-of-rocks-that-nothing-is-dumber-than/</guid>
      <description>According to research from Missouri Education Watchdog, the Department of Elementary and Secondary Education (DESE) agreed to surrender Missouri&amp;rsquo;s education voice under Obama&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Race to the Top&amp;rdquo; scheme. Race to the Top was a contest in which states agreed to let the federal Department of Education, via two puppet organizations, run all of the state&amp;rsquo;s education systems. In exchange, some states were awarded money, but others were not.
Chris Nicastro, chief rock in the DESE box, applied for the grant.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>