<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mueller on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mueller/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mueller on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 10:04:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mueller/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Could Be In Mueller Report</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/just-a-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 15:21:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/just-a-warning/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick warning. On break from Lenten retreat, but this is bugging me.
Many conservatives are celebrating the Mueller report even though they have no idea what it says.
That&amp;rsquo;s dangerous, as I pointed out in my post on loving Rachel Maddow:
 Finally, we still don’t know the details of the Mueller report. It could contain information that sends conservatives to Twitter to express our rage and anger. We don’t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Should Love Rachel Maddow Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/why-we-should-love-rachel-maddow-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 04:44:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/why-we-should-love-rachel-maddow-now/</guid>
      <description>God gives us so many opportunities to love our enemies. How often do we take him up on those offers?
One of those opportunities to love came to us yesterday. Independent counsel Robert Mueller delivered to the Attorney General his final report on potential crimes involving the 2016 presidential election and the Trump campaign.
The lede of that story was this: no new indictments.
And the left lost their minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Ignore the News</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/04/how-to-ignore-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 15:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/04/how-to-ignore-the-news/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Will Trump survive this?&amp;rdquo;
A friend of mine texted me yesterday. I had no idea what the &amp;ldquo;this&amp;rdquo; was. Later, I learned.
Turns out, like most of the media&amp;rsquo;s breathless revelations about Trump&amp;rsquo;s supposed crimes, the story that people reacted to meant little. The anti-Trump media exploded with fake news, fake interpretations of real news, and speculation that supported their own angry fetishes.
But any reasonable person would respond like my friend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>