<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Independence Day on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/independence-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Independence Day on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 14:06:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/independence-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Declare Independence from Social Media. Do This Instead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/04/declare-independence-from-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 14:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/04/declare-independence-from-social-media/</guid>
      <description>The American Revolution started in a tavern.
Actually, it started in many taverns. But taverns they were.
J.R.R. Tolkien and C.S. Lewis hatched their greatest novels in The Eagle and Child tavern in Oxford.
If you want to be as great as the founding fathers or as prolific as Tolkien and Lewis, get off social media and get to a bar. I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you why.
#1: Social Media Breed Depression and Anxiety The more time you spend on Facebook, the more likely you are to suffer depression, attempt suicide, and feel overwhelmed by life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best We Can Do: Freedom and Independence For America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/03/the-best-we-can-do-freedom-and-independence-for-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 16:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/03/the-best-we-can-do-freedom-and-independence-for-america/</guid>
      <description>Tim Gerrity: We may not always get what we want. We may not always get what we need. Just so&amp;rsquo;s we don&amp;rsquo;t get what we deserve!
 &amp;ndash;True Colors, 1991
Do you ever get the feeling we&amp;rsquo;re getting exactly what we deserve?
 As the Crisis deepens, 13ers will feel little stake in the old order, little sense that their names and signatures are on the social contract. They will have reached full adult maturity without ever having believed in either the American Dream or American exceptionalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Am Skipping Independence Day This Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/04/im-skipping-independence-day-because-we-gave-our-independence-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/04/im-skipping-independence-day-because-we-gave-our-independence-back/</guid>
      <description>July 4th became my favorite holiday in 1981, replacing Christmas. Maybe it was a sign of my maturity.

It was also a sign of the times. After a ten-year hiatus, patriotism was chic again, thanks to Ronald Reagan. Here’s a few other things that made me fall in love with Independence Day:
 * Fireworks—who doesn’t love blowing stuff up? * Parties * VP Fair (tragically renamed to Fair St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You, Harvard</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/02/thank-you-harvard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 14:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/02/thank-you-harvard/</guid>
      <description>A Harvard study recently concluded that attending American Independence Day celebrations could turn kids into Republicans.

The reason 4th of July creates Republicans has nothing to do with patriotism and everything to do with education. Here’s why:
* On July 4th, we celebrate the Declaration of Independence, not the founding of the United States. (That would come with the passage of the Constitution thirteen years later).** July 4th events teach kids—in an environment free from teacher-union propaganda—the _reasons_ we broke from England.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditate on This, Why Don’t You?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/01/meditate-on-this-why-dont-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/01/meditate-on-this-why-dont-you/</guid>
      <description>I was 18 and a college freshman. It was a Tuesday night in October. My 1970 Chevy Impala felt wide open in the fifty-degree air and the smell of freshly fallen leaves.
I drove through Forest Park feeling the rhythm of the yellow street lights as I moved between light and dark. &amp;ldquo;Memory&amp;rdquo; from Cats came on the radio. I lit a Camel (no filter).
I was free.

In America, we often think of independence as a collective thing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>