<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Conservative Heart on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/the-conservative-heart/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Conservative Heart on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 15:29:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/the-conservative-heart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We Tore It Apart—We Can Rebuild It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/01/we-tore-it-apart-we-can-rebuild-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 15:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/01/we-tore-it-apart-we-can-rebuild-it/</guid>
      <description>How will history remember the Tea Party movement of 2009 to 2016? The answer to that question depends on what we do next.
The Tea Party movement was an antagonistic movement. We opposed bad stuff. We sought punishment for bad actors. We saw that the experts were wrong, and we pointed out their folly. Like William F. Buckley&amp;rsquo;s charter for National Review, we stood athwart history, yelling &amp;ldquo;STOP!&amp;rdquo; At its heart, the Tea Party movement opposed a corrupt and insulated establishment class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Liberalism Ruins Black Lives in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/17/how-liberalism-ruins-black-lives-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 04:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/17/how-liberalism-ruins-black-lives-in-america/</guid>
      <description>You probably remember that I love The Conservative Heart by Arthur C. Brooks. I learned so much reading that book, and learning feels great. I read a lot and I&amp;rsquo;m 52-years-old, and I&amp;rsquo;m amazed at how much I didn&amp;rsquo;t know. And it feels so good to learn, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Idle Hands Are the Devil&amp;rsquo;s Workshop One of my favorite stories in The Conservative Heart involves the city of Marienthal, Austria, in the 1930s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whip It. Whip It Good.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/11/whip-it-whip-it-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/10/11/whip-it-whip-it-good/</guid>
      <description>Maybe Ann Wagner&amp;rsquo;s the problem.
Rep. Ann Wagner (HA-64) is the House Majority Whip. Her job is to know how every GOP member will vote on bills and to cut deals until House leadership gets the numbers it wants.
It&amp;rsquo;s unfathomable that a majority whip would not have seen the Kevin McCarthy meltdown coming long before the House Republican caucus met to nominate a candidate for speaker. But many accounts suggest that the Republican House leadership thought McCarthy had the votes up to the moment he withdrew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Welfare Reform Must Continue</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/09/why-welfare-reform-must-continue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 22:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/09/why-welfare-reform-must-continue/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I missed this.
It&amp;rsquo;s the story of Marienthal Austria.
Marienthal was a town in Austria that thrived thanks to a single employer. When the flax mill went out of business in 1932, Marienthal&amp;rsquo;s population became mostly unemployed.
Thanks to Austria&amp;rsquo;s liberal unemployment programs that replaced up to 90 percent of income, no one in Marienthal plunged into economic poverty as a result of the mill&amp;rsquo;s closing. But spiritual poverty was another story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Has a Job To Do</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</guid>
      <description>We believe that meaningful work dignifies and enriches human lives.
[olympus_highlight color=&amp;quot;yellow&amp;rdquo;]Every person who wants to work should find a choice of occupations to pursue. And every occupation improves the life of the person doing the work, the people the work is done for, and the family and community in which the worker lives.[/olympus_highlight]
The more workers engaged in meaningful work, the better our country becomes.
The opposite of work is not idleness but dependency, and dependency degrades human lives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>