<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Better Together on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/better-together/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Better Together on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 13:32:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/better-together/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rex the Libertarian Tyrant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-the-libertarian-tyrrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 13:32:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-the-libertarian-tyrrant/</guid>
      <description>I want to take over the world and leave everybody alone
 &amp;ndash;Libertarian Motto
Rex Sinquefield graduated from Bishop DuBourg High School and he&amp;rsquo;s supposedly something of a libertarian. That&amp;rsquo;s about all we have in common.
Rex left St. Louis and became a billionaire by inventing stock market indexing or something. I went the Navy and still thank God every day that I have roof over my head.
Rex is a brilliant chess strategist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elitists Want to Make St. Louis County More Like Failing City #DontMergeUs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-sinquefields-plan-to-strand-you-on-i-44-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 08:56:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-sinquefields-plan-to-strand-you-on-i-44-forever/</guid>
      <description>This blog post will probably destroy my property value.
Snowstorm Humanitarian Crisis on I-44 Last night, hundreds of people (maybe thousands) were trapped in their cars on I-44 eastbound near Eureka, Missouri for 7, 9, 12 hours. Some even longer. According to police scanners, a baby was born on the highway. It was a humanitarian crisis.
Now, St. Louis billionaire Rex Sinquefield wants to make every aspect of your St. Louis County life a humanitarian crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Can Make Missouri More Like Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/09/we-can-make-missouri-more-like-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 16:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/09/we-can-make-missouri-more-like-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Admit it, Missouri. **You have Illini Envy. **
We all grew up in the shadow of the Lincoln State.
We grew up frustrated that the Black Hawks have won Stanley Cups while the Blues end every season in frustration.
Everybody in the world knows where Chicago is. And that it&amp;rsquo;s in Illinois, the Land of Lincoln. Missouri&amp;rsquo;s a little hit-or-miss on geography quizzes.
But Missourians have a chance to make St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>