<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strategy on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strategy on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 16:22:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Without Power, Principles Are Platitudes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/without-power-principles-are-platitudes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 16:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/without-power-principles-are-platitudes/</guid>
      <description>Without power, principles are platitudes.
Consider this a favor to the Freedom Caucusers. Those folks can&amp;rsquo;t see past the end of their own principles.
Knowing the Freedom Caucus people pretty well, I know they&amp;rsquo;re very happy with Neil Gorsuch for the Supreme Court. I know they&amp;rsquo;d be very miserable if Gorsuch were rejected and Trump had to nominate someone who could win a few Democrat votes.
It&amp;rsquo;s all about power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Psychology of The Inevitable</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/01/the-psychology-of-the-inevitable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 16:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/01/the-psychology-of-the-inevitable/</guid>
      <description>I have no idea who will win the Indiana primary 72 hours from the time I write. But the people inside Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s campaign seem to have an idea. And it&amp;rsquo;s not good for them. Cruz&amp;rsquo;s top team expects their candidate to lose. And Senator Cruz seems to have accepted that outcome.
Expectations Matter More Than Preferences Regular readers know that polls that ask &amp;ldquo;who do you think will win&amp;rdquo; trump polls that ask &amp;ldquo;who do you intend to vote for&amp;rdquo; or even &amp;ldquo;who did you vote for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How a Strategist Looks at the Supreme Court Nomination Battle</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/02/strategist-looks-supreme-court-nomination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 15:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/02/strategist-looks-supreme-court-nomination/</guid>
      <description>In a moment, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look the Supreme Court nomination of Merrick Garland and find the best strategy for Senate Republicans. In a moment. First, let&amp;rsquo;s just relax and think about a party. And pretend you&amp;rsquo;re a paid strategist.
Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View Podcast: [soundcloud url=&amp;quot;https://api.soundcloud.com/tracks/256943967&amp;rdquo; params=&amp;quot;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;100%&amp;rdquo; height=&amp;quot;450&amp;rdquo; iframe=&amp;quot;true&amp;rdquo; /]
Party Now or Party Later?  Tim and Mary Johnson want to have a party for their friends. They&amp;rsquo;ve been talking about it since spring, and now it&amp;rsquo;s nearly winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Can I Possibly Vote for Rick Stream for County Executive?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/30/vote-rick-stream-county-exec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 21:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/30/vote-rick-stream-county-exec/</guid>
      <description>Maybe this logic sucks, but this is my logic. When I vote, I ignore my positions on issues. Instead, I use my vote to advance two objectives:
*1. I want my vote to improve policy towards liberty. *2. I want my vote to maximize my political power.
A simple test that I ask myself is this: If I vote for A, do I expect resulting policy to be more or less to my liking?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What Happens Now That Boehner’s “Plan B” Went Down In Flames</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/21/heres-what-happens-now-that-boehners-plan-b-went-down-in-flames/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 15:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/21/heres-what-happens-now-that-boehners-plan-b-went-down-in-flames/</guid>
      <description>Now that Boehner’s “Plan B” strategy has blown up like a poisoned dog, here’s what Boehner will do.
Remember this chart from last month? It shows strategic options from John Boehner’s point of view:

Yesterday, Boehner tried to land about halfway between the top and bottom quadrant on the left, shown here

Now that Plan B has been rejected, Boehner’s choices are limited to these: * Adjourn and hit the fiscal cliff * Cut a deal that will earn most Democrat votes and enough Republican votes to pass</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If We Don’t Flip Some Toss-Up States, Romney, Ryan, and the USA Are Screwed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</guid>
      <description>Choosing Paul Ryan as his running mate was a great Romney move. Looking ahead, Romney sees movement conservatives working hard right up to the election—even if he or his advisors continues to say stupid things. That was necessary.
SCROLL DOWN FOR TWO IMPORTANT EVENTS THIS WEEK
But it wasn’t enough to win the election and unseat America’s first anti-American president. To do that, we must find a way to win over the selfish middle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>