<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jihad on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jihad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jihad on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 01:45:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jihad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>America is for Americans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/09/america-is-for-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 01:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/09/america-is-for-americans/</guid>
      <description>Dave: You hear from your folks, Mooch? Moocher: Yeah, my dad called. He wanted to know if the house was sold. He could use the money something fierce. Dave: Well, you can come and live with me when it&amp;rsquo;s sold. In Italy, everybody lives together. Moocher: [laughs] Since you won that Italian bike, man, you&amp;rsquo;ve been acting weird. You&amp;rsquo;re really getting to think you&amp;rsquo;re Italian, aren&amp;rsquo;t you? Cyril: I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind thinking I was someone myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loretta Lynch Mob **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/i-could-go-to-jail-for-this-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 18:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/06/i-could-go-to-jail-for-this-post/</guid>
      <description>“I think it’s important that as we again talk about the importance of free speech we make it clear that actions predicated on violent talk are not America,&amp;rdquo; said Lynch. &amp;ldquo;They are not who we are, they are not what we do, and they will be prosecuted.” (source: Daily Wire)
 Take a slide on the slippery slope.
Yesterday I warned that thePC Police will soon call for summary incarceration of anyone who violates the rules of their nationwide “safe space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Us Happy?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-makes-us-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-makes-us-happy/</guid>
      <description>Marc, at Bad Catholic, rocks.
In this post on Obama’s continuing jihad against Christianity, he answers a burning question: did human happiness exist before artificial contraception?
Put another way, is chemical birth control a natural state of humanity?
Before you answer, read the post. Think about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s War on Catholics Has Nothing To Do With Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 00:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/10/obamas-war-on-catholics-has-nothing-to-do-with-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Obama’s dictate that Catholic organizations must participate in contraception and abortion has nothing to do with healthcare or rights or contraception or anything of the sort. Not at all. Modern dictatorships don’t operate that way.
**Obama just destroyed the free practice clause of the First Amendment, and that’s exactly what he intended. **
 Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>