<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>George Washington Bridge on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/george-washington-bridge/</link>
    <description>Recent content in George Washington Bridge on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 01:57:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/george-washington-bridge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What Chris Christie Got Right </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/09/heres-chris-christie-got-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 01:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/09/heres-chris-christie-got-right/</guid>
      <description>I stand by my assessment that Chris Christie&amp;rsquo;s leadership and management played a role in the retaliatory shutdown of Fort Lee&amp;rsquo;s access lanes to the George Washington Bridge. Yesterday,I compared the GWB scandal to several Obama scandals. I pointed out that conservatives must apply the same standards to Christie as we did to Obama when the IRS scandal broke.
Today, let&amp;rsquo;s look at Christie&amp;rsquo;s response and contrast it to Obama&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why &#34;Time for Some Traffic Problems in Fort Lee&#34; Matters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/08/time-traffic-problems-fort-lee-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 03:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/08/time-traffic-problems-fort-lee-matters/</guid>
      <description>One argument put forth by conservatives&amp;ndash;and even some liberals&amp;ndash;regarding the IRS scandal was this:
Obama set a tone that encouraged IRS workers to harass conservative and Tea Party groups. He didn&amp;rsquo;t have to give a direct order. His tone and statements clearly condoned such criminal behavior toward his political enemies.
Kimberly Strassel at WSJ.com:
 Mr. Obama didn&amp;rsquo;t need to pick up the phone. All he needed to do was exactly what he did do, in full view, for three years: Publicly suggest that conservative political groups were engaged in nefarious deeds; publicly call out by name political opponents whom he&amp;rsquo;d like to see harassed; and publicly have his party pressure the IRS to take action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>