<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scalia on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/scalia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scalia on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 01:41:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/scalia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Killing Scalia: The Clinton Crime Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/13/killing-scalia-the-clinton-crime-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/13/killing-scalia-the-clinton-crime-family/</guid>
      <description>Do you think the Clinton Crime Family whacked Antonin Scalia? You will soon if you let yourself read this and all the links. But first, a strange call I had last week.
Something Unrelated At the end of our talk, the reporter said, &amp;ldquo;do you mind if I ask you about something else? It has nothing to do with my article, and I won&amp;rsquo;t write about it.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Uh, sure,&amp;rdquo; I said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Act Like You Learned Something About Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/09/how-to-act-like-you-learned-something-about-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 15:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/09/how-to-act-like-you-learned-something-about-trump/</guid>
      <description>People in the media and the GOP are acting like they learned something on Friday. That&amp;rsquo;s when the Washington Post released an audio (later conjoined with video) of Donald Trump talking lewd about his exploits with women.
I say media people and Republicans are &amp;ldquo;acting&amp;rdquo; like they learned something, because they didn&amp;rsquo;t. We didn&amp;rsquo;t. Everybody who&amp;rsquo;s paid attention to the race (or pop culture) already knew how Trump is. Everybody knows Trump brags about his sexual prowess and how women melt around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suddenly 2012 becomes more relevant than 2016</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/13/suddenly-2012-becomes-more-relevant-than-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/13/suddenly-2012-becomes-more-relevant-than-2016/</guid>
      <description>[Stream of consciousness. Please forgive errors and craziness.]
The human brain is very bad at looking to the future.
It&amp;rsquo;s almost impossible to imagine a living person not being here. We naturally assume the future will be a linear progression of the recent past.
Then one of five conservative Supreme Court justices dies. And everything&amp;rsquo;s thrown into chaos.
We have only eleven months until a new president takes the oath of office.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>