<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fiction on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fiction on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapter Twelve</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/03/civil-war-chapter-twelve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/03/civil-war-chapter-twelve/</guid>
      <description>Roger crashed into his office. His sanctuary. It was only two fifteen, but he wanted a drink. Calls first.
He pulled out is cell phone and decided to call the cop again. But the phone buzzed in his hand before he could find the number.
“Hello,” Roger said.
“Hi, Mr. Thompson? This is Amanda Mateo, one of David’s teachers.”
“Hi. Ms. Mateo. Yeah, we met in August.”
“Oh, yeah, right. Parents’ Night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapter Eight</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/27/civil-war-chapter-eight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 19:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/27/civil-war-chapter-eight/</guid>
      <description>Nancy Flanders sat perfectly still. Amanda Mateo fidgeted and rocked. Between lay a false statement and a pen.
Amanda spoke. “I won’t sign that. I’ll write my own report. I should have spoken to the police yesterday. I’ll write my statement and give it you right now. But I’m not signing that,” pointing toward the statement on the desk.
“That won’t be necessary. I’m afraid I’ll have to place you on suspension until the board reviews your case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapters Six and Seven</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/25/civil-war-chapter-six/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 18:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/25/civil-war-chapter-six/</guid>
      <description>Chapter Six “Evan, this is Roger.”
“How’s it going? Where are you?”
“I’m at home. Listen, I’m going to have to use a sick day today.”
“Everything okay?”
“Not really. It’s a long story. David got beat up pretty bad yesterday at school. In school,” Roger said.
“Well, hell. Sorry to hear that. Don’t worry about anything. I’ve got you covered.”
“Thanks, Evan. Sorry about this.”
“No worries. It’s the slow season anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapters Four and Five</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/23/civil-war-chapters-four-and-five/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 19:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/23/civil-war-chapters-four-and-five/</guid>
      <description>Chapter Four “Elizabeth, tell Amanda I need to see her on her planning hour.”
Nancy Flanders’ assistant, Elizabeth Schneider, nodded her head, scribbled a note, and continued eating her bagel dripping with pineapple cream cheese and strawberry jam.
Flanders returned to her office and closed the door. She sat and snatched the receiver from he desk phone, pressed two numbers, then hung up. She glanced out the window toward the school’s playground then reached for the cell phone on her desk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil War: Chapter Three</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/21/civil-war-chapter-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 19:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/21/civil-war-chapter-three/</guid>
      <description>Roger, David, and Natalie, drove home from the hospital in relative silence. It was already dark at six-thirty. Traffic was still snarled as drivers got used to the end of daylight savings.
When they arrived home, David went to his bedroom and Natalie followed. The post-concussion protocol called for lots of rest, no electronics, and soft lighting. David went straight to bed.
Roger walked into his home office with a glass of whiskey.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>