<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fasting on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/fasting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fasting on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 06:05:56 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/fasting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019: Year of the Fast</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2019-year-of-the-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 06:05:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2019-year-of-the-fast/</guid>
      <description>Fasting is probably the healthiest thing you can do for yourself. It&amp;rsquo;s also the cheapest healthy thing you can do. Unlike most diets and exercise plans, supplements, and, especially, trips to a doctor, fasting actually saves money. When you fast, you don&amp;rsquo;t eat.
Further, fasting is the simplest thing you can do to improve your physical and mental health. There are only two things to remember:
 Don&amp;rsquo;t eat. Drink some water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Fast: Day 14</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/06/primary-fast-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 14:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/06/primary-fast-day-14/</guid>
      <description>You made it. If you began the Fast with me, today is the last day of skipping breakfast and lunch. (Unless you decide to makeone-meal-a-day a permanent habit.)
What Fasting Can Do Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened to you during the fast (if you followed the prescription):
 You probably lost about five pounds. Your pants feel looser. You pull your belt a notch tighter. You saved money. (I saved $98.)  You learned that food is an option most of the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Fasting</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/24/primary-fasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 16:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/24/primary-fasting/</guid>
      <description>I invite you to join a centuries-old tradition: fasting for a cause. Moses and Jesus fasted for 40 days. But this Primary Fast will last only 14. Some fasts require that you eat nothing during the fast. But this Primary Fast lets you eat one full, wonderful meal a day. Did you know that General Stanley McChrystal has lived on just one meal a day for decades. And one meal a day was enough to drive him through the war against al Qaeda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Hold Your Breath for 3 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/29/how-to-hold-your-breath-for-3-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/29/how-to-hold-your-breath-for-3-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Remember when you were a kid? All the weird challenges and contests you&amp;rsquo;d wage with your friends? There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance that breath-holding was one of them. Who can hold their breath the longest, right?
I was always good at this when I was young, but I&amp;rsquo;m not that young anymore. I&amp;rsquo;m 53, but I held my breath for two minutes and 47 seconds last Thursday. And I could have gone longer, but I was bored.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>