<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2013 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2013/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2013 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2013 Will Go Down As A Very Weird Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/30/2013-will-go-weird-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 10:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/30/2013-will-go-weird-year/</guid>
      <description>The other one was 1975. At least in my lifetime.
1975 was weird for good reasons and bad. Saturday Night Live debuted with the Not Ready For Prime Time Players: Dan Akroyd, John Belushi, Chevy Chase, Jane Curtain, Gilda Radner, and Garrett Morris. President Gerald Ford tried to stop inflation with WIN buttons (seriously). New York City faced bankruptcy, but, after initially saying &amp;lsquo;drop dead,&amp;rsquo; Gerry Ford ended up bailing it out with $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Progressives and New Yorkers Should Fear Bill de Blasio</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/26/progressives-new-yorkers-fear-bill-de-blasio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 21:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/26/progressives-new-yorkers-fear-bill-de-blasio/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered why moments end?
I wrote about the Irish Moment and the Jewish Moment and the Gay Moment on Saturday. Three Moments enjoyed by identifiable groups of Americans. Moments that ended when the groups joined the main plot of the American story, leaving the artistic sub-plot to the next in line.
Demographics offer only one kind of Moment, though. There are cultural moments and fashion moments and, of course, political moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Christmas 2013 Is The Most Important Christmas Ever</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/25/christmas-2013-important-christmas-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 17:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/25/christmas-2013-important-christmas-ever/</guid>
      <description>The only Christmas I remember getting everything I wanted was in 1975.
First, I was finally old enough (12) to not be so shallow and needy and get pissed off if I didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly what I wanted. Santa Claus and my parents and sisters were really good to me, but until 1975 I could still get worked up if the Erector Set I got wasn&amp;rsquo;t the 118-piece set with real electric motor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/25/merry-christmas-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 16:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/25/merry-christmas-4/</guid>
      <description>H/T Bob the retiree
Trying to keep the old Christian virtues in check on Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This I know to be true</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/25/this-is-all-i-know-to-be-true/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 16:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/12/25/this-is-all-i-know-to-be-true/</guid>
      <description>The vices are, indeed, let loose, and they wander and do damage. But the virtues are let loose also; and the virtues wander more wildly, and the virtues do more terrible damage. The modern world is full of the old Christian virtues gone mad. The virtues have gone mad because they have been isolated from each other and are wandering alone. Thus some scientists care for truth; and their truth is pitiless.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>