<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>irs on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/irs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in irs on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 01:30:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/irs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Not All Lies Are Meant To Fool</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/26/lies-meant-fool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 01:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/26/lies-meant-fool/</guid>
      <description>What line of work was Tony Soprano in? 
Waste management.
Did Tony Soprano expect people to believe he was in waste management?
No. Tony Soprano expected people realize he was a wise guy and treat him with due respect&amp;ndash;or what you and I call fear.
Some lies are meant to make the liar seem more successful or more talented or better than he thinks he is. Trust me, I&amp;rsquo;ve done it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Were No Rogue Agents In the IRS Scandal</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/05/18/there-were-no-rogue-agents-in-the-irs-scandal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2013 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/05/18/there-were-no-rogue-agents-in-the-irs-scandal/</guid>
      <description>They were all looking at me. Staring, actually.
I looked around the silent sales room. No one blinked. They were all stunned.
For twenty minutes, I&amp;rsquo;d laid on a coating of bullshit that would have made Bill Clinton cringe. And it worked. I sold a year of lawn care to a woman who, at first, thought our service was an environmental menace.
&amp;ldquo;Do you know Dr. Peter Raven?&amp;rdquo; I asked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wait ‘til These Kids Meet the Tax Man</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/08/wait-til-these-kids-meet-the-tax-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 14:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/08/wait-til-these-kids-meet-the-tax-man/</guid>
      <description>When the rules become so complicated and convoluted that well-meaning people unwittingly break the law, the legal system has lost its moral authority.
Students at Georgetown University are discovering the horrors of, what Tocqueville called “small complicated rules, minute and uniform, through which the most original minds and the most energetic characters cannot penetrate, to rise above the crowd.”
An editorial in The Hoya, the official student newspaper, students advocate “eliminating bureaucracy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>