<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Your President Trump: Season Six</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-season-six/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:18:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-season-six/</guid>
      <description>Scott Adams says Donald Trump lives his life like a movie or television series. (See Looking Ahead to Season Four of Trump for a complete explanation.) Being New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, it&amp;rsquo;s time to look back on Season Five (2019) and, then, look ahead to season six (2020) of Trump.
Season Five: Mueller Report and Ukraine Hoax Going into 2019, the Fed had slowed the incredible Trump Economy with aggressive interest rate hikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s About the Destination, Not the Journey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/destination-not-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 07:05:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/destination-not-journey/</guid>
      <description>Jerry Garcia Was Wrong
Jerry Garcia of Grateful Dead was famous for saying &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s about the journey, not the destination.&amp;rdquo;
Garcia was wrong.
There are two possible destinations:
 Eternal perfection. Eternal misery.  It&amp;rsquo;s all about the destination. The destination is all that matters.
The journey matters only insofar as it determines the destination. If you know and pursue the right destination, the journey will be difficult, often painful, often lonely, often frustrating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God&#39;s Law or Mans Law</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/gods-law-or-mans-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 19:54:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/gods-law-or-mans-law/</guid>
      <description>A celebrity priest fired up Twitter today by endorsing same-sex &amp;ldquo;marriage&amp;rdquo; and by comparing a same-sex couple favorably to the Holy Family.
Let&amp;rsquo;s assume that the good father is not malicious but so poorly educated into reason and Church teaching that his embarrassing tweets make sense to him. Let&amp;rsquo;s pretend Fr. Sichko thinks he&amp;rsquo;s right.
To help educate the ignorant priest (and educating the ignorant is one of our Christian duties), I&amp;rsquo;ll pose some questions to Fr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Showers and Confession</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/cold-showers-and-confession/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 12:25:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/cold-showers-and-confession/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;There’s no point at which you’ve cleaned yourself so well that you never have to shower again.&amp;rdquo;
 —Eric Greitens, Resilience: Hard-Won Wisdom for Living a Better Life&amp;rdquo;
   &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t walk my dog anymore.&amp;rdquo; I walked him all at once.
 — Comedian Steven Wright
   &amp;ldquo;Get in line in that processional / climb into that small confessional / there the guy who&amp;rsquo;s got religion&amp;rsquo;ll / tell you if your sin&amp;rsquo;s original&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Demons Fear the Woman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/why-do-demons-fear-the-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 09:29:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/why-do-demons-fear-the-woman/</guid>
      <description>A Frenchman named Michel Chiron was possessed by demons for decades. His story of exorcism revealed something remarkable.
In an interview with Solène Tadié for National Catholic Register, Chiron said the demons possessing him mocked Jesus but feared &amp;ldquo;The Woman.&amp;rdquo;
About Jesus:
 They told me he did exist in the past but that he should be forgotten, as nowadays human beings no longer needed him. They even said that he was with their king now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Is a Styrofoam Bird</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/impeachment-and-styrofoam-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 13:16:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/impeachment-and-styrofoam-bird/</guid>
      <description>This post is about impeachment. But, first, you need to hear about a toy bird from the 1970s.
Disappointing Toys When I was seven or eight, I just had to have a Zorr: The Mighty Eagle.
Zorr could soar on the wind for hours, just like a real eagle. The TV commercials left me certain that Zorr would make the most popular kid on my block—maybe the whole parish. I&amp;rsquo;d have a pet eagle, really.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IG Report: Obama Out-Dicked Nixon</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/ig-report-obama-out-dicked-nixon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:47:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/ig-report-obama-out-dicked-nixon/</guid>
      <description>IG Report: Obama Out-Dicked Nixon
Nixon resigned. He resigned after a half-dozen Republican Senators told him, in the Oval Office, that a majority of Senators would vote to remove him from office if the House impeached him.
So Nixon resigned.
Nixon&amp;rsquo;s crimes were limited to covering up a break-in and wiretapping by employees of his re-election committee.
Baraka Obama did worse. And he got by.
Obama out-dicked Nixon.
The IG Report Department of Justice Inspector-General Michael Horowitz released his report on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thatcher Reagan Boris Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/thatcher-reagan-boris-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 22:58:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/thatcher-reagan-boris-trump/</guid>
      <description>Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s Tories will win their biggest victory since Margaret Thatcher. Maybe bigger than Thatcher&amp;rsquo;s. Praise God!
(This will be very short.)
The conservative tide continues. People around the world are fed up with the failed ideas of the 1960s and 1970s. Maybe it was nostalgia that drove world leaders to dig up all the political crap I remember from my childhood. It failed then, and it&amp;rsquo;s failing us now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do Democrats Expect?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/what-do-democrats-expect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 18:50:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/what-do-democrats-expect/</guid>
      <description>If Democrats cross the Rubicon by impeaching President Trump, they will be sending a strong signal: no Republican president will ever survive his first term.
How do you expect people to respond? I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the people President Obama derisively labeled &amp;ldquo;bitter clingers.&amp;rdquo;
  The people RealPolitics data analyst Sean Trende identified as &amp;ldquo;downscale, Northern, rural &amp;hellip; H. Ross Perot voters.&amp;rdquo;
Or, to put it another way, Tea Partiers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Deplatform Twitter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/how-to-deplatform-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 19:53:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/how-to-deplatform-twitter/</guid>
      <description>You can deplatform Twitter and damage their business model. You don&amp;rsquo;t need money or special skills or lawyers. But deplatforming Twitter requires two things:
 Commitment. Friends.  Friends can be strangers, as long as they use Twitter. Twitter followers are perfect friends for this action.
What Is &amp;ldquo;Deplatforming&amp;rdquo; and Why Should We Do It? Deplatforming is one of these new words that irritate me. But new words have the virtue of universality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazonium Pandamonium</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/amazonium-pandamonium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 11:41:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/amazonium-pandamonium/</guid>
      <description>Jesus said to him: Thou shalt love the Lord thy God with thy whole heart, and with thy whole soul, and with thy whole mind. This is the greatest and the first commandment. (Matthew 22:37-38)
 My Protestant friends were angry at the goings on at the Amazon Synod.
It&amp;rsquo;s not unusual for some Protestants to disagree with the Catholic Church. After all, that&amp;rsquo;s what makes them &amp;ldquo;protestants.&amp;rdquo; What is unusual is why the Protestants are upset at the Church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Im Not Good Enough for the New Church</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/im-not-good-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 10:58:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/im-not-good-enough/</guid>
      <description>Call me &amp;ldquo;rigid.&amp;rdquo;
Last night, I saw a tweet that broke my heart.
A woman wrote that her husband told her he was going to Mass after work. But he went to a bar, instead. She went to the bar. He was there. He was drunk.
She asked for our prayers.
I said one for her, and two for her husband.
The woman is a traditional Catholic, like me. Or what the Holy Father calls &amp;ldquo;rigid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Me October 13 at the Arch</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/join-me-october-13-at-the-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 12:46:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/join-me-october-13-at-the-arch/</guid>
      <description>Rosary Coast-to-Coast at the Arch in St. Louis We are in a spiritual battle for America&amp;rsquo;s soul, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been fighting it all wrong.
Politics is important. Christians should engage. But politics isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. And politics isn&amp;rsquo;t first.
 &amp;ldquo;For our wrestling is not against flesh and blood; but against principalities and power, against the rulers of the world of this darkness, against the spirits of wickedness in the high places&amp;rdquo; Ephesians 6:12</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rigid vs Squishy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rigid-vs-squishy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 10:15:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rigid-vs-squishy/</guid>
      <description>The opposites of &amp;ldquo;rigid&amp;rdquo; are more unflattering than rigidity:
 lenient indulgent broken compromising easy imprecise indefinite inexact irresolute unfixed unreliable accommodating liberal permissive resigned soft-hearted
 And that&amp;rsquo;s the problem with name-calling. When we impose a derogatory label on someone, we invite scrutiny upon ourselves. We label ourselves as the opposite of the names we impose on others.
Some of us are better at name-calling, or &amp;ldquo;labelling,&amp;rdquo; than others. Donald Trump does a lot of labeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All (political) Problems Are Demonic in Nature</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/all-problems-are-demonic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 17:32:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/all-problems-are-demonic/</guid>
      <description>A friend commented on a recent blog of mine that he misses my political analysis. So I need to make this clear: my political analysis is that all problems in the world are demonic in nature.
I&amp;rsquo;ll write that again so no one&amp;rsquo;s confused: all problems, including all political problems, are demonic. Stop inviting Satan and the demons out of the abyss God made for them, and problems go away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Be Unpopular</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/how-to-be-unpopular/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 06:33:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/how-to-be-unpopular/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to write a book called How to Lose Friends and Alienate People. But nobody reads autobiographies anymore. So I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how to be unpopular, instead.
Being unpopular is pretty easy. And it&amp;rsquo;s hard, too. It&amp;rsquo;s easy because there&amp;rsquo;s only one rule, which we&amp;rsquo;ll get to in a moment. It&amp;rsquo;s hard for two reasons: beforehand, it&amp;rsquo;s scary to think about following the rule. Afterwards, it&amp;rsquo;s lonely and painful to have followed the rule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need Prayers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/we-need-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 20:41:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/we-need-prayers/</guid>
      <description>Please spread the word. Tweet this. Post to Facebook. If you&amp;rsquo;re Catholic, please forward to your parish office and ask for a blurb in the Sunday bulletin.
Our nation, the Catcholic Church, and the whole world needs prayer. Why? Just read this post.
St. Padre Pio&amp;rsquo;s respond to problems was, &amp;ldquo;Bring me my weapon!&amp;rdquo; His weapon was his Holy Rosary. He prayed the Rosary to combat sin and evil. And it worked!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Post From Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/last-post-from-hennessys-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 11:11:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/last-post-from-hennessys-view/</guid>
      <description>Cross-posted to stlouisteaparty.com
Ten years of syndicating my blog Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View on stlouisteaparty.com comes to an end with this post.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to continue receiving emails when I write, please subscribe to Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View daily updates.
Readers of the Tea Party site have noticed that I rarely write about politics any longer. They&amp;rsquo;re right. I don&amp;rsquo;t. They&amp;rsquo;ve asked me to stop posting my Catholic faith blogs to the Tea Party site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosary Coast-to-Coast Gateway Arch October 13</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rosary-coast-to-coast-gateway-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 20:55:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rosary-coast-to-coast-gateway-arch/</guid>
      <description>Join THOUSANDS of faithful Catholics just like you October 13, 2019, at 3:00 p.m.
Pray for America and the Church.
PLAN  2:30 PM: Opening prayers and sermon by Msgr. Eugene Morris 3:00 PM: The Glorious Mysteries 3:30 PM: Benediction and dismissal  Now, read why we&amp;rsquo;re doing this, via Rosary Coast-to-Coast:
Awesome Video   Awesome Narrative  In 2018 over 1,200 Rosary Rallies across the U.S. and over 50 participating countries!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Whom Is Bishop Barron Angry?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/glad-to-know-bishop-barron-is-angry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 20:19:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/glad-to-know-bishop-barron-is-angry/</guid>
      <description>I was gladdened to see Bishop Robert Barron&amp;rsquo;s tweets of anger about the Pew survey. Watch the attached video. (You will also be happy to hear the Pew survey didn&amp;rsquo;t shock the bishop.)
I wish, though, his excellency had addressed the real cause of Catholics losing their faith: the ugly and sacrilegious farce that is the Novus Ordo (or Ordinary Form) Mass.
Here&amp;rsquo;s Bishop Barron&amp;rsquo;s initial tweet. I urge you to watch the video attached.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Lawrence of Rome</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/st-lawrence-of-rome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 04:39:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/st-lawrence-of-rome/</guid>
      <description>St. Lawrence of Rome is the patron saint of comedians. I had no idea there was one. But there is, and it&amp;rsquo;s St. Lawrence. He earned that designation for his obstinate and comedic refusal to deny Christ, even to his death.
From The Catholic Company:
 He was appointed by Pope St. Sixtus II as archdeacon over the seven deacons of Rome, and held the sacred duty of tending to the Church&amp;rsquo;s wealth and distributing alms to the poor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Trust Father Don Draper</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/most-catholics-arent-catholic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 17:32:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/most-catholics-arent-catholic/</guid>
      <description>This was one of my favorite episodes of Mad Men.
  The post-Vatican II Church epitomizes Don Draper&amp;rsquo;s very accurate definition of advertising. &amp;ldquo;Whatever you&amp;rsquo;re doing . . . it&amp;rsquo;s okay. You&amp;rsquo;re okay.&amp;rdquo;
I&amp;rsquo;m Not Okay; You&amp;rsquo;re Not Okay It&amp;rsquo;s likely yesterday&amp;rsquo;s screed offended some people. Let me tell you where it came from.
A Pew survey found that most Catholics don&amp;rsquo;t believe things they are required to believe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Least They Go</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/at-least-they-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 20:17:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/at-least-they-go/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Well,&amp;rdquo; said the priest, &amp;ldquo;at least they go.&amp;rdquo;
By &amp;ldquo;go,&amp;rdquo; he was referring to Mass.
By &amp;ldquo;they,&amp;rdquo; he meant the people who dress like tramps, talk and laugh through Mass, and know nothing about the Church&amp;rsquo;s teachings. People who are pro-abortion, pro-gay marriage, and pro-women priests.
&amp;ldquo;At least they go.&amp;rdquo;
Lex Orandi, Lex Credendi The law of prayer is the law of belief.
&amp;ldquo;At least they go&amp;rdquo; would be a legit argument IF what they &amp;ldquo;went to&amp;rdquo; left no doubt about what they were participating in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mass Killings Are the Fruit of Modernism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/mass-killings-are-the-fruit-of-modernism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 09:53:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/mass-killings-are-the-fruit-of-modernism/</guid>
      <description>Simple minds seek simple answers.
A man kills innocents with a gun, and the simple mind blames the gun. When a dog sees an approaching shadow, he attacks his tail.
Mass Killings Are Modernism In Action Modernism leads us to simple, but wrong, answers. Modernists have one solution for all problems: consolidate all freedom, all power, all decisions, all goods, all authority, and all thinking into the hands of a few omnipotent men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lousy Bishops</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/lousy-bishops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 19:56:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/lousy-bishops/</guid>
      <description>(Disclosure: I am a traditional Catholic.)
Did you know that for every person who enters the Catholic Church in America six leave? It looks like this:
   Incoming Catholics Outgoing Catholics     1 6    Why?
Simple answers are often problematic, but one answer seems obvious: Catholic leadership sucks. The Church in America offers nothing larger or more significant than the paltry pleasures of television and Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What About False Prophets (and Kooks)?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/what-about-false-prophets-and-kooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 07:48:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/what-about-false-prophets-and-kooks/</guid>
      <description>A prophet is someone who has the gift of recognizing how current behaviors, beliefs, and trends will bring calamity in the future. Prophets tell us what not to do, and predict the dire consequences that will befall us if we don&amp;rsquo;t listen.
And we don&amp;rsquo;t listen.
Yesterday, we looked at three reasons people don&amp;rsquo;t listen:
 The Semmelweis Reflex, which says people reject information that contradicts longstanding beliefs. The Power of the Status Quo, which says people believe the future will always be a linear progression of the recent past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mueller Prophecy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/the-mueller-prophecy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 19:57:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/the-mueller-prophecy/</guid>
      <description>Friends,
Let me begin by saying &amp;ldquo;I am sorry&amp;rdquo; to Robert Mueller and his family.
I have been critical of Mr. Mueller and his sham &amp;ldquo;investigation.&amp;rdquo; I have been uncharitable to him. And I am sorry.
It became clear today that Mr. Mueller wasn&amp;rsquo;t a hostile actor. Obviously, Mueller is seriously impaired. What we saw in his selection of lawyers, in his handling of the investigation, in his management of partisan and criminal conduct by senior Justice Department officials under his command resulted not from malice toward the president but from incompetence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Don&#39;t Believe Prophets</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/why-we-dont-believe-prophets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 08:11:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/why-we-dont-believe-prophets/</guid>
      <description>Q: What was the epitaph on the hypochondriac&amp;rsquo;s tombstone?
A: &amp;ldquo;I told you I was sick!&amp;rdquo;
 I happened to see a Facebook post from the George Gilder today. The post announced why Gilder is coming out of retirement at age 79.
(I rarely look at Facebook, but there&amp;rsquo;s flooding in my town today. Facebook is the best source for reports from the ground.)
I followed George Gilder closely for many years back in the mid-1990s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Tweets Trigger Word-Thinkers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-triggers-word-thinkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 15:37:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/trump-triggers-word-thinkers/</guid>
      <description>For a few weeks in June and July, Nancy Pelosi was doing a good job of isolating the Hate Squad. Pelosi realizes that the Hate Squad is bad for Democrats. She saw the Hate Squad growing in media attention, and she worked hard to stop that trend.
Then, like a genius, Donald Trump did what Trump does best: he stuck out his chin to let his opponent (Pelosi) punch herself out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please Subscribe Before Twitter Bans Me</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-20-please-subscribe-before-twitter-bans-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 23:36:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-20-please-subscribe-before-twitter-bans-me/</guid>
      <description>If you like reading this blog, please click the Subscribe link at the top. Enter your email address, and you&amp;rsquo;ll get one email a day at most.
Twitter and Facebook and Google are trying to remove all conservatives from their social media platforms. So many people come to this blog by clicking links on those platforms, I&amp;rsquo;m afraid you will never know when I&amp;rsquo;m posting unless you subscribe now.
I&amp;rsquo;ll try to keep you informed and entertained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do We Love The World?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-20-do-we-love-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 13:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-20-do-we-love-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Should Christians love this world?
A Catholic parish has, as part of its mission statement, &amp;ldquo;we love this world.&amp;rdquo;
Does this bother anyone? Besides me, I mean.
I Googled the whole phrase, and here are the top 5 results:
 Do Not Love the World What Does It Mean to &amp;ldquo;Love not the things of the world?&amp;rdquo; What does it mean that we are not to love the world? Love Not the World 1 John 2:15 Do not love the world or anything in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Spy&#39;s Guide to Taking Risks: A Book You Need to Read</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-19-a-spys-guide-to-taking-risks-a-book-you-need-to-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 23:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-19-a-spys-guide-to-taking-risks-a-book-you-need-to-read/</guid>
      <description>Imagine yourself in a foreign country with a fake passport, a fake name, a fake cover story, and mission to make it home with stolen, top secret documents from that country&amp;rsquo;s government.
Now, imagine it&amp;rsquo;s the first time you&amp;rsquo;ve ever done this.
That&amp;rsquo;s how John Braddock begins his third book, A Spy&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Taking Risks. With the story of his first mission as an alias.
In his previous books, A Spy&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Thinking and A Spy&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Strategy, Braddock, a retired CIA Field Officer, provided readers with top-notch spy stories and top-shelf tools for success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very Bad Week for Planned Parenthood</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-18-a-very-bad-week-for-planned-parenthood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 17:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-18-a-very-bad-week-for-planned-parenthood/</guid>
      <description>The abortion company fires its CEOs as sloppily as it delivers &amp;ldquo;healthcare.&amp;rdquo;
Before that, the Trump Administration successfully cut some of Planned Parenthood&amp;rsquo;s federal funding, which may have precipitated the decapitation of its management team.
And, today, Planned Parenthood&amp;rsquo;s hand-picked judge tentatively ruled in complete favor with the journalist the company is suing.
Aborting Dr. Wen On Wednesday, Planned Parenthood clumsily fired Dr. Leana Wen as its chief executive. I guess you could call it a late-term firing, since Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, President Trump Will Win Re-election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-17-yes-president-trump-will-win-re-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/2019-07-17-yes-president-trump-will-win-re-election/</guid>
      <description>New York Times columnist Thomas Friedman today asked a rhetorical question: Trump&amp;rsquo;s Going to Get Re-elected, Isn&amp;rsquo;t He?
The headline reflects the question he hears from his Democrat friends. They seem resigned to defeat. And the answer is: Yes. President Trump will win re-election in 2020.
The reasons Trump will get re-elected:
  The Hate Squad. Four radical communist freshmen Representatives are the face of the new Democrat party. They are anti-Semitic, anti-Christian, and anti-American.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easter and the Mueller Report</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/easter-and-the-mueller-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 10:04:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/easter-and-the-mueller-report/</guid>
      <description>I write this on Easter Sunday, 2019, and the secular world, particularly the anti-Christian secular world, is losing its mind again.
This time, the left&amp;rsquo;s insanity arises from the final report of the special investigator, Robert Mueller, into alleged crimes committed by the presidential campaign of Donald Trump in 2015 and 2016.
Amazingly, what we are seeing in the reaction to that Mueller report was seen by an early father of the Church, St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mass by the Numbers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/new-mass-by-the-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 10:34:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/new-mass-by-the-numbers/</guid>
      <description>I prefer the Latin Mass of 1962 (and a thousand years before) for at least 12 reasons listed here. My last reason for loving the Latin Mass (which I failed to list in that blog post) seems important: how American Catholicism has changed since the inception of the new mass in about 1970. So I turned to Georgetown University&amp;rsquo;s Center for Applied Research in the Apostalate for the numbers.
Catholicism is dying in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea, Meet Stoicism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/chelsea-meet-stoicism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 19:29:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/chelsea-meet-stoicism/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s triumph in the 2016 election drove Chelsea Handler into a depraved descent. Weed and depression. Psychiatrists. Broken.
Not because of anything that happened to her. She didn&amp;rsquo;t lose her home. No one close to her died because of the election.
Chelsea Handler lost her mind because reality violated her expectations.
I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Ms. Handler doesn&amp;rsquo;t read Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View, but you do. So, for you, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how to avoid losing your mind when reality violates your expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rex the Libertarian Tyrant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-the-libertarian-tyrrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 13:32:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-the-libertarian-tyrrant/</guid>
      <description>I want to take over the world and leave everybody alone
 &amp;ndash;Libertarian Motto
Rex Sinquefield graduated from Bishop DuBourg High School and he&amp;rsquo;s supposedly something of a libertarian. That&amp;rsquo;s about all we have in common.
Rex left St. Louis and became a billionaire by inventing stock market indexing or something. I went the Navy and still thank God every day that I have roof over my head.
Rex is a brilliant chess strategist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Reasons I Love Latin Mass</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/12-reasons-i-love-latin-mass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 03:43:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/12-reasons-i-love-latin-mass/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been going to Latin Mass instead of the new mass. Latin Mass feels like home to me. It feels like a call to holiness. Every detail of the Latin Mass has meaning, not just to me, but to everyone who&amp;rsquo;s studied scripture. The words, the gestures, the artifacts like the communion rail all have deep meaning. I don&amp;rsquo;t think the new mass is heretical; I just don&amp;rsquo;t think it lifts us up toward God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>90 Days</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/90-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 03:43:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/90-days/</guid>
      <description>I stopped drinking for 90 days Many of you know I enjoy the occasional (hurrumph) adult beverage. You might be curious about my experiences during long periods of abstinence.
I&amp;rsquo;m doing Exodus 90. My exodus began January 21 and ends Easter Sunday, April 21.
Exodus 90 is Catholic thing. It challenges men to escape from the slavery of this world through prayer, asceticism, and fraternity. The asceticism includes abstaining from drinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Could Be In Mueller Report</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/just-a-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 15:21:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/just-a-warning/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick warning. On break from Lenten retreat, but this is bugging me.
Many conservatives are celebrating the Mueller report even though they have no idea what it says.
That&amp;rsquo;s dangerous, as I pointed out in my post on loving Rachel Maddow:
 Finally, we still don’t know the details of the Mueller report. It could contain information that sends conservatives to Twitter to express our rage and anger. We don’t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Should Love Rachel Maddow Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/why-we-should-love-rachel-maddow-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 04:44:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/why-we-should-love-rachel-maddow-now/</guid>
      <description>God gives us so many opportunities to love our enemies. How often do we take him up on those offers?
One of those opportunities to love came to us yesterday. Independent counsel Robert Mueller delivered to the Attorney General his final report on potential crimes involving the 2016 presidential election and the Trump campaign.
The lede of that story was this: no new indictments.
And the left lost their minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Love Is to Will</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/love-is-an-act-of-will/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 06:41:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/love-is-an-act-of-will/</guid>
      <description>Tina Turner not withstanding, love is not an emotion, and that&amp;rsquo;s a good thing.
In today&amp;rsquo;s Gospel (from the modern lectionary), Jesus tells his disciples to &amp;ldquo;love your enemies&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;pray for those who persecute you.&amp;rdquo;
But how? I find it difficult even to be around certain people, much less love them. Surely, Jesus wasn&amp;rsquo;t serious when He told us to love our enemies, right? If Jesus meant what He said, then I must not know what love means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go to Caracas and Say a Rosary</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/go-to-caracas-and-say-a-rosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 07:16:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/go-to-caracas-and-say-a-rosary/</guid>
      <description>Down in the world&amp;rsquo;s newest socialist &amp;ldquo;paradise,&amp;rdquo; the longest blackout in decades has struck Venezuela. The country has been without power for at least 4 days. That&amp;rsquo;s how socialism works.
The constitutional president, Juan Guaido, has called on Venezuelans to pour into the capital city of Caracas to demand the communist dictator Madura surrender. Guaido correctly points out that Maduro&amp;rsquo;s socialism caused the problem.
Guaido&amp;rsquo;s call is great, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go far enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fasting Is a Good Spring Cleaning for the Soul</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/spring-cleaning-for-the-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 07:24:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/spring-cleaning-for-the-soul/</guid>
      <description>My heart and soul needed a good spring cleaning, and Lent arrived just in time.
Lent is fasting season. Most people know what fasting is, but many people don&amp;rsquo;t know what religious fasting is for. What good does fasting do the soul?
Fasting is form of asceticism. That means intentionally depriving yourself of some comfort or sensual pleasure. Asceticism does not require pain or self-flagellation. Self-flagellation tends to lead to pride and should be avoided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I thought this prophetic post was too crazy to publish</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/too-crazy-to-publish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 18:26:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/too-crazy-to-publish/</guid>
      <description>In a blog I never published for fear of being thought insane, I conveyed a prophecy:
 Many Christians will be accused of crimes against the state for simply following Christ&amp;rsquo;s teachings and believing that Jesus is our lord and savior. When you are accused and at trial, the Holy Spirit will speak through you if you let Him. You won&amp;rsquo;t need to come up with your own defense. Anyone might betray you and cause you to be put to death, even your parents or your children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Forward to Lent</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/looking-forward-to-lent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 06:37:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/looking-forward-to-lent/</guid>
      <description>I have never looked forward to the start of Lent.
Lent is a time of repentance and atonement in anticipation of the commemoration of the passion, death, and resurrection of Christ Jesus. The whole idea of repentance and atonement always bothered me.
Until now.
This year, I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for Lent to begin.
First, I&amp;rsquo;ve been called to redirect my zeal away from politics and toward God. Instead of bringing people into communion with the Constitution and liberty, I&amp;rsquo;m asked to bring people to Christ and Christ to people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elitists Want to Make St. Louis County More Like Failing City #DontMergeUs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-sinquefields-plan-to-strand-you-on-i-44-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 08:56:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rex-sinquefields-plan-to-strand-you-on-i-44-forever/</guid>
      <description>This blog post will probably destroy my property value.
Snowstorm Humanitarian Crisis on I-44 Last night, hundreds of people (maybe thousands) were trapped in their cars on I-44 eastbound near Eureka, Missouri for 7, 9, 12 hours. Some even longer. According to police scanners, a baby was born on the highway. It was a humanitarian crisis.
Now, St. Louis billionaire Rex Sinquefield wants to make every aspect of your St. Louis County life a humanitarian crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations Representative Dottie Bailey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/congratulations-representative-dottie-bailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 07:42:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/congratulations-representative-dottie-bailey/</guid>
      <description>The one who has the bride is the bridegroom; the best man, who stands and listens for him, rejoices greatly at the bridegroom’s voice. So this joy of mine has been made complete. (Johhn 3:29)
 Yesterday, January 9, 2019, was a watershed day for everyone who ever associated with the St. Louis Tea Party Coalition. Your own Dottie Bailey was sworn in as Representative of the 110th State House district of Eureka, Wildwood, and Pacific.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Praying for Those Who Persecute Us</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/praying-for-those-who-persecute-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 08:37:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/praying-for-those-who-persecute-us/</guid>
      <description>You might have read the post A Fourth Turning Warning. If you did, you&amp;rsquo;re probably wondering if I&amp;rsquo;ve lost mind. If you conclude I have not lost my mind, you probably wonder why I&amp;rsquo;d run from the fight. So I should probably address that.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start, as we should always, with the Word. In this case, the Book of Matthew 5:43-45:
 &amp;ldquo;You have heard that is was said, &amp;lsquo;You shall love your neighbor and hate your enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fourth Turning Warning for America: Climax</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/a-fourth-turning-warning-for-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 06:16:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/a-fourth-turning-warning-for-america/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I warned, again, that the center didn&amp;rsquo;t hold. There is no center in American politics. Americans are more divided than at any time since the Civil War.
(Read We Have the War Upon Us by William J. Cooper)
Today, I have a short warning from the great book The Fourth Turning by Howe and Strauss.
What Should Have Happened after 2016 Strauss and Howe prophesied an election that changed everything sometime during the Crisis era which began with the fall of Lehman Brothers (the last time Nancy Pelosi was Speaker of the House):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romney Doesn&#39;t Get It: Flanders Fields</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/romney-doesnt-get-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 20:23:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/romney-doesnt-get-it/</guid>
      <description>Mitt Romney&amp;rsquo;s naïveté is almost cute. He thinks it&amp;rsquo;s still 1982.
But it&amp;rsquo;s not cute because it&amp;rsquo;s destructive. The world has changed, and everything is ready to fall apart.
See, Mitt is mad that President Donald Trump hasn&amp;rsquo;t done more to &amp;ldquo;unite&amp;rdquo; the country. Mittens wants the president to be more &amp;ldquo;unifying.&amp;rdquo;
Because &amp;ldquo;trying&amp;rdquo; to unite the country would solve everything, right?
But the world has changed. Americans today are as polarized as they were 1861.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>