<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bureaucrats on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/bureaucrats/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bureaucrats on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 21:31:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/bureaucrats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bureaucratizing Street Gangs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/26/bureaucratizing-street-gangs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/26/bureaucratizing-street-gangs/</guid>
      <description>Did you ever wonder why do-gooders and social planners never pay for their crimes?
Yesterday, I wrote about Jesse Jackson dressing down at the hands of activists in a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s parking lot in Ferguson. I pointed out that Martin Luther King and Dick Gregory were similarly dismissed by rioters in the 1960s. Some things never change.
One thing that has changed is the economic gap between whites and blacks. That&amp;rsquo;s gotten worse despite trillions in federal poverty programs that went mostly to &amp;ldquo;community organizing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What Robin Carnahan Doesn’t Want You Know About Proposition E</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/17/heres-what-robin-carnahan-doesnt-want-you-know-about-proposition-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 23:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/17/heres-what-robin-carnahan-doesnt-want-you-know-about-proposition-e/</guid>
      <description>Robin Carnahan, the Democrat Missouri Secretary of State, writes ballot language like the editorial page editor of the Post-Dispatch.

Carnahan wrote, perhaps, the most biased and unprofessional ballot initiative ever written regarding Proposition E. She wanted you to think that Proposition E would outlaw all insurance in the state of Missouri and compel pet owners to feed rat poison to their animals. Here’s the original ballot language Carnahan wrote:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>