<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>conservative on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/conservative/</link>
    <description>Recent content in conservative on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 22:02:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/conservative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Surface thinking, deep thinking</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/17/surface-thinking-deep-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 22:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/17/surface-thinking-deep-thinking/</guid>
      <description>How people responded to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post, Maybe he&amp;rsquo;s not a conservative, varied. But there were two dominant types.
Surface thinkers ignored most of the content. I warned you about this early on. I decided against a deep examination of conservatism because people don&amp;rsquo;t care. Instead, I wrote a rather tongue-in-cheek story about why definitions of conservatism don&amp;rsquo;t matter.
Deep thinkers got the tongue-in-cheek shtick. Maybe they rolled their eyes at my cheap attempt at being clever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe he&#39;s not a conservative</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/16/more-on-first-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/16/more-on-first-principles/</guid>
      <description>As far as I can tell, the number one reason a few conservatives give for hating Eric Greitens is that he might not be a conservative. He&amp;rsquo;s probably not. But that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t make any difference.
Figuring out whether Greitens is a conservative or not requires a lot of thinking, a lot of writing, and a lot of clear analysis from readers. I won&amp;rsquo;t waste time on the first two because I won&amp;rsquo;t get the last no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know When To Fight Your Own</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/07/know-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 09:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/07/know-fight/</guid>
      <description>I can be pretty hard on Republicans. Not hard enough for some. Too hard for others.
But I, at least, try to time my battles for ideological consistency. As a general rule, odd-numbered years are for cleaning up the GOP. Even-numbered years are for cleaning out Democrats.
This is an odd-numbered year. Right up to the votes on the continuing resolution,my primary targets were Republicans, especially Roy Blunt.
Once the House exercised its Constitutional power of the purse strings, sending a popular continuing resolution to the Senate, the battle lines shifted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Collateral Damage When Hunting for RINOs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/responsible-rino-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/responsible-rino-hunter/</guid>
      <description>Lowell Weicker was a RINO. So was Lincoln Chaffe for a while. And John Linsday, the mayor who tried to destroy New York City in the late 1960s and early 1970s.
RINO stands for &amp;ldquo;Republican In Name Only.&amp;rdquo; Rhinos and Elephants are both pachyderms, so it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty clever name for people who join the Republican Party but prefer the Democrat platform.
The problem is, some people take the concept to extremes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s the Most Encouraging Thing John Boehner Ever Said</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</guid>
      <description>Today on ABC&amp;rsquo;s This Week, Speaker of the House John Boehner spoke very powerful words about himself. They reveal his motivation. And it&amp;rsquo;s very encouraging.
 &amp;ldquo;I’m a reasonable guy. But I didn’t come to Washington to be a congressman. I came to do something for my country.&amp;rdquo;
 Write that down. That statement echos.
Research shows thatpeople motivated by doing, by getting better, by learning, will work harder and stay truer to their principles than people motivated by demonstrating how good they are&amp;ndash;being something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Reasons Why House Republicans Should Pass a Clean Debt Ceiling Bill Now *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/05/4-reasons-to-pass-clean-debt-ceiling-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 16:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/05/4-reasons-to-pass-clean-debt-ceiling-bill/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, I know. Obama&amp;rsquo;s childish, petulant, and tyrannical tantrums over the continuing resolution makes me want to fight like an angry cat, too.
But I don&amp;rsquo;t actually want to fight. Fighting isn&amp;rsquo;t in our interest. As Sun Tzu said:
 Hence to fight and conquer in all your battles is not supreme excellence; supreme excellence consists in breaking the enemy&amp;rsquo;s resistance without fighting.
 I want to succeed in repealing Obamacare and forcing government into its constitutionally limited box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Loathsome War on WWII Vets Deserves Our Scorn and Fury</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/01/obamas-loathsome-war-wwii-vets-deserve-scorn-fury/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 03:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/01/obamas-loathsome-war-wwii-vets-deserve-scorn-fury/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ve all see the reports.
WWII Veterans asked the White House for permission to visit the World War II Memorial in case of a shutdown. The veterans are part of the Honor Flights program that helps aging veterans visit the WWII Memorial.
Even though there&amp;rsquo;s no cost involved, the White House chose to dishonor the veterans&amp;rsquo; request. It send forth &amp;ldquo;goons,&amp;rdquo; in Senator Paul&amp;rsquo;s works, to erect barricades around the memorial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown Week Could Turn Into Big Win for Republicans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/30/shutdown-week-republicans-winning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/30/shutdown-week-republicans-winning/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to offer anything.&amp;rdquo; Barack Obama on why he&amp;rsquo;s shutting down the government.
Obama keeps forgetting he&amp;rsquo;s not a dictator. Or maybe I keep forgetting he is.
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;441&amp;rdquo;] Democrat Speaker Tip O&amp;rsquo;Neill shut down the government 12 times.[/caption]
Did you see that list of government shutdowns?
1976, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1981, 1982, 1983, 1984, 1986, 1987, 1990, 1995.
Those first four shutdowns came with Democrat majorities in both houses of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Learned the House GOP Is A Lot Tougher Than Senate</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/28/ive-learned-house-gop-lot-tougher-senate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 03:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/28/ive-learned-house-gop-lot-tougher-senate/</guid>
      <description>I was wrong.
As the continuing resolution fight approached, I expected House Republicans to cave. I expected Boehner to make a half-hearted attempt to use debt ceiling, instead of continuing resolution, as leverage to stop Obamacare. And I expected Republican Senators to make a stand.
But that&amp;rsquo;s not what happened.
In reverse order, Senate Republican leadership ran away from confrontation like schoolgirls spying a snake. Led by Mitch McConnell, John Cornyn, and Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Junior Senator Roy Blunt, the GOP attacked Senators Mike Lee and Ted Cruz instead of Obamacare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need a Stronger Third Eye</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/we-need-a-stronger-third-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 04:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/we-need-a-stronger-third-eye/</guid>
      <description>What do we look like to people who aren&amp;rsquo;t politics wonks? And why does it matter?
This question is for my friends on the right. By &amp;ldquo;on the right,&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m talking about conservatives and right-leaning libertarians. (I&amp;rsquo;m not going to debate definitions, so accept mine or stop reading.)
Developing a Third Eye When I was an acting student many long years ago, I had a director, Don Garner, who stressed the importance of the actor&amp;rsquo;s third eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Will Not Debate Definitions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/12/i-will-not-debate-definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 02:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/12/i-will-not-debate-definitions/</guid>
      <description>A commenter to my blog about libertarian kids implies that libertarians are okay—as long as they’re not, ya know, too libertarian.
The other night at Heritage Tavern I heard debates break out over the definition of “conservative.”
If you’re wondering why the left is kicking our ass, now you know. They’re busy turning Texas blue while we debate the meanings and merits of political labels.
Maybe this country is beyond hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss A Rising Conservative Star</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/dont-miss-a-rising-conservative-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 23:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/dont-miss-a-rising-conservative-star/</guid>
      <description>I met Raz Shaver in 2010. Even though he’s many years my junior, Raz has been an insightful, patient, and indispensible to mentor in grassroots activism.

Raz continues to help me and St. Louis Tea Party Coalition from his bunker in Texas. He also helps groups like St. Louis Tea Party all around the country. Victories and 2010, those to come in 2012, owe, in a large degree, to Raz Shafer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relate to This, Mitt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/relate-to-this-mitt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/11/relate-to-this-mitt-2/</guid>
      <description>The liberal press cannot issue a story about the Republican presidential race that does not refer to Mitt Romney’s need (and inability) to “relate to” conservatives. Puke.
Relate to this: if Mitt Romney’s a conservative, I’m a Hottentot.

By “relate to,” the media and Romney’s handlers actually mean “hoodwink.” While Romney might secure the GOP nomination without conservative support, his campaign will go down in flames without conservative grassroots boots on the ground from Labor Day to Election Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Ed Martin Running for Attorney General in Missouri *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/26/breaking-ed-martin-running-for-attorney-general-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin Jr. of St. Louis has redirected his fire to the Attorney General race, and this is great news for everyone except Chris Koster.
Back when Ed Martin was talking about running for the Republican nod to take on Claire McCaskill, I had another thought. Well, a bunch of people had another thought: Ed would make an outstanding Attorney General.
UPDATE
HUGE list of endorsements on Ed’s official press release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will You Help Find the Lost?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/10/will-you-help-the-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 21:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/10/will-you-help-the-lost/</guid>
      <description>You might have heard that Jefferson County Council was one of the happiest stories emerging from the 2010 election.
Well, some of the conservative champions who led the crusade to capture the council want to help more citizens become political leaders.
On Saturday, September 24, you can help. You can help while having blast of a good time in Crystal City.

Events all day long, including live music in the caverns from 7 to 9 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Party, Not a Club</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/08/a-party-not-a-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 18:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/08/a-party-not-a-club/</guid>
      <description>Let’s face it: the Missouri GOP has become a club to advance the careers of a select few favorites. It is not a party to advance conservative principles.
And that needs to change here and now.
And that means some old names need to retire.
Here’s just one example of the ideological impotence of the Missouri Republican Party: The St. Louis County Assessor.
The GOP created the St. Louis County Assessor’s office because of corruption and incompetence in the political patronage version of the office under Democrats Buzz Westfall and Charlie Dooley.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>