<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>conservative on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/conservative/</link>
    <description>Recent content in conservative on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 22:02:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/conservative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Surface thinking, deep thinking</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/17/surface-thinking-deep-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 22:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/17/surface-thinking-deep-thinking/</guid>
      <description>How people responded to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post, Maybe he&amp;rsquo;s not a conservative, varied. But there were two dominant types.
Surface thinkers ignored most of the content. I warned you about this early on. I decided against a deep examination of conservatism because people don&amp;rsquo;t care. Instead, I wrote a rather tongue-in-cheek story about why definitions of conservatism don&amp;rsquo;t matter.
Deep thinkers got the tongue-in-cheek shtick. Maybe they rolled their eyes at my cheap attempt at being clever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe he&#39;s not a conservative</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/16/more-on-first-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/16/more-on-first-principles/</guid>
      <description>As far as I can tell, the number one reason a few conservatives give for hating Eric Greitens is that he might not be a conservative. He&amp;rsquo;s probably not. But that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t make any difference.
Figuring out whether Greitens is a conservative or not requires a lot of thinking, a lot of writing, and a lot of clear analysis from readers. I won&amp;rsquo;t waste time on the first two because I won&amp;rsquo;t get the last no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know When To Fight Your Own</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/07/know-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 09:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/07/know-fight/</guid>
      <description>I can be pretty hard on Republicans. Not hard enough for some. Too hard for others.
But I, at least, try to time my battles for ideological consistency. As a general rule, odd-numbered years are for cleaning up the GOP. Even-numbered years are for cleaning out Democrats.
This is an odd-numbered year. Right up to the votes on the continuing resolution,my primary targets were Republicans, especially Roy Blunt.
Once the House exercised its Constitutional power of the purse strings, sending a popular continuing resolution to the Senate, the battle lines shifted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Collateral Damage When Hunting for RINOs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/responsible-rino-hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/responsible-rino-hunter/</guid>
      <description>Lowell Weicker was a RINO. So was Lincoln Chaffe for a while. And John Linsday, the mayor who tried to destroy New York City in the late 1960s and early 1970s.
RINO stands for &amp;ldquo;Republican In Name Only.&amp;rdquo; Rhinos and Elephants are both pachyderms, so it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty clever name for people who join the Republican Party but prefer the Democrat platform.
The problem is, some people take the concept to extremes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s the Most Encouraging Thing John Boehner Ever Said</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/10/06/heres-encouraging-thing-john-boehner-ever-said/</guid>
      <description>Today on ABC&amp;rsquo;s This Week, Speaker of the House John Boehner spoke very powerful words about himself. They reveal his motivation. And it&amp;rsquo;s very encouraging.
 &amp;ldquo;I’m a reasonable guy. But I didn’t come to Washington to be a congressman. I came to do something for my country.&amp;rdquo;
 Write that down. That statement echos.
Research shows thatpeople motivated by doing, by getting better, by learning, will work harder and stay truer to their principles than people motivated by demonstrating how good they are&amp;ndash;being something.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>