<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2004 Election on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/2004-election/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2004 Election on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/2004-election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS vs. The Press</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/cbs-vs-the-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/cbs-vs-the-press/</guid>
      <description>I watched the CBS Evening News tonight, so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see the competition. NBC and ABC were unable to find a single forensic document specialist who believe the documents on CBS News were legitimate. These included former FBI document experts now teaching forensics at universities.
Apparently, the only expert who thinks Jerry Killian typed and signed the CBS papers is the CBS employee featured on their broadcast tonight.
Funny&amp;ndash;the liberal press isn&amp;rsquo;t rallying to CBS&amp;rsquo;s side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Former Navy Personnel Officer Explains Why The &#34;Sugar Coat&#34; Memo is Likely a Fraud</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/former-navy-personnel-officer-explains-why-the-sugar-coat-memo-is-likely-a-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/former-navy-personnel-officer-explains-why-the-sugar-coat-memo-is-likely-a-fraud/</guid>
      <description>Something on TimeIsAFactor.com caught my attention.
One of the 4 CBS memos about George W. Bush&amp;rsquo;s National Guard service contains the following memo supposedly authored by his commanding officer:
&amp;ldquo;Bush wasn&amp;rsquo;t here during rating period and I don&amp;rsquo;t have any feedback from 187th in Alabama. I will not rate.&amp;rdquo;
Having spent 9 years as an enlisted Personnel Officer in the Navy, the marks on Bush&amp;rsquo;s fitness report for the period he was in Alabama are the only ones that could be entered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS and Dems Part 2:  Forged, Phoney Documents?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/09/cbs-and-dems-part-2-forged-phoney-documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/09/cbs-and-dems-part-2-forged-phoney-documents/</guid>
      <description>CNSNew.com is reporting that typography experts are fairly confident that documents exposed on CBS&amp;rsquo;s 60 Minutes II were fake. The documents, allegedly authored in 1972, used proportional fonts and superscript lettering, not widely available in 1972.
I am very familiar with the typewriter the Navy used in the 1980s: IBM Selectric III. It had changable font golfballs, one of which was proportional (CGTimes). But it looked awful. The proportional spacing was in consistent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS and Dems:  Unmitigated Bullshit</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/09/cbs-and-dems-unmitigated-bullshit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/09/cbs-and-dems-unmitigated-bullshit/</guid>
      <description>250 private citizens &amp;ndash; Vietnam veterans all &amp;ndash; attacked John Kerry&amp;rsquo;s previously unscrutinized service record. It made news because Kerry is running for president.
CBS News and the Democrat National Party, now, are re-examining Bush&amp;rsquo;s National Guard service and spewing lies that were already answered and resolved in 2000.
I honestly do not remember a presidential campaign in which the media so forcefully and openly worked to elect one candidate over another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>