<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>happiness on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/happiness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in happiness on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 04:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/happiness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Find Truth In Consistency</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/15/how-to-find-truth-in-consistency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 04:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/15/how-to-find-truth-in-consistency/</guid>
      <description>A great colleague and I invented something in 2010. It was a two-day workshop for companies. It has been incredibly successful.
In that workshop, we cite a lot of behavioral science research. We also point out that some behavioral science research is bogus. Up to 60 percent by a recent study (which might have been bogus itself.) So how do you know good science from bad?
Look for consistency. I&amp;rsquo;ll give you an example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Should We Do Next?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/10/what-should-we-do-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 09:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/10/what-should-we-do-next/</guid>
      <description>God laughs at man&amp;rsquo;s plans.
That&amp;rsquo;s because God has already given us the only plan we need. A plan to get through this life worthy of the next. And that is enough.
Lawrence of Rome Followed the Plan Today is the feast day of Saint Lawrence of Rome. Lawrence is the patron saint of, among others, comedians.
Lawrence was the leader of a group seven deacons whose mission was to distribute alms to the poor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How bad would Trump presidency be?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/24/why-so-many-conservatives-are-wrong-about-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/24/why-so-many-conservatives-are-wrong-about-trump/</guid>
      <description>The world is about to end.
Or civil war is about to break out in Dayton, Ohio.
Believe it?
Glenn Beck, Erick Erickson, and other Republicans have convinced a lot of people that we are doomed if Donald Trump wins the Republican nomination. I know some people who are nearly incapacitated with fear and grief after last night&amp;rsquo;s Nevada caucuses. Because they listen to Glenn Beck. Sad!
Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: **nothing is as bad as you think it will be while you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Pissed That I’m Pissed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/im-pissed-that-im-pissed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/im-pissed-that-im-pissed/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of being angry?
Did you know that a lot of other people are tired of your anger?
Did you know that 70 percent of Americans don’t like politics?
Did you know that the 70 percent of Americans who don’t like politics won’t vote for anything an angry person tells them to vote for?
Go look it up. It’s totally true.
So many conservatives want another Reagan, but they want an angry, vengeful, belligerent Reagan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Ferguson and Dellwood This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 04:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I&amp;rsquo;m so late on this. This sounds whiny, I know, but I have a really involved week at work this week. Sorry. Crap always seems to work out this way, though. When there&amp;rsquo;s a great need for Tea Party services, I&amp;rsquo;m tied up with work obligations. Something has to give, and it&amp;rsquo;s usually the thing that doesn&amp;rsquo;t generate revenue.
But we all have work to do. Ferguson businesses and families are still struggling with the effects of the riots.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>