<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brett Kavanaugh on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/brett-kavanaugh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brett Kavanaugh on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 14:08:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/brett-kavanaugh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to shield Brett Kavanaugh against spells of witches</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/20/how-to-shield-brett-kavanaugh-against-spells-of-witches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 14:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/20/how-to-shield-brett-kavanaugh-against-spells-of-witches/</guid>
      <description>You probably heard that a bunch of witches are gathering in New York City today to put hexes on Justice Brett Kavanaugh, Donald Trump, and others. Don&amp;rsquo;t take this lightly. Father Richard Heilman and folks at the Holy League have asked Christians to pray the Lorica of St. Patrick for Justice Kavanaugh, substituting &amp;ldquo;Brett Kavanaugh&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Justice Kavanaugh&amp;rdquo; for the first person pronouns.
This is a powerful prayer that&amp;rsquo;s more than 1,500 years old!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did I get the Kavanaugh vote so wrong?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/06/how-did-i-get-the-kavanaugh-vote-so-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 19:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/06/how-did-i-get-the-kavanaugh-vote-so-wrong/</guid>
      <description>I predicted that Judge Brett Kavanaugh would be rejected by the Senate. I was wrong. In a few minutes from the time I write, the Senate will confirm Judge Kavanaugh by a vote of 50 ayes to 48 nays. One Republican will vote &amp;ldquo;present.&amp;rdquo;
What went wrong? I underestimated the courage and fortitude of three Senators: Republicans Jeff Flake and Susan Collins, and Democrat &amp;ldquo;Lonely&amp;rdquo; Joe Manchin. I truly believed Flake would put his hatred of Donald Trump before the good of the country and vote nay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Will Be Punished Efficiently</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/02/you-will-be-punished-efficiently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 10:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/02/you-will-be-punished-efficiently/</guid>
      <description>The trains to Auschwitz ran on time. Brutal dictatorships love efficiency. Stalin. Hitler. Mao. Pol Pot. The best mass murderers are efficient. Psychopaths feed on efficiency. They kill because killing is the most efficient means to their end. They kill to rid society of inefficient people. People who introduce inefficiencies to the system. People who get in the way.
Democracy is inefficient. As are all republics. (A republic is any form of government that&amp;rsquo;s open to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;ve Never Been Closer to Totalitarianism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/30/weve-never-been-closer-to-totalitarianism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 13:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/30/weve-never-been-closer-to-totalitarianism/</guid>
      <description>Very scary thought: If the Democrats take over the House and Senate in January, they could impeach both Trump and Pence and try them in the Senate at the same time making Nancy Pelosi president.
You&amp;rsquo;ve Never Lived in a Time Like This One I&amp;rsquo;m almost old enough to remember the Democrat National Convention of 1968. Almost. What a show. Hippies and Yippies marching, tear gas, Mayor Daley, Buckley threatening to punch Gore Vidal on live TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The  Kavanaugh Conniption</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/08/the-kavanaugh-conniption/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 20:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/08/the-kavanaugh-conniption/</guid>
      <description>Judging by the hateful behavior of the materialistic left, you&amp;rsquo;d think Judge Brett Kavanaugh has a history of driving around neighborhoods and stopping to strangle puppies in front of their 5-year-old masters. There was Kamala Harris&amp;rsquo;s outburst at the start of the hearings. There was Cory Booker&amp;rsquo;s sad and embarrassing Spartacus moment which was like a failed scene in a forgotten Woody Allen movie. Now, the left&amp;rsquo;s hate groups are complaining that the Democrats didn&amp;rsquo;t go far enough.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>