<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trump on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/trump/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trump on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 13:11:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Iraq Strategy:  Vindicated</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/12/iraq-stategy-vindicated-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 13:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/12/iraq-stategy-vindicated-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week, a colleague commented that he only put credence into international polls. As if the poll gods were listening, today ABC News released the most affirming poll for President Bush&amp;rsquo;s Iraq strategy ever conducted.
It must have pained the ABC News editors to write such a glowing headline:
Poll: Broad Optimism in Iraq
So pained, in fact, that they felt compelled to immediately qualify that statement:
But Also Deep Divisions Among Groups</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christianity Headlines</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/08/06/christianity-headlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2005 23:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/08/06/christianity-headlines/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s making news around the Christian world
* Chinese become Christians faster than you can say &amp;quot;In nomine Patris, et Filii, et Spiritu Sancto&amp;quot; ([OrthodoxyToday](https://www.orthodoxytoday.org/blog/index.php?p=1041)) * [Emily at AfterAbortion ](https://afterabortion.blogspot.com/2005/08/diarist-at-daily-kos-publishes-this.html)reports that Daily Kos is making anti-life hay because some pro-violence anti-abortionists protested outside an abortion clinic. When will the pro-life side realize that prayer trumps murder?  Updates coming . . .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man, Curb Your Wife</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/22/man-curb-your-wife/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2005 12:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/22/man-curb-your-wife/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s not much to say. Judges have determined, in logical order, the following:
A. Michael Schiavo is Terri Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s husband; therefore, B. Michael Schiavo is Terri&amp;rsquo;s legal guardian; therefore, C. Michael Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s desires trump laws of the state and of morality.
Florida law does not permit the execution of a person in Terri Schiavo&amp;rsquo;s condition. The judges (like Glenn Reynolds and James Joyner and others) are too cowardly to come out and say, &amp;ldquo;Look, people, the mentally ill make us kind of sick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Magazine:  Blogstorm (Corrected Links)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/14/world-magazine-blogstorm-corrected-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2005 04:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/14/world-magazine-blogstorm-corrected-links/</guid>
      <description>World Magazine visits the McCain-Feingold vs. Blogs story and quotes . . . me?
World Magazine | World News | Christian Views
   Still, many conservatives are setting aside their dislike of liberal inconsistencies in hopes of allying against potential regulation. &amp;ldquo;Currently, the limits would hurt conservatives more than it would hurt liberals,&amp;rdquo; said conservative blogger Bill Hennessy, noting that more conservative blogs exist. &amp;ldquo;Ultimately, though, the pain is already even; stifling political speech hurts everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>