<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zen Conservatism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/zen-conservatism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zen Conservatism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 01:52:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/zen-conservatism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Focased Conservatism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/28/focased-conservatism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 01:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/28/focased-conservatism/</guid>
      <description>January 28, 2009, could go down as the day conservatives regained their focus.
What the FOCA?: Some enterprising pro-lifers desiring limited government launched the “What the FOCA?” website. The site kicks some of the 1973-style slogans from the Right to Life movement, updating themes and memes for 2009. A great idea, long overdue. Visit often and donate generously if fighting rampant abortion is one of your action focuses.
A (Republican) House United: Every member of the Republican House Caucus voted against Obama’s Crap Sandwich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Never Was There</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/19/it-never-was-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 00:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/19/it-never-was-there/</guid>
      <description>I’m like a lot of people I know. We may be very different from you and those you know. But we’re familiar to ourselves and to each other.
I’m one of those people who tried to get There.
There isn’t a place; it’s a status. It’s a moment. It’s hearing that someone told someone else that you have “one of those” and they should see it. Maybe it’s the big TV or the cool cappuccino machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evil of Debt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/18/the-evil-of-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 15:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/18/the-evil-of-debt/</guid>
      <description>_The debtor is a slave to his lender. _
Americans hold hundreds of billions of dollars in credit card debt alone. To this add automobiles, student loans, mortgages, medical, and myriad personal loans and you arrive at the staggering figure of$2.55 trillion with a &amp;lsquo;t&amp;rsquo;. 
This massive debt&amp;ndash;encouraged and backed by the US Government&amp;ndash;makes us miserable. Seriously. Are you happy? If the debtor is slave to his lender, then the US Government is slave to China and Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eXtreme Programming and Good Government</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/14/extreme-programming-and-good-government-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 12:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/14/extreme-programming-and-good-government-2/</guid>
      <description>Kent Beck, the genius who discovered eXtreme Programming, from whence sprang all so-called Agile methodologies, can lead us to good government. Beck, a senior consultant in the 1990s, noticed that all big software development programs began and ended the same way in the days of waterfall. Massive Requirements: Every project began with lots of highly paid people sitting in endless series of meetings aiming to document everything that a system must and should do and how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Focused Blogging for Conservatives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/12/focused-blogging-for-conservatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 12:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/12/focused-blogging-for-conservatives/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, when blogging was fresh and new, conservative blogs dominated the top of Technorati&amp;rsquo;s most popular lists. Michelle Malkin, Powerline, and InstaPundit routinely led Talking Points and Kos. But we&amp;rsquo;ve fallen. Big time.
Yesterday, Michelle was still the #1 conservative blog&amp;ndash;at 39 overall. Huffington Post is #1, Kos is #8.
Why?
Reason 1: Focus
Or lack thereof. The rising stars of the right aren&amp;rsquo;t necessarily political, but scientific.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>