<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>neuroscience on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/neuroscience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in neuroscience on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 13:30:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/neuroscience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Caution: Identifying as &#39;NeverTrump&#39; Changes Your Brain</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/what-happens-you-identify-as-nevertrump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/what-happens-you-identify-as-nevertrump/</guid>
      <description>When a person declares himself &amp;ldquo;NeverTrump,&amp;rdquo; he thinks he&amp;rsquo;s making a political statement. Or a moral one. But he&amp;rsquo;s not. He&amp;rsquo;s making a psychological commitment that&amp;rsquo;s very difficult and painful to break.
Identity is the highest, most powerful form of persuasion. Identity also drives our decisions in parts of the brain we don&amp;rsquo;t really have conscious control over. I realize many conservatives reject brain science, but, for those of you who are open to learning, I&amp;rsquo;ll explain as best I can in a moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use This One Word Because It Makes You More Influential</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/use-this-one-word-because-it-makes-you-more-influential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/use-this-one-word-because-it-makes-you-more-influential/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me to explain why the human brain works the way it does. And don&amp;rsquo;t ask me how scientists get the idea for some experiments.
Instead, take note of the most influential work in the English language, because I want you to be more influential.
What&amp;rsquo;s that one word?
It&amp;rsquo;s not &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;instantly&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;new.&amp;rdquo; They&amp;rsquo;re very powerful words, as every copywriter knows. But they&amp;rsquo;re not the most influential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss The Brain Study That Tells You How to Influence Democrats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/01/dont-miss-the-brain-study-that-tells-you-how-to-influence-democrats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/01/dont-miss-the-brain-study-that-tells-you-how-to-influence-democrats/</guid>
      <description>One of the most powerful tools of influence is fear.
Decades of research shows that fear of loss is about three times as motivating as hope for gain. (This changes under certain situations, like conditions of certain loss, but that’s for another time.)
So political message writers often use negative messages to influence voters to take a chance on a cause or a candidate.
This tactic works well with Republican voters, and less well with Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why GOP Pandering to Young Voters Backfires</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/25/why-gop-pandering-to-young-voters-backfires/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/25/why-gop-pandering-to-young-voters-backfires/</guid>
      <description>Marco Rubio gave the Republican response to the State of the Union address for two reasons.
First, Rubio’s Cuban, and the GOP wants to court Latinos.
Second, Rubio’s relatively young, and the GOP wants to stop the bleeding when it comes to young voters.
But there’s a fundamental problem with the Republican approach, and it stems from the GOP’s least favorite discipline: behavioral science.
Young People Are Naturally Skeptical You hear about scams that target older folks all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>