<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>America on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/america/</link>
    <description>Recent content in America on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 22:30:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/america/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Expect Much More of Republicans on Obamacare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/25/expect-much-republicans-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 05:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/25/expect-much-republicans-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>Sam Adams and friends risked their lives in the commission of a felony in their outrage over government overreach.
That was the Boston Tea Party.
Look at us now! People furious with me for going after Senator Roy Blunt. I went after him because he announced he will vote for cloture knowing full well that cloture give Harry Reid his only chance to strip the House&amp;rsquo;s Obamacare defund language from the continuing resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Election’s Over, and America Gave Obama His Eviction Notice. Here’s What Went Down.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/the-elections-over-and-america-gave-obama-his-eviction-notice-heres-what-went-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/the-elections-over-and-america-gave-obama-his-eviction-notice-heres-what-went-down/</guid>
      <description>The look on George “Stephie” Stephanopoulos’s face was priceless. He had to say it.

“ABC News now projects that President Obama will go down to defeat.”
He couldn’t bring himself to say, “Romney won” or “Republicans won.” He just couldn’t.
The network analysis was a political cliché run amok. My favorite came from James Carville who told CNN viewers that the election result “proves that crackers and racists vote.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Empire?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/11/why-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 19:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/11/why-empire/</guid>
      <description>“Why would a nation become imperial?,” Steven asked me. “I mean, why would you want to take that on?”
The conversation had been on Japan leading up to World War II. The question was important. Why would a nation conquer dissimilar nations? Why accept that burden and risk?
My answer, which I’ve grown more fond of as time’s passed, was something like this: Imperial people view everything as a fixed pie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are We the Last Americans?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/07/are-we-the-last-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/07/are-we-the-last-americans/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes nightmares end well.
Sometimes they don’t.
Salon carries a depressing story for the lower 48 of North America. Author Alfred McCoy writes:
 Despite the aura of omnipotence most empires project, a look at their history should remind us that they are fragile organisms. So delicate is their ecology of power that, when things start to go truly bad, empires regularly unravel with unholy speed: just a year for Portugal, two years for the Soviet Union, eight years for France, 11 years for the Ottomans, 17 years for Great Britain, and, in all likelihood, 22 years for the United States, counting from the crucial year 2003.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>