<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>socialism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/socialism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in socialism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 09:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/socialism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Socialism Sucks. Here’s How to Avoid It In America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/23/socialism-sucks-heres-how-to-avoid-it-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/23/socialism-sucks-heres-how-to-avoid-it-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Some of the “cool” kids say they like socialism. Of course they have no emotional clue what socialism is.

Maybe they’ve read about socialism, seen the movies, and heard about it from their college professors—ya know, like the one who actually visited the old Soviet Union.
But those sources give only an intellectual view of socialism. You can’t actually _feel _it. And life, in the end, is about feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas: Point of No Return</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/08/kansas-point-of-no-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/08/kansas-point-of-no-return/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday in Kansas, President Barack Obama revealed his contempt for liberty. He declared that human beings are incapable of running their own lives . . . but, somehow, other, superior human beings are capable of running their own and others’.
  He said that free markets have always failed, everywhere . . . ignoring most of the last 240 years.
He all but declared himself a Marxist.
I am depressed that America let this dangerous man into our government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Lucky?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/14/whos-lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 23:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/14/whos-lucky/</guid>
      <description>There’s a “special” school in St. Louis County. Its seniors graduated on last Friday.

How sad it must be for those kids. They’re not graduating from the district’s “normal” schools with their peers. For various reasons, they’ve been relegated to a school for misfits.
Seeing the building makes the bad feelings worse. It’s a former grade school, crammed inconveniently behind a bank and a Taco Bell. Its Eisenhower era architecture stands out amidst its Mortgage Boom surroundings like a dandelion on golf course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Plan to Punish Voters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/democrats-plan-to-punish-voters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 22:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/democrats-plan-to-punish-voters/</guid>
      <description>Democrats are planning to punish the American people with draconian, destructive legislation during the lame duck session following November’s election, according the Wall Street Journal.
 That&amp;rsquo;s why there have been signs in recent weeks that party leaders are planning an ambitious, lame-duck session to muscle through bills in December they don&amp;rsquo;t want to defend before November. Retiring or defeated members of Congress would then be able to vote for sweeping legislation without any fear of voter retaliation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Days of Free Markets Numbered</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/days-of-free-markets-numbered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/days-of-free-markets-numbered/</guid>
      <description>The statists are moving faster through the Constitution than Hitler moved through France. Today, Democrats in the House of Representatives voted to advance a bill to socialize medicine without debate.
 House Democrats went on record again in favor of advancing the legislation while allowing only limited debate, which would hobble the ability of Republicans to wrest concessions on one of Obama&amp;rsquo;s top domestic priorities.
 **Accelerating the **Banana Republic</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>