<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Living Insurance Exchanges on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/living-insurance-exchanges/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Living Insurance Exchanges on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/living-insurance-exchanges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Can Missouri Legislators Learn From 19th Century St. Louis Politicians?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/13/what-can-missouri-legislators-learn-from-19th-century-st-louis-politicians/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/13/what-can-missouri-legislators-learn-from-19th-century-st-louis-politicians/</guid>
      <description>I’ll let one of my favorite thinkers, St. Louis native Don Peppers, tell about St. Louis in 1850:
 My hometown of St. Louis, Missouri was the largest city west of the Mississippi River in 1850, and the second largest port city in the entire country. Only New York handled more tonnage than the riverboats that docked, often more than a hundred at a time, at the St. Louis levee. Among other things, the riverboats supplied equipment, people, horses, and other materials to a burgeoning population of pioneers who rode wagon trains out from St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What Robin Carnahan Doesn’t Want You Know About Proposition E</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/17/heres-what-robin-carnahan-doesnt-want-you-know-about-proposition-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 23:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/17/heres-what-robin-carnahan-doesnt-want-you-know-about-proposition-e/</guid>
      <description>Robin Carnahan, the Democrat Missouri Secretary of State, writes ballot language like the editorial page editor of the Post-Dispatch.

Carnahan wrote, perhaps, the most biased and unprofessional ballot initiative ever written regarding Proposition E. She wanted you to think that Proposition E would outlaw all insurance in the state of Missouri and compel pet owners to feed rat poison to their animals. Here’s the original ballot language Carnahan wrote:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>