<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Activism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/activism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Activism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 15:42:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/activism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This Day Comes Only Once a Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/23/this-day-comes-only-once-a-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 15:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/23/this-day-comes-only-once-a-year/</guid>
      <description>But the urgency of this moment comes only twice per millennium. Will you be there?
On October 7, Christians around the world will unsheathe the most powerful weapon with which God has ever armed his people. We will, together, wage a great battle in the spiritual war of our age. What is this weapon? What is the spiritual war? If you&amp;rsquo;re paying attention at all, you know the spiritual war we&amp;rsquo;re all in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosary Coast-to-Coast October 7—Pray for America! *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/18/rosary-coast-to-coast-october-7-pray-for-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 02:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/18/rosary-coast-to-coast-october-7-pray-for-america/</guid>
      <description>The holy Rosary is a powerful weapon!
St. Josemaria Escriva
 On Sunday, October 7 at 3:30 p.m. Central (and simultaneously across the USA and the whole world), millions will say the Rosary in unison. Will you join us?
 We are at war. A war without borders, where no man is exempt but where most haven’t recognized, let alone been trained, to fight. Casualties often go unseen, but very few are left unwounded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Descend on Jefferson City</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/17/descend-on-jefferson-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 11:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/17/descend-on-jefferson-city/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time. Powerful and corrupt people want to undo the 2016 election. In Washington. In Missouri.
Win or lose, Americans deal with the results of elections. Our commitment to open, public government, of the people, by, the people, for people, has sustained this nation. And made it the greatest nation in the history of humanity.
But dark forces in Missouri want to turn your government into their private club. A club managed by corrupt business who rely on tax dollars to keep their failed enterprises afloat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Kemp Stood for Civil Rights . . . And America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</guid>
      <description>Jack Kemp is on the top of my wall of heroes. Literally. An autographed Kemp card sits on top of my bookshelf housing the works and images of my heroes.
As the NFL self-destructs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth reading about Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s work for civil rights. And for the Republican Party. And for conservatism.
Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s Activism Kemp did it all. And, thanks to Jeffrey Lord, we can remember Kemp&amp;rsquo;s finest moments of civil rights activism:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spy Tactics for Conservatives: 7 Easy Steps to Protect Yourself</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/15/7-steps-to-safety-for-conservatives-think-like-a-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 22:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/15/7-steps-to-safety-for-conservatives-think-like-a-spy/</guid>
      <description>You are a target. They want you dead.
You are a conservative activist. They call themselves &amp;ldquo;progressives.&amp;rdquo;
You want to live. And you want to remain active in politics.
They want you dead. Or submissive. Like a slave. Or a battered woman.
No, you can&amp;rsquo;t attack them. You shouldn&amp;rsquo;t engage them. They&amp;rsquo;re rabid animals. Neither reason nor normal persuasion can change progressives from their deadly habits.
So what do you do?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>