<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Debates on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/debates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Debates on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 10:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/debates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do Presidential Debates and Colonoscopies Have in Common?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/30/what-do-presidential-debates-and-colonoscopies-have-in-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/30/what-do-presidential-debates-and-colonoscopies-have-in-common/</guid>
      <description>At some point, each additional GOP Presidential debate becomes just a bigger pain in the . . . But science shows us that the last debate before a vote—and the last memorable event in the last debate—is paramount to how we remember the entire event.
In fact, memorable moments at the end, not consistent performance throughout, determine who wins and who loses.
In this awesome TED talk, Nobel winning psychologist Daniel Kahneman explains the weird difference between our experiencing selves and our remembering selves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Rick Perry Can Learn From Clark Griswold</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/24/what-rick-perry-can-learn-from-clark-griswold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 17:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/24/what-rick-perry-can-learn-from-clark-griswold/</guid>
      <description>In 2001, I loaded my three boys, ages 13, 10, and 8 at the time, into the car and headed to downtown St. Louis. The Cubs were in town, and I planned to introduce my boys to the greatest rivalry in pro sports. We parked (for twenty dollars) and headed toward the stadium.
There was only one problem: we didn’t have any tickets. I planned to buy some on the street.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>