<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>evil on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/evil/</link>
    <description>Recent content in evil on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 10:15:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/evil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rigid vs Squishy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rigid-vs-squishy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 10:15:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rigid-vs-squishy/</guid>
      <description>The opposites of &amp;ldquo;rigid&amp;rdquo; are more unflattering than rigidity:
 lenient indulgent broken compromising easy imprecise indefinite inexact irresolute unfixed unreliable accommodating liberal permissive resigned soft-hearted
 And that&amp;rsquo;s the problem with name-calling. When we impose a derogatory label on someone, we invite scrutiny upon ourselves. We label ourselves as the opposite of the names we impose on others.
Some of us are better at name-calling, or &amp;ldquo;labelling,&amp;rdquo; than others. Donald Trump does a lot of labeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Wrong--Evil</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/not-just-wrong-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/not-just-wrong-evil/</guid>
      <description>Today was a particularly busy day for me.
I had a series of meetings. Like every hour, another meeting. From 9:00 on.
I saw the text from my wife. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to click on a video. I was in a room full of people. Important business. Major client and all that. And I completely misunderstood the &amp;ldquo;H/T Gina L.&amp;rdquo; thing. For some reason, I thought Angela was mad at Gina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socialism Sucks. Here’s How to Avoid It In America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/23/socialism-sucks-heres-how-to-avoid-it-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/23/socialism-sucks-heres-how-to-avoid-it-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Some of the “cool” kids say they like socialism. Of course they have no emotional clue what socialism is.

Maybe they’ve read about socialism, seen the movies, and heard about it from their college professors—ya know, like the one who actually visited the old Soviet Union.
But those sources give only an intellectual view of socialism. You can’t actually _feel _it. And life, in the end, is about feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>