<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>liberty on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/liberty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in liberty on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 14:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/liberty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Which Freedoms Are We Losing? </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</guid>
      <description>I confess.
When I write about freedoms lost, I don&amp;rsquo;t itemize the freedoms. I don&amp;rsquo;t feel too bad, though, because almost no one does. Itemizing sucks.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s hard work. &amp;ldquo;Losing freedom,&amp;rdquo; takes about three seconds to type and less time to read. Listing freedoms,on the other hand, takes that much time just to highlight all the freedoms and click the un-ordered list button. God forbid I find myself working in straight HTML and have to hand-type &amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Government’s Surrender to Cliven Bundy Destroys Taleb’s Weak Argument for Gun Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</guid>
      <description>Events of the past week show the power of the Second Amendment to challenge government tyranny, regardless of the government’s firepower advantage. Let me back up, though.
A Smart Man’s Stupid Argument for Gun Control A year ago, the gun control lobby pumped a Facebook post by Nassim Nicholas Taleb, one of my favorite thinkers.
In his post, Taleb argued that the Second Amendment means nothing because the federal government has massively superior firepower:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need a Stronger Third Eye</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/we-need-a-stronger-third-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 04:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/we-need-a-stronger-third-eye/</guid>
      <description>What do we look like to people who aren&amp;rsquo;t politics wonks? And why does it matter?
This question is for my friends on the right. By &amp;ldquo;on the right,&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m talking about conservatives and right-leaning libertarians. (I&amp;rsquo;m not going to debate definitions, so accept mine or stop reading.)
Developing a Third Eye When I was an acting student many long years ago, I had a director, Don Garner, who stressed the importance of the actor&amp;rsquo;s third eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head To Jefferson City Wednesday To Fight Common Core and Medicaid Expansion</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/09/fight-common-core-and-medicaid-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/09/fight-common-core-and-medicaid-expansion/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;196&amp;rdquo;] State Senator John Lamping is sponsoring a bill in the Missouri Legislature to curb privacy invasions built into Common Core State Standards. Missouri liberty groups will support him in Jefferson City on March 13.[/caption]
John Lamping is one of the brightest stars for liberty in the Missouri Senate, and he needs our help this week. Let&amp;rsquo;s support liberty by fighting Medicaid Expansion and Common Core State Standards in education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Planning Is Killing the Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</guid>
      <description>Friedrich Hayek warned more than half a century ago that central planning doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. Here’s why:
 * Central Planners (government) makes a plan * The plan includes specific expectations * The expectations are never, ever, realized * A “crisis” ensues * So the planners demand more control * And create more plans * Ad hoc * Willy nilly * Capriciously * So you must wait for things to settle down to make your decision  Today’s Wall Street Journal article about the fiscal cliff demonstrates the futility of central planning:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socialism Sucks. Here’s How to Avoid It In America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/23/socialism-sucks-heres-how-to-avoid-it-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/23/socialism-sucks-heres-how-to-avoid-it-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Some of the “cool” kids say they like socialism. Of course they have no emotional clue what socialism is.

Maybe they’ve read about socialism, seen the movies, and heard about it from their college professors—ya know, like the one who actually visited the old Soviet Union.
But those sources give only an intellectual view of socialism. You can’t actually _feel _it. And life, in the end, is about feelings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s What’s Great About the Supreme Court’s Obamacare Decision</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/30/heres-whats-great-about-the-supreme-courts-obamacare-decision/</guid>
      <description>In the Ronald Reagan movie Kings Row, Reagan plays Drake McHugh, whose legs are sawn off by a sadistic, class-conscious doctor.

Everyone remembers the line “Where’s the rest of me?” No remembers what happens after that. I’ll fill you in.
McHugh’s best friend, a psychiatrist, decides to tell McHugh (Reagan) the truth: his legs were perfectly healthy, but the doctor cut them off to keep the lower class McHugh from pursuing the doctor’s debutante daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Not an Annual Celebration of Freedom?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/28/when-did-we-stop-getting-freer-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/28/when-did-we-stop-getting-freer-in-america/</guid>
      <description>The first entry in National Review’s “The Week” from sometime around 1990 listed ten or so former Soviet bloc countries that recently had shed the yoke of communist repression. And it made a simple statement:
 “It must be nice to live in a country where you get freer every day.”
 I thought of this while talking about the 13th Amendment Freedom Week with its evangelist-in-chief Kariem Haqq at St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMSL Econ Professor David Rose on Moral Foundations of Economic Behavior</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/24/umsl-econ-professor-david-rose-on-moral-foundations-of-economic-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 20:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/24/umsl-econ-professor-david-rose-on-moral-foundations-of-economic-behavior/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m proud to know David Rose. Dr. Rose is chairman of UMSL&amp;rsquo;s economics department. He&amp;rsquo;s also the President of the Discussion Club, one of St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s most valuable intellectual assets.
In this interview with Russ Roberts, Dr. Rose discusses his new book Moral Foundations of Economic Behavior.
This is great stuff for everyone, especially economic liberty fiends like me.
https://rcm.amazon.com/e/cm?lt1=_blank&amp;amp;bc1=000000&amp;amp;IS2=1&amp;amp;bg1=FFFFFF&amp;amp;fc1=000000&amp;amp;lc1=0000FF&amp;amp;t=hennesssview-20&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;p=8&amp;amp;l=as4&amp;amp;m=amazon&amp;amp;f=ifr&amp;amp;ref=ss_til&amp;amp;asins=0199781745</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/24/the-ghost-of-christmas-yet-to-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 20:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/24/the-ghost-of-christmas-yet-to-come/</guid>
      <description>In the course of our lives, we sometimes lose our way. We wander off the good path. Or we fail to blaze the trail we should.

 THE Phantom slowly, gravely, silently, approached. When it came near him, Scrooge bent down upon his knee; for in the very air through which this Spirit moved it seemed to scatter gloom and mystery.
It was shrouded in a deep black garment, which concealed its head, its face, its form, and left nothing of it visible save one outstretched hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Tea Party?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/19/why-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/19/why-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>A college student asked me a question: Why join the Tea Party?

He was wondering why anyone would want to associate with people who behaved reprehensibly at two earlier Republican debates.
Here’s how I replied:
 Johnny,
 Sorry that I&amp;rsquo;m just getting to this. I get a lot of email, and sometimes I miss things.
I organized the tea party in St. Louis in 2009. I did so because I&amp;rsquo;ve seen that governments accumulate power until they crush liberty and freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s the Big Deal with the Establishment?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/14/whats-the-big-deal-with-the-establishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/14/whats-the-big-deal-with-the-establishment/</guid>
      <description>A friend of mine told me this story.
 He sat that there bragging about getting a tax cut for friends of his.
I said, ‘you do realize, don’t you, that you’re just like the Democrats, except you’re giving taxpayers money to a different special interest.’
He looked at me and said, ‘but our special interests do good with the money.’
 My friend was talking about the second highest-ranking Republican in the Missouri House at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who will feed the hungry, clothe the naked, tend the sick, visit the imprisoned . . . ?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/19/who-will-feed-the-hungry-clothe-the-naked-tend-the-sick-visit-the-imprisoned/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/19/who-will-feed-the-hungry-clothe-the-naked-tend-the-sick-visit-the-imprisoned/</guid>
      <description>The candidates blew the emotional turning point in Monday’s CNN/Tea Party debate. Blew it. Big.
Before we go into that, hear me out on the pressure on those candidates.
Lights, Camera, Panic
Imagine being on a stage. Searing white brightness reduces your range of vision to a few degrees of arc. You hear hundreds of people making the sounds that audiences make, but you can’t really see them.
Before you are journalists bent on catching in a gaffe, or unprepared, or vulnerable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Believe in Man-Made Liberty?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/22/do-you-believe-in-man-made-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 03:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/22/do-you-believe-in-man-made-liberty/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you’ll reconsider.
Wallbuilders with Rick Green, Saturday, Aug. 27, First Baptist Church/Wentzville
For more information, here’s the link.
(h/t Rick Tsa’ara)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You, Harvard</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/02/thank-you-harvard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 14:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/02/thank-you-harvard/</guid>
      <description>A Harvard study recently concluded that attending American Independence Day celebrations could turn kids into Republicans.

The reason 4th of July creates Republicans has nothing to do with patriotism and everything to do with education. Here’s why:
* On July 4th, we celebrate the Declaration of Independence, not the founding of the United States. (That would come with the passage of the Constitution thirteen years later).** July 4th events teach kids—in an environment free from teacher-union propaganda—the _reasons_ we broke from England.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditate on This, Why Don’t You?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/01/meditate-on-this-why-dont-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/01/meditate-on-this-why-dont-you/</guid>
      <description>I was 18 and a college freshman. It was a Tuesday night in October. My 1970 Chevy Impala felt wide open in the fifty-degree air and the smell of freshly fallen leaves.
I drove through Forest Park feeling the rhythm of the yellow street lights as I moved between light and dark. &amp;ldquo;Memory&amp;rdquo; from Cats came on the radio. I lit a Camel (no filter).
I was free.

In America, we often think of independence as a collective thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Must Evangelize Liberty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/why-we-must-evangelize-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 20:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/why-we-must-evangelize-liberty/</guid>
      <description>Earlier I linked to Glenn Reynolds’s Examiner column about the hard work that lies ahead for Tea Partyers. If you haven’t read that piece, do so after reading this.
At Tea Party marches and rallies, we are surrounded by others who understand and cherish liberty. We know the horrors that occur when a government loses accountability to and, yes, fear of the people they govern. Such regimes become murderous, intolerant, and repressive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>