<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>liberty on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/liberty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in liberty on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 14:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/liberty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Which Freedoms Are We Losing? </title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/29/just-freedoms-losing/</guid>
      <description>I confess.
When I write about freedoms lost, I don&amp;rsquo;t itemize the freedoms. I don&amp;rsquo;t feel too bad, though, because almost no one does. Itemizing sucks.
First, it&amp;rsquo;s hard work. &amp;ldquo;Losing freedom,&amp;rdquo; takes about three seconds to type and less time to read. Listing freedoms,on the other hand, takes that much time just to highlight all the freedoms and click the un-ordered list button. God forbid I find myself working in straight HTML and have to hand-type &amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Government’s Surrender to Cliven Bundy Destroys Taleb’s Weak Argument for Gun Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</guid>
      <description>Events of the past week show the power of the Second Amendment to challenge government tyranny, regardless of the government’s firepower advantage. Let me back up, though.
A Smart Man’s Stupid Argument for Gun Control A year ago, the gun control lobby pumped a Facebook post by Nassim Nicholas Taleb, one of my favorite thinkers.
In his post, Taleb argued that the Second Amendment means nothing because the federal government has massively superior firepower:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Need a Stronger Third Eye</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/we-need-a-stronger-third-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 04:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/21/we-need-a-stronger-third-eye/</guid>
      <description>What do we look like to people who aren&amp;rsquo;t politics wonks? And why does it matter?
This question is for my friends on the right. By &amp;ldquo;on the right,&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m talking about conservatives and right-leaning libertarians. (I&amp;rsquo;m not going to debate definitions, so accept mine or stop reading.)
Developing a Third Eye When I was an acting student many long years ago, I had a director, Don Garner, who stressed the importance of the actor&amp;rsquo;s third eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head To Jefferson City Wednesday To Fight Common Core and Medicaid Expansion</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/09/fight-common-core-and-medicaid-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/09/fight-common-core-and-medicaid-expansion/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;196&amp;rdquo;] State Senator John Lamping is sponsoring a bill in the Missouri Legislature to curb privacy invasions built into Common Core State Standards. Missouri liberty groups will support him in Jefferson City on March 13.[/caption]
John Lamping is one of the brightest stars for liberty in the Missouri Senate, and he needs our help this week. Let&amp;rsquo;s support liberty by fighting Medicaid Expansion and Common Core State Standards in education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Planning Is Killing the Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</guid>
      <description>Friedrich Hayek warned more than half a century ago that central planning doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. Here’s why:
 * Central Planners (government) makes a plan * The plan includes specific expectations * The expectations are never, ever, realized * A “crisis” ensues * So the planners demand more control * And create more plans * Ad hoc * Willy nilly * Capriciously * So you must wait for things to settle down to make your decision  Today’s Wall Street Journal article about the fiscal cliff demonstrates the futility of central planning:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>