<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2011 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2011/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2011 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2011/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hennessy’s View of 2011</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/31/hennessys-view-of-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/31/hennessys-view-of-2011/</guid>
      <description>Here are the top Hennessy’s View posts of each month of 2012, scientifically selected by . . . me.

January
The Gabrielle Giffords shooting by lunatic Jerod Lee Loughner was the biggest news event of the month. The cynically attempted to use the tragedy for political gain. The left failed.
February
The Arab Spring began last winter. When Mubarak was on the ropes in Egypt, some questioned whether or not his fall would be good for the region and the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork For Me But Not For Thee</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/31/pork-for-me-but-not-for-thee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/31/pork-for-me-but-not-for-thee/</guid>
      <description>Some St. Louis area conservatives cheered Roy Blunt’s (R-MO) elevation to the Number 5 leadership position in the Senate Republican caucus.

I didn’t. At least not politically. I like Senator Blunt personally, so I’m happy in that respect. But I’m not happy for the reasons some others are.
First, as I told Jo Mannies of the St. Louis Beacon, internal party stuff isn’t really a Tea Party matter. Leadership in the Senate’s GOP caucus is for Republican Senators to worry about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the RCGA Is Ruining St. Louis and What Businesses Can Do About It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/29/how-the-rcga-is-ruining-st-louis-and-what-businesses-can-do-about-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 18:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/29/how-the-rcga-is-ruining-st-louis-and-what-businesses-can-do-about-it/</guid>
      <description>Everyone knows and accepts that government does stupid things. Sometimes it feels like people institute governments and delegate them certain powers just to give us something to complain about.
Government stupidity, scandal, and corruption hits different people in different ways. Government hyperactivity keeps poor people poor by limiting opportunity and by building barriers to exiting poverty programs. “If you take that job, you’ll lose your health insurance.” Compassion my non-qualifying asset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Scrooge Teaches Millennials</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/28/what-scrooge-teaches-millennials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/28/what-scrooge-teaches-millennials/</guid>
      <description>_This is the fourth in a series. If you haven’t, please read part 1, part 2, and part 3. _
Because so many school systems have driven great English literature out of students’ hands and minds, it’s possible that some kids never read Charles Dickens’s A Christmas Carol. If you’ve never read this classic, please do so now. You need it.

Back? Good. Fascinating stuff, isn’t it? And so much more accessible than David Copperfield, which was my introduction to Dickens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Government Growth Creates Scrooges</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/27/how-government-growth-creates-scrooges/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/27/how-government-growth-creates-scrooges/</guid>
      <description>Scrooge’s nephew left the office and let in two men in the process. They came to ask for a donation for London’s poor.
 &amp;ldquo;At this festive season of the year, Mr. Scrooge,&amp;rdquo; said the gentleman, taking up a pen, &amp;ldquo;it is more than usually desirable that we should make some slight provision for the Poor and destitute, who suffer greatly at the present time. Many thousands are in want of common necessaries; hundreds of thousands are in want of common comforts, sir.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>