<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dictator on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/dictator/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dictator on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 07:04:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/dictator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>America’s Dictator</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/12/americas-dictator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 07:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/12/americas-dictator/</guid>
      <description>From the New York Times:
 President Obama, who came to office promising transparency and adherence to the rule of law, has become the first president to claim the legal authority to order an American citizen killed without judicial involvement, real oversight or public accountability.
 In one sentence, the newspaper conservatives love to hate condemned Barack Obama to the title “dictator.”
Those who voted for him—the ones who still want to be thought of as “American”—will rationalize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Contempt for the Rule of Law</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/obamas-contempt-for-the-rule-of-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 10:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/obamas-contempt-for-the-rule-of-law/</guid>
      <description>When he identified the three branches of government as President, House, and Senate, Was Chuck Schumer confused, or did he accurately state the Obama administration’s intent to subjugate the Judicial Branch of government? It seems the White House no longer considers the Judicial Branch the equal of the Executive.
In two cases—the Gulf oil drilling ban and Obamacare—the White House refuses to obey ruling from federal judges. In New Orleans, federal judge Martin Feldman found the White House in contempt for its re-imposition of oil drilling bans after his previous ruling to the contrary.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>