<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dottie Bailey on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/dottie-bailey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dottie Bailey on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 07:42:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/dottie-bailey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations Representative Dottie Bailey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/congratulations-representative-dottie-bailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 07:42:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/congratulations-representative-dottie-bailey/</guid>
      <description>The one who has the bride is the bridegroom; the best man, who stands and listens for him, rejoices greatly at the bridegroom’s voice. So this joy of mine has been made complete. (Johhn 3:29)
 Yesterday, January 9, 2019, was a watershed day for everyone who ever associated with the St. Louis Tea Party Coalition. Your own Dottie Bailey was sworn in as Representative of the 110th State House district of Eureka, Wildwood, and Pacific.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember: Vote for Dottie Bailey in Wildwood, Eureka, Pacific MO</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/11/05/remember-vote-for-dottie-bailey-in-wildwood-eureka-pacific-mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 02:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/11/05/remember-vote-for-dottie-bailey-in-wildwood-eureka-pacific-mo/</guid>
      <description>You know why. I&amp;rsquo;ve told you repeatedly. You have one job tomorrow if you live in Eureka, Wildwood, or Pacific.
One job. VOTE FOR DOTTIE BAILEY, STATE HOUSE 110.
To make the sniveling legalists happy, I am treasurer for Dottie Bailey for Missouri. Please tweet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How will God answer our prayers?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/11/05/how-will-god-answer-our-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/11/05/how-will-god-answer-our-prayers/</guid>
      <description>How will God answer our prayers to make America holy again?
For 17 days we&amp;rsquo;ve been praying, going to confession, going to mass as often as we can. Rosaries. Chaplet of St. Michael. Tomorrow, election day, our back-to-back novenas wrap up.
Fr. Heilman asked his Spiritual Warriors to do as many of these daily devotions as possible:
 Pray in a State of Grace (Go to Confession) Believe God will answer our prayers October 20 – October 28 – Novena #1 – Pray the St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dottie Bailey Won</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/08/dottie-bailey-won/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 18:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/08/dottie-bailey-won/</guid>
      <description>Dottie Bailey defeated Rockwood School Board President Matt Doell in the Republican primary for Missouri House District 110. Dottie now faces Democrat Cody Kelley in November.
Dottie is a phenomenal campaigner. She knocked on over 4,000 doors between April and August. Her efforts resulted in an enormous 19 percentage-point win despite being outspent by her opponent. Making Dottie&amp;rsquo;s more impressive is the fact that Doell had been elected to the Rockwood board three times while this was Dottie&amp;rsquo;s first race ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Fast: Day 14</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/06/primary-fast-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 14:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/06/primary-fast-day-14/</guid>
      <description>You made it. If you began the Fast with me, today is the last day of skipping breakfast and lunch. (Unless you decide to makeone-meal-a-day a permanent habit.)
What Fasting Can Do Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened to you during the fast (if you followed the prescription):
 You probably lost about five pounds. Your pants feel looser. You pull your belt a notch tighter. You saved money. (I saved $98.)  You learned that food is an option most of the time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>