<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paul Ryan on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/paul-ryan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paul Ryan on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:17:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/paul-ryan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Ryan&#39;s Spokesperson Renounces Support for Antifa</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/31/paul-ryans-spokesperson-renounces-support-for-antifa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/31/paul-ryans-spokesperson-renounces-support-for-antifa/</guid>
      <description>It was probably a coincidence.
One day after Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View reported Speaker Paul &amp;ldquo;Dumbbell&amp;rdquo; Ryan as a member of the Antifa caliphate support team, Speaker Ryan&amp;rsquo;s office renounced his membership in the terrorist group&amp;rsquo;s fan club.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_23491&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;460&amp;rdquo;]Paul &amp;ldquo;Dumbbell&amp;rdquo; Ryan[/caption]
As reported by The Gateway Pundit:
 Social media was set ablaze after Paul Ryan attacked President Trump for condemning ‘both sides’ for the violence in Charlottesville. Trump supporters hammered Paul Ryan for refusing to condemn Antifa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Not Freaking Out About the Budget</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/02/why-im-not-freaking-out-about-the-budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 17:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/02/why-im-not-freaking-out-about-the-budget/</guid>
      <description>Congress is about to pass a budget. I call it a &amp;ldquo;Paul Ryan Special.&amp;rdquo; This budget lets the government spend money for four months. It expires in September.
The budget is horrible. Republicans are spinning a few &amp;ldquo;wins&amp;rdquo; in the budget, but that&amp;rsquo;s a terrible argument. It&amp;rsquo;s like telling a terminal cancer patient, &amp;ldquo;but your blood pressure&amp;rsquo;s pretty good.&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: you cannot control Congress. You can only control what you focus on and what you do next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Ryan&#39;s Battle of Kasserine Pass</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/paul-ryans-battle-of-kasserine-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 19:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/paul-ryans-battle-of-kasserine-pass/</guid>
      <description>General George S. Patton arrived in North Africa with a single mission: lead the Allied forces to victory over the Hun.
But Patton&amp;rsquo;s assignment was also in response to a miserable and deadly failure of leadership. The failed leadership of General Lloyd Fredendall.
 Fredendall was a Francophobe and an Anglophobe ill-suited to wage coalition warfare; a micromanager who bypassed the chain of command – giving orders as far down as company level; a coward, he allowed animus with subordinates to affect his judgment and undercut their authority; and finally, staring defeat in the face at Kasserine, he tried to pin the blame on others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare Repeal Vote Results (Prediction)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/23/obamacare-repeal-vote-results-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 03:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/23/obamacare-repeal-vote-results-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Today, President Trump changed the game. He changed the Prisoner&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma (coordination) into a game of Chicken (competition).
Lifer Republicans have no experience with games of chicken. They were raised on coordination games.
By changing the game to Chicken, Donald Trump greatly increased the chances that phony Paul Ryan&amp;rsquo;s healthcare will PASS.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why briefly.
Psychologically, people always think they have more time. Republicans, in particular, believe time is limitless. Lifelong Republicans think they can delay any decision until the decision they want is a given.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forgive Paul Ryan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/09/forgive-paul-ryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 05:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/06/09/forgive-paul-ryan/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people are mad at Paul Ryan. Millions of people want Mr. Ryan to step down as Speaker of the House. I am not mad at him. Paul Ryan is a victim of his circumstances, just like a lot of other Republicans.
Paul Ryan stepped up to a microphone this week and said what he was programmed to say. Essentially, Mr. Ryan said he&amp;rsquo;s not happy with Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s statements about a La Raza judge who started issuing anti-Trump rulings after Trump called on America to enforce its immigration laws.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>