<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>terrorism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/terrorism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in terrorism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 01:01:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/terrorism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama to America:  F**k You!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/21/obama-to-america-fk-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 01:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/21/obama-to-america-fk-you/</guid>
      <description>Bill Clinton began his presidency in a recession, promising to make a middle class tax cut and more jobs his laser-beam focus. But first, he let gays into the military and sent his wife off to socialize medicine. Barack Obama began his presidency during a borderline depression, promising to save the country from economic collapse, lowering the seas, and scripting quality endings to Stephen King&amp;rsquo;s movies. But first, he symbolically flipped off everyone affected by Islamofascist terrorists,snubbed military heroes, andredifined ethics as the way one behaves when the whole world&amp;rsquo;s watching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Favor Terrorists Over Constituents</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/21/democrats-favor-terrorists-over-constituents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2007 01:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/21/democrats-favor-terrorists-over-constituents/</guid>
      <description>I hyperbolize now and then, but not this time.
Democrats in the House and Senate voted to encourage criminal prosecution of Americans who report suspicious activity (Gateway Pundit). Do you know how difficult it is to formulate a more dramatic representation of that fact than the fact itself (Discerning Texan)?
I hate Democrats. Yeah, I know, you&amp;rsquo;re not supposed to &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; anyone. But Democrats are anti-American ass hats. They breed socialism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>