<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3rd anniversary tea party on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/3rd-anniversary-tea-party/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3rd anniversary tea party on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 12:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/3rd-anniversary-tea-party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd Anniversary Tea Party: Thank You!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/27/3rd-anniversary-tea-party-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/27/3rd-anniversary-tea-party-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>The 3rd Anniversary Tea Party rocked . . . because of the great patriot-activists who have decided it’s time to act and win.

Although Dr. Larry Schweikart couldn’t make it (because of the Chicago snow storm), Friday’s event was better than planned or expected. Tea Party champion Michael Patrick Leahy jumped into fill a last-minute void, and the crowd loved it.
  I had the the pleasure of reading and advanced copy of Mike Leahy&amp;rsquo;s new book, Covenant of Liberty: The Ideological Origins of the Tea Party Movement  in December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overtime</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/25/overtime-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2012 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/25/overtime-2/</guid>
      <description>Just because it’s after 10:00 am, doesn’t mean you can’t come to the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party.
No, we didn’t come up with a policy for people who arrive late to the feast. We will find a way to get you involved that’s fair to everyone.
Grab your laptop or your mobile device, if you have one, get in your car, and drive to the Crowne Plaza in Clayton. Ask for the Tea Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time’s Up!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/24/times-up-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/24/times-up-2/</guid>
      <description>The 3rd Anniversary Tea Party begins tonight at 6:30 at the Crowne Plaza in Clayton.
You can make a difference. But not alone. If you join forces with just three other people, you’ll triple your influence.
Show up. Bring two friends. Leave with a company a soldiers for the America’s liberation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Attend the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/23/why-attend-the-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/23/why-attend-the-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-2/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I’ve written about little else. The 3rd Anniversary Tea Party is something of an obsession with me. And for good reasons: * Obama is surging * Apathy has seized the right * America’s future hangs in the balance
But there’s a much bigger reason you—you, the person reading this blog—should attend the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party.
That reason is personal, powerful, and acute.
That reason is this:You cannot live with yourself if Obama wins and you failed to do everything in your power to stop him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You’re Almost Out of Time</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/22/youre-almost-out-of-time-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/22/youre-almost-out-of-time-2/</guid>
      <description>There will be only one 3rd Anniversary Tea Party, and it will be this coming Friday and Saturday, February 24 and 25. Today’s Wednesday. You have two days. Order today, because the future needs you.
This could be the only chance you get to learn about how the brain votes, how social media can change the outcome, how you can influence casual voters with minimal effort, how to caucus, and how 7 obscure events changed American history.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>