<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics Day on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics Day on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 21:30:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday Is Election Day. Here&#39;s What You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/01/tuesday-is-election-day-heres-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 21:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/04/01/tuesday-is-election-day-heres-what-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <description>Before I get to Election Day . . .
Join Bill Hennessy at The Creek in Washington, MO First, a plug.
Wednesday, April 3, 2013, at 5:30 p.m. I will be in Washington, Missouri, and you&amp;rsquo;re invited. I have the high honor and distinct privilege of speaking to the great women of Washington Federated Republican Women. at 5:30 p.m. I&amp;rsquo;ll be talking about Heritage Foundation, Heritage Action for America, and Blaine Luetkemeyer&amp;rsquo;s Brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is How To Spend Election Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/this-is-how-to-spend-election-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/this-is-how-to-spend-election-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives take great pride in working, and for good reason. Work gives shape to life. Work is the poles of a tent, the bones of a body, the beams in the ceiling.

But work isn’t why we live. We live to pursue happiness.
For some, the pursuit of happiness involves acquiring property. Land, clothes, cars, plastic surgery. All examples of the pursuit of happiness.
Voting is another pursuit. People vote for minor candidates representing strange parties who have no chance of winning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Maximize Your Election Influence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/how-to-maximize-your-election-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/04/how-to-maximize-your-election-influence/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s What To Do Today And On Election Day
Tuesday is the most important election of your life, but voting is never enough. You can have a bigger impact by using social proof to increase your influence. I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how, and it won&amp;rsquo;t take you long.
  First, though, make sure nothing gets in the way of exercising your duty to vote.
Studies have shown that you are more likely to vote if you answer these questions before Election Day:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Questions You Must Answer Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/01/3-questions-you-must-answer-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 16:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/01/3-questions-you-must-answer-right-now/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Missouri becomes the first state in the union to vote on ObamaCare. If being a Tea Partyer means anything, it means you vote Yes on Prop C on Tuesday. I urge not to wing it.
Most elections, I wake up and think “it’s election day.” Then I take a shower and go to work. I think about stopping to vote, but I don’t want to walk into the office at 9:00.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis County Votes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/05/st-louis-county-votes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 00:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/05/st-louis-county-votes/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow, Tuesday, April 6, is Election Day in St. Louis County. In some places, especially throughout South County, the only measure on the ballot is Proposition A: a sales tax increase.
Prop A’s backers—principally County Exec Charlie Dooley and Chesterfield Mayor John Nations—claim this tax increase of up to $650 per family will allow Metro to grow. You know otherwise.
* Dooley and Nations cannot point to a specific plan. They point to four.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>