<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>crash on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/crash/</link>
    <description>Recent content in crash on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 21:58:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/crash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 21:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/interrupt-world-war-democratic-fundraiser/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_14949&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;]&amp;ldquo;What, me worry?&amp;quot;[/caption]
Russian troops or Russian proxies murdered 293 people, today, including 23 Americans by many reports.
Israel was forced to invade Gaza to destroy tunnels Hamas uses to invade Israel and murder children.
The world teeters on the brink of all-out war.
But the President refused to cancel partisan fundraising efforts tonight.
Via The Blaze:
 At 2:25 p.m., the White House press office e-mailed a response to an inquiry from TheBlaze, “No scheduling changes to be reported at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This David Stockman Quote Should Scare the Hell Out of Everyone</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/05/this-david-stockman-quote-should-scare-the-hell-out-of-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/05/this-david-stockman-quote-should-scare-the-hell-out-of-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Is the US economy about to collapse worse the Greece’s?
Some, like Paul Krugman, say that it’s okay for governments to print unlimited money. Others, who have actually managed businesses, say otherwise.
**David Stockman is among the latter. He was Reagan’s budget director for a few years. He became a media sensation because of his command of numbers. **
He left the White House early, fretting over federal debt. But debt in the 1980s was as a piggy bank to Wells Fargo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>