<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CIA on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/cia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CIA on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 01:25:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/cia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the New York Times blackmailing FBI and CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 01:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</guid>
      <description>Sounds ridiculous, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
How could a reporter at New York Times blackmail an FBI or CIA agent?
Easily. And everyone who ever went through counter-espionage training knows it.
What Went Down This morning, British Prime Minister Theresa May chastised the US government. The UK freely shares anti-terrorism intelligence with the US. The US is expected to keep secrets secret.
But the US intel community is one gigantic sieve these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed: Coup Attempt Is Under Way In America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/14/confirmed-coup-attempt-is-under-way-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 13:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/14/confirmed-coup-attempt-is-under-way-in-america/</guid>
      <description>You might have thought I was paranoid for wondering if some people in the CIA and the Deep State are plotting a coup to overturn our recent election.
The Wall Street Journal seems to agree with my conclusion: a coup attempt is going on in America. Rogue actors within the CIA, all of the major leftist media (New York Times, Washington Post, CNN, NBC, ABC, CBS), and probably major defense contractors seem to be involved, though the Wall Street Journal stops short of accusing advertisers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Trump Might Never Become President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/12/why-trump-might-never-become-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 01:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/12/why-trump-might-never-become-president/</guid>
      <description>Call me paranoid, but it seems Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s chances of taking the oath of office for President are diminishing every day.
You might find yourself wondering why the CIA would plot a coup against Trump and his supporters. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t wondered about a CIA coup, you should.** Focus your awareness for a moment on what Trump means to the people of the Deep State.**
The Deep State involves those people and institutions that have insulated themselves from the consequences of elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the CIA Plotting a Coup? *UPDATE* FBI Disputes CIA Allegation - VIDEOS</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/11/is-the-cia-plotting-a-coup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/12/11/is-the-cia-plotting-a-coup/</guid>
      <description>Many powerful interests around the world loathe Donald Trump and the people who elected him. There&amp;rsquo;s no disputing that.
One of those powerful interests is the Central Intelligence Agency. One of the CIA&amp;rsquo;s own, Evan McMullin, attempted to disrupt the election. Like Bay of Pigs and Saddam&amp;rsquo;s weapons of mass destruction, that CIA plot failed. Even George Will admits the CIA makes some horrible, deadly mistakes. And sometimes those mistakes come from seeing the results they want to see, not the results presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When The Three O&#39;Clock Call Came, Barack Obama Froze</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</guid>
      <description>The fog of war is lifting from Benghazi, and what lies beneath should shame Obama’s most ardent supporters. Barack Obama choked, and Americans died.

When America came under attack, Obama panicked and froze.
When Americans under his direction pleaded for their lives, he was afraid to pull the trigger.
Here’s the emerging picture.
White House Ordered Military and CIA to Stand Down and Let Al Qaeda Kill Former Navy SEALs Ty Woods and Glen Doherty, so disgusted by the White House’s refusal to help Americans under attack, defied an order to stand down.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>