<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2020 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2020 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It Begins: Isolation, Fear, and Masks Make People Mean</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/it-begins-isolation-fear-and-masks-make-us-mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 09:28:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/it-begins-isolation-fear-and-masks-make-us-mean/</guid>
      <description>An ice cream parlor in Massachusetts closed one day after re-opening because customers treated his employees like dirt.
Owner Mark Lawrence told Fox25 Boston, via Fox News:
 “People have forgotten how to treat other human beings in the six or seven weeks that they’ve been confined to their homes,” he told the station. “They have no clue how to respect other human beings.”
 After just one day, Lawrence closed his shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Efficiency Caused Food and Toilet Paper Shortages</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/how-efficiency-caused-food-shortages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 09:08:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/how-efficiency-caused-food-shortages/</guid>
      <description>If you work for corporation, you&amp;rsquo;ve undoubtedly heard about the virtues of efficiency. And, if you&amp;rsquo;re living in America, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably noticed shortages of stables like meat, packaged food, cleaning supplies, toilet paper, and more.
What you probably don&amp;rsquo;t realize is that business&amp;rsquo;s pathological concerns for efficiency caused the shortages. And, what&amp;rsquo;s worse, most of the &amp;ldquo;expert&amp;rdquo; recommendations for dealing with pandemics will put us all at risk for precisely the same reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Triumphant</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 04:56:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/trump-triumphant/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump just had another one of those weeks for which he&amp;rsquo;s become famous.
 There was the week hit bombed Syria while dining with President Xi of China at Mar a Lago. There was Easter Week 2019 when the Mueller Report exonerated and the economy hit new highs. There was the week of the State of the Union Address that included his exoneration in the Senate.  But, this week&amp;rsquo;s outbreak of liberty and its commensurate exposure of Trump&amp;rsquo;s enemies as pure scum is the best so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Is on the Verge of Depression</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/america-on-verge-of-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 11:36:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/america-on-verge-of-depression/</guid>
      <description>The Congressional Budget Office release a report yesterday (April 24, 2020) that expects our response to Coronavirus will wipe out 40 percent of the US economy and throw 27 million Americans into long-term unemployment. We could see unemployment rates of 20 percent or more for a decade.
The Last Depression My parents were born in 1925. Their understanding of the world was shaped by the Great Depression and World War II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunlight Kills Coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/sunlight-kills-coronavirus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 19:12:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/sunlight-kills-coronavirus/</guid>
      <description>An expert is someone who can&amp;rsquo;t be fired for being wrong about everything 100 percent of the time.
You can call that Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s Law, and Coronavirus is proving this law iron clad. Iron clad.
The latest confirmation of Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s Law just completed.
In March, Donald Trump and others said that warm weather would diminish the spread of Coronavirus, just as it diminishes the flu. The reason: virus that survive well in cool, dry conditions don&amp;rsquo;t do well in warm, humid conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>