<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Washington on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/washington/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Washington on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 01:25:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/washington/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Time To End War On Weed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/01/its-time-to-end-war-on-weed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/01/its-time-to-end-war-on-weed/</guid>
      <description>When in the course of human events it becomes necessary for conservatives to divorce themselves from superstitions they’ve embraced since the Progressive Movement of the 1920s and join the pantheon of reasonable people, a decent respect to the opinions of mankind requires that they should declare the causes which impel them to the separation.
I hold these truths to be totally friggin’ obvious, that all drugs are not created equal, that we’ve wasted billions of dollars and millions of lives pursuing a** demented “zero tolerance” temperance goal that was Never Going To Happen**, that the losses we’ve endured trying stamp out weed have cost American society more than they&amp;rsquo;ve gained, that among these losses are lives, money, and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is The Infographic That The Whole Republican Party Is Freaking Out About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</guid>
      <description>The 3 million McCain voters who didn’t vote for Romney?
They’re dead.

[Click image to view full size. Please forward, download, and print. This is important.]
To survive, the GOP needs to stop being afraid of Millennials and tell them truth: they can move out of mom and dad’s house, they can drop out of school, they can quit their dead-end job with the idiot supervisor. But they can’t get away from government and debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Rock the Election Like Scott Walker and Richard Mourdock</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/08/how-to-rock-the-election-like-scott-walker-and-richard-mourdock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 20:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/08/how-to-rock-the-election-like-scott-walker-and-richard-mourdock/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] The Gadsden flag (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
We&amp;rsquo;re past Empty Chair Day. The conventions are over. Barack Obama still stands between us and liberty. And the Establishment&amp;rsquo;s more worried about its $$$ future than about America&amp;rsquo;s future.
What does that mean? It means _you and I _ will determine what happens in Election 2012 and beyond.
If you want to have a hand in America&amp;rsquo;s future, listen up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Have No Idea How Much Your Boss Pays in Payroll Taxes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/you-have-no-idea-how-much-your-boss-pays-in-payroll-taxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 09:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/14/you-have-no-idea-how-much-your-boss-pays-in-payroll-taxes/</guid>
      <description>America is suffocating under an amazing tax burden, but most Americans STILL underestimate how much their tax bill really is. That’s because Washington has done a fantastic job of forcing employers to hide most of the taxes you pay. If people had to see and deal with their total liability, the Democratic Party would be swept into the dust bin of history.

Here are some frightening facts from Rasmussen:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>