<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>oil prices on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/oil-prices/</link>
    <description>Recent content in oil prices on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/oil-prices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Forcing Functions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/01/forcing-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/01/forcing-functions/</guid>
      <description>An old boss of mine liked “forcing functions.” Forced us to meet delivery dates, while arbitrary dates tended to cause a “so what” attitude toward deadlines. Forcing functions like trade shows, magazine reviews, and client launches forced development teams to ship, no matter what.
Keep that in mind for a moment while we look at the Obama Administration.
Barack Obama campaigned on a promise to clip America’s wings. I know he didn’t use that term, but it was clear what he meant when he visited the Mediterranean and Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s 1978 All Over Again **UPDATE: Thaddeus McCotter Agrees With Me**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/28/its-1978-all-over-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 22:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/28/its-1978-all-over-again/</guid>
      <description>The news might seem unimportant to us in the USA:
 Day after day they marched, tens of thousands strong, defiant chanting demonstrators surging through the streets of Cairo, a capital unaccustomed to the shouts and echoes of dissent. The subject of their protest was the policies of Egypt’s supreme ruler, Hosni Mubarak. Some carried signs demanding his ouster. Others called for a return of long denied civil and political liberties and the enforcement of Islamic laws.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>