<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>American Tea Party on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/american-tea-party/</link>
    <description>Recent content in American Tea Party on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 02:26:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/american-tea-party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cincinnati Tea Party HUGE</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/15/cincinnati-tea-party-huge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 02:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/15/cincinnati-tea-party-huge/</guid>
      <description>Michelle Malkin has impressive photos from the Cincinnati Tea Party. Thousands upon thousands of angry tax payers.
Perhaps they were spurred on by Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s accusation that anyone who has done well financially in the past 8 years is a criminal who will be punished. Directly from his budget, page 5:
 While middle-class families have been playing by the rules, living up to their responsibilities as neighbors and citizens,_ those at the commanding heights of our economy have not_.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Your Tax Day Tea Party Apparel and Stickers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/14/get-your-tax-day-tea-party-apparel-and-stickers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2009 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/14/get-your-tax-day-tea-party-apparel-and-stickers/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Tax Day Tea Party store is open! Proceeds will keep the movement going forward.
This is a 10-round fight that will bring about a truly conservative House of Representatives in 2010. You&amp;rsquo;ve already done much just by visiting this site and attending the rallies. Now, show the whole world that you&amp;rsquo;re fed up with an irresponsible, tax-and-spend government that has grown beyond the consent of the governed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell the World You Support the Tea Party Movement</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/07/tell-the-world-you-support-the-tea-party-movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 14:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/07/tell-the-world-you-support-the-tea-party-movement/</guid>
      <description>Cafe Press has dozens of shirts, stickers, and mugs that let you tell the world you belong to the Tea Party Movement.
The lefties proudly wear their Che t-shirts and those idiotic coexist bumper stickers. Conservatives shy away from Public Displays of Protest.
NO LONGER!
While we&amp;rsquo;re brewing up some St. Louis-flavored Tea Party logos, grab the generics now. You&amp;rsquo;re kids will thank you some day.
Technorati Tags: tea party,spirit wear</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Dispatch Out of Touch (no matter what Eric Mink says)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/07/st-louis-post-dispatch-does-not-like-criticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 14:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/07/st-louis-post-dispatch-does-not-like-criticism/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Post-Dispatch was once a powerful, respected cornerstone of the Pulitzer publishing company. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s little more than a community newspaper. Some near-tomorrow, it will go the way of Rocky Mountain News. Its demise can be traced in large measure to the arrogance of its editorial board.
Take Eric Mink. This is a man who rose through the organization by leveling unfair, nearly libelous attacks on anyone who deviated from Mink&amp;rsquo;s party line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, I Make the New York Times</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/02/hey-i-make-the-new-york-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/02/hey-i-make-the-new-york-times/</guid>
      <description>And I didn&amp;rsquo;t even have to shoot anybody.
The Tea Party Movement will make history books, people. I&amp;rsquo;m telling you now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>