<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>American Tea Party on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/american-tea-party/</link>
    <description>Recent content in American Tea Party on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 02:26:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/american-tea-party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cincinnati Tea Party HUGE</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/15/cincinnati-tea-party-huge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 02:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/15/cincinnati-tea-party-huge/</guid>
      <description>Michelle Malkin has impressive photos from the Cincinnati Tea Party. Thousands upon thousands of angry tax payers.
Perhaps they were spurred on by Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s accusation that anyone who has done well financially in the past 8 years is a criminal who will be punished. Directly from his budget, page 5:
 While middle-class families have been playing by the rules, living up to their responsibilities as neighbors and citizens,_ those at the commanding heights of our economy have not_.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Your Tax Day Tea Party Apparel and Stickers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/14/get-your-tax-day-tea-party-apparel-and-stickers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2009 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/14/get-your-tax-day-tea-party-apparel-and-stickers/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Tax Day Tea Party store is open! Proceeds will keep the movement going forward.
This is a 10-round fight that will bring about a truly conservative House of Representatives in 2010. You&amp;rsquo;ve already done much just by visiting this site and attending the rallies. Now, show the whole world that you&amp;rsquo;re fed up with an irresponsible, tax-and-spend government that has grown beyond the consent of the governed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell the World You Support the Tea Party Movement</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/07/tell-the-world-you-support-the-tea-party-movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 14:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/07/tell-the-world-you-support-the-tea-party-movement/</guid>
      <description>Cafe Press has dozens of shirts, stickers, and mugs that let you tell the world you belong to the Tea Party Movement.
The lefties proudly wear their Che t-shirts and those idiotic coexist bumper stickers. Conservatives shy away from Public Displays of Protest.
NO LONGER!
While we&amp;rsquo;re brewing up some St. Louis-flavored Tea Party logos, grab the generics now. You&amp;rsquo;re kids will thank you some day.
Technorati Tags: tea party,spirit wear</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Dispatch Out of Touch (no matter what Eric Mink says)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/07/st-louis-post-dispatch-does-not-like-criticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 14:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/07/st-louis-post-dispatch-does-not-like-criticism/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Post-Dispatch was once a powerful, respected cornerstone of the Pulitzer publishing company. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s little more than a community newspaper. Some near-tomorrow, it will go the way of Rocky Mountain News. Its demise can be traced in large measure to the arrogance of its editorial board.
Take Eric Mink. This is a man who rose through the organization by leveling unfair, nearly libelous attacks on anyone who deviated from Mink&amp;rsquo;s party line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, I Make the New York Times</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/02/hey-i-make-the-new-york-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/02/hey-i-make-the-new-york-times/</guid>
      <description>And I didn&amp;rsquo;t even have to shoot anybody.
The Tea Party Movement will make history books, people. I&amp;rsquo;m telling you now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Approval in Free Fall</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/01/obamas-approval-in-free-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/01/obamas-approval-in-free-fall/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;405&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Obama&amp;rsquo;s Approval Free Fall&amp;rdquo;][/caption]
Barack Obama is now less popular than George W. Bush at the same point in their respective presidencies according to Rasmussen.
The poll also indicates that deficits are more important to Americans than anything else. This could be the result of theTea Party movement which drew more than 30,000 people in 40 cities to take to the streets over the weekend.
At this rate, Obama&amp;rsquo;s overall popularity will turn net negative this time next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tax Day Tea Party and other news</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/01/tax-day-tea-party-and-other-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 19:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/01/tax-day-tea-party-and-other-news/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE: NOTHING TENTATIVE ABOUT IT
Repeal the Pork and Cut Taxes
The next Tea Party event is April 15: Tax Day. Learn more at Tax Day Tea Party. Register for the St. Louis event on FaceBook today. Tell your friends. Possible locations include the Old Courthouse in St. Louis, the Federal Reserve Building, and several others. LOCATION: KIENER PLAZA, St. Louis, MO 63101
Repeal the Pork and Learn the Constitution</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Budget Threatens American Sovereignty *update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/01/obamas-budget-threatens-american-sovereignty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 15:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/01/obamas-budget-threatens-american-sovereignty/</guid>
      <description>The immediacy of our challenge in defending the Republic against Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s socialist,one-world ambitions reached new levels over the weekend.
UPDATE: The eminent domain story appears to be a hoax. My apologies. I found it on several blogs that are generally reliable, so I assume the hoaxter is good at his craft
Eminent Domain Rights to China*
First, as Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View has predicted for months, the rate and size of US borrowing has reduced Uncle Sam&amp;rsquo;s credit worthiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video of St. Louis Event--Almost as Good as Being There *update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/video-of-st-louis-event-almost-as-good-as-being-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 23:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/video-of-st-louis-event-almost-as-good-as-being-there/</guid>
      <description>My hat&amp;rsquo;s off to Bob Anders and the crew from Creative Video Services for this 3-part series of the St. Louis Nationwide Chicago Tea Party protest held February 27, 2009. If you need videography, you can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with Creative Video.
Part I: https://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=3408578&amp;amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;amp;show_title=1&amp;amp;show_byline=1&amp;amp;show_portrait=0&amp;amp;color=&amp;amp;fullscreen=1 St. Louis Tea Party (Part 1) from CR8VDO on Vimeo.
Click here for Parts 2 and 3.
Dana has lots of great links. UPDATES
   It was a 3-part, not 4-part video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City: 200&#43; Marching in the Snow</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/kansas-city-200-marching-in-the-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 21:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/kansas-city-200-marching-in-the-snow/</guid>
      <description>More than 200 hearty patriots marched through driving snow and 20 degree temps in Kansas City today as part of the ongoing Tea Party Protest.
Congratulations to the organizers and demonstrators. You&amp;rsquo;re simple act of rebellion against Obama&amp;rsquo;s socialist power-grab is a noble statement of your intent to preserve and defend our Republic.
 [caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;314&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Snow won&amp;rsquo;t stop the patriots in Kansas City. &amp;ldquo;][/caption]
  I will post photos as soon as they are uploaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow-Thru Afterglow</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/flow-thru-afterglow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/flow-thru-afterglow/</guid>
      <description>Dangerous Thoughts Standing in the Wings
_Why are you here? _I thought.
I was standing on the steps of the Arch fully aware that my fingers were painfully cold when the wrong thought crossed my mind. By &amp;ldquo;wrong thought,&amp;rdquo; I mean that one thought that will subconsciously sabotage the important or dangerous thing you are about to attempt. Like thinking, &amp;ldquo;what if the front wheel just fell off?&amp;rdquo; as you&amp;rsquo;re cruising down a winding road on a motorcycle, or &amp;ldquo;what if I forget my lines?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Tea Party Turnout Rocks!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-turnout-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 20:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-turnout-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the 1,000+ patriots who stood in the snow at the Arch, Dana &amp;ldquo;The Energizer&amp;rdquo; Loesch, Doug Saur, the speakers, Michelle Moore and Jeff who managed the fairgrounds, Desiree&amp;rsquo; the Poster Party Lady, and the true leaders at #TCOT who held my hand after I stumbled into this event. Today at the Arch in St. Louis was simple patriotic magic. I have to do some wrapping up of the event, but I&amp;rsquo;ll say this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Tea Party Live Feed All Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-live-feed-all-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 14:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-live-feed-all-day/</guid>
      <description>Stay on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View for continous live coverage of the St. Louis Tea Party
https://www.ustream.tv/flash/live/1/528594Free TV : Ustream</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the World with Twitter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/25/how-to-change-the-world-with-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 02:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/25/how-to-change-the-world-with-twitter/</guid>
      <description>My light blogging owes to our efforts to change the world in a week. My role is, appropriately, miniscule.
When Congress listens, it will repeal the trillions of waste, fraud, and abuse it has produced over the past 4 months, it will stop proposed borrowing and bailouts, it will stop rewarding bad behavior in corporations and citizens, or it will retire. This time, there are no two ways.
 Using tools like Twitter, email, and Facebook, TCOT has provided at least 163 patriots a forum to voice its discontent on Friday, February 27 at 11:00 a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Sczesny Rocks, and other Tea Party News</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/24/matt-sczesny-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 04:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/24/matt-sczesny-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Great coverage of the St. Louis Tea Party on KMOV Channel 4 by reporter Matt Sczesny. Channel 4 has not posted the video (that I can find). I&amp;rsquo;ll link or embed it as soon as it&amp;rsquo;s available.
Please say &amp;ldquo;thanks&amp;rdquo; to Matt and KMOV for a fair report.
 Amy at Top Conservatives on Twitter has put together a convenient list of the Tea Parties across the country. This list is NOT exhaustive, as not all cities have a Facebook Event page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See Dana&#39;s Channel 5 Interview</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/24/see-danas-channel-5-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 04:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/24/see-danas-channel-5-interview/</guid>
      <description>Go Dana. How &amp;lsquo;bout a little equal time? Why does the WU prof get 80 percent of the time?
DELETED VIDEO EMBED
I detest videos that start automatically. You can see the report on KSDK&amp;rsquo;s web site. Not the best coverage, certainly not fair, but publicity is publicity. So thanks to Rebecca for visiting with Dana and selecting 7 seconds of the interview to air ahead of 30 minutes of some college professor who wrote a book in his spare time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Blogging Barry&#39;s Crappy Reagan Imitation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/24/live-blogging-barrys-crappy-reagan-imitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 02:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/24/live-blogging-barrys-crappy-reagan-imitation/</guid>
      <description>The future is ours. Your disgust with the borrowing and spending, your noble desire to restore the republic the founders wrought, those are the real protests. The tea party is in our hearts and souls&amp;ndash;the events are just the physical manifestations. But now, the President:
Ninety percent of live blog posts suck. So I did my blog readers a big favor: I tested my quips on Twitter. Here I present my instant reactions that were good enough to get retweeted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See me on PJTV</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/23/see-me-on-pjtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 03:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/23/see-me-on-pjtv/</guid>
      <description>I look like a burrowing creature, but I made it through the toughest interview of my life. (Not really)
PJTV.com
Forward to friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Barry’s Adding Machine Stimulator Regulation Gimmick</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/23/uncle-barrys-adding-machine-stimulator-regulation-gimmick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 02:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/23/uncle-barrys-adding-machine-stimulator-regulation-gimmick/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, shortly after his inauguration, Barry “The President” Obama panicked: the Republicans might talk the people out of the stimulus bill.
Barry moved quickly. But Barry is an organizer, not an engineer. He’s the cheerleader, not the quarterback. He moves mobs, not nations. And when panicked, he fell apart.
Barry decided to announce that life as we know it would economically end the Day After The Stimulus Bill Is Defeated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>