<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Living on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/living/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Living on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 15:59:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/living/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Significant: CDC Death Count Inflated by 25% per Dr. Birx</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/cdc-death-count-inflated-by-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 15:59:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/cdc-death-count-inflated-by-25/</guid>
      <description>We have all come to know some things about Dr. Deborah Birx, the doctor responsible for the White House&amp;rsquo;s Coronavirus response. Her clear explanations often highlighted the nightly White House Coronavirus Task Force press conferences.
Night after night, we watched and listened as Dr. Birx carefully explained complex statistical and medical information in a way even a reporter could understand. Her style is considered and precise. Understatement and exaggeration seem genetic impossibilities for Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Louis: More People Shot Than Diagnosed with Coronavirus Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-more-shot-than-diagnosed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 17:59:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-more-shot-than-diagnosed/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, May 9, in St. Louis, more people were shot than diagnosed with Coronavirus. Two died from gunshot wounds. The other eight are alive in unknown or unreported condition.
Via the Washington Times:
 Authorities say at least 10 people were shot, two of them fatally, in a single day in St. Louis.
  The St. Louis Post-Dispatch reports that the the gunfire began around 1:15 p.m. Saturday when a 28-year-old man was fatally shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons Why theFourth Stimulus Bill Is Not a Bill at All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/fourth-stimulus-bill-is-not-a-bill-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 12:29:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/fourth-stimulus-bill-is-not-a-bill-at-all/</guid>
      <description>Everybody&amp;rsquo;s talking about the fourth stimulus bill. Infrastructure. Payroll tax cut. Vote by mail.
But there won&amp;rsquo;t be one.
There will be a stimulus, but it will not come from Congress. The fourth stimulus will come from you and me.
There are three reasons for this, which I will get to in a moment. But, first, do me a favor: Please share this post with your members of Congress. It&amp;rsquo;s that important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Begins: Isolation, Fear, and Masks Make People Mean</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/it-begins-isolation-fear-and-masks-make-us-mean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 09:28:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/it-begins-isolation-fear-and-masks-make-us-mean/</guid>
      <description>An ice cream parlor in Massachusetts closed one day after re-opening because customers treated his employees like dirt.
Owner Mark Lawrence told Fox25 Boston, via Fox News:
 “People have forgotten how to treat other human beings in the six or seven weeks that they’ve been confined to their homes,” he told the station. “They have no clue how to respect other human beings.”
 After just one day, Lawrence closed his shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forbidden Secrets of Coronavirus Data Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:21:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/forbidden-secrets-of-coronavirus-data-manipulation/</guid>
      <description>Nate Silver let the cat out of the bag.
In case you don&amp;rsquo;t recognize his name, Nate Silver is the data analyst who launched Five Thirty-Eight, orignally in the New York Times. He was famous for not predicting an election a few years ago.
Today, Nate unloaded on the media for just one aspect of their narrative-driven Coronavirus coverage. In short, noted the same thing Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View pointed out a month ago: positive tests is meaningless unless it&amp;rsquo;s indexed to the number of tests administered.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>