<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>medicaid expansion on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/medicaid-expansion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in medicaid expansion on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 02:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/medicaid-expansion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashcroft Passes on Opportunity to Deny Medicaid Expansion Fix</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/16/ashcroft-passes-opportunity-deny-medicaid-expansion-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 02:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/16/ashcroft-passes-opportunity-deny-medicaid-expansion-fix/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I wrote about the Missouri Republican Establishment&amp;rsquo;s plan to win a windfall for lobbyist Kit Bond via Senate candidate Jay Ashcroft. Not that the Establishment cares about Bond, but they want Medicaid expansion passed before they beg for money for 2016 from the Missouri Hospital Association and Chamber of Commerce.
Well, the St. Louis Post Dispatch asked Ashcroft about the deal, and he couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite bring himself to deny that he would pass Medicaid expansion if elected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head To Jefferson City Wednesday To Fight Common Core and Medicaid Expansion</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/09/fight-common-core-and-medicaid-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/09/fight-common-core-and-medicaid-expansion/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;196&amp;rdquo;] State Senator John Lamping is sponsoring a bill in the Missouri Legislature to curb privacy invasions built into Common Core State Standards. Missouri liberty groups will support him in Jefferson City on March 13.[/caption]
John Lamping is one of the brightest stars for liberty in the Missouri Senate, and he needs our help this week. Let&amp;rsquo;s support liberty by fighting Medicaid Expansion and Common Core State Standards in education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weednesday Post: Why The GOP Needs To Champion Marijuana Law Reform</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/27/weednesday-post-why-the-gop-needs-to-champion-marijuana-law-reform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/27/weednesday-post-why-the-gop-needs-to-champion-marijuana-law-reform/</guid>
      <description>**If Republicans want to put their liberty where their mouths are, they can begin by ending the war on weed. **
When I was a kid in South St. Louis in the 70s, marijuana was the weed in the field that separated traditional post-war American values from the hippies. It was an easy black-and-white issue: smoke dope, you’re un-American. It was the Boomers against the Greatest Generation, and no one questioned the pure evil of pot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Prostitutes In Business Suits Cost Ed Martin A Place On The Rules Committee?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/23/did-prostitutes-in-business-suits-cost-ed-martin-a-place-on-the-rules-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 16:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/23/did-prostitutes-in-business-suits-cost-ed-martin-a-place-on-the-rules-committee/</guid>
      <description>You probably never heard of Lance Beshore of Joplin, MO. He’s been Missouri’s delegate to the Republican National Committee’s Rules Committee for 12 years. He runs the lobbying department of Leggett &amp;amp; Platt furniture company. He’s on the Missouri Chamber of Commerce, and he’s chairman of the board of Freeman Health Systems.

In his roles at Freeman and the Missouri Chamber, Beshore advocates for Obamacare Medicaid Expansion in Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Let Missouri’s Businesspeople Become Prostitutes in Business Suits</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/02/dont-let-missouris-businesspeople-become-prostitutes-in-business-suits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 18:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/02/dont-let-missouris-businesspeople-become-prostitutes-in-business-suits/</guid>
      <description>Why would the Missouri Chamber of Commerce want to expand Obamacare in Missouri? Short-sighted pursuit of money.

The Missouri Chambermaids of Cronyism Here’s the simple truth: the Missouri Chamber of Commerce is not conservative. It does not exist to advance limited government and fiscal responsibility and free enterprise capitalism. The Missouri Chamber of Commerce has become convinced that it must lie down before government and beg for scraps from the federal table.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>