<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ed martin on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/ed-martin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ed martin on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 14:38:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/ed-martin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Erick Erickson Protecting Reince Priebus?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 22:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE:
Welcome, Donald Trump fans! Thanks for reading.
Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s true, I have had disagreements with Erick in the past. I try to assess the situation, not just the person. It&amp;rsquo;s possible to disagree with someone on one subject and to agree with them on another.
If anything, Erick showed consistency by rescinding Trump&amp;rsquo;s invitation to Red State. Erick didn&amp;rsquo;t want the event to descend into chaos led by my friends over the Barbour episode; he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a descent into chaos led by Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin Moves to Censure Henry Barbour Over Racist Mississippi Ads</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/ed-martin-moves-censure-henry-barbour-racist-mississippi-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 04:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/ed-martin-moves-censure-henry-barbour-racist-mississippi-ads/</guid>
      <description>Go Ed!
A few weeks ago, hunkered down at my laptop in my hotel room in Jacksonville, Florida. I was exhausted from seven hours of travel and a time change. But I had to take a moment to recognize Ed Martin&amp;rsquo;s commitment to all the best the Republican Party stands for.
Ed is determined to expose the GOP establishment&amp;rsquo;s willingness to do anything to destroy grassroots insurgents. Thad Cochran&amp;rsquo;s forces in Mississippi threw ethics, morality, and decency to the wind in their quest to stop a Tea Party candidate from unseating the 128-term Cochran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Fascinating Results In The Missouri Primary</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/10-curious-results-missouri-primary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/10-curious-results-missouri-primary/</guid>
      <description>CORRECTION: My sincerest apologies for an inexcusable error in this post earlier. I erroneously congratulated my friend Martin Baker in the US House 1st District primary. I understand that Martin was about 500 votes short. I failed to verify information I received on the race, and I apologize for my irresponsibility.
Well, this got people talking. (See the comments.)
Yesterday was the Missouri Primary. Congratulations to Rick Stream and Jay Ashcrofton their wins in contested races for St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s Why John Danforth&#39;s Attack On Ed Martin Is So Bad for the GOP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/16/dear-senator-danforth-rockefeller-is-dead-and-so-is-your-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 04:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/16/dear-senator-danforth-rockefeller-is-dead-and-so-is-your-message/</guid>
      <description>Old Jack Danforth is a troubled man.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_13392&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] &amp;ldquo;You once called me a &amp;lsquo;warped, frustrated old man.&amp;rsquo; Well, what are you, but a warped, frustrated young man?&amp;rdquo;
John Danforth Attacked Ed Martin for Supporting Rand Paul[/caption]
Danforth&amp;rsquo;s wiry frame got bent all out of shape because the chairman of Missouri’s GOP stated the uber-obvious in an email to friends: the McCain-Graham angry old man meme ain’t sellin’ no more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shane Schoeller Is The New MOGOP Executive Director And That’s Great News For Missouri Republicans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/28/shane-schoeller-is-the-new-mogop-executive-director-and-thats-great-news-for-missouri-republicans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/28/shane-schoeller-is-the-new-mogop-executive-director-and-thats-great-news-for-missouri-republicans/</guid>
      <description>Shane Schoeller narrowly missed winning the job he and I wish he had: Missouri Secretary of State. Shane lost—along with every other non-incumbent Republican for a statewide office.
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;560&amp;rdquo;] Shane Schoeller becomes the new Missouri Republican Party Executive Director. Party Chairman Ed Martin made the announcement on February 28, 2013[/caption]
The good news is that Missouri Republican Chairman, Ed Martin, has tapped Shane Schoeller as the party’s Executive Director.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>