<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 08:56:10 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pray for Our Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/28/pray-for-our-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 09:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/28/pray-for-our-nation/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I missed it.
A 54-day novena for our nation. It ends on October 7 with the Rosary Coast-to-Coast. Which means it started before I learned of either. But that&amp;rsquo;s okay. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to do the novena to do say the Rosary. Just show up at any of the Rosary stations around the area at 3:00 on October 7. I&amp;rsquo;m helping organize one location at the Black Madonna Shrine in Eureka/Pacific area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Fast on Sundays</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/28/dont-fast-on-sundays/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 13:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/07/28/dont-fast-on-sundays/</guid>
      <description>Many years ago, a company hired a new president.
After several months on the job, this new president learned that most of his employees couldn&amp;rsquo;t pick him out of a line-up. He spent so much time in his office or in meetings or traveling that he rarely met with the people who reported to him.
To fix this problem, he set up a series of lunches. They were off-site at restaurants around town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s what will happen in 2018 election (POLL)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/30/heres-what-will-happen-in-2018-election-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 16:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/30/heres-what-will-happen-in-2018-election-poll/</guid>
      <description>Do you think Democrats will retake the House, the Senate, or both in the 2018 election?
[socialpoll id=&amp;quot;2479812&amp;rdquo;]
Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve answered, let&amp;rsquo;s consider the limits of data science in 2018.
The best data scientists in the world agreed with nearly absolute certainty. These scientists determined, beyond a reasonable doubt, that Hillary Clinton would be the 45th President of the United States. That was in 2016.
Those scientists were wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Are Not the Enemy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/10/01/liberals-are-not-the-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/10/01/liberals-are-not-the-enemy/</guid>
      <description>Forgive me. I say &amp;ldquo;liberal&amp;rdquo; sometimes when I mean something else.
My mistake is habit, not irony. (Irony would require some intent on my part.)
I grew up disparaging liberalism. I grew up reading and watching William F. Buckley Jr., for whom liberalism was the enemy.
In the post-WWII era, the liberalism of the day was a problem. But it was never the problem.
The problem in Western Civilization was a faction that used liberalism as cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Can Stop the Antifa Caliphate?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/31/who-can-stop-the-antifa-caliphate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/31/who-can-stop-the-antifa-caliphate/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I explained the military strategy behind Antifa&amp;rsquo;s remarkable growth.
In case you didn&amp;rsquo;t realize it, Antifa has effectively shut down grass roots conservative speech. You cannot hold a public rally, march, or carnival if your views conflict with Antifa&amp;rsquo;s.
Antifa has established a small caliphate in North America. Just like ISIS did in Syria and Iraq.
And the government&amp;rsquo;s doing absolutely nothing about it. You should read my military strategy post and all the links.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>