<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tilley on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tilley/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tilley on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 02:03:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tilley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTION:  Steve Tilley and Kevin Engler Want to Implement Obamacare. Stop Them.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/03/action-steve-tilley-and-kevin-engler-want-to-implement-obamacare-stop-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 02:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/03/action-steve-tilley-and-kevin-engler-want-to-implement-obamacare-stop-them/</guid>
      <description>Missouri House Speaker Steve Tilley and Senate Leader Kevin Engler never tire of implementing Obama’s totalitarian agenda.

This time, Tilley and Engler are shoving HB 1193 through to passage. This bill is designed to score brownie points with Sibelius and Obama by creating a prescription spy network that monitors the prescription drug purchases of every Missouri resident.
If Tilley and Engler get their way, every time your doctor writes a prescription, your pharmacist will be required to inform Jefferson City and Washington bureaucrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Tilley vs. the Constitution</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/17/steve-tilley-vs-the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2011 18:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/17/steve-tilley-vs-the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>And, he’s back.
Missouri House Speaker Steve Tilley (R-Perryville) has signed onto legislation designed to circumvent the Electoral College in presidential elections. Like his position on embryonic stem cell research and the national debt, Tilley seems far out of step with Missouri’s Republican base on this. And this guy wants to be Lt. Governor? Please.
This might be old news to some.
I see that Big Government’s Josie Wales blogged about the national effort last August.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>