<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HillarysHealth on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/hillaryshealth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HillarysHealth on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 22:23:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/hillaryshealth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>More 1980 Election Parallels: Passing Out and Falling Down</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/12/more-1980-election-parallels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 22:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/12/more-1980-election-parallels/</guid>
      <description>The more you think about it, the more you realize 2016 gets more and more like 1980 every day.
As you ponder Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s fall from grace (even David Axelrod is trashing her now), you might remember Jimmy Carter&amp;rsquo;s collapse.
I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about his collapse on election night. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about one of the two incidents that psychologically destroyed Carter&amp;rsquo;s image as a leader. In a moment, I&amp;rsquo;ll remind you of the collapse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Press Has Let Us Down</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/11/how-the-press-has-let-us-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 03:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/11/how-the-press-has-let-us-down/</guid>
      <description>Earlier I said the press has covered up Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s horrible health problems. The press (or media as some call it) now admit as much. But they&amp;rsquo;re trying to weasel out of their culpability. See this line from an otherwise sound article on Commentary:
  While most serious people dismissed the rumors about Clinton’s health that were being circulated by Donald Trump’s supporters, what happened Sunday morning will deepen suspicions both about her health and whether her campaign has been telling the truth about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>