<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rathergate on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/rathergate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rathergate on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2004 01:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/rathergate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sugar Coat Memo is a Fraud</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/12/the-sugar-coat-memo-is-a-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2004 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/12/the-sugar-coat-memo-is-a-fraud/</guid>
      <description>Having spent 9 years as a Personnel Officer in the Navy, I can tell you that the Sugar Coat memo is likely a fraud. In that memo, Killian supposedly writes to himself that hes going to give Bush no marks for the period, but Killian had no choice. Thats the way fitreps work.
When an officer is away from his permanent duty station for a significant period portion of the reporting period, the reporting senior must submit a &amp;ldquo;not observed&amp;rdquo; report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS vs. The Press</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/cbs-vs-the-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/cbs-vs-the-press/</guid>
      <description>I watched the CBS Evening News tonight, so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see the competition. NBC and ABC were unable to find a single forensic document specialist who believe the documents on CBS News were legitimate. These included former FBI document experts now teaching forensics at universities.
Apparently, the only expert who thinks Jerry Killian typed and signed the CBS papers is the CBS employee featured on their broadcast tonight.
Funny&amp;ndash;the liberal press isn&amp;rsquo;t rallying to CBS&amp;rsquo;s side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan Rather Source of Documents?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/dan-rather-source-of-documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/dan-rather-source-of-documents/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I conjectured that Dan Rather fabricated the Bush ANG documents as a vendetta against the Bushes for 41&amp;rsquo;s undressing of Rather on the CBS Evening News in 1988&amp;ndash;the interview that turned the election in Bush&amp;rsquo;s favor. Apparently, I&amp;rsquo;m not alone. Here&amp;rsquo;s an interesting quote from Powerline:
 Last night, it was reported that senior executives at CBS News were promising an investigation. Today, Dan Rather is personally vouching for the documents&amp;rsquo; authenticity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Former Navy Personnel Officer Explains Why The &#34;Sugar Coat&#34; Memo is Likely a Fraud</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/former-navy-personnel-officer-explains-why-the-sugar-coat-memo-is-likely-a-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/10/former-navy-personnel-officer-explains-why-the-sugar-coat-memo-is-likely-a-fraud/</guid>
      <description>Something on TimeIsAFactor.com caught my attention.
One of the 4 CBS memos about George W. Bush&amp;rsquo;s National Guard service contains the following memo supposedly authored by his commanding officer:
&amp;ldquo;Bush wasn&amp;rsquo;t here during rating period and I don&amp;rsquo;t have any feedback from 187th in Alabama. I will not rate.&amp;rdquo;
Having spent 9 years as an enlisted Personnel Officer in the Navy, the marks on Bush&amp;rsquo;s fitness report for the period he was in Alabama are the only ones that could be entered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS and Dems Part 2:  Forged, Phoney Documents?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/09/cbs-and-dems-part-2-forged-phoney-documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/09/cbs-and-dems-part-2-forged-phoney-documents/</guid>
      <description>CNSNew.com is reporting that typography experts are fairly confident that documents exposed on CBS&amp;rsquo;s 60 Minutes II were fake. The documents, allegedly authored in 1972, used proportional fonts and superscript lettering, not widely available in 1972.
I am very familiar with the typewriter the Navy used in the 1980s: IBM Selectric III. It had changable font golfballs, one of which was proportional (CGTimes). But it looked awful. The proportional spacing was in consistent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>