<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>phyllis schlafly on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/phyllis-schlafly/</link>
    <description>Recent content in phyllis schlafly on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 10:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/phyllis-schlafly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hear Exactly What Jim Hoft and I Think of the Fake News Media</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/20/hear-exactly-what-jim-hoft-and-i-think-of-the-fake-news-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 10:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/20/hear-exactly-what-jim-hoft-and-i-think-of-the-fake-news-media/</guid>
      <description>. . . And It&amp;rsquo;s Deep-State Handlers Jim Hoft is a genius.
From his St. Louis home, Jim runs one of the most influential websites in the universe, according to Harvard researchers. He&amp;rsquo;s a legend. Like Andrew Breitbart, Jim Hoft reshaped the media. Hoft exposes the rotten bastards who call themselves &amp;ldquo;journalists.&amp;rdquo;
** Caustic Jim Acosta ** F*** Chuck Todd ** Jake &amp;ldquo;The Fake&amp;rdquo; Tapper ** Juannabe Williams
Jim Hoft exposed these knuckle-dragging liars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phyllis Schlafly, RIP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/05/phyllis-schlafly-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 23:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/05/phyllis-schlafly-rip/</guid>
      <description>If you asked me to define Phyllis Schlafly, my answered would be: &amp;ldquo;She wanted to destroy the king makers.&amp;rdquo;
Phyllis Schlafly, the conservative icon who roared to national prominence with her 1964 classic, A Choice, Not an Echo, passed away today, September 5, 2016. She was 92.
Eagle Forum, the pro-family, pro-American organization Phyllis launched in 1974, said in a statement:
 Phyllis Schlafly spent an astounding** 70 years in public service of her fellow Americans**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Can&#39;t the Establishment Fix America&#39;s Problems?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/11/14/why-cant-the-establishment-fix-americas-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 10:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/11/14/why-cant-the-establishment-fix-americas-problems/</guid>
      <description>America has but one political party capable of winning races on a scale large enough to change government practices: the Republican Party.
When the GOP takes Washington (or Jefferson City), things don&amp;rsquo;t seem to get better. Wonder why?
Let&amp;rsquo;s take a little stroll down memory lane.
 &amp;ldquo;To secure the nomination, the Dewey forces spent money and made deals and promises that Taft would never make. Offers were made of Federal jobs that Delegates could not resist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Moves for Herman Cain Supporters Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/25/top-5-moves-for-herman-cain-supporters-right-now/</guid>
      <description>Herman Cain is riding a wave of popularity because of his upset win in the Florida straw poll on Saturday. He’s helped by Rick Perry’s free-fall and Mitt Romney’s establishmentarianism. But Cain is a huge underdog.
That’s okay because **America loves an underdog. **
Here’s what must happen right now for Herman Cain to win:
1. Social Media avalanche. Get @THEHermanCain trending on Twitter, and keep it there for five consecutive days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>