<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pope Francis on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/pope-francis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pope Francis on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 10:15:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/pope-francis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rigid vs Squishy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rigid-vs-squishy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 10:15:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/rigid-vs-squishy/</guid>
      <description>The opposites of &amp;ldquo;rigid&amp;rdquo; are more unflattering than rigidity:
 lenient indulgent broken compromising easy imprecise indefinite inexact irresolute unfixed unreliable accommodating liberal permissive resigned soft-hearted
 And that&amp;rsquo;s the problem with name-calling. When we impose a derogatory label on someone, we invite scrutiny upon ourselves. We label ourselves as the opposite of the names we impose on others.
Some of us are better at name-calling, or &amp;ldquo;labelling,&amp;rdquo; than others. Donald Trump does a lot of labeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Pope Francis and Vatican Sec State Admit Viganò&#39;s Testimony?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/03/did-pope-francis-and-vatican-sec-state-admit-viganos-testimony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 12:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/03/did-pope-francis-and-vatican-sec-state-admit-viganos-testimony/</guid>
      <description>One week after Archbishop Carlo Viganò released his bombshell letter, it looks obvious that Pope Francis admits the key allegation: Francis knew McCarrick to be a serial molester, and he returned McCarrick to public ministry anyway. As we&amp;rsquo;ll see later in this post, Pope Francis has a pattern of letting molesters and their protectors off the hook.
Speaks for Itself Did the pope admit to the horrendous allegations directly? Not directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Towey Is Confused</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/01/jim-towey-is-confused/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 18:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/01/jim-towey-is-confused/</guid>
      <description>God bless Jim Towey and the work of his school, Ave Maria University. I am confident that he is confused, and we should pray for clarity.
I&amp;rsquo;m talking about his recent series of letters and clarifications regarding how Catholics should express their obedience to the pope. Jim is partially right and partially off base.
What Jim Towey Gets Right Jim is right that that conservative Catholics need to be very gracious and obedient when they challenge the pope&amp;rsquo;s formal teaching on matters like the death penalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fisherman&#39;s Other Shoe Just Dropped</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/the-fishermans-other-shoe-just-dropped/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/the-fishermans-other-shoe-just-dropped/</guid>
      <description>God, come to our assistance O, Lord, make haste to help us
 Pope Francis ignored evidence of crimes and overturned punishment imposed by Pope Benedict on the wicked and disgraced Cardinal McCarrick. That&amp;rsquo;s according to a former papal nuncio and corroborated by a former first counselor to the nunciature to the United States speaking on the record. The two men have direct knowledge of the matter.
Pope Francis refused to comment on the allegations that he personally covered up McCarrick&amp;rsquo;s crimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Deal With the Pope&#39;s Teaching on the Death Penalty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/11/how-i-deal-with-the-popes-teaching-on-the-death-penalty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/11/how-i-deal-with-the-popes-teaching-on-the-death-penalty/</guid>
      <description>Last week, Pope Francis approved a change to the Catechism of the Catholic Church.
Longtime readers might recall that my views on the death penalty are a bit nuanced. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t always have the courage to express it.
In 2014, I wrote:
 I don’t buy the idea that the death penalty is no deterrent. I don’t buy the notion that the death penalty should be banned. I think the availability of such a punishment serves its purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>