<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2017 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2017/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2017 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking News: Multiple Deputies Down in Shooting South of Denver (Active)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/31/breaking-news-multiple-deputies-down-in-shooting-south-of-denver-active/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/31/breaking-news-multiple-deputies-down-in-shooting-south-of-denver-active/</guid>
      <description>Latest: Sheriff sets up emergency shelter for displaced residents:
   Due to the size and cope of this investigation an emergency shelter has been set up @ East Ridge Rec Center, located at 9568 University Blvd. in Highlands Ranch. If anyone has been displaced from their homes due to this event please feel free to head there.
 — DC Sheriff (@dcsheriff) December 31, 2017
Earlier: Domestic disturbance led to shots fired, via Douglas County Sheriff:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s what will happen in 2018 election (POLL)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/30/heres-what-will-happen-in-2018-election-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 16:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/30/heres-what-will-happen-in-2018-election-poll/</guid>
      <description>Do you think Democrats will retake the House, the Senate, or both in the 2018 election?
[socialpoll id=&amp;quot;2479812&amp;rdquo;]
Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve answered, let&amp;rsquo;s consider the limits of data science in 2018.
The best data scientists in the world agreed with nearly absolute certainty. These scientists determined, beyond a reasonable doubt, that Hillary Clinton would be the 45th President of the United States. That was in 2016.
Those scientists were wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: State Department releases Huma Abedin emails found on Weiner&#39;s hard drive</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/breaking-state-department-releases-huma-abedin-emails-found-on-weiners-hard-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 20:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/breaking-state-department-releases-huma-abedin-emails-found-on-weiners-hard-drive/</guid>
      <description>The US Department of State released 2,800 emails involving Hillary aid Huma Abedin that were found on Anthony Weiner&amp;rsquo;s hard drive last year, Judicial Watch reports. You can read all the emails here: FOIA Abedin Emails
In a statement, Judicial Watch, which forced the release through lawsuits, said this:
 This is a major victory. After years of hard work in federal court, Judicial Watch has forced the State Department to finally allow Americans to see these public documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking ahead to season four of Trump: The President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/looking-ahead-to-season-four-of-trump-the-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 18:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/looking-ahead-to-season-four-of-trump-the-president/</guid>
      <description>Scott Adams first identified Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s greatest strength. What do you think that might be?
It&amp;rsquo;s not his money or his business experience. Those are strengths, sure, but they&amp;rsquo;re not THE strength.
Scott Adams believes Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign was a movie script. Here&amp;rsquo;s what Adams wrote way, way back when Trump&amp;rsquo;s candidacy was still just a PR stunt because he had zero chance of winning even a single primary:
 A movie script is almost always arranged in what the professionals call a three-act form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018: The beginning of the end of the Fourth Turning in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/27/2018-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-fourth-turning-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 19:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/27/2018-the-beginning-of-the-end-of-the-fourth-turning-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Regardless of its ideology, that new leadership will assert public authority and demand private sacrifice. Where leaders had once been inclined to alleviate societal pressures, they will now aggravate them to command the nation&amp;rsquo;s attention.
 —William Strauss and Neil Howe: The Fourth Turning: What the Cycles of History Tell Us About America&amp;rsquo;s Next Rendezvous with Destiny
Donald Trump can&amp;rsquo;t stand festering problems. Trump forces problems to the surface, into the daylight, where they can be fought and settled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 will change American culture at its core</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/26/2018-will-change-american-culture-at-its-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 18:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/26/2018-will-change-american-culture-at-its-core/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re wondering how things will change in 2018, you might think back the mid-1980s.
In the 1980s, leftist professors, leftist news media, and leftist entertainers were angry. For years, they&amp;rsquo;d preached that Ronald Reagan was a neo-Nazi buffoon whose incompetence and malice would destroy America. Maybe even wipe out the human species. &amp;ldquo;I believe Ronald Reagan can turn America back into what it once was,&amp;rdquo; said comedian Steve Martin on Saturday Night Live in 1980, &amp;ldquo;a vast wasteland covered with ice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Years Ago Today, I Predicted de Blasio Would Ruin New York City</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/26/4-years-ago-today-predicted-de-blasio-ruin-new-york-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 10:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/26/4-years-ago-today-predicted-de-blasio-ruin-new-york-city/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m scheduling this blog on December 26, 2013. I&amp;rsquo;m predicting Bill de Blasio will be as bad for New York City as Mayor John Lindsay (1967-1974).
Read the original blog here.
Now, let&amp;rsquo;s look back at the New York City de Blasio inherited. According to ZeroHedge blog:
  New York crime rates are at historic lows, the $72.7 billion budget is balanced, jobs are at an all-time high and a record 54 million tourists pumped money into the economy this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Are Not the Enemy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/10/01/liberals-are-not-the-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/10/01/liberals-are-not-the-enemy/</guid>
      <description>Forgive me. I say &amp;ldquo;liberal&amp;rdquo; sometimes when I mean something else.
My mistake is habit, not irony. (Irony would require some intent on my part.)
I grew up disparaging liberalism. I grew up reading and watching William F. Buckley Jr., for whom liberalism was the enemy.
In the post-WWII era, the liberalism of the day was a problem. But it was never the problem.
The problem in Western Civilization was a faction that used liberalism as cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Instigates NFL Labor Dispute</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/28/trump-initiates-nfl-labor-dispute/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/28/trump-initiates-nfl-labor-dispute/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I predicted the NFL would suffer a season-shortening labor dispute this season or next.
The reason: President Trump&amp;rsquo;s pressure on owners to crack down on anthem haters will stir up a fight between NFL Players Association and the owners.
As if on cue:
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_24766&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;1285&amp;rdquo;]Fox News[/caption]
 President Trump, in an exclusive interview with &amp;ldquo;Fox &amp;amp; Friends,&amp;rdquo; said that NFL owners are “afraid” to act against their players protesting the national anthem at games across the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Losing a Laugher (Video)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/27/nfl-losing-a-laugher-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 01:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/27/nfl-losing-a-laugher-video/</guid>
      <description>Blowout. Embarrassment. Lopsided. Laugher.
Humiliation.
Fans are doing to the NFL what Ray Rice did to his girlfriend in that elevator.
https://youtu.be/Dp47DeNAukw
Bars are banning football.
The VFW has condemned the NFL. 
Fans are burning jerseys.
American Sniper&amp;rsquo;s widow livid.
Viewership is down 11% year-over-year.
Fans boo players they recognize.
Baltimore fans demanding Ray Lewis statue come down like he&amp;rsquo;s General Lee.
Major NFL sponsors are under increasing pressure to pull ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Kemp Stood for Civil Rights . . . And America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</guid>
      <description>Jack Kemp is on the top of my wall of heroes. Literally. An autographed Kemp card sits on top of my bookshelf housing the works and images of my heroes.
As the NFL self-destructs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth reading about Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s work for civil rights. And for the Republican Party. And for conservatism.
Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s Activism Kemp did it all. And, thanks to Jeffrey Lord, we can remember Kemp&amp;rsquo;s finest moments of civil rights activism:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Trump Popped the NFL&#39;s Biggest Zit</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/25/president-trump-popped-the-nfls-biggest-zit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 01:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/25/president-trump-popped-the-nfls-biggest-zit/</guid>
      <description>Coming to a head.
President Trump seems pathologically opposed to festering problems. When he sees a festering problem, he pops it like a zit. For example, the North Korean nukes problem has festered since the Clinton administration. Trump is bringing Little Rocket Man to a head.
NAFTA has been festering since the Clinton administration. Trump is bringing NAFTA to a head.
The latest example: the NFL anthem-haters.
This anthem-hating is over a year old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Villanueva Was Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/25/what-villanueva-did-was-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/25/what-villanueva-did-was-wrong/</guid>
      <description>By now you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the photo. The iconic photo. One lone Army Ranger veteran defying his team to salute the flag during the Star-Spangled Banner.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_media-17&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;1200&amp;rdquo;]screenshot CBS[/caption]
You know that Alejandro Villanueva&amp;rsquo;s jersey and t-shirt immediately became the best-selling merchandise from the NFL&amp;rsquo;s store.
Villanueva served three tours of combat duty as an Army Ranger. He&amp;rsquo;s authorized to wear the Bronze Star. He stood for his country. In Afghanistan with the Army and in Pittsburgh alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Else Can You Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/24/what-else-can-you-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 16:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/24/what-else-can-you-do/</guid>
      <description>Brain damage. They all have brain damage. And they&amp;rsquo;ll likely die from it. Like Aaron Hernandez.
99 out of every 100 football players have serious brain damage.
Kneeling for CTE NFL players and owners decided to show their disrespect to the flag, law enforcement, and the USA by kneeling during the national anthem. In a foreign country.
The president responded by saying the NFL (and the TV networks) would be in big trouble if people stopped watching or attending games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franco Harris: All American</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/franco-harris-all-american/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 21:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/franco-harris-all-american/</guid>
      <description>You might not know about Franco Harris. You might wonder why he&amp;rsquo;s so unhappy, like many of us are, with the NFL&amp;rsquo;s anti-American antics lately. But his wonderful heritage tells a lot about why my favorite running back respects America.
His dad was an Army soldier. His dad met his mom in Italy during World War II. They married and returned to New Jersey.
[Read this fantastic 1996 Baltimore Sun biography of Franco Harris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Hates Football Fans; Fire Them All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/nfl-hates-football-fans-fire-them-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 15:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/23/nfl-hates-football-fans-fire-them-all/</guid>
      <description>You can see the battle brewing. It&amp;rsquo;s coming to a head. And no one is telling you the real reason the NFL is dying before your eyes.
Everyone sees the symptoms of football&amp;rsquo;s death spiral: empty stadiums. Crashed ratings. low quality. Criminals on the field. Some people call it &amp;ldquo;the National Felony League.&amp;rdquo;
Frustrated fans look for better entertainment. Ticket sales remain high for one reason: stupid corporate executives. Stupid executives think it&amp;rsquo;s still a status symbol to control lots of NFL tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hear Exactly What Jim Hoft and I Think of the Fake News Media</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/20/hear-exactly-what-jim-hoft-and-i-think-of-the-fake-news-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 10:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/20/hear-exactly-what-jim-hoft-and-i-think-of-the-fake-news-media/</guid>
      <description>. . . And It&amp;rsquo;s Deep-State Handlers Jim Hoft is a genius.
From his St. Louis home, Jim runs one of the most influential websites in the universe, according to Harvard researchers. He&amp;rsquo;s a legend. Like Andrew Breitbart, Jim Hoft reshaped the media. Hoft exposes the rotten bastards who call themselves &amp;ldquo;journalists.&amp;rdquo;
** Caustic Jim Acosta ** F*** Chuck Todd ** Jake &amp;ldquo;The Fake&amp;rdquo; Tapper ** Juannabe Williams
Jim Hoft exposed these knuckle-dragging liars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally! A President Stands Tall</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/finally-our-president-stands-tall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 02:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/finally-our-president-stands-tall/</guid>
      <description>They were dumbfounded.
Those United Nations stuffed shirts were dumbfounded. Struck dumb. Silenced. Shocked. Floored.
Those sissy diplomats were shaken. Appalled. Frightened.
Never in the sordid history of the United Nations has an American president spoken in unvarnished truth in unvarnished terms.
Trump has the best words.
Trump used his best words today.
The best of the best.
Trump called Kim Jung Un &amp;ldquo;Rocket Man.&amp;rdquo; The funniest and most effective linguistic kill-shot to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Jeff Session</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/fire-jeff-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 01:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/fire-jeff-session/</guid>
      <description>Greg Jarrett thinks Jeff Sessions should resign. I do, too.
I felt like the lone voice on the right last week when I wrote &amp;ldquo;Counseling Sessions.&amp;rdquo; It feels great to have Greg Jarrett agree: Jeff Sessions should resign.
As Jarrett puts it:
 Sessions appears either incapable or incompetent. He has resisted producing the documents relevant to the anti-Trump dossier which were subpoenaed by the House Intelligence Committee. He has failed to appoint a special counsel to reopen the case against Hillary Clinton for likely violations of the Espionage Act in the use of her email server, obstruction of justice for destroying 33,000 emails under congressional subpoena, and potential self-dealing for profit through her foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flush the Clapper. It Stinks!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/flush-the-clapper-it-stinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 23:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/flush-the-clapper-it-stinks/</guid>
      <description>James Clapper lied to Chuck Todd.
Clapper wiretapped Paul Manafort and lied about it. Just like Trump said.
James Clapper looks like a kind old grandfather. Like Josef Stalin. Or an elderly Charles Manson.
Like Stalin and Manson, **Clapper&amp;rsquo;s soiled name deserves to be flushed into the bowels of history&amp;rsquo;s bio hazard tank. **
James Clapper categorically denied that anyone associated with the Trump campaign was ever wiretapped. He lied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equifax Update: More Breaches, More Lies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/equifax-update-more-breaches-more-lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 21:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/equifax-update-more-breaches-more-lies/</guid>
      <description>You will be mad.
You probably don&amp;rsquo;t have a contract with Equifax. Your creditors do.
When you apply for a loan, you give creditors permission to:
*1. Obtain your credit file. *2. Update your credit file.
You expect that creditors vet their vendors, don&amp;rsquo;t you? You assume banks and credit card companies test their vendors&amp;rsquo; security.
And you expect financial services companies like Equifax to be on the up and up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Was Right! Obama White House &#39;Wiretapped&#39; Paul Manafort **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/18/trump-was-right-obama-white-house-wiretapped-paul-manafort/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 23:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/18/trump-was-right-obama-white-house-wiretapped-paul-manafort/</guid>
      <description>CAUTION: This report comes from very fake news blog CNN and may fall apart over the next 24 to 48 hours (like most of CNN&amp;rsquo;s fake reports fall apart).
CNN is reporting that Special Investigator Robert Mueller leaked secret documents to the press indicating the Obama White House &amp;ldquo;wiretapped&amp;rdquo; Paul Manafort before and after last year&amp;rsquo;s election.
CNN previously mocked and scorned President Trump for suggesting Obama wiretapped Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign. CNN says Mueller&amp;rsquo;s office cautioned that conclusions about Russian connection were &amp;ldquo;inconclusive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leftists Turn Against Nancy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/18/leftist-turn-against-nancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 23:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/18/leftist-turn-against-nancy/</guid>
      <description>Nancy Pelosi is paying a price for statesmanship.
Remember when this blog wrote about liberals saving us from Antifa?
 But one group can save us from the Antifa caliphate. An unlikely group. A group you’d never believe could be the heroes of this terrifying story.
 Who’s this group? Who will save America? Who will preserve Western Civilization? Christendom? Judaism?
Not the Right.
Not the Center.
Not the Great “Undecided” Voter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck and Nancy and Donald and Mitch and Paul</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/17/chuck-and-nancy-and-donald-and-mitch-and-paul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 20:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/17/chuck-and-nancy-and-donald-and-mitch-and-paul/</guid>
      <description>You can almost see it in your mind if you try. The cartons of Chinese takeout. The torn blisters of soy sauce. Nancy Pelosi, former swimsuit model, laughing at The Donald&amp;rsquo;s off-color jokes. About Mitch McConnell. Or Paul Ryan. While Chuck fills color of his own, about deals he helped The Donald put together back in New York. Stuff that didn&amp;rsquo;t make it into The Art of the Deal or The Art of the Comeback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graceless</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/14/graceless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 01:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/14/graceless/</guid>
      <description>Not often does a person or an event fit every definition of a single word. But Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s life after the election fits perfectly all three definitions of graceless.
__
Graceless.
Graceless Hillary.
Why didn&amp;rsquo;t Donald Trump think of that one during the campaign. &amp;ldquo;Graceless Hillary…&amp;rdquo;
Not a single rational being could challenge the accuracy of that monicker. Graceless Hillary.
Clumsy.
No sense of propriety or decency.
Inferior or clumsy in treatment or performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counselling Sessions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/10/counselling-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 16:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/10/counselling-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Eight months into the Trump Administration, one cabinet appointment stands out as a flop: Attorney General Jeff Sessions.
 We all had a lot of hope. Back in January. Hope.
Hope for the Trump administration. Hope for American greatness. And hope for justice. If you&amp;rsquo;re a Tea Partier, you had a lot of hope.
Jeff Sessions looked like the ultimate pick for Attorney General. Conservatives berated Mitch McConnell to accelerate Sessions&amp;rsquo; confirmation by the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Mercy for Equifax: Stock Price Zero</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/09/no-mercy-for-equifax-stock-price-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 15:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/09/no-mercy-for-equifax-stock-price-zero/</guid>
      <description>Move Over, Enron: Equifax Is Next  The worst problem of modernity lies in the malignant transfer of fragility and antifragility from one party to the other, with one getting the benefits, the other one (unwittingly) getting the harm, with such transfer facilitated by the growing wedge between the ethical and the legal. This state of affairs has existed before, but is acute today— modernity hides it especially well.
 —Nassim Taleb, Antifragile: Things That Gain from Disorder (Incerto)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strategy That Dare Not Speak Its Name</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/06/the-strategy-that-dare-not-speak-its-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/06/the-strategy-that-dare-not-speak-its-name/</guid>
      <description>By now you&amp;rsquo;ve heard that President Trump struck a deal with Nancy Pelosi and Chuck Schumer. Trump struck a deal to raise the debt ceiling. Trump struck a deal by going around Congressional Republicans. Trump struck a deal with Democrats.
It&amp;rsquo;s about time, frankly. But Trump can go a lot further on this path. If I were his chief strategist, I&amp;rsquo;d tell him to go further. How far? Keep reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Mark and Andrew Madoff Profit from Bernie&#39;s Crimes?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/05/did-mark-and-andrew-madoff-profit-from-bernies-crimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 00:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/05/did-mark-and-andrew-madoff-profit-from-bernies-crimes/</guid>
      <description>Many people say, &amp;ldquo;you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t punish children for sins of the parent.&amp;rdquo; That&amp;rsquo;s something we firmly believe as Americans. The US Constitution even prohibits &amp;ldquo;corruption of blood.&amp;rdquo; Corruption of blood refers to laws that pass guilt genetically from generation to generation.
I think we can all agree that punishing children for their parents&amp;rsquo; crimes is un-American. But what about children who profit from their parents&amp;rsquo; crimes? Should they be allowed to keep the booty?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for the Worst Case Scenario in North Korea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/04/preparing-for-the-worst-case-scenario-in-north-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 21:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/04/preparing-for-the-worst-case-scenario-in-north-korea/</guid>
      <description>You wake up and nothing works.
No electricity.
No cell phone or land line.
No radio.
No electric tooth brush.
No internet or cable.
No laptop. No tablet.
Car: nothing.
What happened?
No, it&amp;rsquo;s not a scene from the Twilight Zone. It&amp;rsquo;s the aftermath of an electromagnetic pulse attack. EMP for short.
An EMP attack would look like this:
** North Korea launches an ICBM toward North America ** The warhead detonates 100 miles above Colorado ** Waves of electromagnetic energy pulse down across the fruited plain ** Every semiconductor and small wire in the United States burns out</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next: The Great Lefty Shark Jump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/04/next-the-great-lefty-shark-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/04/next-the-great-lefty-shark-jump/</guid>
      <description>It might happen before I finish typing this post.
Maybe it already happened. Maybe we just haven&amp;rsquo;t heard.
Or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a few days away.
But it&amp;rsquo;s coming, folks. Believe me, it&amp;rsquo;s coming. And it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be a doozy.
So many lefties were hoping that Hurricane Harvey would finally knock out President Trump. If they pray, they prayed. They prayed for a monumental catastrophe. They prayed for total collapse of FEMA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laugh at them, not with them</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/03/laugh-at-them-not-with-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 02:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/03/laugh-at-them-not-with-them/</guid>
      <description>The left is crying. One guy on twitter is nearly suicidal. Hoft has more.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened.
Someone posted this photo on twitter. All the sane people laughed.
@realDonaldTrump retweeted. And now it&amp;rsquo;s the left&amp;rsquo;s new Russian conspiracy.
I remember when all the best comedians were liberals. But the new left traded its sense of humor for baseball bats with ten penny nails.
USA!
Meanwhile, the pre-schoolers at CNN have their panties in a bunch because the President of the United States wore a hat emblazoned with USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston&#39;s Gift</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/03/houstons-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 14:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/03/houstons-gift/</guid>
      <description>“It’s your life. You don’t know how long it’s gonna last, but you know it doesn’t end well. You’ve gotta move forward … as soon as you can figure out what that means.” —Don Draper, Mad Men, Season two, Six Month Leave
 Dear People of Houston (and thereabouts),
President Trump has said, &amp;ldquo;the whole world is watching.&amp;rdquo; And he&amp;rsquo;s right!
When people say &amp;ldquo;the whole world is watching,&amp;rdquo; they usually mean it as a warning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now, America Is Back!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/02/now-america-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 20:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/02/now-america-is-back/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been saying &amp;ldquo;America is back&amp;rdquo; ever since President Trump&amp;rsquo;s beautiful inauguration in January. And we meant it.
  But &amp;ldquo;America is back&amp;rdquo; rose to a higher level today. A level not since the days following 9-11. Or maybe the greatest moments of the Reagan administration.
Today, in Houston, we saw the America of our dreams. The America that makes us cry when we hear the national anthem. Or when we see a soldier in Iraq bending down to help a tiny Iraqi child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Character and Leadership in Houston</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/02/character-and-leadership-in-houston/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 18:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/02/character-and-leadership-in-houston/</guid>
      <description>When I watch President Trump in Texas, I am reminded of one of my favorite books.
Arthur C. Brooks wrote in The Conservative Heart:
 There is a common misconception that conservatives are materialistic. We are not, and this confusion is a central political irony of our time. Progressives truly want to help the poor but have tried to solve poverty primarily with government money, relegating talk of culture to the past and focusing more and more on income inequality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I still think James Comey is a felon, and the FBI is corrupt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/01/i-still-think-james-comey-is-a-felon-and-the-fbi-is-corrupt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 01:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/01/i-still-think-james-comey-is-a-felon-and-the-fbi-is-corrupt/</guid>
      <description>James Comey exonerated Hillary Clinton three months before he interviewed her.
James Comey exonerated Hillary Clinton before interviewing 16 key witnesses.
James Comey exonerated Hillary Clinton before he gathered any significant evidence.
James Comey gave Hillary Clinton permission to destroy evidence in a felony investigation.
James Comey leaked classified information to the media.
These are all facts. No one disputes them.
They are all crimes of various degrees. Some felonies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Ryan&#39;s Spokesperson Renounces Support for Antifa</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/31/paul-ryans-spokesperson-renounces-support-for-antifa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/31/paul-ryans-spokesperson-renounces-support-for-antifa/</guid>
      <description>It was probably a coincidence.
One day after Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View reported Speaker Paul &amp;ldquo;Dumbbell&amp;rdquo; Ryan as a member of the Antifa caliphate support team, Speaker Ryan&amp;rsquo;s office renounced his membership in the terrorist group&amp;rsquo;s fan club.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_23491&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;460&amp;rdquo;]Paul &amp;ldquo;Dumbbell&amp;rdquo; Ryan[/caption]
As reported by The Gateway Pundit:
 Social media was set ablaze after Paul Ryan attacked President Trump for condemning ‘both sides’ for the violence in Charlottesville. Trump supporters hammered Paul Ryan for refusing to condemn Antifa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Can Stop the Antifa Caliphate?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/31/who-can-stop-the-antifa-caliphate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/31/who-can-stop-the-antifa-caliphate/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I explained the military strategy behind Antifa&amp;rsquo;s remarkable growth.
In case you didn&amp;rsquo;t realize it, Antifa has effectively shut down grass roots conservative speech. You cannot hold a public rally, march, or carnival if your views conflict with Antifa&amp;rsquo;s.
Antifa has established a small caliphate in North America. Just like ISIS did in Syria and Iraq.
And the government&amp;rsquo;s doing absolutely nothing about it. You should read my military strategy post and all the links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Military Strategist&#39;s View of Antifa</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/30/a-military-strategists-view-of-antifa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 10:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/30/a-military-strategists-view-of-antifa/</guid>
      <description>If equally matched, we can offer battle; if slightly inferior in numbers, we can avoid the enemy; if quite unequal, we can flee from him.
    If we wish to fight, the enemy can be forced to an engagement even though he be sheltered behind a high rampart and a deep ditch. All we need do is attack some other place that he will be obliged to relieve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Trump&#39;s Only Failure</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/28/president-trumps-only-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/28/president-trumps-only-failure/</guid>
      <description>You know this blog rarely criticizes President Trump. There&amp;rsquo;s a simple reason for that. That reason is the thousands of fraudulent journalists who create and repeat lies about President Trump every day. Like Jake &amp;ldquo;The Fake&amp;rdquo; Tapper. Those fake journalists don&amp;rsquo;t need my help.
You also know that I have criticized President Bush, Republican candidates for president, and many, many other Republicans and conservatives. I just adopted a simple rule last year: until the fake news media treats President Trump honestly and fairly, I won&amp;rsquo;t criticize my president.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harvey vs. Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/27/harvey-vs-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/27/harvey-vs-trump/</guid>
      <description>Looks like Trump knows how to deal with natural disasters.
Things could change. I&amp;rsquo;m sure the dishonest media will fake stories about minorities getting stiffed by FEMA. Total lies.
But right now it looks like Trump knows how to handle disasters.
My president</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Statue Wars Will End</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/26/how-the-statue-wars-will-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 16:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/26/how-the-statue-wars-will-end/</guid>
      <description>You probably believe the narrative. Because that narrative is strong right now. It has become common knowledge. Common knowledge in the formal, game theory sense of the word.
In game theory, common knowledge is something everyone knows everyone knows. And everyone know everyone knows. And everyone knows how everyone else will behave because of that knowledge.
Common knowledge doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be true. In a common knowledge game, truth doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In 3 Minutes You&#39;ll Be Able Fend Off Any Verbal Attack About Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/23/in-3-minutes-youll-be-able-fend-off-any-verbal-attack-about-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 04:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/23/in-3-minutes-youll-be-able-fend-off-any-verbal-attack-about-trump/</guid>
      <description>You probably don&amp;rsquo;t believe it. You&amp;rsquo;re probably reading just to argue. But three minutes from now, you&amp;rsquo;ll be armed.
Armed and ready to do verbal combat.
Armed and ready to defend your Trump vote.
Armed and read to win any intellectual confrontation.
Think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible? Keep reading. You&amp;rsquo;ll find out defending your vote for Trump is easier than you could imagine. Your opponent will be standing there, jaw moving, lips quivering, voice lost, brain scrambled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USS John S. McCain</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/22/uss-john-s-mccain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 13:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/22/uss-john-s-mccain/</guid>
      <description>You kind of knew how the story would end. How the search for the 10 missing sailors would end.
This morning, we began hearing about bodies discovered on board the McCain and in waters near the collision. I grieve for those families.
The news breaks a lot of hearts. Especially the hearts of people with loved ones deployed on ships in dangerous waters.
I know my readers never forget the work our military does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;We Are Killing Terrorists&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/21/we-are-killing-terrorists/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 01:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/21/we-are-killing-terrorists/</guid>
      <description>Elections have consequences.
One consequence that we&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced: when you elect a street fighter, you get street fights.
Another consequence that terrorists are experiencing: when you elect a street-fighter patriot, terrorists die.
President Trump tonight reminded so many of us why we elected him. Because he&amp;rsquo;s a street fighter. Because he&amp;rsquo;s a patriot. Because there are bad people who wish us harm, and Donald Trump is okay with killing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Kind of Person Are You?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/21/what-kind-of-person-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 22:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/21/what-kind-of-person-are-you/</guid>
      <description>This is one-question values study. It&amp;rsquo;s very revealing. Please take the survey, share your results, and encourage others to take it. The more people take this survey, the more accurate its results would be. I will not record any personal information. You can remain anonymous if you&amp;rsquo;d like.
[os-widget path=&amp;rdquo;/billhennessy1/moral-hypothetical&amp;rdquo; of=&amp;quot;billhennessy1&amp;rdquo; comments=&amp;quot;false&amp;rdquo;]
Please forward to friends. Compare your results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace Through Violence: CNN&#39;s Radical Chic Moment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/20/peace-through-violence-cnns-radical-chic-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/20/peace-through-violence-cnns-radical-chic-moment/</guid>
      <description>CNN screwed up. And it reminds me of an incident from 1970.
A headline writer admitted that the Antifa terror group seeks &amp;ldquo;peace through violence.&amp;rdquo; Later, presumably after receiving threats from Antifa terrorists, CNN removed the &amp;ldquo;peace through violence&amp;rdquo; sub-head.
But the damage was done. CNN stumbled onto real news. Real news that exposes Antifa&amp;rsquo;s terrorist aims.
Before we get to the dangers of normalizing political violence, aka &amp;ldquo;terrorism,&amp;rdquo; let&amp;rsquo;s remember a famous party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s a Racist?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/whos-a-racist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 23:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/whos-a-racist/</guid>
      <description>So many people say it&amp;rsquo;s okay for Antifa to beat people they don&amp;rsquo;t like. Tim Cook says it. Mitt Romney says it. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to agree with them. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to say, &amp;ldquo;I hate racists and Nazis. I&amp;rsquo;m glad somebody&amp;rsquo;s taking the initiative and beating them with clubs.&amp;rdquo;
Many people feel that way. Many people feel it&amp;rsquo;s good and just to beat and maim wicked people. Especially people who hold wicked beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Character?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/what-is-character/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/17/what-is-character/</guid>
      <description>Worry about your character, not your reputation. Reputation is what people think of you. Character is who you are.
 —John Wooden, legendary coach of basketball and character
Everyone admits that President Trump cares more about his character than about his reputation. Only a man concerned with his character would tell the truth.
Reputation is what people think of you. Character is who you are.
The Stoics teach us that reputation is beyond our control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Was Good About Charlottesville</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/13/what-was-good-about-charlottesville/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 14:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/13/what-was-good-about-charlottesville/</guid>
      <description>Charlottesville used to be a place. Now, it&amp;rsquo;s a thing.
On Friday, Charlottesville was a city in Virginia.
Today, Charlottesville is an event. A thing.
In our hyper-emotional world of 2017, we are told to explore our emotions. Then act upon those emotions. Like poorly trained animals. Like half-wits. Like narcissists and spoiled brats. Like lower primates.
Like the KKK and BLM and Antifa thugs who turned that place into a thing yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Greitens Protected Privacy in Missouri</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/07/how-greitens-protected-privacy-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 02:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/07/how-greitens-protected-privacy-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Angry texts.
I got a bunch of very angry texts this morning.
My friends are fired up. Because of Governor Greitens&amp;rsquo;s executive order. **An executive order that implements a novel approach to prescription drug databases. **
In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard, Governor Greitens signed an executive order on July 17. The EO made Missouri the 50th state to establish some sort of prescription drug tracking.
Most states track everything about prescriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Ignore the News</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/04/how-to-ignore-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 15:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/08/04/how-to-ignore-the-news/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Will Trump survive this?&amp;rdquo;
A friend of mine texted me yesterday. I had no idea what the &amp;ldquo;this&amp;rdquo; was. Later, I learned.
Turns out, like most of the media&amp;rsquo;s breathless revelations about Trump&amp;rsquo;s supposed crimes, the story that people reacted to meant little. The anti-Trump media exploded with fake news, fake interpretations of real news, and speculation that supported their own angry fetishes.
But any reasonable person would respond like my friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foxconn&#39;s Hiring and Mooch Is Safe</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/28/foxconns-hiring-and-mooch-is-safe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 02:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/28/foxconns-hiring-and-mooch-is-safe/</guid>
      <description>You know it&amp;rsquo;s coming. Some fake news hack will claim the whole Foxconn-Wisconsin deal was a plot to find a new job for Reince Priebus.
Reince Priebus, the erstwhile White House chief of staff who prides himself on blocking deplorables from the White House posts they deserve, has been relieved of duties. He&amp;rsquo;s on his way back to native Wisconsin where Foxconn is building a $10 billion plant. Maybe Foxconn needs an establishment-connected middle manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Priebus Over-Under (under)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/27/priebus-over-under/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 05:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/27/priebus-over-under/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll set the over-under on Priebus&amp;rsquo;s resignation/firing at 10 days (August 6).
Pick over or under in the comments.
Winners will get great satisfaction.
I&amp;rsquo;m taking under.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about, Gateway Pundit has it all. It&amp;rsquo;s juicy!
Just yesterday, Washington Times pointed out that the very swampy Priebus is increasingly isolated and lonely in the Trump White House. Nobody likes Reince.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regarding Jeff Sessions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/25/regarding-jeff-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 03:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/25/regarding-jeff-sessions/</guid>
      <description>I campaigned for and voted for Donald Trump. I stand 100% behind Trump today.
I support Trump because he&amp;rsquo;s a fighter. He&amp;rsquo;s a man of action. Trump prosecutes his causes, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t navel gaze.
Jeff Sessions is a good man. He&amp;rsquo;s a good Washington man. He has standards of decorum. Standards I admire.
Trump has no standards of decorum. But I voted for Trump because history has made decorum a liability, even a vice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Must See Dunkirk</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/24/why-you-must-see-dunkirk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 04:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/24/why-you-must-see-dunkirk/</guid>
      <description>When Winston Churchill mouthed these eternal words, his nation&amp;rsquo;s life expectancy was about six months.
All of Western Civilization, all of Christiandom, seemed doomed.
One defiant man ended a speech to his House of Commons with this:
 I have, myself, full confidence that if all do their duty, if nothing is neglected, and if the best arrangements are made, as they are being made, we shall prove ourselves once again able to defend our Island home, to ride out the storm of war, and to outlive the menace of tyranny, if necessary for years, if necessary alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Exposed and Protected</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/24/feeling-exposed-and-protected/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 05:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/24/feeling-exposed-and-protected/</guid>
      <description>People want cover. Danger drives us together.
It&amp;rsquo;s our nature. Our herding response gave our species an advantage. The herders lived to breed. The wanderers, the stragglers, fell prey. Genes of herders increased. Genes of loners receded.
But our strongest cover is our parents. They&amp;rsquo;re the protection we seek.
The pair of humans who brought us into the world provide the best cover. We are born helpless. Our parents sustain us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Kid Rock Winning MI Senate Race</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/23/update-kid-rock-winning-mi-senate-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/23/update-kid-rock-winning-mi-senate-race/</guid>
      <description>If the election were held today, Senator Kid Rock would be a thing.
Via The Gateway Pundit:
News broke this weekend that Kid Rock is LEADING challenger, Dem Debbie Stabenow in a new poll 30% to 26%!   Everyone who wrote this off as a joke, then as a publicity stunt, then as impossible, then as improbable will be forced to say &amp;ldquo;Senator Rock&amp;rdquo; soon. Very soon.
Try this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Forever Through Stoicism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/16/free-forever-through-stoicism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 22:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/16/free-forever-through-stoicism/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Some things we can control, some we can’t. We can control our attitudes, opinions, goals and desires – choices of our own. We can’t control health, wealth, fame or power – things we can’t have by choosing them.&amp;rdquo; —Epictetus
 Freedom begins with understanding what we control and we do not. Yet very few people even begin to consider this essential dichotomy.
Even in the complete absence of &amp;ldquo;administration&amp;rdquo; as Tocqueville observed in early 19th century America, no one was free who failed to understand Epictetus&amp;rsquo;s control dichotomy: some things are under our control, some are not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senator Rock: Who&#39;s the Joke? (offensive) VIDEO</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/15/senator-rock-whos-the-joke-offensive-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 22:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/15/senator-rock-whos-the-joke-offensive-video/</guid>
      <description>My serious Republican friends (think of people like Chris Wallace and Charles Krauthammer) worry.
They worry about this trend toward &amp;ldquo;unserious&amp;rdquo; politicians getting elected.
They worry about &amp;ldquo;what it says about voters&amp;rdquo; who elect Sarah Palin, Donald Trump, and (very soon) Kid Rock.
These serious Republicans long for the days of serious men and serious matters. Of gray flannel suits beneath salt-and-pepper hair belonging to Yale grads and Harvard Law professors who can, on occasion, in the right circumstances, with just the right audience, shock the world with an (are you ready for this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sorry If Governor Greitens Hurts Your Feelings</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/10/sorry-if-governor-greitens-hurts-your-feelings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 22:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/10/sorry-if-governor-greitens-hurts-your-feelings/</guid>
      <description>Kudos to Governor Greitens and the Missouri legislature. They killed a minimum wage law in St. Louis. The law was designed to make city politicians feel better about themselves. It&amp;rsquo;s certain result would have been fewer jobs for the people who need jobs the most.
Why are you complaining about Governor Greitens&amp;rsquo; first term? Did you not read his books?
Like Donald Trump, Eric Greitens called his plays at the line of scrimmage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Can Make Missouri More Like Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/09/we-can-make-missouri-more-like-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 16:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/09/we-can-make-missouri-more-like-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Admit it, Missouri. **You have Illini Envy. **
We all grew up in the shadow of the Lincoln State.
We grew up frustrated that the Black Hawks have won Stanley Cups while the Blues end every season in frustration.
Everybody in the world knows where Chicago is. And that it&amp;rsquo;s in Illinois, the Land of Lincoln. Missouri&amp;rsquo;s a little hit-or-miss on geography quizzes.
But Missourians have a chance to make St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War &amp; Tariffs: What to do about North Korea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/04/what-to-do-about-north-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 17:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/04/what-to-do-about-north-korea/</guid>
      <description>If you think about geopolitics at all, you know North Korea poses many problems for its neighbors. And for the United States. And for the whole world.
If we take attack North Korea militarily, over a million South Koreans will die. Along with a lot of Americans on ships and on land over there. Nobody wants that. It might come to that, but nobody wants it.
Now, North Korea has ICBMs that can drop a nuke on Alaska.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First 13er President: A Gen X Independence Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/03/first-13er-president-a-gen-x-independence-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 00:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/03/first-13er-president-a-gen-x-independence-day/</guid>
      <description>“As they reach their turn for national leadership, 13ers will produce no-nonsense winners who will excel at cunning, flexibility, and deft timing.”
 —Neil Howe and William Strauss, 13th Gen: Abort, Retry, Ignore, Fail?
I’ve written before that 2016 was the first Gen X Election. And that Donald Trump would be the first Gen X president. Not because he’s an Xer, but because he personifies our coming-of-age view of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greatest 4th of July! WrestlemaniaCNNTakeDown! (Video)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/02/greatest-4th-of-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 15:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/07/02/greatest-4th-of-july/</guid>
      <description>President Trump makes everything better. Everything. And this video, which he just tweeted, made this 4th of the July the best since 1776. (Click twice to get play this video)
   #FraudNewsCNN #FNN pic.twitter.com/WYUnHjjUjg
 — Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) July 2, 2017
The left and CNN will, of course, be outraged. They don&amp;rsquo;t have a sense of humor.
President Trump has a fine sense of humor. I can see the grin on his face as he tapped out &amp;ldquo;#FraudNewsCNN&amp;rdquo; and hit the send button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I disavow every Republican who disavowed Trump&#39;s tweets</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/29/i-disavow-every-republican-who-disavowed-trumps-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/29/i-disavow-every-republican-who-disavowed-trumps-tweets/</guid>
      <description>When Reagan was president, we wanted him to hit back harder on the press. We wanted him to put Sam Donaldson in his place. We wanted him to call out the fake news.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_22208&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;750&amp;rdquo;]  2/5/1981 President Reagan during an interview with Sam Donaldson of ABC News Leslie Stahl of CBS News and Judith Woodruff of NBC News with James Brady at the Cross Hall White House Library[/caption]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When the Russian Narrative Broke</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/27/when-the-russian-narrative-broke/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 14:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/27/when-the-russian-narrative-broke/</guid>
      <description>When did the narrative break?
Was it the assassination attempt on GOP Congressmen?
Was it Comey&amp;rsquo;s admission that Trump was never under investigation?
Was it Kathy Griffin&amp;rsquo;s grim ISIS imitation?
Was it Trump&amp;rsquo;s 5-0 winning streak in special elections?
Like the ageless question of how many licks it takes to get to the Tootsie-Roll center of a Tootsie-Pop, the world may never know. Never know just when the Russian narrative broke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Terrible Day for the Navy Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/18/a-terrible-day-for-the-navy-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 14:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/18/a-terrible-day-for-the-navy-family/</guid>
      <description>[SEARCH CALLED OFF  US Navy ends hunt for 7 missing sailors as bodies are found in the ship](https://www.foxnews.com/world/2017/06/18/us-navy-calls-off-search-for-7-missing-sailors-several-bodies-found-inside-destroyer.html)
  I saw the FoxNews.com headline last night. My face sagged. Those tiny muscles that control our facial expressions all fell asleep at once. A long, slow breath-flood rushed from my slack lips.
I thought about those seven families. The families who haven&amp;rsquo;t heard from their USS Fitzgerald sailors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spy Tactics for Conservatives: 7 Easy Steps to Protect Yourself</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/15/7-steps-to-safety-for-conservatives-think-like-a-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 22:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/15/7-steps-to-safety-for-conservatives-think-like-a-spy/</guid>
      <description>You are a target. They want you dead.
You are a conservative activist. They call themselves &amp;ldquo;progressives.&amp;rdquo;
You want to live. And you want to remain active in politics.
They want you dead. Or submissive. Like a slave. Or a battered woman.
No, you can&amp;rsquo;t attack them. You shouldn&amp;rsquo;t engage them. They&amp;rsquo;re rabid animals. Neither reason nor normal persuasion can change progressives from their deadly habits.
So what do you do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/14/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 02:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/14/leadership/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/JjMfrBY-K6g?t=2m15s
President Trump wins praise from all side for his strength, dignity, and leadership following the left&amp;rsquo;s rifle attack on Republican members of Congress.
&amp;ldquo;We can all agree that we are blessed to be Americans.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Washington Post Radicalizes Murderers (video)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/14/how-the-washington-post-radicalizes-murderers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 01:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/14/how-the-washington-post-radicalizes-murderers/</guid>
      <description>To liberals, the murder of a Republican is like the swatting of a mosquito. They oppose violence in theory, but they also want the pest dead. They&amp;rsquo;re just too lazy to get out of their easy chairs to do it themselves.
Cass Sunstein, a leftist who&amp;rsquo;s happy whenever a conservative dies early, wrote a book called Nudge. It&amp;rsquo;s a good psychology book. Nudge is about persuasion, which is my chief interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Betting on an Indictment of Comey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/10/why-im-betting-on-an-indictment-of-comey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 21:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/10/why-im-betting-on-an-indictment-of-comey/</guid>
      <description>I made a lot of money on the election. Most of that money I cashed out. But I left a small balance in case I saw another opportunity to bet against the prevailing wisdom.
I saw that opportunityt last night.
My PredictIt Success In January 2016, I bought three kinds of shares on PredictIt, the prediction market.
*1. Trump would win the Republican nomination. *2. Trump would win the White House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Obstruction. No Collusion. He&#39;s a Leaker. UPDATES</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/09/no-obstruction-no-collusion-hes-a-leaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 23:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/09/no-obstruction-no-collusion-hes-a-leaker/</guid>
      <description>Scott Adams pointed out the linguistic brilliance of Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s perfect summation of James Comey&amp;rsquo;s failed takedown attempt.
&amp;ldquo;No obstruction. No collusion. He&amp;rsquo;s a leaker.&amp;rdquo;
That&amp;rsquo;s how Trump summarized Comey&amp;rsquo;s testimony to the Senate&amp;rsquo;s Russian Conspiracy Hoax Committee.
Click to watch:
  
Scott is a genius in persuasion and psychology. Everything he just said about Trump&amp;rsquo;s linguistic kill-shot is dead-on accurate. Trump destroyed Comey without firing a shot. &amp;ldquo;No obstruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Comey&#39;s GlassDoor.com Review of Donald Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/08/james-comeys-glassdoor-com-review-of-donald-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 23:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/08/james-comeys-glassdoor-com-review-of-donald-trump/</guid>
      <description>I read a lot of GlassDoor.com reviews. I do it for work. It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to get a feel for a client&amp;rsquo;s culture.
I&amp;rsquo;m smart enough to discount reviews from people who were recently fired from the company. I don&amp;rsquo;t ignore those reviews, but I discount the negative stuff. There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance that the disgruntled former employee is just venting. They feel wronged, even if they were terrible employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gullible Evil Losers at CNN Criticize London Cops for Using Too Many Bullets. UPDATE</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/04/gullible-evil-losers-at-cnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 21:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/04/gullible-evil-losers-at-cnn/</guid>
      <description>Maybe we should consider CNN employees enemy combatants.
CNN&amp;rsquo;s latest hate-crime: **CNN is criticizing London police for using too many bullets. **
That&amp;rsquo;s right. CNN will soon demand a UN war crimes tribunal to try, convict, and hang the London cops who put down the London Bridge terrorists.
  This photo caption appeared below this critical headline.
  CNN has not responded to my request for comments.
Specifically, I asked CNN to provide the exact number of rounds police are allowed to use to stop a terrorist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shark-Jumping Update: the Left Is Losing It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/04/shark-jumping-update-the-left-is-loosing-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 19:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/04/shark-jumping-update-the-left-is-loosing-it/</guid>
      <description>Previously on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View:
 Because of tolerance, it’s getting harder and harder to make people laugh with Trump jokes. Everybody’s heard them all. So comedians have to ramp up the shock factor. And they have been. And it was working.
 Until Kathy Griffin went too far.
Comedians and leftist news people are bound to go too far. It&amp;rsquo;s bio-chemical response. And now, so many leftists are in a race to the top on excess and insanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Kathy Griffin Helped Trump, Based on Brain Science</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/02/how-kathy-griffin-helped-trump-based-on-brain-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 20:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/02/how-kathy-griffin-helped-trump-based-on-brain-science/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to see in the fog of war, but comedienne Kathy Griffin did Donald Trump a huge favor. Before I explain, look at all the benefits Trump got from Griffin&amp;rsquo;s decapitation humor:
** Prominent Democrats and CNN turned against Hillary Clinton ** Andrea Mitchell and other journalists began admitting the Russian conspiracy theory is a hoax ** Americans sympathize with the Trump family ** Kathy Griffin&amp;rsquo;s crazy press conference made Trump look mature, sober, and sane by comparison</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the New York Times blackmailing FBI and CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 01:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</guid>
      <description>Sounds ridiculous, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
How could a reporter at New York Times blackmail an FBI or CIA agent?
Easily. And everyone who ever went through counter-espionage training knows it.
What Went Down This morning, British Prime Minister Theresa May chastised the US government. The UK freely shares anti-terrorism intelligence with the US. The US is expected to keep secrets secret.
But the US intel community is one gigantic sieve these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Is Back!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/22/america-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/22/america-is-back/</guid>
      <description>On the night that a deranged terrorist murdered and maimed little girls in Manchester England, we can take some solace in the fact that the greatest bastion of Western Civilization is back.
America is back.
Back on the watch.
Back on the hunt.
Back in the world.
When President Trump became the first American president to speak in Saudi Arabia, he delivered a message beyond his words. He delivered a message that no one missed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Rich Murder Case Closing In On Clinton Crime Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/20/seth-rich-murder-case-closing-in-on-clinton-crime-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 21:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/20/seth-rich-murder-case-closing-in-on-clinton-crime-family/</guid>
      <description>Was Seth Rich murdered as an example?
Seth Rich was murdered. Two gunshots to his back. Like you&amp;rsquo;d see on The Sopranos (video). The police called it a robbery. But nothing was stolen. Not his cell phone. Not his wallet. Not his watch. Not his cash.
Shortly after his murder, Wikileaks posted embarrassing emails. Emails from the Democratic National Committee&amp;rsquo;s email server. Wikileaks maintains that the theft of the emails was an inside job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study Links Journalism, Stupidity</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/19/study-links-journalism-stupidity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 18:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/19/study-links-journalism-stupidity/</guid>
      <description>From the &amp;ldquo;we could have told you that&amp;rdquo; department:
 Journalists&amp;rsquo; brains show a lower-than-average level of executive functioning, according to a new study, which means they have a below-average ability to regulate their emotions, suppress biases, solve complex problems, switch between tasks, and show creative and flexible thinking. [emphasis added]
 It&amp;rsquo;s okay to laugh. You suspected that reporters are kind of dumb. Now you know. They can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with Trump, but they probably can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with a young adult novella, either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox News&#39; Ratings Collapse Is Almost Complete. Here&#39;s Why.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/17/fox-news-ratings-collapse-is-almost-complete-heres-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/17/fox-news-ratings-collapse-is-almost-complete-heres-why/</guid>
      <description>Guest post by Lee A. Presser
For those of you who do not follow things as mundane as television rating scores, you may be surprised to learn that Fox News Channel (FNC) is losing its lead as the powerhouse in primetime cable TV ratings to MSNBC. There are a couple of reasons why.
First, control of FNC has been transferred to two brothers, Lachlan and James Murdoch, who do not believe in the political message espoused by Fox for the last twenty years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How &#34;Healthy&#34; Diets Kill You and Your Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/08/how-healthy-diets-kill-you-and-your-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 13:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/08/how-healthy-diets-kill-you-and-your-family/</guid>
      <description>Do you follow the recommended diets? Low fat. High carbohydrate? Eat lots of fruit?
If so, you&amp;rsquo;re probably overweight. And your blood tests are probably a mess. Maybe your doctor recommends expensive prescriptions to lower your cholesterol.
A new study finds the problem is not your fault. Your doctor, poorly educated in nutrition, and government recommendations, prompted by industry lobbyists, are designed to keep you fat and sick. And it&amp;rsquo;s not just US government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persuasion and Fat</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/07/persuasion-and-fat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 12:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/07/persuasion-and-fat/</guid>
      <description>The Easiest Formula for Mastering Persuasion, Losing Weight, and Avoiding Disease (video) &amp;ldquo;Persuasion&amp;rdquo; is part of my job title. When you&amp;rsquo;re a persuasion professional, you get a lot of questions about persuasion. Some are sincere. Others are skeptical, like, &amp;ldquo;Okay, persuasion boy, persuade me to give you a hundred dollars.&amp;rdquo;
Persuasion doesn&amp;rsquo;t work like that. But it also does. Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: if you ask me to persuade you to give me a hundred bucks, you already want to give me a hundred bucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Not Freaking Out About the Budget</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/02/why-im-not-freaking-out-about-the-budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 17:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/02/why-im-not-freaking-out-about-the-budget/</guid>
      <description>Congress is about to pass a budget. I call it a &amp;ldquo;Paul Ryan Special.&amp;rdquo; This budget lets the government spend money for four months. It expires in September.
The budget is horrible. Republicans are spinning a few &amp;ldquo;wins&amp;rdquo; in the budget, but that&amp;rsquo;s a terrible argument. It&amp;rsquo;s like telling a terminal cancer patient, &amp;ldquo;but your blood pressure&amp;rsquo;s pretty good.&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: you cannot control Congress. You can only control what you focus on and what you do next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz: Mensch!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/27/ted-cruz-mensch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 02:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/27/ted-cruz-mensch/</guid>
      <description>If you read my blog, you know I&amp;rsquo;ve had differences with Senator Ted Cruz. But the Senator has stepped up. Bigly! Only a gentleman would do what Cruz just did with his El Chapo bill.
Remember the GOP race? Cruz and Trump went at each other like nobody&amp;rsquo;s business. Wives and all. While Cruz couldn&amp;rsquo;t bring himself to endorse Trump at the convention, Ted has stepped up a lot since the election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Ruin the World (f-bombs included!)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/17/democrats-ruin-the-world-f-bombs-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/17/democrats-ruin-the-world-f-bombs-included/</guid>
      <description>Picture this.
Every time you leave your teenage kids home alone for a weekend, you come back to stink-eyes from your neighbors, a living room that&amp;rsquo;s a sea of empty beer cans, a yard filled with cigarette butts, and a pregnant cat.
Pretty soon, you&amp;rsquo;d stop leaving those kids to their own devices, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you? If you had to leave town, you&amp;rsquo;d find a sitter. Maybe a retired Marine uncle. Or a friendly cop to send a car by the house every half hour during the dark hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Might Be Thinking About &#39;Passion&#39; All Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/16/you-might-be-thinking-about-passion-all-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 16:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/16/you-might-be-thinking-about-passion-all-wrong/</guid>
      <description>You hear people say &amp;ldquo;follow your passion.&amp;rdquo; It sounds nice.
Then you hear wildly successful people say &amp;ldquo;do NOT follow your passion.&amp;rdquo; Mark Cuban is in this camp. So is Dilbert creator Scott Adams.
So which is it? Do you follow your passion or not?
My answer might disappoint you. Because it&amp;rsquo;ll sound evasive. But I&amp;rsquo;ll give it a shot. I&amp;rsquo;ll need you to help out here, though. Think of this as an exercise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>False Flag or Not</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/08/false-flag-or-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/08/false-flag-or-not/</guid>
      <description>The contemporary term false flag describes covert operations that are designed to deceive in such a way that activities appear as though they are being carried out by entities, groups, or nations other than those who actually planned and executed them. [Wikipedia]
 Think of a time when you acted on false information. You knew it might be false, but you acted as if it was true. Why did you do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Do I Mean By &#34;Narrative&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/07/what-do-i-mean-by-narrative/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 22:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/07/what-do-i-mean-by-narrative/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t agree.&amp;rdquo;
Some folks disagreed with my instant assessment of the Syrian strike. My assessment: Trump&amp;rsquo;s surprise military attack will shift four narratives in Trump&amp;rsquo;s favor:
** Trump is Hitler: dead ** Trump is a Russian agent: dead ** Trump is incompetent: dying ** Trump is a lightweight among world leaders: dead
In other words, it took 59 cruise missiles to blow up the left&amp;rsquo;s anti-Trump narratives.
But my friends disagree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Launched 59 Cruise Missiles at Leftist Narratives</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/06/trump-launched-59-cruise-missiles-at-leftist-narratives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 02:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/06/trump-launched-59-cruise-missiles-at-leftist-narratives/</guid>
      <description>No child of God should ever suffer such horror.
 —President Donald J. Trump
The most powerful weapon in the world is narrative.
The most powerful weapon in the world is narrative.
That&amp;rsquo;s another way of saying the pen is mightier than the sword.
The most powerful weapon in the world is narrative.
Tonight, President Trump blew up four narratives of the left. And he made America great again in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Right Question to Bring Down Susan Rice</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/05/the-right-question-to-bring-down-susan-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 22:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/04/05/the-right-question-to-bring-down-susan-rice/</guid>
      <description>Susan Rice admitted she lied. She requested unmaskings of Trump associates.
Rice says her unmasking requests were routine. Maybe they were.
We can find out. It&amp;rsquo;s simple data analysis. I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how. But, first, you have to know the right question to ask. And few people do.
Right Questions You hear a lot of talk about whether Susan Rice requested unmasking of Trump associates. That&amp;rsquo;s a good question, but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Admin Wiretapped Trump *UPDATE 2*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/31/obama-admin-wiretapped-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/31/obama-admin-wiretapped-trump/</guid>
      <description>Now you know. You can stop doubting. You have more than hope.
The Obama administration spied on Donald Trump and his campaign and transition teams. There is no longer any doubt.
The questions that remain are:
** Who ordered and authorized the illegal wiretaps? ** Who illegally received and disseminated the intelligence? ** What did Obama know?
It&amp;rsquo;s easy to declare the Obama Admin guilty after Evelyn Farkas&amp;rsquo;s admissions on MSNBC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day Reagan Was Shot</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/30/the-day-reagan-was-shot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/30/the-day-reagan-was-shot/</guid>
      <description>Think about the sun, Pippin
  Think about her golden glance
  How she lights the world up
  Well, now it&amp;rsquo;s your chance
  With the guardian of splendor
  Inviting you to dance
  Pippin
  Think about the sun
  —Finale, Pippin by Stephen Schwarz
 We were standing near the glass doors at the back of the theatre waiting for the bell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Next Move: Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/27/trumps-next-move-infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 21:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/27/trumps-next-move-infrastructure/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve changed my mind on priority.
Instead of going to tax reform next, President Trump should work on that big-league infrastructure bill. Now. Fast.
President Trump needs a big win because power is in perception. He also needs to put Democrats in a bind. Plus, he needs to prove he can pass big legislation without all GOP factions on board.
The solution is infrastructure.
During the campaign, Trump spoke of a massive building project to rejuvenate our roads, modernize our airports, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Neuter a Crossing Guard</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/27/how-to-neuter-a-crossing-guard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 14:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/27/how-to-neuter-a-crossing-guard/</guid>
      <description>This is for my conservative friends who are celebrating the healthcare bill&amp;rsquo;s demise. You&amp;rsquo;ll want to read it all.
Let&amp;rsquo;s begin with a little story about a crossing guard.
 Imagine you are standing at a dangerous intersection now. Cars whizzing by nonstop in all 4 directions. You feel powerless and frustrated. There are no structural safeguards, no physical barriers, to keep us from getting hit. There is a crossing guard, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Without Power, Principles Are Platitudes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/without-power-principles-are-platitudes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 16:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/without-power-principles-are-platitudes/</guid>
      <description>Without power, principles are platitudes.
Consider this a favor to the Freedom Caucusers. Those folks can&amp;rsquo;t see past the end of their own principles.
Knowing the Freedom Caucus people pretty well, I know they&amp;rsquo;re very happy with Neil Gorsuch for the Supreme Court. I know they&amp;rsquo;d be very miserable if Gorsuch were rejected and Trump had to nominate someone who could win a few Democrat votes.
It&amp;rsquo;s all about power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jobs Trump Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/jobs-trump-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 14:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/jobs-trump-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>I feel drunk but I&amp;rsquo;m sober, I&amp;rsquo;m young and I&amp;rsquo;m underpaid I&amp;rsquo;m tired but I&amp;rsquo;m working, yeah I care but I&amp;rsquo;m restless, I&amp;rsquo;m here but I&amp;rsquo;m really gone I&amp;rsquo;m wrong and I&amp;rsquo;m sorry baby
 —Alanis Morissette, One Hand In My Pocket
If your biggest problem involves choosing between multiple appealing jobs, everything else will seem less important. Because picking the right job is a really big deal.
For the past decade, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably worried about finding or keeping any job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antibiotic-Resistent Bacterium: Obamacare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/25/antibiotic-resistent-bacterium-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/25/antibiotic-resistent-bacterium-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>Overexposure to antibiotics and antibacterial soaps and lotions makes bacteria stronger. They adapt.
That same thing happened to Obamacare over the years. It&amp;rsquo;s now untouchable.
** Obamacare survived the election of Scott Brown in Massachusetts. So it was born in a toxic environment. ** Then, Obamacare survived two Supreme Court rulings, each time by a single vote from the chief justice. ** Finally, Obamacare survived seven years of Republican promises to repeal it immediately upon winning the White House and Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Questions for the Freedom Caucus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/25/7-questions-for-the-freedom-caucus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/25/7-questions-for-the-freedom-caucus/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I placed blame for the healthcare debacle at Speaker Ryan&amp;rsquo;s feet. I also wrote that I expected the Republican establishment to blame the tea party. To blame us for aborting the Trump presidency in his first 100 days.
Today, I&amp;rsquo;m going to beat the establishment to that punch a little. Because the Freedom Caucus and some of my favorite action organizations looked a little juvenile in this debate. Juvenile and stupid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Ryan&#39;s Battle of Kasserine Pass</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/paul-ryans-battle-of-kasserine-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 19:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/paul-ryans-battle-of-kasserine-pass/</guid>
      <description>General George S. Patton arrived in North Africa with a single mission: lead the Allied forces to victory over the Hun.
But Patton&amp;rsquo;s assignment was also in response to a miserable and deadly failure of leadership. The failed leadership of General Lloyd Fredendall.
 Fredendall was a Francophobe and an Anglophobe ill-suited to wage coalition warfare; a micromanager who bypassed the chain of command – giving orders as far down as company level; a coward, he allowed animus with subordinates to affect his judgment and undercut their authority; and finally, staring defeat in the face at Kasserine, he tried to pin the blame on others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neediness</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/neediness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 15:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/24/neediness/</guid>
      <description>President Trump is teaching the world a huge lesson. That valuable lesson goes something like this:
Don&amp;rsquo;t be needy.
Jim Camp is a world-famous negotiation coach. Jim has led some enormous negotiations: labor disputes, huge multi-national buys, and mergers. This is is what Jim says about neediness in his book Start With No:
 It is absolutely imperative that you as a negotiator understand the importance of this point. You do NOT need this deal, because** to be needy is to lose control and make bad decisions**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare Repeal Vote Results (Prediction)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/23/obamacare-repeal-vote-results-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 03:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/23/obamacare-repeal-vote-results-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Today, President Trump changed the game. He changed the Prisoner&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma (coordination) into a game of Chicken (competition).
Lifer Republicans have no experience with games of chicken. They were raised on coordination games.
By changing the game to Chicken, Donald Trump greatly increased the chances that phony Paul Ryan&amp;rsquo;s healthcare will PASS.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why briefly.
Psychologically, people always think they have more time. Republicans, in particular, believe time is limitless. Lifelong Republicans think they can delay any decision until the decision they want is a given.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Strategy: Ignore Government Diet Advice</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/22/healthcare-strategy-ignore-government-diet-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 22:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/22/healthcare-strategy-ignore-government-diet-advice/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I established an end: great health care that ordinary people can afford.
You remember I talked about John Braddock&amp;rsquo;s explanation of strategy: choose the end and work backward. Then forword.
And Braddock&amp;rsquo;s first step after choosing an end: what comes immediately before. That&amp;rsquo;s where we are today.
A few weeks back, I wrote several posts about diet (here and here). I warned you that the government and doctors and, especially, dieticians have been poising us for years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Strategy Beats  Hyperventilating</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/20/healthcare-strategy-beats-hyperventilating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/20/healthcare-strategy-beats-hyperventilating/</guid>
      <description>Paul Ryan unveiled a health care bill two weeks ago. Ryan&amp;rsquo;s favorite lobbyists wrote it. They wrote it in secret. They dumped it on the House GOP caucus.
A lot of my friends on the right went hermatile. &amp;ldquo;Shoved down our throats!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Obamacare two-point-oh!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Obamacare Lite!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Tyranny!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Entitlements!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Worse than Obamacare!&amp;rdquo; The most frequently used key on the keyboards of tea partiers was the exclamation point!
It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get spun up over the way Speaker Ryan handled the bill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can&#39;t Unsee This</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/17/you-cant-unsee-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 10:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/17/you-cant-unsee-this/</guid>
      <description>If you see some idiot in a kilt today, it might be me.
  You know my story. Aon scéal? (Gaelic for &amp;ldquo;Any story?&amp;quot;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reagan Gives Trump&#39;s Budget TWO THUMBS UP!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/16/reagan-gives-trumps-budget-two-thumbs-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 02:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/16/reagan-gives-trumps-budget-two-thumbs-up/</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump delivered his budget and a message for Congress.
Since I&amp;rsquo;m lazy, I&amp;rsquo;ll quote Time magazine.
First, the President&amp;rsquo;s message to Congress:
 &amp;ldquo;I urge the members of Congress to remember that last November the American people&amp;rsquo;s message was loud and clear. The mandate for change, expressed by the American people, was not my mandate; it was our mandate.&amp;rdquo;
 Then, the analysis:
 The President&amp;rsquo;s meaning was unmistakable: the public wants deep cuts in both spending and taxes, and any legislator who tries to keep the ax from falling risks putting his own neck under an ax at the polls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump, The Jobs President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/08/trump-the-jobs-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 13:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/08/trump-the-jobs-president/</guid>
      <description>You can actually FEEL America getting GREAT again!
ADP payroll report shows President Trump made a big down payment on his promise to be the **greatest jobs president ever. **
The economy added nearly 300,000 new jobs last month. Economists expected a rise of 190,000. It was the biggest jump in jobs in 6 years.
The jobs were the good kind of jobs Trump talks about: manufacturing, mining. Jobs with grit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Many Times Trump&#39;s Crazy Statements Turned Out to Be Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/07/many-times-trumps-crazy-statements-turned-out-to-be-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 01:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/07/many-times-trumps-crazy-statements-turned-out-to-be-right/</guid>
      <description>Almost every time Donald Trump says something crazy, something so outlandish and wrong, he later turns out to be right.
I know his critics can&amp;rsquo;t read my blog. (Literally, they can&amp;rsquo;t. They have a psychological problem that prevents their brains from processing information that&amp;rsquo;s inconsistent with their beliefs.) But for those of you who want to be right with the truth instead of just right with your own opinion, this will be a great post to forward to your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BACKFIRE: Psychological Tricks Used to Advance Russian Conspiracy Theory</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/07/how-newspapers-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 18:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/07/how-newspapers-lie/</guid>
      <description>Newspapers lie. And by &amp;ldquo;newspapers,&amp;rdquo; I mean the whole mainstream media.
Yesterday I told you how Donald Trump punked the media by pulling a Crazy Ivan maneuver. A critic on Twitter thinks I&amp;rsquo;m lying. He thinks I&amp;rsquo;m lying because he read a news article. He read it in the New York Times.
This Twitter critic thinks it&amp;rsquo;s okay for the New York Times to lie (&amp;ldquo;Wiretapped Data Used In Inquiry of Trump Aides&amp;rdquo;), as long as they only lie in their headlines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump&#39;s Crazy Ivan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/06/donald-trumps-crazy-ivan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 03:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/06/donald-trumps-crazy-ivan/</guid>
      <description>Cold War submarine lore. I can&amp;rsquo;t go into all of it here, but I can tell you about one bit of that lore: the Crazy Ivan.
Modern submarines have incredible passive sonar arrays. They can hear everything in the ocean for hundreds of miles around. Everything.
Everything except something directly behind them. Behind a submarine is a big propeller or &amp;ldquo;screw.&amp;rdquo; It turns. It pushes water abaft. The noise and the motion combine to prevent sound waves from reaching the sensors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John McCain&#39;s Most Evil Sin</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/05/john-mccains-most-evil-sin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 18:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/05/john-mccains-most-evil-sin/</guid>
      <description>John McCain may have done some heroic things, but he is a hero no more.
Imagine how you&amp;rsquo;d feel.
A knock on your door.
Through the deadlights around your front door, you see a car with government stencils on the side. When you get close enough, you look out and see a man in uniform. An officer. You know. You know why he&amp;rsquo;s here. Your throat tightens. You want to turn around and walk away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Democrats Loved &#39;em Some Ruskies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/when-democrats-loved-em-some-ruskies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/when-democrats-loved-em-some-ruskies/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/Py8BF0hHPnc
In 2012, Barack Obama got caught telling Russian Prime Minister Medvedev that he&amp;rsquo;d have more &amp;ldquo;flexibility&amp;rdquo; after the election.
Later in 2012, during a debate, Obama accused GOP candidate Mitt Romney of stoking Cold War fears against our new friends in Moscow. Obama said, “The 1980s are now calling to ask for their foreign policy back because…the Cold War’s been over for 20 years!” In fact, in 2012, the whole pantheon of pantsuit partiersmocked warnings about Russia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Russians Are Coming! The Russians Are Coming!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/the-russians-are-coming-the-russians-are-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/the-russians-are-coming-the-russians-are-coming/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/IEWWRbn4zG0
In 1966, Hollywood liberals made a very funny movie. The Russians Are Coming! The Russians Are Coming! The movie mocked Cold Warriors and ridiculed hyper-paranoia about the dangers posed by Russia.
Some of those same Hollywood liberals are now running around screaming &amp;ldquo;The Russians Are Coming! The Russians Are Coming!&amp;rdquo;
Funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rally in Ballwin, Missouri Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/trump-rally-in-ballwin-missouri-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 20:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/03/trump-rally-in-ballwin-missouri-saturday/</guid>
      <description>Reader Rick reminded me that there&amp;rsquo;s a Trump rally closer to St. Louis on Saturday. He provides a link to the Facebook page.
 If you can’t make it to Jeff City, here is another opportunity on Saturday, March 4, 11-1. Vlasis Park, Balwin https://www.facebook.com/events/1227190650721092 See you there!
 Thanks, Rick!
DETAILS MARCH 4 11 am to 1pm 14811 Manchester Rd, BALLWIN 63011 VLASIS PARK *
97.1 FM Emcee Marc Cox Alyssa and Celeste Drinkard perform National Anthem</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rally Missouri</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/02/trump-rally-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 05:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/02/trump-rally-missouri/</guid>
      <description>The President needs us. From Show Me Trump
THIS SATURDAY!
  
President Trump needs our support and hundreds of Missourians have already RSVP&amp;rsquo;d that they&amp;rsquo;ll be attending! It&amp;rsquo;s clear he is being severely pressured by Democrats and the media alike. Our rally will send an important message to our new Commander in Chief&amp;ndash;We The People support you! Find the Facebook event page by clicking here.
These pro-Trump rallies are happening on Saturday across the entire USA - don&amp;rsquo;t miss the Missouri statewide rally in Jefferson City!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Tell a Lie</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/02/how-to-tell-a-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 03:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/02/how-to-tell-a-lie/</guid>
      <description>You had to laugh. Claire McCaskill jumped on Twitter to announce she&amp;rsquo;d never met the Russian ambassador to the US. Before that, she jumped on Twitter to brag about being so damned important and vital that the Russian ambassador sought her oracle-like guidance.
After people mocked and scorned her silly lie, Claire McCaskill made up more lies to cover the first lie. You know, like a liar.
Senator McCaskill believes Jeff Sessions should resign for not telling a lie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How ObamaCare Benefits from the Scarcity Heuristic</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/23/obamacare-benefits-from-scarcity-heuristic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 13:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/23/obamacare-benefits-from-scarcity-heuristic/</guid>
      <description>The Concorde was a supersonic passenger plane. It shuttled people between New York and Paris very quickly.
When commercial Concorde flights began in 1976, the novelty and excitement of flying at twice the speed of sound led people to line up to take the flights. But after 27 years and several safety mishaps, the Concorde&amp;rsquo;s popularity waned. Flights were often less than half full, so British Airways, the operator, was losing money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give McCain a Break</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/19/give-mccain-a-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 17:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/19/give-mccain-a-break/</guid>
      <description>Hate John McCain if you want. Call McCain a traitor, even.
I look at John McCain and marvel at his strength. Many do.
Everyone knows about McCain being shot down over Vietnam and spending 5 years in a POW camp. But most people don&amp;rsquo;t know about the deep emotional scar McCain brought home with him. And that emotional scar undoubtedly drives him to his fits of anger and telling lies about people he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/17/the-joy-of-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 18:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/17/the-joy-of-trump/</guid>
      <description>What bothers you most when you&amp;rsquo;re in a bad mood?
You can imagine what it&amp;rsquo;s like be in a bad mood, can&amp;rsquo;t you? People go through periods of deep funk when nothing seems bright or cheerful, don&amp;rsquo;t they?
And when you&amp;rsquo;re in those moods, what&amp;rsquo;s the worst thing? That&amp;rsquo;s right, it&amp;rsquo;s being around a bunch of happy people having fun.
And that&amp;rsquo;s exactly how the left feels when they see Trump at a press conference: miserable amid the fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greatest Presser Ever. Wow. Stunned Happy.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/16/greatest-presser-ever-wow-stunned-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 00:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/16/greatest-presser-ever-wow-stunned-happy/</guid>
      <description>Imagine Michael Jordan&amp;rsquo;s best game ever. Or Tiger Woods. That&amp;rsquo;s what it was like watching President Trump today. Amazing.
The President looked poised, cheerful, and humorous. He volleyed with Jim Acosta of CNN. He rated each question &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;bad.&amp;rdquo; He explained why he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a nuclear war with Russia because the press seems to think nuclear war is a good thing. He mocked those in the press who want him to bomb that Russian intel ship off Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slouching Towards the Climax</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/11/slouching-toward-the-climax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 21:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/11/slouching-toward-the-climax/</guid>
      <description>Soon thereafter, this great gate is sealed by the Crisis resolution, when victors are rewarded and enemies punished; when empires or nations are forged or destroyed; when treaties are signed and boundaries redrawn; and when peace is accepted, troops repatriated, and life begun anew. One large chapter of history ends, and another starts.
 In a very real sense, one society dies— and another is born.
—The Fourth Turning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Resistance: Defined</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/10/the-resistance-defined/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 23:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/10/the-resistance-defined/</guid>
      <description>The leftists who want you and me to die (at their hands?) call themselves The Resistance.
Okay. Let&amp;rsquo;s call them that.
Author Steven Pressfield wrote a book about defeating The Resistance. It&amp;rsquo;s called The War of Art, and it&amp;rsquo;s an awesome, wonderful book.
Overcoming and defeating The Resistance, Pressfield tells us, is the key to living the good life. I agree, even if I don&amp;rsquo;t agree on some of his enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Want You Dead</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/09/people-want-you-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 23:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/09/people-want-you-dead/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself in the midst of a riot? Even if you’ve only seen riots on television, you can probably imagine how it feels to be inside one.
Imagine yourself surrounded on all sides by angry faces dressed in shabby clothes, some faces covered with bandanas or ski masks. People are chanting something you can&amp;rsquo;t quite understand, like a private joke you&amp;rsquo;re not allowed to get. Or maybe they&amp;rsquo;re chanting at you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Diet Makes You Fat and Kills You</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/08/government-diet-makes-you-fat-and-kills-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/08/government-diet-makes-you-fat-and-kills-you/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re sick and fat, it might not be your fault. You listen to your doctor. You follow government diet guidelines. You eat more fresh fruit and vegetables. You cut down on animal fat. You eat more grains.
And you just get sicker and fatter.
You&amp;rsquo;re told it&amp;rsquo;s your fault. But it&amp;rsquo;s probably not.
You might be a good mom or dad who wants your kids to learn healthy eating habits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are You Letting Your Doctor Kill You?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/05/why-are-you-letting-your-doctor-kill-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 20:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/05/why-are-you-letting-your-doctor-kill-you/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re overweight, have high cholesterol, diabetes, Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s, heart disease, or cancer, it&amp;rsquo;s probably not your fault. You&amp;rsquo;ve been told to eat poison your whole life, by people who are supposed to know better. Here&amp;rsquo;s some truth to set you free.
Actually, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why. But it&amp;rsquo;s happening to you and millions of other people. Doctors are killing their patients. And they&amp;rsquo;re getting a lot of help from the government and big agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Hold Your Breath for 3 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/29/how-to-hold-your-breath-for-3-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/29/how-to-hold-your-breath-for-3-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Remember when you were a kid? All the weird challenges and contests you&amp;rsquo;d wage with your friends? There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance that breath-holding was one of them. Who can hold their breath the longest, right?
I was always good at this when I was young, but I&amp;rsquo;m not that young anymore. I&amp;rsquo;m 53, but I held my breath for two minutes and 47 seconds last Thursday. And I could have gone longer, but I was bored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unprotected Sects</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/28/unprotected-sects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 16:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/28/unprotected-sects/</guid>
      <description>The television activists at CNN look like college seniors who learned upon returning from winter break that credit requirements for graduation were just upped from 120 hours to 180 hours. And there ain&amp;rsquo;t grandfathering!
Diehard NeverTrumpers attack Trump supporters on social media like bitter, divorcing spouses locked in a pitched custody battle. And there ain&amp;rsquo;t no reconciliation!
Establishment Republicans, Democrats who count on union support, the more radical unions like SEIU and NEA, Planned Parenthood baby killers, and tenured communist professors shriek like hormone-crazed adolescents in fall-down hysterics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Steel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/25/american-steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 13:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/25/american-steel/</guid>
      <description>I know people, and you probably do too, who are out of work from the United Steel Granite City (aka Granite City Steel) closure. It&amp;rsquo;s disheartening and depressing for people who worked hard all those years, thrown into the street because of bad trade deals and stifling regulations.
But President Trump has ordered the Keystone Pipeline renegotiated to require American steel pipes. That&amp;rsquo;s great news for our friends and neighbors in GC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Don&#39;t Matter to American Liberals</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/24/black-lived-dont-matter-to-american-liberals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 03:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/24/black-lived-dont-matter-to-american-liberals/</guid>
      <description>President Trump (who, by the way, has accomplished more in two days than Obama did in eight years) saw Chicago&amp;rsquo;s horrific crime statistics and warned the mayor and the governor to get to work or he&amp;rsquo;ll fix it himself. Seventy-five percent of murder victims in Chicago are black.
Immediately, leftists, who apparently enjoy all the carnage in Chicago, attacked Trump&amp;rsquo;s call for fewer shootings and murders.
Think of that. LIBERALS WANT MORE MURDER!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrible Day for NeverTrump—Great Day for the Constitution</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/terrible-day-for-nevertrump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/terrible-day-for-nevertrump/</guid>
      <description>One way to summarize Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s first business day in office is to say he followed through on many, many campaign promises. Another way to look at it is that Trump slaughtered NeverTrump. Both explanations are accurate, but one is the cause, the other the effect.
First, you know I pay very little attention to Facebook. Too much craziness over there. But friends of mine do occasionally send me screen shots of things they find outrageous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean Spicer and the White House Press Corp Proved Me 100% Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/sean-spicer-and-the-white-house-press-corp-proved-me-100-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 22:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/sean-spicer-and-the-white-house-press-corp-proved-me-100-right/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s great to be right.
Yesterday I told you that White House Press Secretary Sean Spicer played the White House press corps by telling the truth. But the press corps and many Americans have a psychosis that literally replaces some words with other words. It&amp;rsquo;s not dyslexia. It&amp;rsquo;s far worse because it&amp;rsquo;s selective.
In this case, Spicer said &amp;ldquo;witness&amp;rdquo; but journalists everywhere repeated, &amp;ldquo;attend.&amp;rdquo; I wrote about it here.
Well, today, Spicer explained the situation to a psychotic journalist almost the same way I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Spot Journalism&#39;s Psychosis</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/how-to-spot-journalisms-psychosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 12:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/23/how-to-spot-journalisms-psychosis/</guid>
      <description>When your brain automatically alters perceptions, there&amp;rsquo;s something wrong with you.
Reporters have this psychosis. Journalists. They have very bad ADHD it seems. They can&amp;rsquo;t pay attention. Like kids with ADHD. Chuck Todd and everybody at Business Insider should probably take Ritalin or something.
Reporters are also narcissists. No one goes into journalism unless they have a pathologically inflated ego. No one.
So I&amp;rsquo;m going to walk you through the proof, slowly, so even our narcissistic, hyperactive, attention-deficit-disordered journalists can understand that Sean Spicer played with them like a cat pawing a dying moth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: San Antonio Mall Shooting: One Dead, Six Wounded, Armed Citizen Shot Murderer</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/22/breaking-san-antonio-mall-shooting-one-dead-six-wounded-armed-citizen-shot-murderer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 23:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/22/breaking-san-antonio-mall-shooting-one-dead-six-wounded-armed-citizen-shot-murderer/</guid>
      <description>A Good Samaritan was shot and killed and three shot in a &amp;ldquo;robbery gone very wrong&amp;rdquo; at Rolling Oaks Mall in San Antonio, Texas Sunday afternoon about 3:30 p.m. Two others transported to hospitals with other medical conditions. One suspect is still at large and assumed armed and dangerous.
The dead man was a shopper who attempted to stop two robbers after they robbed a Kay Jewelers store in the mall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Meant It All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/22/trump-meant-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 18:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/22/trump-meant-it-all/</guid>
      <description>Trump&amp;rsquo;s enemies took refuge in the self-created narrative that his campaign was 100% American showmanship. The crooked press and the corrupt establishment, while dissing Trump publicly, scoffed privately. They &amp;ldquo;knew&amp;rdquo; his supporters were idiots and yahoos—marginally functional Neanderthals from America&amp;rsquo;s unreconstructed backwoods whose ability to think, handicapped by genetics, was further crippled by the moonshine distilled in the shed behind their putrid outhouse for personal consumption by their incest-ridden family of knuckle-dragging racist homophobes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebuilding St. Louis</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/21/rebuilding-st-louis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 21:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/21/rebuilding-st-louis/</guid>
      <description>A lot of well-connected St. Louis Democrats like to say &amp;ldquo;everything&amp;rsquo;s fine&amp;rdquo; with the city and the St. Louis region. You know, though, that St. Louis is a mess. A hot, simmering mess covered with rot. (Check out StLouisPatina&amp;rsquo;s photo essay of St. Louis decay.) But the people responsible for St. Louis&amp;rsquo;s decay want you to pretend there are no problems. Of course, they do.
And it&amp;rsquo;s getting worse. You might find yourself wondering how bad things are in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/20/hallelujah-hallelujah-hallelujah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 17:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/20/hallelujah-hallelujah-hallelujah/</guid>
      <description>https://youtu.be/TLYAyuf1I1Q</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the America of Our Dreams</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/19/welcome-to-the-america-of-our-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 01:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/19/welcome-to-the-america-of-our-dreams/</guid>
      <description>Jim Durbin called me this evening. &amp;ldquo;Are you excited?&amp;rdquo; he asked.
Jim was in the crowd at the very first Tea Party in St. Louis, February 27, 2009. A cold Friday. He and more than a thousand other folks took off work and school to see what this protest was all about. Like so many others, Jim knew America needed a change. A big one. A change built on the hopes and dreams and fierce independence of ordinary people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America&#39;s Business is Jobs, Not College</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/14/americas-business-is-jobs-not-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/14/americas-business-is-jobs-not-college/</guid>
      <description>Many of us are guilty. I am, too. You, probably.
In high school (and after) we mocked the kids who took shop. The &amp;ldquo;greasers&amp;rdquo; who got credit for wrenching on cars or welding or making cabinets. It was the 1980s and shop, along with home economics, became an elective in most schools.
Until the 80s, some practical life skill class was a requirement at most American public and parochial high schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stan Kroenke&#39;s Long Con Has Just Started</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/04/stan-kroenkes-long-con-has-just-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 04:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/04/stan-kroenkes-long-con-has-just-started/</guid>
      <description>You thought Stan Kroenke wanted a team in Los Angeles? I don&amp;rsquo;t think so. I think Stan is playing a long con. And I think it&amp;rsquo;s a brilliant strategy.
Los Angeles is a terrible market for football teams, but it&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic market for the NFL. It would be a perfect place to build a permanent home for the Super Bowl. Los Angeles has fantastic weather, great attractions, and a huge pool of football fans, fans of every team in the NFL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Don&#39;t Hear &#34;Big Data&#34; Much Anymore, And For That I&#39;m Thankful</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/04/you-dont-hear-big-data-much-anymore-and-for-that-im-thankful/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 02:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/04/you-dont-hear-big-data-much-anymore-and-for-that-im-thankful/</guid>
      <description>This is about Big Data.
You really can&amp;rsquo;t over-estimate what suckers business people are.
I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about people who create things or improve things. Guys like Steve Jobs and Donald Trump built great businesses. But they weren&amp;rsquo;t business people. They were builders. Running a business was a necessary evil that allowed them the freedom to build what they wanted to build. They were great businessmen because they cared about the work their companies did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Tore It Apart—We Can Rebuild It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/01/we-tore-it-apart-we-can-rebuild-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 15:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/01/we-tore-it-apart-we-can-rebuild-it/</guid>
      <description>How will history remember the Tea Party movement of 2009 to 2016? The answer to that question depends on what we do next.
The Tea Party movement was an antagonistic movement. We opposed bad stuff. We sought punishment for bad actors. We saw that the experts were wrong, and we pointed out their folly. Like William F. Buckley&amp;rsquo;s charter for National Review, we stood athwart history, yelling &amp;ldquo;STOP!&amp;rdquo; At its heart, the Tea Party movement opposed a corrupt and insulated establishment class.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>