<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academics on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academics on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Don&#39;t Need More Technology--They Need Less</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</guid>
      <description>I was on my high school&amp;rsquo;s board of education for a year. It was quite an honor, honestly, but I screwed it up.
At the time, I was a software architect. They put me on the board as the technology guy. I was supposed to make the case for more funding for smart boards and other tech stuff.
But I said kids really don&amp;rsquo;t need more technology in school. Technology, I said, was like sex education: they&amp;rsquo;ll get more than they can handle on the streets or watching TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today Is National Stomp On Marx Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/today-is-national-stomp-on-marx-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 03:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/today-is-national-stomp-on-marx-day/</guid>
      <description>Join the fun and Stomp On Marx!

Stomping on things is all the rage on some college campuses. But the kids are missing out on the real fun.
Here’s an exercise I highly recommend for teachers of kids age 14 and up.
Stomp On Marx!
Here’s how you do it.
 Download and print this picture of the father of communism, Karl Marx. (click for larger image)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s The Dirty Little Secret About Teachers Nobody Is Telling You About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/15/heres-the-dirty-little-secret-about-teachers-nobody-is-telling-you-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 05:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/15/heres-the-dirty-little-secret-about-teachers-nobody-is-telling-you-about/</guid>
      <description>I know a teacher pretty well, and I know nasty little secrets she’s not telling.
She sneaks out of bed at 4:45 every morning. No one else is up. No one’s watching her. At that hour, she can do whatever she wants without consequence.
She sneaks downstairs and puts on her make-up in front of the TV. She also encrypts mysterious lesson plans into a little black book. Names and numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Schools Replace Great Fiction With Government propaganda</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</guid>
      <description>[Originally posted on Redstate.com]
English was my favorite subject in school, so much so that I can still recite from memory large passages of the books we read, like A Separate Peace:
 I went back to Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there 15 years before.
 And who doesn’t know this by heart:
 If you really want to hear about it, the first thing you’ll probably want to know is where I was born and what my lousy childhood was like and how my parents were occupied and all before they had me and all that David Copperfield kind of crap, but I don’t feel like going into it, if you want to know the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Suffocate Free Speech</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 15:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</guid>
      <description>Colleges in the United States are systematically destroying free speech, free thought, and creative writing. Sixty-five percent of colleges and universities censor students, even in creative writing classes.
[youtube=https://youtu.be/Z3vgGqlZGGE] Hillsdale or nothing.
Related articles  * [GREG LUKIANOFF IN THE NEW YORK TIMES: Feigning Free Speech on Campus. &amp;quot;Colleges and universities a...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/155479/) (pjmedia.com) * [ONE WAY FREE SPEECH: The progressive vision of free speech is decidedly one-way, excluding any s...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/154514/) (pjmedia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>