<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academics on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academics on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Don&#39;t Need More Technology--They Need Less</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</guid>
      <description>I was on my high school&amp;rsquo;s board of education for a year. It was quite an honor, honestly, but I screwed it up.
At the time, I was a software architect. They put me on the board as the technology guy. I was supposed to make the case for more funding for smart boards and other tech stuff.
But I said kids really don&amp;rsquo;t need more technology in school. Technology, I said, was like sex education: they&amp;rsquo;ll get more than they can handle on the streets or watching TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today Is National Stomp On Marx Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/today-is-national-stomp-on-marx-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 03:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/today-is-national-stomp-on-marx-day/</guid>
      <description>Join the fun and Stomp On Marx!

Stomping on things is all the rage on some college campuses. But the kids are missing out on the real fun.
Here’s an exercise I highly recommend for teachers of kids age 14 and up.
Stomp On Marx!
Here’s how you do it.
 Download and print this picture of the father of communism, Karl Marx. (click for larger image)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s The Dirty Little Secret About Teachers Nobody Is Telling You About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/15/heres-the-dirty-little-secret-about-teachers-nobody-is-telling-you-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 05:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/15/heres-the-dirty-little-secret-about-teachers-nobody-is-telling-you-about/</guid>
      <description>I know a teacher pretty well, and I know nasty little secrets she’s not telling.
She sneaks out of bed at 4:45 every morning. No one else is up. No one’s watching her. At that hour, she can do whatever she wants without consequence.
She sneaks downstairs and puts on her make-up in front of the TV. She also encrypts mysterious lesson plans into a little black book. Names and numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Schools Replace Great Fiction With Government propaganda</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</guid>
      <description>[Originally posted on Redstate.com]
English was my favorite subject in school, so much so that I can still recite from memory large passages of the books we read, like A Separate Peace:
 I went back to Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there 15 years before.
 And who doesn’t know this by heart:
 If you really want to hear about it, the first thing you’ll probably want to know is where I was born and what my lousy childhood was like and how my parents were occupied and all before they had me and all that David Copperfield kind of crap, but I don’t feel like going into it, if you want to know the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Suffocate Free Speech</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 15:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</guid>
      <description>Colleges in the United States are systematically destroying free speech, free thought, and creative writing. Sixty-five percent of colleges and universities censor students, even in creative writing classes.
[youtube=https://youtu.be/Z3vgGqlZGGE] Hillsdale or nothing.
Related articles  * [GREG LUKIANOFF IN THE NEW YORK TIMES: Feigning Free Speech on Campus. &amp;quot;Colleges and universities a...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/155479/) (pjmedia.com) * [ONE WAY FREE SPEECH: The progressive vision of free speech is decidedly one-way, excluding any s...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/154514/) (pjmedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studies Show Most Americans Are Too Stupid to Vote</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/29/studies-show-most-americans-are-too-stupid-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 21:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/29/studies-show-most-americans-are-too-stupid-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>The new fad among Democrats is to see how many illegal aliens they can pack into a voting booth. While we conservatives decry this illegal and anti-American grab at tyrannical power, we should take some solace in this sobering fact: those illegal aliens probably know as much about the American political system as most 13th generation Americans.
  
The fact is, most Americans are too stupid about politics to vote, which explains the 2008 election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Biggest Rip-Off in America is College Tuition</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/29/the-biggest-rip-off-in-america-is-college-tuition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/29/the-biggest-rip-off-in-america-is-college-tuition/</guid>
      <description>While everyone was screaming about the rising cost of medical treatment, America’s leftist incubation chambers—colleges and universities—robbed us of our economic future. And the federal government’s misguided student aid program is to blame.
**What allows this growth? ** * Increased per student government funding * Massive private and public debt
Who benefits? * College administrators * Unions working on college campuses * Political causes that college administrators like (liberal)
Who pays?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin Talks to Lee Presser</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/31/ed-martin-talks-to-lee-presser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 10:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/31/ed-martin-talks-to-lee-presser/</guid>
      <description>This is an important conversation in an important race. Please watch.
Ed talks about regulation, taxes, debt, Race to the Top, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Lucky?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/14/whos-lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 23:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/14/whos-lucky/</guid>
      <description>There’s a “special” school in St. Louis County. Its seniors graduated on last Friday.

How sad it must be for those kids. They’re not graduating from the district’s “normal” schools with their peers. For various reasons, they’ve been relegated to a school for misfits.
Seeing the building makes the bad feelings worse. It’s a former grade school, crammed inconveniently behind a bank and a Taco Bell. Its Eisenhower era architecture stands out amidst its Mortgage Boom surroundings like a dandelion on golf course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Great Reasons to Send Your Kids to Vacation Liberty School</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/25/3-great-reasons-to-send-your-kids-to-vacation-liberty-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/25/3-great-reasons-to-send-your-kids-to-vacation-liberty-school/</guid>
      <description>Register today for Vacation Liberty School. Here&amp;rsquo;s 3 reasons why you should:
 Most school systems don&amp;rsquo;t care about liberty; they care about conformity. The only way kids will learn an appreciation for the blessings of libertyis if their parents send them to schools that put liberty at the center of the cirriculum. That&amp;rsquo;s what Vacation Liberty School does.
  Many teachers would love to teach more about the blessings of liberty to their skulls full of mush, but they can&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Despots Use Money to Buy Power</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/29/despots-use-money-to-buy-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 17:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/29/despots-use-money-to-buy-power/</guid>
      <description>Politicians don’t seek money. They seek power. They use money to acquire power. Once they have the power, money becomes irrelevant.
Did you see how states behaved last summer? The “Race to the Top” is all you need to know about the relationship between government money, power, and degradation.
The Race to the Top education initiative dangled cash in front of states. Most states, including Missouri, bit. They competed against each other for the privilege of surrendering their sovereignty over education to a DoE overlord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Has the Fear?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</guid>
      <description>For 100 years in America, government, business, and the education establishment built schools and laws about education. The purpose of these government schools and education laws was to produce compliant, unimaginative, order-taking automatons.
Don’t believe me? Here’s Woodrow Wilson, educator and president, speaking on the American plan for education:
 We want one class of persons to have a liberal education, and we want another class of persons, a very much larger class of necessity in every society, to forgo the privilege of a liberal education and fit themselves to perform specific difficult manual tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>