<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economy on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economy on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 14:25:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jobs Trump Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/jobs-trump-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 14:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/jobs-trump-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>I feel drunk but I&amp;rsquo;m sober, I&amp;rsquo;m young and I&amp;rsquo;m underpaid I&amp;rsquo;m tired but I&amp;rsquo;m working, yeah I care but I&amp;rsquo;m restless, I&amp;rsquo;m here but I&amp;rsquo;m really gone I&amp;rsquo;m wrong and I&amp;rsquo;m sorry baby
 —Alanis Morissette, One Hand In My Pocket
If your biggest problem involves choosing between multiple appealing jobs, everything else will seem less important. Because picking the right job is a really big deal.
For the past decade, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably worried about finding or keeping any job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump, The Jobs President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/08/trump-the-jobs-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 13:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/08/trump-the-jobs-president/</guid>
      <description>You can actually FEEL America getting GREAT again!
ADP payroll report shows President Trump made a big down payment on his promise to be the **greatest jobs president ever. **
The economy added nearly 300,000 new jobs last month. Economists expected a rise of 190,000. It was the biggest jump in jobs in 6 years.
The jobs were the good kind of jobs Trump talks about: manufacturing, mining. Jobs with grit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Steel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/25/american-steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 13:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/25/american-steel/</guid>
      <description>I know people, and you probably do too, who are out of work from the United Steel Granite City (aka Granite City Steel) closure. It&amp;rsquo;s disheartening and depressing for people who worked hard all those years, thrown into the street because of bad trade deals and stifling regulations.
But President Trump has ordered the Keystone Pipeline renegotiated to require American steel pipes. That&amp;rsquo;s great news for our friends and neighbors in GC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America&#39;s Business is Jobs, Not College</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/14/americas-business-is-jobs-not-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/14/americas-business-is-jobs-not-college/</guid>
      <description>Many of us are guilty. I am, too. You, probably.
In high school (and after) we mocked the kids who took shop. The &amp;ldquo;greasers&amp;rdquo; who got credit for wrenching on cars or welding or making cabinets. It was the 1980s and shop, along with home economics, became an elective in most schools.
Until the 80s, some practical life skill class was a requirement at most American public and parochial high schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Climax</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/22/predicting-the-climax/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 22:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/22/predicting-the-climax/</guid>
      <description>We are watching The Fourth Turning unfold before our eyes.
While you should read all of The Fourth Turning by generational historians William Strauss and Neil Howe, here&amp;rsquo;s one of their predictions for this point in time. The prediction was published in 1997:
 The economy will in time recover from its early and vertiginous reversals. Late in the Crisis, with trust and hope and urgency growing fast, it may even achieve unprecedented levels of efficiency and production.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>