<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gateway pundit on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/gateway-pundit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gateway pundit on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:24:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/gateway-pundit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Left Doubles Down on Threats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</guid>
      <description>What would you do?
Suppose you did something stupid. You blamed the wrong person, for instance, for a capital crime. Then supposed one of your comrades compounded your . . . error . . . by threatening to kill someone on national television?
If you’re an American leftist, you might double down by issuing even more death threats to even more people.
That’s what’ happening right now in America. Death threats are pouring into Trent Humphries, Tucson Tea Party organizer, Dana Loesch, Sarah Palin (who vows not to be silenced), Glenn Beck, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All-American Alternative to Leftist Omaha Steaks</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/18/all-american-alternative-to-leftist-omaha-steaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 14:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/18/all-american-alternative-to-leftist-omaha-steaks/</guid>
      <description>Jim Hoft of Gateway Pundit exposed Omaha Steak’s leftism yesterday. Omaha pulled its ads from Glenn Beck for ideological reasons.
 We took your comments regarding the Glenn Beck Program to heart. After further review and careful consideration, we have decided to pull all advertising from Glenn Beck programming effective December 20th, 2010.
 Then the president of the company, Bruce Simon, tried to deny his political motives.
If you want to order top quality meats at great prices, you don’t have to put money in a lefty’s pocket.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>