<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RCGA on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/rcga/</link>
    <description>Recent content in RCGA on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 18:57:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/rcga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How the RCGA Is Ruining St. Louis and What Businesses Can Do About It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/29/how-the-rcga-is-ruining-st-louis-and-what-businesses-can-do-about-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 18:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/29/how-the-rcga-is-ruining-st-louis-and-what-businesses-can-do-about-it/</guid>
      <description>Everyone knows and accepts that government does stupid things. Sometimes it feels like people institute governments and delegate them certain powers just to give us something to complain about.
Government stupidity, scandal, and corruption hits different people in different ways. Government hyperactivity keeps poor people poor by limiting opportunity and by building barriers to exiting poverty programs. “If you take that job, you’ll lose your health insurance.” Compassion my non-qualifying asset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Selling St. Louis?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/04/whos-selling-st-louis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2011 10:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/04/whos-selling-st-louis/</guid>
      <description>Aerotropolis is a pretty obvious attempt to shift tax money into the pockets of Jefferson City favorites. It&amp;rsquo;s an example of crony capitalism at its worst.
Now,KMOV Channel 4&amp;rsquo;s Craig Cheatham shines the light on the people buying and selling St. Louis in this series. Not just Aerotropolis, but the whole oligarchy of incompetent, corrupt, and self-serving Boss Hog-types who seem bent on reducing the St. Louis region to irrelevance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>