<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greece on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/greece/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Greece on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 10:55:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/greece/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics Is War By Other Means</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/15/politics-is-war-by-other-means/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 10:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/15/politics-is-war-by-other-means/</guid>
      <description>WAR IS A MERE CONTINUATION OF POLICY BY OTHER MEANS.
 Good old Clausewitz. Best book on war ever written. (The Art of War was about something else.)
But the 21st century has reversed his famous line. Politics has become war by other means.
Germany has a history of waging wars of conquest. World War I. World War II. The Greek bailout. As Stratfor&amp;rsquo;s George Friedman explains:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chili Palmer</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/13/chili-palmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/13/chili-palmer/</guid>
      <description>The greatest mob movie of all time was Get Shorty. (Please, don’t argue.) The whole movie revolved around this exchange:
 Ronnie Wingate: Excuse me bro&amp;rsquo;, but who the fuck are you? Chili Palmer: I&amp;rsquo;m the one tellin&amp;rsquo; you how it is&amp;hellip;
 Last Sunday, Greece was Chili Palmer. A few days later, Angela Merkel is.
  
Funny how things change.
You probably heard that Greece’s Prime Minister called for a referendum on the troika’s terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Is Crashing and Greece Is Spinning Out of Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/07/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/07/f/</guid>
      <description>The world is even more fragile than it was in 2007. The big banks are bigger. Aggregate bank assets are concentrated in fewer hands. The bank derivatives books are much larger. Market liquidity is worse.
 —James Rickards, The Daily Reckoning
Well, ain’t that just dandy?
And it’s undeniably true. We were told that the 2008 financial meltdown was caused by entities that had grown too large: banks, insurance companies, corporations, derivitives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greece Rejects Central Banksters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/greece-rejects-central-banksters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/05/greece-rejects-central-banksters/</guid>
      <description>Greece has voted to reject the “troika&amp;rsquo;s” bailout terms. The people of Greece said “no” to the central banksters who encourage sovereigns to enslave themselves under mountains of debt.
The Greeks showed remarkable courage and resiliency, and their example could disrupt the entire international banking system. Tyler Durden at Zero Hedge:
 The Greek people have spoken and they said &amp;ldquo;OXI&amp;rdquo;! So congratulations Greece: for the first time you had the chance to tell the Troika, the unelected eurocrats, and the entire status quo establishment, not to mention all the banks, how you really felt and based on the most recent results, some 61% of you told it to go fuck itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Decay in the Age of Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/human-decay-in-the-age-of-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/human-decay-in-the-age-of-obama/</guid>
      <description>In 47BC, Julius Caesar assumed dictatorial power in Rome. He instituted “reforms” that transformed the Republic into the Empire. In the process, he became a dictator. Rome’s decent into oblivion began. In 44BC, seeing the damage Caesar’s tyranny and reforms, three men removed Caesar from power by the method of the day.
History moves faster now than it did 2,000 years ago. A megalomaniacal leaders bent on fundamentally transforming a nation can do remarkable damage in the blink of an eye.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>