<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KMOX on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/kmox/</link>
    <description>Recent content in KMOX on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 04:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/kmox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Will KMOX Drop Candy Crowley Or Lose Its Credibility?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/will-kmox-drop-candy-crowley-or-lose-its-credibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 04:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/16/will-kmox-drop-candy-crowley-or-lose-its-credibility/</guid>
      <description>CNN’s Candy Crowley talks politics during KMOX’s Total Information AM every Friday. KMOX Presents Crowley as a credible source of political information.
But Crowley’s credibility is gone.
On Tuesday, Crowley jumped into the Presidential Debate by claiming Barack Obama called the Benghazi attack “an act of terror” in the Rose Garden on September 12. In hockey, she’d have earned a game misconduct for being the third player into a fight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Candy Crowley: Tea Party Groups Resemble the 13 Colonies, Not the Balkans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/06/hey-candy-crowley-tea-party-groups-resemble-the-13-colonies-more-than-the-balkans/</guid>
      <description>Analogies say more about the speaker than about the subject.
Candy Crowley told KMOX Radio listeners on Friday that Tea Party groups resemble the Balkans without guns.
Wrong. Crappy analogy, Candy. The diverse and autonomous, often quarrelsome,** Tea Party groups remind me of the original 13 colonies.**
The colonies were divided on just about every subject imaginable. The disagreed on slavery, on economics, on agraculture, manufacturing, cities, names &amp;ndash; name it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Herbert Hoover Launched Cardinal Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals were the major league team farthest west and farthest south until the 1950s. But that’s not the only reason the Redbirds built a massive flock of fans from the Alleghenies to the Rockies, and from Canada to the Gulf of Mexico.
The St. Louis Cardinals owe big government statism and technological innovation a big thanks, in addition to geography and great teams. The technology was radio. The big government statist?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>