<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>racism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/racism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in racism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 04:07:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/racism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Blacks Want, According to Science</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/26/what-blacks-want-according-to-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 04:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/26/what-blacks-want-according-to-science/</guid>
      <description>If this shocks you, you&amp;rsquo;re probably a racist. I probably am, too.
Blacks want the same things whites want. Well, blacks want the same things non-elitist whites want. And it&amp;rsquo;s been quantified. By a Jew. Here&amp;rsquo;s what he found, as reported by Business Insider:
 His report (featured below) found that black voters care most about lowering taxes in their community, having a strong leader, creating jobs, changing the tax code to help workers and small businesses, making college affordable, and improving the financial health of the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Emphasis on Race Hurts Efforts to Reform Municipal Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/08/how-race-hurts-efforts-to-reform-municipal-courts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 22:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/08/how-race-hurts-efforts-to-reform-municipal-courts/</guid>
      <description>My story on the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s Ferguson report addressed race early. .
So let&amp;rsquo;s have a little blunt talk about race from a West County white guy&amp;rsquo;s point of view (which is alway helpful).
Faction A and Faction B Whenever race comes up, two large factions shut down. They shut down intellectually because &amp;lsquo;race&amp;rsquo; touches an irrational, emotional nerve.
Faction A views every issue as a race problem. They see rain at a picnic as racist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Would Call Out Maxine Waters?  Martin Baker Would</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/29/who-would-call-out-maxine-waters-martin-baker-would/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 03:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/29/who-would-call-out-maxine-waters-martin-baker-would/</guid>
      <description>Martin Baker, candidate for Missouri’s 1st Congressional District, lays it on the line, challenging Tea Party critics Maxine Waters and Frederica Wilson.
Read Martin’s challenge:
 Today, I am inviting both of these distinguished ladies to St Louis, Missouri to tell me and my Tea Party compatriots in person why we should go straight to Hell. Congresswoman Waters should know the way here, having been born and raised in our esteemed area and a graduate of Vashon High School, which is in the St Louis Public School District.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innocent Victims</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/20/innocent-victims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 04:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/20/innocent-victims/</guid>
      <description>When the NAACP’s Ben Jealous fired a reckless volley at the Tea Party, he missed his marked and struck an innocent woman.
One week ago tonight, the news cycle was alive with the excitement of a heavyweight fight. The NAACP’s Ben Jealous needed to raise money and restore a sagging membership. He decided to pick a fight with the Tea Party.
On Monday, the NAACP leaked a resolution to the Kansas City Star that stated:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tea Party Is Intolerant . . . of Racism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/18/the-tea-party-is-intolerant-of-racism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/18/the-tea-party-is-intolerant-of-racism/</guid>
      <description>Between a touch of the flu and the flurry of activity over this very issue, I missed the best, most direct breakdown of Ben Jealous&amp;rsquo;s misguided and hypocritical attack on the Tea Party. Read this column by Michael Graham on BostonHerald.com dated Thursday, July 15.
Money quote:
 When you’re looking for bigots at a Tea Party rally, they’re on the fringe. When you’re looking for them at the NAACP, they’re on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Took a Stand Against the NAACP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/16/why-we-took-a-stand-against-the-naacp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 00:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/16/why-we-took-a-stand-against-the-naacp/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it is personal.

Beginning with a simple blog post in February 2009, the St. Louis Tea Party Coalition has attracted over 40,000 people to dozens of events and online crusades. The vast majority of these folks represent America’s highest ideals in character and citizenship. We are educated, polite, and patriotic. We are stand-up people who fix our own problems and earn our own livings. We are not perfect, of course, but we understand that no one else can live our lives for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fighting Back Against NAACP Defamation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/13/fighting-back-against-naacp-defamation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 12:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/13/fighting-back-against-naacp-defamation/</guid>
      <description>The NAACP has decided that it’s worth time to call 20 million American patriots “racists” for advancing liberty and economic opportunity.
At midnight, the St. Louis Tea Party Coalition sent a resolution condemning the NAACP’s bigotry and hatred to its Washington bureau.
The Tea Party’s principles are simple and clear:
* Smaller federal government** Lower taxes** Fiscal responsibility** National defense** Federalism  Those are precisely the tools to lift all Americans out of poverty.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>