<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics Missouri on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-missouri/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics Missouri on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-missouri/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Shuts Down Another Small Business</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 01:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</guid>
      <description>200,000 That&amp;rsquo;s the number of** small businesses lost during the Obama Administration**.
If re-elected, Obama promises to accelerate the policies that destroyed American jobs, investments, and companies.
https://youtu.be/NlFHrLeeJIU
Voting isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. We need your help at 9966 Lin Ferry Drive, St. Louis, MO 63123.
Pick you day to work the phones and get out the vote:
 * Friday, November 2 Noon to 8 p.m. * Saturday, November 3 Noon to 5 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners Proves Government Can’t Get Anything Right</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/04/st-louis-board-of-police-commissioners-proves-government-cant-get-anything-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/04/st-louis-board-of-police-commissioners-proves-government-cant-get-anything-right/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives love cracking on government and its unintended consequences. How often does a government initiative give us backassward results?
Exhibit A: Obama hands Solyndra millions in tax dollars to promote green energy. Solyndra (and numerous other green energy grant recipients) goes bankrupt.
Another example is the St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners.
In 1861, Missouri’s legislature created a board of commissioners to oversee the St. Louis Police Department. Why? Because Missouri was a slave state, but St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Police Department Is Crumbling, But You Can Vote to Save It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/st-louis-police-crumbling-but-you-can-save-it/</guid>
      <description>You get the feeling that Rex Sinquefield holds a grudge against his home state, and he’s using some of his fortune to punish us.
Rex gave a quarter million dollars to Obama’s Lawyer, Chris Koster. But that wasn’t his first assault on us. Rex’s war against the St. Louis Police Department is older and far more bitter.
Rex wants to force the state to surrender the Board of Police Commissioners for St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Rock the Election Like Scott Walker and Richard Mourdock</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/08/how-to-rock-the-election-like-scott-walker-and-richard-mourdock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 20:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/08/how-to-rock-the-election-like-scott-walker-and-richard-mourdock/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] The Gadsden flag (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
We&amp;rsquo;re past Empty Chair Day. The conventions are over. Barack Obama still stands between us and liberty. And the Establishment&amp;rsquo;s more worried about its $$$ future than about America&amp;rsquo;s future.
What does that mean? It means _you and I _ will determine what happens in Election 2012 and beyond.
If you want to have a hand in America&amp;rsquo;s future, listen up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>