<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tucson tea party on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/tucson-tea-party/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tucson tea party on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 00:46:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/tucson-tea-party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tucson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/tucson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 00:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/tucson/</guid>
      <description>Almost pulled a muscle laughing in the ride from the Tucson airport to our hotel.
It’s only 5:30 here. Weird. That call that “time difference” for you lefties who read my blog. Has to do with the earth being round and all.
Been a whirlwind day so far. Met Trent and Jennifer Humphries, remarkable Tea Party leaders here in Tucson. Most gracious hosts you can imagine. Funny, dedicated, joyous.
After checking into hotel, I spoke to Mike Ferguson of Eagle 93.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billy left his home for Tucson Arizona</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/billy-left-his-home-for-tucson-arizona/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/billy-left-his-home-for-tucson-arizona/</guid>
      <description>I am so proud to be bringing the Spirit of St. Louis to the great people of Tucson, Arizona, this weekend.
Dana Loesch and Jim Hoft are among the speakers at Tucson’s Tea Party on April 30.
The Tea Party is on Saturday, April 30 at 9 am Pacific (11 am Central). And there’s much, much more than just the Tea Party going on. Check it all out here. If you have friends in the area, please ask them to come out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please Join Me in Tucson, Arizona</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/06/please-join-me-in-tucson-arizona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 00:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/06/please-join-me-in-tucson-arizona/</guid>
      <description>I am very pleased and honored to tell you this news: Trent Humphries and the good people of the Tucson Tea Party have asked me to speak at their Third Annual April Tea Party on April 30, 2011, at 11:00 am. The theme is Reduce Taxes, Spending, and Waste.
Of course, they’re not really inviting me to speak; they’re inviting the thousands of St. Louis area activists who have done so much to advance liberty and defend freedom over the past 25 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shout It Out: Renegade Arizona Sheriff Intimidating Citizens *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/05/shout-it-out-renegade-arizona-sheriff-intimidating-citizens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 00:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/05/shout-it-out-renegade-arizona-sheriff-intimidating-citizens/</guid>
      <description>The incompetent Sheriff Dupnik of Pima County Arizona has intimidated speakers in an attempt to shut down the Tucson Tea Party.
Now, Tucson’s asking for our help. Jennifer Humphries wrote to Gateway Pundit Jim Hoft. She asked Jim of his help defending the First Amendment rights of the people of Tucson. Those rights are under assault from an incompetent and irresponsible sheriff who has now turned to intimidation to silence dissent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Left Doubles Down on Threats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</guid>
      <description>What would you do?
Suppose you did something stupid. You blamed the wrong person, for instance, for a capital crime. Then supposed one of your comrades compounded your . . . error . . . by threatening to kill someone on national television?
If you’re an American leftist, you might double down by issuing even more death threats to even more people.
That’s what’ happening right now in America. Death threats are pouring into Trent Humphries, Tucson Tea Party organizer, Dana Loesch, Sarah Palin (who vows not to be silenced), Glenn Beck, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bill Maher’s Vitriol Responsible for Arrest?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</guid>
      <description>Last week, America’s sleaziest leftists—Bill Maher, Chris Matthews, Keith Olbermann, E. J. Dionne, Paul Krugman, others – have [executed a prepared propaganda war](https://hennessysview.com/crime/a-national-day-of-shame/) against anyone who disagrees with them. Their theorem is: vitriolic rhetoric inspires conservatives to act out in violence.
Unfortunately for the loony left, there was no evidence to support their theorem. The evidence they falsely pointed to—Jarod Lee Loughner’s deranged murder rampage in Tucson—was determined to be a lie only hours after the event.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>