<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marxism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/marxism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marxism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 04:09:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/marxism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Companies Should Adopt Conscious Capitalism Because It Pays</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/27/companies-adopt-conscious-capitalism-pays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 04:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/27/companies-adopt-conscious-capitalism-pays/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re going to hit me with the small sample size argument here, but that&amp;rsquo;s okay.
I firmly believe that the purpose of a company is to make life better, and if it does that well, it will make a profit. If, on the other hand, a company makes life worse, the market should let that company die.
Some companies try to improve life with insanely great technology products. Some make life better with fast, safe cars that are fun to drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas: Point of No Return</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/08/kansas-point-of-no-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/08/kansas-point-of-no-return/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday in Kansas, President Barack Obama revealed his contempt for liberty. He declared that human beings are incapable of running their own lives . . . but, somehow, other, superior human beings are capable of running their own and others’.
He said that free markets have always failed, everywhere . . . ignoring most of the last 240 years.
He all but declared himself a Marxist.
I am depressed that America let this dangerous man into our government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMSL: Communist Recruiting With Taxpayer Dollars</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/09/umsl-communist-recruiting-with-taxpayer-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 02:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/09/umsl-communist-recruiting-with-taxpayer-dollars/</guid>
      <description>The University of Missouri St. Louis uses tax dollars to provide a recruiting station for the Communist Party USA—an organization whose purpose is to shred the United States Constitution.
UMSL Student Philip Christofanelli heroically chronicles the remarkable Marxist indoctrination known as “Introduction to Labor Studies” on BigGovernment.com. I’ll give you a taste:
 Prof. Giljum then introduced Tony Pecinovsky, a local organizer for the Communist Party, who proceeded to speak to us for two hours about the beliefs of the Communist Party and the benefits of membership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Answer Chavez</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/how-to-answer-chavez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 23:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/how-to-answer-chavez/</guid>
      <description>Communist dictator Hugo Chavez has has stolen eleven oil rigs owned by the American company Helmerich and Payne. As Reuters points out, Chavez has now nationalized oil, telecommunications (including news), power, steel, and banking.
If you’re keeping score, Chavez leads Obama 5-3, as Obama so far has managed to seize only banking, automotive, and healthcare. But Obama has vowed a comeback.
Over the weekend, I had the pleasure of cutting and splitting some oak and hickory with a friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama To Control Banks Permanently</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/obama-to-control-banks-permanently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 18:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/obama-to-control-banks-permanently/</guid>
      <description>The Obama administration has no intention of relinquishing dictatorial control of the banks according to financial expert Stuart Varney.  The government wants to control the banks, just as it now controls GM and Chrysler, and will surely control the health industry in the not-too-distant future. Keeping them TARP-stuffed is the key to control. And for this intensely political president, mere influence is not enough. The White House wants to tell &amp;lsquo;em what to do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>