<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Governor on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/governor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Governor on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 10:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/governor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric Greitens’ Shocking Revelation Could Shatter People’s Faith</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/eric-greitens-shocking-revelation-could-shatter-peoples-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 10:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/14/eric-greitens-shocking-revelation-could-shatter-peoples-faith/</guid>
      <description>Were you shocked when you learned that Navy SEAL, author, humanitarian, and charity founder, Eric Greitens, was born and raised and voted Democrat?
I was.
Sure, I’d heard the rumors. The whispers spread by some Republican campaign operatives. But I’ve learned to trust those campaign operatives about as far as I fund the national debt.
Then, Senator John Lamping sent me a link to this Fox News story:
Former Navy SEAL: Why I am no longer a Democrat So, the rumors were true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Define Tom Schweich With One Word</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/18/define-tom-schweich-one-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 22:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/01/18/define-tom-schweich-one-word/</guid>
      <description>Work screwed up my plans.
Our annual St. Louis Tea Party / Heritage Action Christmas Party started at 6:00 in the evening on December 17. I knew Auditor Tom Schweich planned to attend, and I looked forward to seeing him.
About 3:00 the problems started. People scurrying to wrap up projects before the Christmas break led to errors, questions, and never-ending email threads.
I finally made it out of the office about 7:30 and arrived at Scarecrow in Chesterfield a little after 8:00.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin’s AG Race Makes 3rd Anniversary Tea Party Even More Important</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/27/ed-martins-ag-race-makes-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-even-more-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 01:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/27/ed-martins-ag-race-makes-3rd-anniversary-tea-party-even-more-important/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago, weeks ago, how many Missouri statewide offices did you expect to flip? Be honest.
Yes, there are great people running for Governor, Secretary of State, and Treasurer. And we already have a fine Lieutenant Governor Kinder running for re-election.
But numerous factors, like name recognition, experience, and Jay Nixon’s weird relationship with Republican House leadership, made a major upset unlikely. And no Republicans had stepped up to challenge Chris Koster for Attorney General.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>