<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Todd Akin on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/todd-akin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Todd Akin on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/todd-akin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why Turning People Off Is A Terrible Idea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a cause’s worst enemies are its best friends.

In 1995, 56 percent of American described themselves as “pro-choice.” At the time, Michael Kinsley on CNN’s Crossfire declared the debate over.
Then something strange happened. Americans started changing their minds. The pro-life movement whittled away at public opinion.
By May of this year, Gallup found “pro-choice” to be at an all-time low:
 The 41% of Americans who now identify themselves as &amp;ldquo;pro-choice&amp;rdquo; is down from 47% last July and is one percentage point below the previous record low in Gallup trends, recorded in May 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turns Out The Guy Dumping On The Middle Class Is Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/09/turns-out-the-guy-dumping-on-the-middle-class-is-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/09/turns-out-the-guy-dumping-on-the-middle-class-is-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, Joe Biden made the news by declaring that the middle class in America has been getting dumped on ever since he and Obama took their oaths of office. The statement marked the first time Biden got something right since that day. What Uncle Joe failed to mention was that he has been in charge of the White House’s Middle Class Task Force since January 30, 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Write Yourself Into the Great American Novel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/24/how-to-write-yourself-into-the-great-american-novel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/24/how-to-write-yourself-into-the-great-american-novel/</guid>
      <description>A couple years ago, a lot of folks believed that victory in 2010 would be a cakewalk. Led by Tea Party activists, the GOP picked up over 800 legislative seats, state and federal, in the 2010 off-year election. Rumors of the Republican Party&amp;rsquo;s death had been greatly exaggerated.
  
Or so it seemed.
Novels and action movies involve a hero&amp;rsquo;s quest. The main character hopes to accomplish something. Dorothy wants to return to Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Karl Rove School of Sanctimony</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/03/the-karl-rove-school-of-sanctimony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 23:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/03/the-karl-rove-school-of-sanctimony/</guid>
      <description>When I read about Todd Akin&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate comments to Charles Jaco, my first thought was uncharitable. &amp;ldquo;I could just kill him.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I could kill him,&amp;rdquo; is an idiom. Its cousins include &amp;ldquo;wring his neck&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;poke his eyes out.&amp;rdquo; Idioms hyperbolize our emotional reaction to an event.
I was angry because Todd Akin gave the left a great talking point in the infamous interview. I like Todd Akin. I voted for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abraham, Isaac, and Todd</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/24/abraham-isaac-and-todd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 13:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/24/abraham-isaac-and-todd/</guid>
      <description>The story Isaac is about tests of faith.
God commanded Abraham to sacrifice Isaac, his only son, born after Abraham and Sarah had given up hope of conceiving.
Once Isaac was bound and placed on the altar, God stayed Abraham&amp;rsquo;s hand. &amp;ldquo;Now I know you fear God.&amp;rdquo;
You know the rest.
It just struck me this morning, listening to the weather during Jamie Allman&amp;rsquo;s show, that Isaac now threatens the GOP convention, dangling above Tampa like Abraham&amp;rsquo;s dagger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 3:  Todd Akin Needs to Lead or Get Out of the Way</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-3-todd-akin-needs-to-lead-or-get-out-of-the-way/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo;] Todd Akin: member of the United States House of Representatives. (Photo credit: Wikipedia)[/caption]
Part 3 of 3 | Read Part 1 | Read Part 2
Before we get too far down the Akin rally road, let&amp;rsquo;s get some solid advice to Mr. Akin.
His principles, his spine, his grassroots do no good if Missouri turns blue. He cannot advance his causes from his house in Wildwood. Failure to take the Senate makes Obamacare permanent, at least in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: Here Is Todd Akin’s Real Crime</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-2-here-is-todd-akins-real-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-2-here-is-todd-akins-real-crime/</guid>
      <description>Part 2 of 3 | Read Part 1 | Read Part 3
What is Todd&amp;rsquo;s real crime?
He&amp;rsquo;s a damaged candidate, sure, but he is not a damaged man.
He was wrong, but** he erred on the side of life**.
It says something about a society and political mood where a man can be disqualified for loving life and God, but another man celebrated for enabling the slaughter of living children with surgical scissors through the base of their skulls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 1: Contingencies Every Conservatives Needs Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-1-contingencies-every-conservatives-needs-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/23/part-1-contingencies-every-conservatives-needs-right-now/</guid>
      <description>Part 1 of 3 | Read Part 2 | Read Part 3
I think it&amp;rsquo;s smart to have a plan in case Todd Akin drops. The GOP central committee is working on a plan. If you wait until after a vacancy occurs, your preferences will be meaningless.
That said, if you should decide to plot a contingency to influence the selection of a candidate to fill a vacancy that might occur, consider this: **the MOGOP central committee is not tea-party-ish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preserving the Republic Is Paramount in 2012</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/20/preserving-the-republic-is-paramount-in-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/20/preserving-the-republic-is-paramount-in-2012/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I blogged about loyalty to people and loyalty to principles. Both are important. Loyalty to people is an honorable principle.
Sometimes, the ideal is paramount. In 2012, we simply must take the US Senate. We must put Claire McCaskill out of office. And we must send a strong conservative to the US House of Representatives from Missouri’s 2nd Congressional district.
Missouri’s 2nd Congressional District has been well served by Todd Akin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Are the Bill in Congress That Need Your Attention</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/these-are-the-bill-in-congress-that-need-your-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/13/these-are-the-bill-in-congress-that-need-your-attention/</guid>
      <description>Even though Congress is winding down, there are dangerous bills on the desk. I used Heritage Action’s Popvox program to tell Congressman (and future Senator) Todd Akin I oppose the FARM bill that does less for farmers and more for wasteful government statism.

Here’s the whole slate of bills you should write to Congress about:
Oppose the Big-Spending Farm Bill: Email Your Representative Now Tell Blunt and McCaskill to Kill LOST—A Bill to Surrender US Sovereignty</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If We Don’t Flip Some Toss-Up States, Romney, Ryan, and the USA Are Screwed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</guid>
      <description>Choosing Paul Ryan as his running mate was a great Romney move. Looking ahead, Romney sees movement conservatives working hard right up to the election—even if he or his advisors continues to say stupid things. That was necessary.
SCROLL DOWN FOR TWO IMPORTANT EVENTS THIS WEEK
But it wasn’t enough to win the election and unseat America’s first anti-American president. To do that, we must find a way to win over the selfish middle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Akin Example</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/26/the-akin-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 00:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/26/the-akin-example/</guid>
      <description>Todd Akin need doesn’t to build tea party street cred. He thumps primary and general election opponents in biennial blowouts for Missouri’s Second District. Todd is also a legitimate, committed member of the US House Tea Party Caucus. Todd Akin is the last politician who needs to prove his tea party cred. We trust him.

Akin Lives the Message
So when Todd Akin dashed from Springfield to Jefferson City to address the &amp;ldquo;Restore Common Sense” rally on the south steps of the Missouri Capitol, he didn’t do it to “prove” anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Liberty Congressional Town Hall</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/ensuring-liberty-congressional-town-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 23:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/ensuring-liberty-congressional-town-hall/</guid>
      <description>Over at Ensuring Liberty, we held our first Congressional Virtual Town Hall on Tuesday, May 11. In case you missed it, Reps Michele Bachmann and Steve King discussed Senator Dodd’s proposed financial takeover bill with thousands of Americans.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y6AvG1HVcDE&amp;amp;color1;=0xb1b1b1&amp;amp;color2;=0xd0d0d0&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;feature;=player_embedded&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]
Segment 1 of May 11 Ensuring Liberty Town Hall
Ensuring Liberty plans to team up with Bachmann, King, and many other conservative House members throughout 2010 and beyond. We want to bring your voices to their ears—again, and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Todd Akin: Putting Al-Qaeda Ahead of the CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/05/rep-todd-akin-putting-al-qaeda-ahead-of-the-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 03:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/05/rep-todd-akin-putting-al-qaeda-ahead-of-the-cia/</guid>
      <description>Hey, one of our favorite members of Congress, and a true gentleman, Todd Akin (R-MO), has made the front page of BigGovernment.com.
The Obama Justice Department is quietly investigating the lawyers associated with the John Adams Project who may have violated a number of laws in place to protect our covert operatives and their families. But so far, with few exceptions, the media and their friends on Capitol Hill haven’t found this case nearly as interesting as Valerie Plame.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>