<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Todd Akin on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/todd-akin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Todd Akin on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/todd-akin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why Turning People Off Is A Terrible Idea</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/20/this-is-why-turning-people-off-is-a-terrible-idea/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes a cause’s worst enemies are its best friends.

In 1995, 56 percent of American described themselves as “pro-choice.” At the time, Michael Kinsley on CNN’s Crossfire declared the debate over.
Then something strange happened. Americans started changing their minds. The pro-life movement whittled away at public opinion.
By May of this year, Gallup found “pro-choice” to be at an all-time low:
 The 41% of Americans who now identify themselves as &amp;ldquo;pro-choice&amp;rdquo; is down from 47% last July and is one percentage point below the previous record low in Gallup trends, recorded in May 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turns Out The Guy Dumping On The Middle Class Is Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/09/turns-out-the-guy-dumping-on-the-middle-class-is-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/09/turns-out-the-guy-dumping-on-the-middle-class-is-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, Joe Biden made the news by declaring that the middle class in America has been getting dumped on ever since he and Obama took their oaths of office. The statement marked the first time Biden got something right since that day. What Uncle Joe failed to mention was that he has been in charge of the White House’s Middle Class Task Force since January 30, 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Commercial by Ed Martin for Missouri Attorney General</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/01/excellent-commercial-by-ed-martin-for-missouri-attorney-general/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s new TV commercial is excellent for many fundamental marketing reasons. Ed’s energy, commitment, and love of people shines through.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzJS2bqIlyY]
Still, the commercial is a waste of time and money unless people see it.
Here’s how you can help: buy air time. If you want an Attorney General who will protect Missouri’s sovereignty and treasury, you can simply buy air time for this ad.
And there’s more you can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Write Yourself Into the Great American Novel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/24/how-to-write-yourself-into-the-great-american-novel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/24/how-to-write-yourself-into-the-great-american-novel/</guid>
      <description>A couple years ago, a lot of folks believed that victory in 2010 would be a cakewalk. Led by Tea Party activists, the GOP picked up over 800 legislative seats, state and federal, in the 2010 off-year election. Rumors of the Republican Party&amp;rsquo;s death had been greatly exaggerated.
  
Or so it seemed.
Novels and action movies involve a hero&amp;rsquo;s quest. The main character hopes to accomplish something. Dorothy wants to return to Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>