<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Obesity on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/obesity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Obesity on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 13:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/obesity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How &#34;Healthy&#34; Diets Kill You and Your Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/08/how-healthy-diets-kill-you-and-your-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 13:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/08/how-healthy-diets-kill-you-and-your-family/</guid>
      <description>Do you follow the recommended diets? Low fat. High carbohydrate? Eat lots of fruit?
If so, you&amp;rsquo;re probably overweight. And your blood tests are probably a mess. Maybe your doctor recommends expensive prescriptions to lower your cholesterol.
A new study finds the problem is not your fault. Your doctor, poorly educated in nutrition, and government recommendations, prompted by industry lobbyists, are designed to keep you fat and sick. And it&amp;rsquo;s not just US government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Diet Makes You Fat and Kills You</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/08/government-diet-makes-you-fat-and-kills-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/08/government-diet-makes-you-fat-and-kills-you/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re sick and fat, it might not be your fault. You listen to your doctor. You follow government diet guidelines. You eat more fresh fruit and vegetables. You cut down on animal fat. You eat more grains.
And you just get sicker and fatter.
You&amp;rsquo;re told it&amp;rsquo;s your fault. But it&amp;rsquo;s probably not.
You might be a good mom or dad who wants your kids to learn healthy eating habits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are You Letting Your Doctor Kill You?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/05/why-are-you-letting-your-doctor-kill-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 20:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/05/why-are-you-letting-your-doctor-kill-you/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re overweight, have high cholesterol, diabetes, Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s, heart disease, or cancer, it&amp;rsquo;s probably not your fault. You&amp;rsquo;ve been told to eat poison your whole life, by people who are supposed to know better. Here&amp;rsquo;s some truth to set you free.
Actually, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why. But it&amp;rsquo;s happening to you and millions of other people. Doctors are killing their patients. And they&amp;rsquo;re getting a lot of help from the government and big agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Obama&#39;s Dictates Force Eureka High PTO To Beg</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/04/michelle-obamas-dictates-force-eureka-high-pto-beg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 21:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/04/michelle-obamas-dictates-force-eureka-high-pto-beg/</guid>
      <description>When did first ladies become dictators?
Seriously. The president&amp;rsquo;s family has no more authority than anyone else. The reason people show contempt for activist spouses of presidents is the same reason history hates Marie Antoinette.
I know, the all-Democrat Congress passed the school nutrition law in 2010, but Michelle Obama wrote it.
Michelle Obama has dictated that no tasty foods may enter any school property. That ban includes school bake sales and snack shops which has PTOs scrambling to replace lost income.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>