<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dana loesch on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/dana-loesch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dana loesch on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 01:50:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/dana-loesch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Um, What’s Going On?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/21/um-whats-going-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 01:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/07/21/um-whats-going-on/</guid>
      <description>Look, folks, let’s remember who’s on whose side.
Dana Loesch is a champion of liberty, the conservative grassroots, and everything else we stand for. And she’s a great friend to me, to the Tea Party, and, in a sense, to all of us. She’s elevated this movement locally and nationally like no one else. You wouldn’t be reading this post if not for her.
I am so sorry that my piece from last night raised tempers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dana Bouncing Back</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/27/dana-bouncing-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 01:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/27/dana-bouncing-back/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch has been plagued with a perstistent cold. Yesterday, her stairs leapt up and kicked her in the . . .
Turns out to be a fractured coccyx (aka, tailbone).
We feel terrible that Dana had this tale to share with the world, but we congratulate ourselves for limiting the number of cheap jokes.
Certainly, we pray for minimal pain and minimal recovery time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Left Doubles Down on Threats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</guid>
      <description>What would you do?
Suppose you did something stupid. You blamed the wrong person, for instance, for a capital crime. Then supposed one of your comrades compounded your . . . error . . . by threatening to kill someone on national television?
If you’re an American leftist, you might double down by issuing even more death threats to even more people.
That’s what’ happening right now in America. Death threats are pouring into Trent Humphries, Tucson Tea Party organizer, Dana Loesch, Sarah Palin (who vows not to be silenced), Glenn Beck, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes a Morris is Just a Morris</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/sometimes-a-morris-is-just-a-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 05:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/sometimes-a-morris-is-just-a-morris/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch invited Dick Morris onto her radio show today. Dana expected to discuss START with Mr. Morris. But Dick has a mind of his own.
Morris decided, about a minute and a half into a five-minute segment, that he wanted to talk about the 2012 US Senate race in Missouri instead. Specifically, he wanted spend the segment campaigning for Sarah Steelman for the the Republican nomination.
Decide for yourself: here’s the link to Dana’s show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Journalism’s Big News</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/11/big-journalisms-big-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/11/big-journalisms-big-news/</guid>
      <description>It seems impossible that nearly nineteen months have passed since I met Dana Loesch for the first time.
 It was on the sidewalk on Leonor K. Sullivan Blvd, 27 February 2010. Snow flurries drifted and bounced like little kids playing around at a wedding reception. Two-hundred or so people had already arrived, and Dana brought the cutest little megaphone you’ve ever seen. With that megaphone, we announced the first St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>