<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>911 Hair Salon on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/911-hair-salon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 911 Hair Salon on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 23:37:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/911-hair-salon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day of Hope, Prayer, and Clean-up in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/a-day-of-hope-prayer-and-clean-up-in-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 23:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/a-day-of-hope-prayer-and-clean-up-in-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Dellena Jones’s 911 Hair Salon was attacked at about 11:15 PM by a small band of young men. The break-in and robbery occurred close to the time of the first shooting. The hair salon is less than 100 yards from the scene of the shooting.
But that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop volunteers from St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and friends from helping.
[caption width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;quot;attachment_16631&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo;]Volunteers pose for a picture after helping clean and repair 911 Hair Salon in Ferguson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a Beautiful Spring Day, And Dellena Struggles to Stay In Business</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/18/its-a-beautiful-spring-day-and-dellena-struggles-to-stay-in-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 17:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/18/its-a-beautiful-spring-day-and-dellena-struggles-to-stay-in-business/</guid>
      <description>We metDellena Jones during our first Ferguson BUYcott in August. Since then, St. Louis Tea Partier, Dottie Bailey, has made it her mission to help Dellena&amp;rsquo;s business survive and flourish.
https://youtu.be/r-ye3nSe2Vk
Dellena&amp;rsquo;s business has fallen 60 percent since the first riots. She&amp;rsquo;s repaired the damage to her salon, but business is slow.
Despite all her challenges, Dellena still found the time and energy to host Center for Self-Governance training in her shop on a Saturday, foregoing that day&amp;rsquo;s revenue to learn about freedom and responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>