<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gabrielle Giffords on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/gabrielle-giffords/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gabrielle Giffords on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 17:30:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/gabrielle-giffords/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s About Love</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/its-about-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/30/its-about-love/</guid>
      <description>Trent and Jennifer Humphries—hated by all the right people—just brought to tears to 5,200 eyes.
After Trent told us that the secret to our success is Christ’s love, his wife, Jennifer, described the depths to which evil journalists stooped in the moments following the Giffords shooting.
As the Humphries and their small children returned home from the grocery store, they learned that their next door neighbor—and a beloved friend—was killed in the tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Orwell Write This Weekend?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/did-orwell-write-this-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/did-orwell-write-this-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Democrats—from Jane Fonda to Senator Bob Brady of Pennsylvania—are pushing to ban words, phrases, and images they don’t like, as P/Od Patriot points out.
Yes, we are living in very dangerous times. And the danger comes almost exclusively from the left.
* Democrat [McCaskill calls for Americans to take up arms](https://gatewaypundit.rightnetwork.com/2010/12/claire-mccaskill-promotes-violence-if-dems-dont-get-their-historic-tax-hikes-it-really-is-time-for-americans-to-take-up-pitchforks-video/) if Democrat tax increase fails. (It did. And Gabrielle Giffords helped it fail.)** Democrat [Joe Biden threatened to strangle Republicans](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A National Day of Shame</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/a-national-day-of-shame/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/a-national-day-of-shame/</guid>
      <description>It’s bad enough that five people died, including a wonderful nine-year-old girl.
It’s bad enough that a dozen or more people were shot.
It’s bad enough that a deranged man attacked our American system.
But America’s liberal elite turned the tragedy into a national day of shame. They accomplished this by callously and capriciously blaming innocent political opponents for the violence. When confronted with facts to the contrary, liberals, including Paul Krugman, CBS News, the New York Times, CNN, MSNBC, Jane Fonda, Sheriff Dupnick of Pima County Arizona, and others, continued to lie, slander, and libel the tea party, Rush Limbaugh, Sarah Palin, Glenn Beck, and conservatives in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cowardly, Leftist Punks Go Silent</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/cowardly-leftist-punks-go-silent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 22:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/cowardly-leftist-punks-go-silent/</guid>
      <description>The tragedy in Tucson exposed America’s leading leftists for what they are.
Andrew Breitbart points out on Twitter that his cowardly leftist accusors, including Markos Moulitsas and Eric Boehlert, quieted down on their libelous attacks on Breitbart, Palin, Bush, and Tea Party.
These leftist cowards shut up only after it became undeniably clear that the evil bastard who shot Rep. Gabrielle Giffords and 11 others is not a tea partier, but a deranged socialist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Giffords Shooter: Jared Loughner Leaves Video *UPDATES*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/alleged-giffords-shooter-jared-loughner-leaves-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 21:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/alleged-giffords-shooter-jared-loughner-leaves-video/</guid>
      <description>Update: Gateway Pundit has much more on the alleged shooter.
These appear to be the paranoid ramblings of the man in custody for shooting Rep. Gabrielle Giffords and 11 others, including a federal judge, in Tucson, AZ. Lots of hard left references in his favorite books, including Mein Kampf and The Communist Manifesto. Politico’s Ben Smith calls Laughner’s writings “socialist.”
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nHoaZaLbqB4&amp;amp;hl;=en&amp;amp;hd;=1]
Another Video by alleged shooter in Arizona made 3 weeks before shooting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Go With Hope—reports that Gabrielle Giffords is still alive, needs our prayers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/gabrielle-giffords-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 19:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/gabrielle-giffords-rip/</guid>
      <description>Like all decent people, I am disgusted to hear the sad news out of Tucson, AZ: Rep. Gabrielle Giffords (D-AZ) was shot and killed along with four others today. Twelve were shot altogether. The murderer was apprehended by heroic bystanders and is in custody.
Not sure of the young murderer’s motives. I’m sure they weren’t worth killing or dying for. Except to him.
Please prayer for the souls of the faithful departed, the well-being of their families, the quick recovery of the wounded, and the delivery of justice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>