<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jobs on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jobs on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 14:25:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jobs Trump Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/jobs-trump-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 14:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/26/jobs-trump-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>I feel drunk but I&amp;rsquo;m sober, I&amp;rsquo;m young and I&amp;rsquo;m underpaid I&amp;rsquo;m tired but I&amp;rsquo;m working, yeah I care but I&amp;rsquo;m restless, I&amp;rsquo;m here but I&amp;rsquo;m really gone I&amp;rsquo;m wrong and I&amp;rsquo;m sorry baby
 —Alanis Morissette, One Hand In My Pocket
If your biggest problem involves choosing between multiple appealing jobs, everything else will seem less important. Because picking the right job is a really big deal.
For the past decade, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably worried about finding or keeping any job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump, The Jobs President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/08/trump-the-jobs-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 13:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/08/trump-the-jobs-president/</guid>
      <description>You can actually FEEL America getting GREAT again!
ADP payroll report shows President Trump made a big down payment on his promise to be the **greatest jobs president ever. **
The economy added nearly 300,000 new jobs last month. Economists expected a rise of 190,000. It was the biggest jump in jobs in 6 years.
The jobs were the good kind of jobs Trump talks about: manufacturing, mining. Jobs with grit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America&#39;s Business is Jobs, Not College</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/14/americas-business-is-jobs-not-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/14/americas-business-is-jobs-not-college/</guid>
      <description>Many of us are guilty. I am, too. You, probably.
In high school (and after) we mocked the kids who took shop. The &amp;ldquo;greasers&amp;rdquo; who got credit for wrenching on cars or welding or making cabinets. It was the 1980s and shop, along with home economics, became an elective in most schools.
Until the 80s, some practical life skill class was a requirement at most American public and parochial high schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Smart Phones Are More Popular Than the Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/why-smart-phones-are-more-popular-than-the-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2015 00:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/12/why-smart-phones-are-more-popular-than-the-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>Does it bother you that people would give up essential freedoms before they’d give up their iPhone?
 While 26 percent of Americans report that they can’t live without their smartphone, only 20 percent of Americans say they can’t live without sex, according to this infographic compiled by FinancesOnline.com, a personal finance website.
 Seriously.
It should bother you. [olympus_highlight color=&#39;yellow]Without essential freedoms, smart phones can be taken away or banned[/olympus_highlight].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Has a Job To Do</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</guid>
      <description>We believe that meaningful work dignifies and enriches human lives.
[olympus_highlight color=&amp;quot;yellow&amp;rdquo;]Every person who wants to work should find a choice of occupations to pursue. And every occupation improves the life of the person doing the work, the people the work is done for, and the family and community in which the worker lives.[/olympus_highlight]
The more workers engaged in meaningful work, the better our country becomes.
The opposite of work is not idleness but dependency, and dependency degrades human lives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>