<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reagan on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/reagan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reagan on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 02:38:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/reagan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reagan Gives Trump&#39;s Budget TWO THUMBS UP!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/16/reagan-gives-trumps-budget-two-thumbs-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 02:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/16/reagan-gives-trumps-budget-two-thumbs-up/</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump delivered his budget and a message for Congress.
Since I&amp;rsquo;m lazy, I&amp;rsquo;ll quote Time magazine.
First, the President&amp;rsquo;s message to Congress:
 &amp;ldquo;I urge the members of Congress to remember that last November the American people&amp;rsquo;s message was loud and clear. The mandate for change, expressed by the American people, was not my mandate; it was our mandate.&amp;rdquo;
 Then, the analysis:
 The President&amp;rsquo;s meaning was unmistakable: the public wants deep cuts in both spending and taxes, and any legislator who tries to keep the ax from falling risks putting his own neck under an ax at the polls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Trump</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/17/the-joy-of-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 18:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/17/the-joy-of-trump/</guid>
      <description>What bothers you most when you&amp;rsquo;re in a bad mood?
You can imagine what it&amp;rsquo;s like be in a bad mood, can&amp;rsquo;t you? People go through periods of deep funk when nothing seems bright or cheerful, don&amp;rsquo;t they?
And when you&amp;rsquo;re in those moods, what&amp;rsquo;s the worst thing? That&amp;rsquo;s right, it&amp;rsquo;s being around a bunch of happy people having fun.
And that&amp;rsquo;s exactly how the left feels when they see Trump at a press conference: miserable amid the fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Second-Born Twin Can Be Older Than the First</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/12/how-the-second-born-twin-can-be-older-than-the-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 17:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/12/how-the-second-born-twin-can-be-older-than-the-first/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever noticed that twins have a pecking order? Even identical twins born minutes apart show a subtle seniority complex. Usually the first-born twin leads the second-born.
Makes you wonder how these Peterson twins will relate to each other, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Because of the time change at the end of daylight saving time, the second-born twin is officially older than the first. That&amp;rsquo;ll be interesting to watch. And if you find yourself pondering the oddness of those twins&amp;rsquo; birth order, you can easily find yourself pondering America&amp;rsquo;s little sister relationship to the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Gets the Credit Matters Most</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/19/who-gets-the-credit-is-most-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 22:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/19/who-gets-the-credit-is-most-important/</guid>
      <description>Some people on the right say they won&amp;rsquo;t vote for Trump. Those people list various reasons, mostly about his demeanor and things he&amp;rsquo;s said in the past. They think who gets the credit is more important than what gets done. We all know people like that, don&amp;rsquo;t we?
Most of those NeverTrumpers were okay with Trump&amp;rsquo;s policies. They all love his Supreme Court list. Most of them liked Ted Cruz&amp;rsquo;s ideas, and Cruz&amp;rsquo;s weren&amp;rsquo;t far from Trump&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Reagan Almost Blew It in 1980</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/23/how-reagan-almost-blew-it-in-1980/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/23/how-reagan-almost-blew-it-in-1980/</guid>
      <description>If you enjoy this post, you have to thank your fellow reader, Tony, for reading the whole TIME article from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post. He pointed out more similarities between 1980 and 2016. Especially Reagan&amp;rsquo;s gaffes and Democrats&amp;rsquo; complacency.
First, the gaffes.
You hear about Trump stepping on his own applause lines. He announced Steve Bannon and Kellyanne Conway the day after the best speech of his life (until then). He wondered aloud (via Twitter) what Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 looks like a repeat of 1980</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/22/2016-repeat-1980/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 17:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/22/2016-repeat-1980/</guid>
      <description>You probably remember that in September 1980 voters couldn’t wait to cast a vote for Reagan.
If you remember it like that, you remember wrong. At least a little wrong.
TIME magazine examined voter sentiment in its September 15, 1980, issue. Voters that year sounded a lot like voters this year. Here’s how TIME’s Ed Magnuson summarized the voters of 1980:
 Disenchanted, but not apathetic. Caring about issues, although much more concerned about character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Were Once the Party of Ideas and Optimism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/13/we-were-once-the-party-of-ideas-and-optimism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 04:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/13/we-were-once-the-party-of-ideas-and-optimism/</guid>
      <description>On my desk is a book titled &amp;ldquo;Grinning With the Gipper.&amp;rdquo;
It&amp;rsquo;s 117 pages of Ronald Reagan&amp;rsquo;s humor.Think of that. A US president who could fill a book with jokes.
My cursory review shows that about 60 percent of the jokes are on Reagan himself. And another 20 percent are on Republicans.
Ronald Reagan knew that life is too short and too precious to waste it on anger and pride. Better to spend your days getting laughs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Be President When Russia Goes Berserk Starring Ronald Reagan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 03:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/17/president-russia-goes-berserk-starring-ronald-reagan/</guid>
      <description>Since the scrawny punk from Chicago still hasn&amp;rsquo;t figured it out, this President 101 lesson delivered without further comment:
https://youtu.be/9VA4W1wDMAk?t=18s
Previously on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View:
We Interrupt This World War For a Democratic Fundraiser</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s My Electoral Map Prediction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I’m feeling a wave toward Romney.

My gut tells me this year is a lot like 1980.
1980 Was A Dead Heat
The final Gallup poll that year had a dead heat. Time Magazine’s November 3, 1980, called the race a dead heat. So did Newsweek.
The press was hoping John B. Anderson, a former Republican Congressman running for president as an independent, would siphon votes from Reagan. He did siphon votes from Reagan, but not nearly enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Old Reagan Soviet Jokes Are on US</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/18/the-old-reagan-soviet-jokes-are-on-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/18/the-old-reagan-soviet-jokes-are-on-us/</guid>
      <description>Ronald Reagan loved to tell jokes about the Soviet Union.If Obama’s re-elected, though, these same jokes could be turned on the United States.

Some of them already can be.
 It&amp;rsquo;s hard to get an automobile in the United States. They are owned mainly by elite bureaucrats. It takes an average of 10 years to get a car. 1 out of 7 families owned automobiles. You have to go through a major process and put the money out in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Magical Moment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/17/a-magical-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 02:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/17/a-magical-moment/</guid>
      <description>On November 5, 1980, ABC News Nightline was devoted to the aftermath of the election. Ronald Reagan won 51-41 over incumbent Jimmy Carter. Republicans took the Senate and picked up 30+ seats in the house.
The YouTube clip below shows us only the beginning of the program. But it’s a great reminder of what lies ahead for movement conservatives. Well, what lies ahead IF we continue to focus on moving the conversation toward first principles and away from the class warfare and Balkanization that Democrats love so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A lovely trip down memory lane</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/08/a-lovely-trip-down-memory-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 03:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/08/a-lovely-trip-down-memory-lane/</guid>
      <description>1980 [youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PsDe-8cOSYY&amp;amp;hl;=en]
Reagan didn’t transform America. You did. All Reagan supplied was the blueprint, the story that brought economics and history to life.
You will do it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Horrors of Inflation *Update*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/5-horrors-of-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/5-horrors-of-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Scroll for Updates
Ronald Reagan and Jack Kemp wanted to index everything, especially Treasury notes and taxes. By &amp;ldquo;indexing,&amp;rdquo; we mean tying rates (interest and tax) to the inflation rate. Calls for indexing subsided after Reagan and Volcker did what Ford and Carter could not: whip inflation now.
With a $2 trillion deficit this year and multi-trillion deficits projected as far as the eye can see, inflation will return to ravage the American consumer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>