<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics 2010 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-2010/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics 2010 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 03:11:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/politics-2010/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drowning Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/06/drowning-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 03:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/06/drowning-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Someday I’ll write more – much more – on this. But it’s important to remember what’s at stake in America, in the world, this election: beauty.
Totalitarian regimes despise beauty. They bury it in palaces where the rulers roam, their cancerous eyes raking over someone’s masterpiece the way raw sewage pollutes a clear stream after a pipe’s failure.
Regimes, in their attempts to hoard beauty, bury it.
In free America (remember it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Freedom Pledge</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/10/healthcare-freedom-pledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 00:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/10/healthcare-freedom-pledge/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s launched the HealthcareFreedomPledge.com site.

Here you can find candidates who committed to protecting your right to choose your own healthcare options.
Great idea. The site contains short statements from candidates for both state and federal office who pledge to defend our basic rights.
Ask candidates in your area to sign the pledge today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On to November</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/on-to-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/on-to-november/</guid>
      <description>The primaries are over.
I honestly believe that in the St. Louis area, the rightward-most, viable candidate won each of the key votes. The people of Missouri are in a position to make historical shifts in our Washington representation. And those shifts are just the first step and restoring America’s First Principles.

View Full Album
Roy Blunt is a conservative. He will be a big step up for conservatism in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>