<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>schools on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/schools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in schools on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/schools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Don&#39;t Need More Technology--They Need Less</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</guid>
      <description>I was on my high school&amp;rsquo;s board of education for a year. It was quite an honor, honestly, but I screwed it up.
At the time, I was a software architect. They put me on the board as the technology guy. I was supposed to make the case for more funding for smart boards and other tech stuff.
But I said kids really don&amp;rsquo;t need more technology in school. Technology, I said, was like sex education: they&amp;rsquo;ll get more than they can handle on the streets or watching TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Schools Replace Great Fiction With Government propaganda</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</guid>
      <description>[Originally posted on Redstate.com]
English was my favorite subject in school, so much so that I can still recite from memory large passages of the books we read, like A Separate Peace:
 I went back to Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there 15 years before.
 And who doesn’t know this by heart:
 If you really want to hear about it, the first thing you’ll probably want to know is where I was born and what my lousy childhood was like and how my parents were occupied and all before they had me and all that David Copperfield kind of crap, but I don’t feel like going into it, if you want to know the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Has the Fear?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</guid>
      <description>For 100 years in America, government, business, and the education establishment built schools and laws about education. The purpose of these government schools and education laws was to produce compliant, unimaginative, order-taking automatons.
Don’t believe me? Here’s Woodrow Wilson, educator and president, speaking on the American plan for education:
 We want one class of persons to have a liberal education, and we want another class of persons, a very much larger class of necessity in every society, to forgo the privilege of a liberal education and fit themselves to perform specific difficult manual tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>