<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weather on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/weather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weather on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:43:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>So Much For an Ice-Free Arctic</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/05/so-much-for-an-ice-free-arctic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/05/so-much-for-an-ice-free-arctic/</guid>
      <description>DailyTech - Sea Ice Ends Year at Same Level as 1979
 Thanks to a rapid rebound in recent months, global sea ice levels now equal those seen 29 years ago, when the year 1979 also drew to a close.
 Let&amp;rsquo;s give credit where it&amp;rsquo;s due: Al Gore.
When Al Gore speaks, the opposite happens. Where Al Gore goes,snow is sure to follow. So when Al Gorefrightened a bunch of German kids by telling them that the North Pole would be gone in 5 years, that Santa Claus would die along with his reindeer, and that Polar Bears would either become extinct or catch the last few ice floes south to Europe where they&amp;rsquo;d &amp;ldquo;eat little kiddies like you,&amp;rdquo; you just knew that the Arctic would grow ice faster than Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s head grows hair plugs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Superior Freezing Over</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/27/lake-superior-freezing-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 15:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/27/lake-superior-freezing-over/</guid>
      <description>Even as CO2 levels rise, western Lake Superior is freezing over for the first time years.
 The western tip of Lake Superior has frozen over in December for the first time in recent memory, and that could mean a long season of ice angling that hasn’t been seen in years.
 “We were just talking that it’s been something like 17 years since we had a good, long ice fishing season at this corner of Lake Superior,’’ said Russ Francisco, owner of Marine General sporting goods store in Duluth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Video of 2008</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/25/best-video-of-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 04:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/25/best-video-of-2008/</guid>
      <description>OMG, this is golden: [youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JmPSUMBrJoI&amp;amp;w;=425&amp;amp;h;=344]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC:  Somehow Winter Survived Global Warming</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/21/msnbc-somehow-winter-survived-global-warming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 16:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/21/msnbc-somehow-winter-survived-global-warming/</guid>
      <description>Winter madness
MSNBC.com lea  ds off this Sunday with a photo montage of serious winter weather from Pacific to Maine. To the left, all snow, all winter weather is &amp;ldquo;freak.&amp;quot; To those of us with memories longer than our . . . privates . . . and a sense of history that exceeds our senses of fashion, winters are beginning to look a like winters past. The temperature was 7 when I got up this morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USAToday Admits It&#39;s Cold</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/16/usatoday-admits-its-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 04:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/16/usatoday-admits-its-cold/</guid>
      <description>Even liberals are noticing that [global warming has been reversed](Can you explain the enormous hole in Earth&amp;rsquo;s magnetic field that allowed solar winds to flood our personal space on June 3, 2007? ).
  No doubt Gore and The One will take credit.
Technorati Tags: AGW</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Historic Winter Storm</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/13/historic-winter-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 20:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/13/historic-winter-storm/</guid>
      <description>The massive storm brewing out west will plunge Los Angeles into the 30s, threatening all-time record lows for that city. Seattle is looking at highs in the mid-20s for the week ahead. That&amp;rsquo;s cold. Amazingly, the Ottawa Weather Center predicted this blast last week (here and here).
Meanwhile, to the east and north or Southern California, blizzards will extend from New Mexico to Minneapolis. The cold and snow is forecast to continue for the next 48-72 hours, striking St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/01/congratulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 03:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/01/congratulations/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll dispense with hyperbole and sarcasm.
I want to congratulate and thank the people who are making Gustav a better experience than Katrina.
The People of the Gulf Coast
You rebuilt, prayed, and left your homes, business, and schools in God&amp;rsquo;s able hands. You were rewarded, or will be, for, not only your wisdom in retreating from nature, but your perseverance and faith. You deserve our help, our thanks, and our support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN:  Levee Breech, Rapid Flooding in Lower 9th Ward **Update**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/01/cnn-levee-breech-rapid-flooding-in-lower-9th-ward/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 16:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/01/cnn-levee-breech-rapid-flooding-in-lower-9th-ward/</guid>
      <description>CNN (TV, not .com) just reported that the Industrial Levee in the Lower 9th Ward of New Orleans has ruptured under the strain of water and wind, flooding homes and streets throughout the same area that was devastated by Katrina.
The Army Corps of Engineers&amp;rsquo; latest release said that levees were overtopped, relieving some pressure, but all levees were holding. It&amp;rsquo;s possible that the CNN&amp;rsquo;s reporters doesn&amp;rsquo;t know the definition of a breech.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>