<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>president on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/president/</link>
    <description>Recent content in president on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 12:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/president/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life As You’ve Known It Is About To Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 03:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/02/life-as-youve-known-it-is-about-to-change/</guid>
      <description>You have a choice. You can drive that change, or you can be swallowed by it.
In a free society, people have liberty to do anything except a few prohibited things.
In a totalitarian society, people have liberty to do nothing except a few permitted things.
In a free society, the people have a black list of things they must not do, and government has a white of a few things it may do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Shuts Down Another Small Business</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 01:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/01/obama-shuts-down-another-small-business/</guid>
      <description>200,000 That&amp;rsquo;s the number of** small businesses lost during the Obama Administration**.
If re-elected, Obama promises to accelerate the policies that destroyed American jobs, investments, and companies.
https://youtu.be/NlFHrLeeJIU
Voting isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. We need your help at 9966 Lin Ferry Drive, St. Louis, MO 63123.
Pick you day to work the phones and get out the vote:
 * Friday, November 2 Noon to 8 p.m. * Saturday, November 3 Noon to 5 p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now We Know Why Mitt Romney Has Been Wildly Successful In Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 00:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/07/now-we-know-why-mitt-romney-has-been-wildly-successful-in-life/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama’s performance was not nearly as bad as Romney’s performance was good.

Not good—terrific.
I’m not talking about his politics and policies; I’m talking Romney’s remarkable presence. Here are the four principles of presence that Romney knocked out of the park.
Command of the Facts When it came to facts—and to how those facts matter to the listeners—Mitt Romney seemed more prepared for the office of President than the President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Barack Obama is Right?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/19/which-barack-obama-is-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/19/which-barack-obama-is-right/</guid>
      <description>A genius is someone who can hold contrary concepts simultaneously in mind.
What, then, do we call a person who simultaneously argues two contrary concepts?

How ‘bout “demagogue?”
A few weeks ago, Barack Obama told America’s business owners that they are not responsible for their success. “Someone else built that.”
Today, the same Obama told Mitt Romney that there not many people who consider themselves victims.
Does Mr. Obama believe that people in dire straights are not victims of circumstances?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can You Trust Barack Obama for 4 More Years?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/17/can-you-trust-barack-obama-for-4-more-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/09/17/can-you-trust-barack-obama-for-4-more-years/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama came to office promising to heal the planet (I didn’t know it was sick), lower the waters, and end war as we knew it “whilst waking on water squirting wine out his ass,” to borrow William S. Burroughs’s anti-Christian blasphemy in Naked Lunch. (Funny. I don’t recall reading about Christians blowing up embassies over that book’s publication.)

Four years later, The One might want to let the waters rise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If the election were held today, there’d be a lot of crying and gnashing of teeth</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/17/gnashing-of-teeth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/17/gnashing-of-teeth/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a screen grab from RealClearPolitics.com’s presidential tracking poll:

RCP aggregates dozens of polls to produce its RCP average. The method has been remarkably accurate, especially at the state level.
It’s time to focus on preventing the unmitigated disaster of a second Obama term.
In 112 days, Americans will vote on whether or not to continue our experiment in self-government. If the election were held today, that experiment would be aborted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitt Romney Shut Down a Company Over a Young Woman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/24/mitt-romney-shut-down-a-company-over-a-young-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/24/mitt-romney-shut-down-a-company-over-a-young-woman/</guid>
      <description>There are many stories about Mitt Romney’s evil-doings when he ran Bain Capital, a $1 billion company famous for buying troubled companies and making money off them.

Some of the stories involve Bain laying off workers to make companies profitable, then selling them off.
Some of the stories involve Bain and Romney chopping companies to bits and selling off the parts.
This story is about Romney shutting down a thriving business over a woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Election’s Over, and America Gave Obama His Eviction Notice. Here’s What Went Down.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/the-elections-over-and-america-gave-obama-his-eviction-notice-heres-what-went-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/18/the-elections-over-and-america-gave-obama-his-eviction-notice-heres-what-went-down/</guid>
      <description>The look on George “Stephie” Stephanopoulos’s face was priceless. He had to say it.

“ABC News now projects that President Obama will go down to defeat.”
He couldn’t bring himself to say, “Romney won” or “Republicans won.” He just couldn’t.
The network analysis was a political cliché run amok. My favorite came from James Carville who told CNN viewers that the election result “proves that crackers and racists vote.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Fit?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/23/whos-fit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 05:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/23/whos-fit/</guid>
      <description>Take a look at Drudge.
I’ll wait. The day doesn’t really matter. It’s always full of stuff that makes you think rivets are flying out of the planet like a jalopy in a cartoon.
** Two girls beat another girl into convulsions over the course of eight minutes while cowardly young men quiver in fear. (But an old lady steps in and protects the victim.) ** Syrian security opens fire on demonstrators killing 90.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Blogging Barry&#39;s Crappy Reagan Imitation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/24/live-blogging-barrys-crappy-reagan-imitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 02:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/24/live-blogging-barrys-crappy-reagan-imitation/</guid>
      <description>The future is ours. Your disgust with the borrowing and spending, your noble desire to restore the republic the founders wrought, those are the real protests. The tea party is in our hearts and souls&amp;ndash;the events are just the physical manifestations. But now, the President:
Ninety percent of live blog posts suck. So I did my blog readers a big favor: I tested my quips on Twitter. Here I present my instant reactions that were good enough to get retweeted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>