<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Living on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/living/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Living on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 07:42:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/living/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations Representative Dottie Bailey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/congratulations-representative-dottie-bailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 07:42:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2019/congratulations-representative-dottie-bailey/</guid>
      <description>The one who has the bride is the bridegroom; the best man, who stands and listens for him, rejoices greatly at the bridegroom’s voice. So this joy of mine has been made complete. (Johhn 3:29)
 Yesterday, January 9, 2019, was a watershed day for everyone who ever associated with the St. Louis Tea Party Coalition. Your own Dottie Bailey was sworn in as Representative of the 110th State House district of Eureka, Wildwood, and Pacific.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019: Year of the Fast</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2019-year-of-the-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 06:05:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2018/2019-year-of-the-fast/</guid>
      <description>Fasting is probably the healthiest thing you can do for yourself. It&amp;rsquo;s also the cheapest healthy thing you can do. Unlike most diets and exercise plans, supplements, and, especially, trips to a doctor, fasting actually saves money. When you fast, you don&amp;rsquo;t eat.
Further, fasting is the simplest thing you can do to improve your physical and mental health. There are only two things to remember:
 Don&amp;rsquo;t eat. Drink some water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persuasion and Fat</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/07/persuasion-and-fat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 12:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/07/persuasion-and-fat/</guid>
      <description>The Easiest Formula for Mastering Persuasion, Losing Weight, and Avoiding Disease (video) &amp;ldquo;Persuasion&amp;rdquo; is part of my job title. When you&amp;rsquo;re a persuasion professional, you get a lot of questions about persuasion. Some are sincere. Others are skeptical, like, &amp;ldquo;Okay, persuasion boy, persuade me to give you a hundred dollars.&amp;rdquo;
Persuasion doesn&amp;rsquo;t work like that. But it also does. Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: if you ask me to persuade you to give me a hundred bucks, you already want to give me a hundred bucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Destroy Radical Islam Without Firing a Shot</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/29/how-to-destroy-radical-islam-without-firing-a-shot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 04:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/29/how-to-destroy-radical-islam-without-firing-a-shot/</guid>
      <description>You probably know that I admire Scott Adams quite a bit. He&amp;rsquo;s brilliantly predicted everything Trump has done. And he&amp;rsquo;s not finished dazzling us with his prediction skills.
Yesterday he made a prediction of how we&amp;rsquo;ll kill ISIS. It isn&amp;rsquo;t pretty. He&amp;rsquo;s not advocating what will happen. He&amp;rsquo;s just telling us what will happen.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to offer an alternative end to ISIS. It&amp;rsquo;s one I&amp;rsquo;ve advocated for attacking radical Islam since 2001.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caution: Identifying as &#39;NeverTrump&#39; Changes Your Brain</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/what-happens-you-identify-as-nevertrump/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/12/what-happens-you-identify-as-nevertrump/</guid>
      <description>When a person declares himself &amp;ldquo;NeverTrump,&amp;rdquo; he thinks he&amp;rsquo;s making a political statement. Or a moral one. But he&amp;rsquo;s not. He&amp;rsquo;s making a psychological commitment that&amp;rsquo;s very difficult and painful to break.
Identity is the highest, most powerful form of persuasion. Identity also drives our decisions in parts of the brain we don&amp;rsquo;t really have conscious control over. I realize many conservatives reject brain science, but, for those of you who are open to learning, I&amp;rsquo;ll explain as best I can in a moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Have a New Son, America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/15/you-have-a-new-son-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/15/you-have-a-new-son-america/</guid>
      <description>My son Patrick (closest to the camera at a civilian’s idea of parade rest) listens to the instructions of the enlisting officer among 9 young men and women preparing to swear an oath to the Constitution of the United States. They were here to make their first commitment to the armed forces.
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_16700&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;711&amp;rdquo;]Patrick Hennessy takes the oath of enlistment at the Federal Building in St. Louis August 14, 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buckley vs. Friedman on Service-Part 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 10:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</guid>
      <description>This is part 2 of a series on national service and the Franklin Project. Read part 1 here.
First, answer this for yourself: would you vote for William F. Buckley Jr?
Milton Friedman on National Service My friend Lloyd Sloan points out that Milton Friedman disagreed with Buckley’s call for national service. It seems appropriate, then, to view the idea of a service ethos through the eyes of two champions of conservatism of the 20th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use This One Word Because It Makes You More Influential</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/use-this-one-word-because-it-makes-you-more-influential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/use-this-one-word-because-it-makes-you-more-influential/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me to explain why the human brain works the way it does. And don&amp;rsquo;t ask me how scientists get the idea for some experiments.
Instead, take note of the most influential work in the English language, because I want you to be more influential.
What&amp;rsquo;s that one word?
It&amp;rsquo;s not &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;instantly&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;new.&amp;rdquo; They&amp;rsquo;re very powerful words, as every copywriter knows. But they&amp;rsquo;re not the most influential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy Erases 600 years of Scientific Progress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/26/italy-erases-600-years-of-scientific-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/26/italy-erases-600-years-of-scientific-progress/</guid>
      <description>The next time some liberal tells you the United States needs to act more like Europe, tell them, “no, we believe in science.”

Italy sentenced six scientists to prison for the felony of failing to predict an earthquake.
Seriously.
The people who brought us da Vinci, Columbus, and Marconi believe that those wizards in lab coats with all the machines that go “beep” are actually gods who control the earth and the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Bet On Election Outcomes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/01/dont-bet-on-election-outcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/01/dont-bet-on-election-outcomes/</guid>
      <description>“Anybody will beat Obama.”
I get some comments and see a lot of tweets about the inevitability that any Republican will win in November.
That’s frightening.
The prospect of a Republican beating Obama isn&amp;rsquo;t frightening, of course—any of the four remaining candidates would be night and day better for our future. What’s frightening is that so many people bet on the unknowable.
Except in rare cases—one candidate is caught stealing from a church weeks before the election—political elections carry too many variables for anyone to predict their results a month in advance, much less three-quarters of a year ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>