<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>paul krugman on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/paul-krugman/</link>
    <description>Recent content in paul krugman on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 10:38:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/paul-krugman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This David Stockman Quote Should Scare the Hell Out of Everyone</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/05/this-david-stockman-quote-should-scare-the-hell-out-of-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/05/this-david-stockman-quote-should-scare-the-hell-out-of-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Is the US economy about to collapse worse the Greece’s?
Some, like Paul Krugman, say that it’s okay for governments to print unlimited money. Others, who have actually managed businesses, say otherwise.
**David Stockman is among the latter. He was Reagan’s budget director for a few years. He became a media sensation because of his command of numbers. **
He left the White House early, fretting over federal debt. But debt in the 1980s was as a piggy bank to Wells Fargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bill Maher’s Vitriol Responsible for Arrest?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</guid>
      <description>Last week, America’s sleaziest leftists—Bill Maher, Chris Matthews, Keith Olbermann, E. J. Dionne, Paul Krugman, others – have [executed a prepared propaganda war](https://hennessysview.com/crime/a-national-day-of-shame/) against anyone who disagrees with them. Their theorem is: vitriolic rhetoric inspires conservatives to act out in violence.
Unfortunately for the loony left, there was no evidence to support their theorem. The evidence they falsely pointed to—Jarod Lee Loughner’s deranged murder rampage in Tucson—was determined to be a lie only hours after the event.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>