<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rodger Cook on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/rodger-cook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rodger Cook on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 04:40:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/rodger-cook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Vote in Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/19/go-vote-in-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 04:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/19/go-vote-in-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Go vote, please. Please. Vote now. Don’t Put It Off!!
Did you know that ObamaCare is my fault?
Of course, it is. Read my story below the clock.

**I didn’t vote in 2006. You know why? **
I put it off.
I decided not to stop on my way to work in the morning. Why? _I’ll have plenty of time tonight, _I thought. I’ll stop on my way home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rodger Cook Best Choice for Southern Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/17/rodger-cook-best-choice-for-southern-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/17/rodger-cook-best-choice-for-southern-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Rodger Cook fools no one into thinking he’s a member of the political class. He’s not. Rodger’s a human being, like the rest of us. That’s just one of the reasons that Rodger Cook has earned my personal endorsement in next Tuesday’s (March 20) Illinois primary.*

Actually, Rodger’s not so much like the rest of us. Rodger has served the people of Illinois all of his adult life. Rodger has been a police officer, a detective, a mayor, and private businessman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Plummer Steps In It</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/16/jason-plummer-steps-in-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 14:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/16/jason-plummer-steps-in-it/</guid>
      <description>When you’re the Republican Establishment’s candidate, you have one simple assignment: don’t screw up.
Jason Plummer, a 29-year-old lumber heir, is the GOP Establishment’s appointed candidate for US Congress in Illinois’ 12th Congressional District. He’s facing a shockingly tough race from former police detective and former Belleville Mayor, Rodger Cook. (Never underestimate a detective’s tenacity.)
In a debate last week, Plummer failed his one simple assignment. Despite a nearly unlimited war chest from his family’s fortune and the Illinois GOP treasury, Plummer said something stupid.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>