<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bob mccarty on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/bob-mccarty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bob mccarty on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 17:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/bob-mccarty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the Perfect Ingredients of Great Book?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/10/15/what-are-the-perfect-ingredients-of-great-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 17:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/10/15/what-are-the-perfect-ingredients-of-great-book/</guid>
      <description>Writers are always looking for the perfect topic for a book. But there’s a problem.
What’s important to me may not be important to you. And what you to read about, I might not care about.
That’s why great books achieve a certain universality. They touch on the essence of life itself, of humanity itself, of existence.
Some say that the secret to perfectly spellbinding stories is a mixture of just three elements: sex, food, and spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seducing the States</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/08/seducing-the-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/08/seducing-the-states/</guid>
      <description>You can’t call yourself a conservative and ask for education money from Washington.
Republicans dominate both houses of the Missouri legislature. You’d think they’d act like republicans (lower case). But when it comes to education bribes from Washington, many of our Republican legislators show little resistance to political seduction. We can help them.
On BigGovernment. com, Bob McCarty highlights the hypocrisy of blasting ObamaCare from one side of the mouth while begging for federal cash out of the other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>