<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John Brunner on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/john-brunner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in John Brunner on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 10:05:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/john-brunner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Paul Holzer Expose John Brunner? Part III</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/29/why-did-paul-holzer-out-john-brunner-part-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 10:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/29/why-did-paul-holzer-out-john-brunner-part-iii/</guid>
      <description>This is part III of a four-part series. Here&amp;rsquo;s partI and part II.
Why Now? Why did Holzer choose last week to out himself? Why show himself now, putting his old boss, John Brunner, in such a bad light? And right before the August 2 primary?
**Holzer has damaged Brunner&amp;rsquo;s reputation and credibility. **And Brunner spent a ton of his own money in the process, including paying $100,000 to the guy who made the video, then squealed about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Brunner&#39;s Charade, Part II</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/28/why-did-paul-holzer-out-john-brunner-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/28/why-did-paul-holzer-out-john-brunner-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>This is part II of a three-part series. Here&amp;rsquo;s part__I.
That Shadowy Paul Holzer Paul Holzer is a former Navy SEAL Lieutenant Commander and a medical student at Dartmouth in New Hampshire. (Oddly, his bio shows MD, MBA, even though is still in medical school and simultaneously working toward an MBA.) Holzer also runs a biotech 501c3 and a political consulting firm, Draper Sterling LLC. He did some work for Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign, and he was John Brunner&amp;rsquo;s chief of staff last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Brunner&#39;s Charade, part I</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/27/paul-holzer-john-brunner-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 10:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/27/paul-holzer-john-brunner-1/</guid>
      <description>Why in the world would a political operative who once worked for John Brunner out himself and expose Brunner as either a liar or a patsy two weeks before an election?
 Reggie Lampert: Of course, you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to lie on your back for a while but then you can lie from any position, can&amp;rsquo;t you? &amp;ndash;Charade, 1963
 Things just got weirder in Missouri. After the stunning revelation that people associated with John Brunner&amp;rsquo;s campaign did, in fact, produce a false, negative video attacking Eric Greitens, you might be wondering what&amp;rsquo;s going on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I know it was you, Fredo</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/29/fredo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 23:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/29/fredo/</guid>
      <description>Fredo Corleone: I&amp;rsquo;m your older brother, Mike, and I was stepped over! Michael Corleone: That&amp;rsquo;s the way Pop wanted it. Fredo Corleone: It ain&amp;rsquo;t the way I wanted it! I can handle things! I&amp;rsquo;m smart! Not like everybody says&amp;hellip; like dumb&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m smart and I want respect!
 —The Godfather: Part II
I&amp;rsquo;m sure John Brunner never saw himself as Fredo Corleone.
A Burning Question Did you ever ask yourself why John Brunner would release a surreptitious recording of a phone call with an opponent?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fascinating Results from Leaders Eat Last Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</guid>
      <description>This is the story of hard choices and how people resist making them.
Last week&amp;rsquo;s poll asked you to watch a video by Simon Sinek before answering two, simple, two-part questions: which Republican candidate for President and Missouri Governor is most likely and least likely to eat last?
I intended the poll to be hard. Not complicated, not long, but emotionally challenging.
Why the Poll Was Emotionally Challenging For several weeks, I have built a case for the importance of leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>