<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>featured on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/featured/</link>
    <description>Recent content in featured on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 03:42:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Farewell, Joe LeGrand</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/farewell-joe-legrand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/farewell-joe-legrand/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time I didn&amp;rsquo;t like Joe LeGrand.
It was 3rd grade. I was in the Epiphany Toppers Drum and Bugle Corps, and Joe was a bugler who stood right in front of me. He kept turning around and giving me dirty looks. So I decided right then and there that I didn&amp;rsquo;t like him.
Joe was a year ahead of me in school. While our lives intersected a lot, we weren&amp;rsquo;t really close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep Missouri Money in Missouri with TEA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/28/keep-missouri-money-in-missouri-with-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 01:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/28/keep-missouri-money-in-missouri-with-tea/</guid>
      <description>The Transportation Empowerment Act gives states control and funding for their roads. It is a far superior to the Highway Trust Fund, which is slush fund for pork projects.
Transportation Empowerment Act (TEA) from Senator Mike Lee would gradually shift federal gasoline taxes from Washington back to the states where they were collected without a Washington DC handling fee and without strings attached.
TEA embodies an idea I first heard from Ronald Reaganwhen he was governor of California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What&#39;s Happening on the Muni Courts Front</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 02:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</guid>
      <description>He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harrass our people, and eat out their substance.
 &amp;ndash; The Declaration of Independence
Back in August, I asked for your help in pushing for municipal court reform.
Cities that abuse their police and courts destroy liberty:
** Abusive citiesturn citizens against their police forces ** Abusive cities sponge off the poor ** Abusive cities operate debtor prisons ** Abusive cities subvert respect for the law and the courts ** Abusive citiesdemean and demoralize their citizens ** Abusive cities repel business and jobs ** Abusive cities condition people to bow down to government</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Ideas to Save Christmas in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Nixon buck-passed while Ferguson burned. With the city’s main business district laid to rubble, buycotts won’t have much effect. And Christmas is around the corner.
Who got hurt last night?
*1. People who own businesses *2. People who work at businesses *3. People who rely on businesses
Time is short. The people affected by last night’s riots need help rebuilding and jobs right now. While I don’t have complete plans, I can throw out eight ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Municipal Courts Matter to Liberty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 03:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</guid>
      <description>I am embarrassed.
I am embarrassed that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about this problem sooner. Or I heard about it and ignored it, which is even worse. Maybe I thought it was just the usual liberal whining about trumped up racial problems. Whatever, I should have listened.
On September 2, I asked a room of about 30 tea partiers, &amp;ldquo;Do you trust our justice system?&amp;rdquo; I heard a chorus of &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Municipal Court or Kangaroo Court?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/20/municipal-court-kangaroo-court/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 22:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/20/municipal-court-kangaroo-court/</guid>
      <description>Guest post by Lee A. Presser
On Wednesday, April 16, 2003, I was in Bel-Ridge, Missouri, Municipal Court to plead “not guilty.” The violation listed on the ticket did not match the reality of what actually happened on the road. In a file folder, I had documents and photographs to rebut the charge. The ticket stated that Court convened at 6:30 P.M. I arrived twenty minutes early.
Before 9:30 that evening, I had been tightly handcuffed twice, verbally abused by police, pushed into a depressing detention cell, and made an example of in front of seventy-five to one hundred people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Hard to Deny North County Has Problems with Police and Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/19/end-game-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>What did you think when you first heard reports of violence in Ferguson? I mean, after the shooting death of Michael Brown?
Did you ever for a moment think, &amp;ldquo;this is about more than just Michael Brown?&amp;rdquo;
I hate to say that. It&amp;rsquo;s embarrassing to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m so jaded as to think &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s all&amp;rdquo; when a young man dies. Sorry. I&amp;rsquo;m just being honest.
I understand community grief and anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonah Goldberg Perfectly Defines the GOP Establishment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 18:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/19/jonah-goldberg-perfectly-defines-gop-establishment/</guid>
      <description>I hope you read Jonah Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s short article on National Review Online last week. If not, you missed the best definition of Establishment Republicans EVER!
Goldberg&amp;rsquo;s piece also exploded the myth of &amp;ldquo;pro-business&amp;rdquo; way too many conservatives believe. Conservatism isn&amp;rsquo;t pro-business, it&amp;rsquo;s pro-market. I&amp;rsquo;ll let Jonah explain:
 Just to clarify, the difference between being pro-business and pro-market is categorical. A politician who is a “friend of business” is exactly that, a guy who does favors for his friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Government’s Surrender to Cliven Bundy Destroys Taleb’s Weak Argument for Gun Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</guid>
      <description>Events of the past week show the power of the Second Amendment to challenge government tyranny, regardless of the government’s firepower advantage. Let me back up, though.
A Smart Man’s Stupid Argument for Gun Control A year ago, the gun control lobby pumped a Facebook post by Nassim Nicholas Taleb, one of my favorite thinkers.
In his post, Taleb argued that the Second Amendment means nothing because the federal government has massively superior firepower:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Weinstein and His Call to Jail Global Warming Skeptics</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Yet, in holding scientific research and discovery in respect, as we should, we must also be alert to the equal and opposite danger that public policy could itself become the captive of a scientific-technological elite.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ndash;President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Farewell Address, 1961
A young man named Adam Weinstein recently called for incarceration of disbelievers in the cult of catastrophic anthropogenic global warming (CAGW). His argument mirrors the argument Goebbels used in 1930s to quash dissent from eugenics and to take immediate policy actions for the betterment of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Abdullah Kicks Obama Out of Saudia Arabia ? **Video Added**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 00:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/28/king-abdullah-kicks-obama-saudia-arabia/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think American foreign policy couldn&amp;rsquo;t sink any lower than standing by while Vladimir Putin re-conquers the Warsaw Pact nations. Then you&amp;rsquo;ve underestimated Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s incompetence.
Apparently, Obama didn&amp;rsquo;t bow low enough to King Abdullah of Saudi Arabia. Whatever happened, an &amp;ldquo;intimate&amp;rdquo; evening planned for Obama and Abdullah was abruptly cancelled after a two-hour meeting between the two leaders. A meeting intended to &amp;ldquo;mend fences&amp;rdquo; between the two men.
UPDATE: Here&amp;rsquo;s the video from Lou Dobbs on Fox Business</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pousosa for County Executive</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/25/tony-pousosa-county-executive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 23:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/25/tony-pousosa-county-executive/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t you just love brash upstarts? People with verve and moxie?
I do. I like pesky guys full of gumption, like Vladimir Sobotka. I like energetic young political activists like Kenny Newhouse. And I like bold conservative organizers like Eileen Tyrrell. In fact, nothing pleases me more than seeing young, libertarian-ish Republicans making the establishment squirm.
Sometimes the squirming establishment is as small as a GOP township or a school district.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now, the White House Says Russia Preparing to Invade Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/now-the-white-house-says-russia-preparing-to-invade-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 20:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/now-the-white-house-says-russia-preparing-to-invade-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>This morning, a White House aide told reporters that Obama’s sanctions are visibly “weakening” Putin and Russia.
Hours later, the White House recognizes that Russia’s invasion of Ukraine could come any moment.
 Speaking from the Georgian capital, Tbilisi, Mike Rogers, the chair of the House of Representatives intelligence committee, said US intelligence officials were convinced “that Putin is not done in Ukraine”.
 Surprise. As I’ve written, Russian paranoia demands a larger sphere of influence and a large buffer of puppet governments, all the way to the German border with Poland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Would You Do If You Were Putin?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 18:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/23/what-would-you-do-if-you-were-putin/</guid>
      <description>You saw Obama stand by as you threatened Georgia in 2009.
You heard Obama whisper to Medvedev that he’ll be willing to defy Congress to capitulate to you after Obama’s re-election.
You watched Obama and his bumbling Secretary of State mangle its its own strategy in Syria—if the US ever had a Syrian strategy at all.
You saw that the US was completely unprepared for your annexation of Crimea.
You see the headlines of massive NSA spying on US citizens, though that same NSA was blind to your invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Secrets Politicians Don&#39;t Want You to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/20/5-secrets-politicians-dont-want-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 14:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/20/5-secrets-politicians-dont-want-know/</guid>
      <description>How long has it been since you said, &amp;ldquo;they just don&amp;rsquo;t listen to us?&amp;rdquo;
By &amp;ldquo;they,&amp;rdquo; you mean politicians, of course. Maybe you feel they listen to lobbyists and big corporations and banksters, but they don&amp;rsquo;t listen to their constituents.
I have to agree with you. Politicians don&amp;rsquo;t listen to their constituents. They don&amp;rsquo;t even know who their constituents are.
They know demographics and statistics about their constituents, but that&amp;rsquo;s like saying you know how a banana tastes because you read a chemical assay report of its contents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Will Putin Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/will-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 01:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/will-putin/</guid>
      <description>Ask yourself this: why did the stock markets rally today after Obama announced sanctions against Russians? I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to that, but first some background.
I&amp;rsquo;ve often said that Putin plays chess while Obama fumbles with checkers. I picture our president, chin resting on fist, brows squeezed in childlike concentration, as he carefully chooses between jumping Putin&amp;rsquo;s piece to end the game or getting another of his pieces &amp;ldquo;kinged.&amp;rdquo;
Of course, Obama goes for the kingship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Million Reasons to Vote for Eileen Tyrrell on April 8</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/1-2-million-reasons-vote-eileen-tyrrell-april-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 18:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/1-2-million-reasons-vote-eileen-tyrrell-april-8/</guid>
      <description>Do you live in Rockwood School District?
I do. My kids all went to Rockwood schools. My wife taught in a Rockwood school for three years.
The teachers in Rockwood tend to think a lot like the people who live here. They&amp;rsquo;re not a bunch of wacked-out lefties. Not most of them.
Still, that good education has come with HUGE price tag. Rockwood is one of the most expensive districts in Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Book Predicted Russia&#39;s Ukraine Adventure. Poland&#39;s Next.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/16/predicted-russias-ukraine-adventure-polands-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/16/predicted-russias-ukraine-adventure-polands-next/</guid>
      <description>Did you ever read a book and think, &amp;ldquo;I need to tell people about this?&amp;rdquo;
Then you didn&amp;rsquo;t tell people about it. I mean, you didn&amp;rsquo;t blog about it. You didn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;officially&amp;rdquo; proclaim the book &amp;ldquo;required reading.&amp;rdquo;
Then something happened that you knew could happen because of the book, but you don&amp;rsquo;t get credit for calling it because you never got around to pumping the book.
That&amp;rsquo;s how I feel today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Steps To Negotiating With a Politician</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/15/talk-politician/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 21:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/15/talk-politician/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever said, &amp;ldquo;vote them all out?&amp;rdquo;
Do you sometimes think anybody would do a better job than the incumbent? Do you feel you have no influence in Jefferson City, Springfield, or Washington? Do you feel that way because you don&amp;rsquo;t have thousands of dollars to donate and rich friends with oodles of cash you can bundle?
I feel that way all the time. Ask my friends Ben Evans and Michelle Moore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Messages Backfire?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/04/why-do-messages-backfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/04/why-do-messages-backfire/</guid>
      <description>In the 1970s, a magazine ad for Benson &amp;amp; Hedges cigarettes portrayed a hockey fight. Two players slug it out. Sticks and gloves litter the ice.
The point of view is on-ice, in the midst of the scrum. The crowd is on its feet, banging the glass. You&amp;rsquo;re right there with linesmen trying to break it up.
The hockey gloves are Coopers. Every hockey player knows the name. In the photo, one of the gloves has been doctored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Roy Blunt Needs a Psychologist</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/03/can-roy-blunt-save-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/03/can-roy-blunt-save-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>Senator Roy Blunt (HA-57) proposed that all Obamacare ads contain a disclaimer: &amp;ldquo;Paid for by the American Taxpayer.&amp;rdquo;
I get the idea. I can&amp;rsquo;t stand it when my tax dollars buy ads intended to raise my taxes. It means I&amp;rsquo;m fighting against myself.
Still, I don&amp;rsquo;t like Senator Blunt&amp;rsquo;s plan because I think it could backfire.
The Psychology of Ownership Right now, few people have a sense of ownership of Obamacare.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>