<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>featured on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/featured/</link>
    <description>Recent content in featured on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 03:42:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Farewell, Joe LeGrand</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/farewell-joe-legrand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/04/farewell-joe-legrand/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time I didn&amp;rsquo;t like Joe LeGrand.
It was 3rd grade. I was in the Epiphany Toppers Drum and Bugle Corps, and Joe was a bugler who stood right in front of me. He kept turning around and giving me dirty looks. So I decided right then and there that I didn&amp;rsquo;t like him.
Joe was a year ahead of me in school. While our lives intersected a lot, we weren&amp;rsquo;t really close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep Missouri Money in Missouri with TEA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/28/keep-missouri-money-in-missouri-with-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 01:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/28/keep-missouri-money-in-missouri-with-tea/</guid>
      <description>The Transportation Empowerment Act gives states control and funding for their roads. It is a far superior to the Highway Trust Fund, which is slush fund for pork projects.
Transportation Empowerment Act (TEA) from Senator Mike Lee would gradually shift federal gasoline taxes from Washington back to the states where they were collected without a Washington DC handling fee and without strings attached.
TEA embodies an idea I first heard from Ronald Reaganwhen he was governor of California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s What&#39;s Happening on the Muni Courts Front</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 02:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/09/heres-whats-happening-muni-courts-front/</guid>
      <description>He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harrass our people, and eat out their substance.
 &amp;ndash; The Declaration of Independence
Back in August, I asked for your help in pushing for municipal court reform.
Cities that abuse their police and courts destroy liberty:
** Abusive citiesturn citizens against their police forces ** Abusive cities sponge off the poor ** Abusive cities operate debtor prisons ** Abusive cities subvert respect for the law and the courts ** Abusive citiesdemean and demoralize their citizens ** Abusive cities repel business and jobs ** Abusive cities condition people to bow down to government</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Ideas to Save Christmas in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Nixon buck-passed while Ferguson burned. With the city’s main business district laid to rubble, buycotts won’t have much effect. And Christmas is around the corner.
Who got hurt last night?
*1. People who own businesses *2. People who work at businesses *3. People who rely on businesses
Time is short. The people affected by last night’s riots need help rebuilding and jobs right now. While I don’t have complete plans, I can throw out eight ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Municipal Courts Matter to Liberty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 03:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/05/municipal-courts-matter-liberty/</guid>
      <description>I am embarrassed.
I am embarrassed that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about this problem sooner. Or I heard about it and ignored it, which is even worse. Maybe I thought it was just the usual liberal whining about trumped up racial problems. Whatever, I should have listened.
On September 2, I asked a room of about 30 tea partiers, &amp;ldquo;Do you trust our justice system?&amp;rdquo; I heard a chorus of &amp;ldquo;No.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>