<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mississippi on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mississippi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mississippi on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 12:33:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mississippi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Erick Erickson Protecting Reince Priebus?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 22:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/09/erick-erickson-reince-priebus/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE:
Welcome, Donald Trump fans! Thanks for reading.
Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s true, I have had disagreements with Erick in the past. I try to assess the situation, not just the person. It&amp;rsquo;s possible to disagree with someone on one subject and to agree with them on another.
If anything, Erick showed consistency by rescinding Trump&amp;rsquo;s invitation to Red State. Erick didn&amp;rsquo;t want the event to descend into chaos led by my friends over the Barbour episode; he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want a descent into chaos led by Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin Moves to Censure Henry Barbour Over Racist Mississippi Ads</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/ed-martin-moves-censure-henry-barbour-racist-mississippi-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 04:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/ed-martin-moves-censure-henry-barbour-racist-mississippi-ads/</guid>
      <description>Go Ed!
A few weeks ago, hunkered down at my laptop in my hotel room in Jacksonville, Florida. I was exhausted from seven hours of travel and a time change. But I had to take a moment to recognize Ed Martin&amp;rsquo;s commitment to all the best the Republican Party stands for.
Ed is determined to expose the GOP establishment&amp;rsquo;s willingness to do anything to destroy grassroots insurgents. Thad Cochran&amp;rsquo;s forces in Mississippi threw ethics, morality, and decency to the wind in their quest to stop a Tea Party candidate from unseating the 128-term Cochran.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>