<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jack Spooner on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/jack-spooner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jack Spooner on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 23:46:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/jack-spooner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Come to Export Import Speaking and Gathering This Saturday at Paddy O&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/27/come-to-export-import-speaking-and-gathering-this-saturday-at-paddy-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 23:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/27/come-to-export-import-speaking-and-gathering-this-saturday-at-paddy-os/</guid>
      <description>With Opportunity for All; With Favoritism Toward None Join Us Paddy O&amp;rsquo;s&amp;ndash;618 S. 7th Street, St. Louis, MO 4:15 PM Saturday, May 30 RSVP on Facebook
They say the Export Import Bank is a tiny agency that creates jobs for small business while producing a profit for the Treasury. And rescues baby rabbits from dangerous predators. And it’s gluten free.
Call us skeptics.
We saw the news that Goldman Sachs used the Export Import Bank to secure funding for a financially unstable buyer—after paying the Secretary of State’s husband $200,000 for a fifteen-minute speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashcroft Passes on Opportunity to Deny Medicaid Expansion Fix</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/16/ashcroft-passes-opportunity-deny-medicaid-expansion-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 02:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/16/ashcroft-passes-opportunity-deny-medicaid-expansion-fix/</guid>
      <description>Last week, I wrote about the Missouri Republican Establishment&amp;rsquo;s plan to win a windfall for lobbyist Kit Bond via Senate candidate Jay Ashcroft. Not that the Establishment cares about Bond, but they want Medicaid expansion passed before they beg for money for 2016 from the Missouri Hospital Association and Chamber of Commerce.
Well, the St. Louis Post Dispatch asked Ashcroft about the deal, and he couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite bring himself to deny that he would pass Medicaid expansion if elected.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>