<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>al-qaeda on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/al-qaeda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in al-qaeda on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 15:17:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/al-qaeda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Obama Aid the Kenyan Mall Massacre?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/22/did-obama-aid-the-kenyan-mall-massacre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2013 15:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/22/did-obama-aid-the-kenyan-mall-massacre/</guid>
      <description>I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d have to ask.
In Nairobi, Kenya, al Qaeda terrorists stormed an upscale mall yesterday to kill all the Christians.So far, 59 are dead and at least 175 wounded. Another 30 or so hostages remain inside with the terrorists.Kenyan police are hunting the terrorists and attempting to free the hostages.
The USA, surely, is on the side of the Kenyan authorities. Right?
Well, last week, President Obama waived (aka, violated) a US law that prohibited the arming of terrorists and terrorist-linked groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When The Three O&#39;Clock Call Came, Barack Obama Froze</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</guid>
      <description>The fog of war is lifting from Benghazi, and what lies beneath should shame Obama’s most ardent supporters. Barack Obama choked, and Americans died.

When America came under attack, Obama panicked and froze.
When Americans under his direction pleaded for their lives, he was afraid to pull the trigger.
Here’s the emerging picture.
White House Ordered Military and CIA to Stand Down and Let Al Qaeda Kill Former Navy SEALs Ty Woods and Glen Doherty, so disgusted by the White House’s refusal to help Americans under attack, defied an order to stand down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Todd Akin: Putting Al-Qaeda Ahead of the CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/05/rep-todd-akin-putting-al-qaeda-ahead-of-the-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 03:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/05/rep-todd-akin-putting-al-qaeda-ahead-of-the-cia/</guid>
      <description>Hey, one of our favorite members of Congress, and a true gentleman, Todd Akin (R-MO), has made the front page of BigGovernment.com.
The Obama Justice Department is quietly investigating the lawyers associated with the John Adams Project who may have violated a number of laws in place to protect our covert operatives and their families. But so far, with few exceptions, the media and their friends on Capitol Hill haven’t found this case nearly as interesting as Valerie Plame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Al Qaeda Impotent?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/23/is-al-qaeda-impotent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/23/is-al-qaeda-impotent/</guid>
      <description>Captain Ed raises an interesting point in response to al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s declaration of war on North Africa
 Despite their general inability to prevail in Iraq, successfully detonate explosives in Britain, and do anything else in the US, AQ warned Muslims to stay away from their own government buildings on the south side of the Mediterranean
 He writes a good piece&amp;ndash;which reminded me of this humor entry I posted in 2003 and agian in 2005:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>