<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cliven Bundy on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/cliven-bundy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cliven Bundy on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 09:35:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/cliven-bundy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What the ACLU Teaches Us About Cliven Bundy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/26/aclu-teaches-us-principles-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 09:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/26/aclu-teaches-us-principles-people/</guid>
      <description>In 1977, the National Socialist Party (Nazi) applied to march and rally in Skokie, Illinois. Few communities want Nazis marching down their streets, but Skokie held a stronger case against the Nazis than most towns in America. About one person in every six of Skokie&amp;rsquo;s large Jewish population was a Nazi prison camp survivor.
 The debate was clear-cut: American Nazis claimed the right of free speech while their Jewish &amp;ldquo;targets&amp;rdquo; claimed the right to live without intimidation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Government’s Surrender to Cliven Bundy Destroys Taleb’s Weak Argument for Gun Control</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/12/governments-surrender-cliven-bundy-destroys-talebs-weak-argument-gun-control/</guid>
      <description>Events of the past week show the power of the Second Amendment to challenge government tyranny, regardless of the government’s firepower advantage. Let me back up, though.
A Smart Man’s Stupid Argument for Gun Control A year ago, the gun control lobby pumped a Facebook post by Nassim Nicholas Taleb, one of my favorite thinkers.
In his post, Taleb argued that the Second Amendment means nothing because the federal government has massively superior firepower:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>