<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steve Tilley on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/steve-tilley/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steve Tilley on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 18:21:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/steve-tilley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Jay Nixon Spit in Our Faces?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/15/why-did-jay-nixon-spit-in-our-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 18:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/15/why-did-jay-nixon-spit-in-our-faces/</guid>
      <description>When Jay Nixon decided to ignore the voters, ignore the Missouri Constitution, and ignore the power of the legislature, he spit in our faces. But why?
Maybe because his special session is failing.
Maybe because, to save the centerpiece of that legislation, House Speaker Steve Tilley needed protection from the grass roots.
Maybe because Jay Nixon is as crooked as a dog’s hind leg and doesn’t give a hoot about you, your state, your country, or the law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Tilley vs. the Constitution</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/17/steve-tilley-vs-the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2011 18:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/17/steve-tilley-vs-the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>And, he’s back.
Missouri House Speaker Steve Tilley (R-Perryville) has signed onto legislation designed to circumvent the Electoral College in presidential elections. Like his position on embryonic stem cell research and the national debt, Tilley seems far out of step with Missouri’s Republican base on this. And this guy wants to be Lt. Governor? Please.
This might be old news to some.
I see that Big Government’s Josie Wales blogged about the national effort last August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Tilley vs. Fiscal Responsibility</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/14/steve-tilley-vs-fiscal-responsibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/14/steve-tilley-vs-fiscal-responsibility/</guid>
      <description>Four men risked their political lives to help solve the problem of our lifetimes, but they forgot to massage Steve Tilley’s monstrous ego.
When John McCain (R-AZ) and Roy Blunt (R-MO) agree with Michele Bachmann and Rush Limbaugh, you can bet the issue is beyond debate.
In this case, the issue is the massive U.S. debt and what that debt is about to do to America.
McCain compared the U.S. situation to Greece and Spain, saying we should prepare for a “fiscal meltdown.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>