<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economic meltdown on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/economic-meltdown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economic meltdown on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 22:02:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/economic-meltdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nobody Is Telling You About The Regulatory Armageddon About To Swamp The US Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/nobody-is-telling-you-about-the-regulatory-armageddon-about-to-swamp-the-us-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 22:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/07/nobody-is-telling-you-about-the-regulatory-armageddon-about-to-swamp-the-us-economy/</guid>
      <description>If you think federal regulation is bad today, just wait. You ain’t seen nothin’ yet.
 By the EPA&amp;rsquo;s own reckoning, the rule if implemented annually would cost American businesses $90 billion. But a related rule due to be taken up in December similarly would declare large swaths of the U.S. &amp;ldquo;closed for new business&amp;rdquo; until emissions are reduced to meet lower caps than exist today, says Anne Kolton, spokeswoman for the American Chemistry Council.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats led by Barney Frank caused the economic meltdown</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/17/democrats-led-by-barney-frank-caused-the-economic-meltdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 11:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/17/democrats-led-by-barney-frank-caused-the-economic-meltdown/</guid>
      <description>The current economic mess is a gift of the DNC. Massechusetts Congressman Barney Frank (D) bears the lion&amp;rsquo;s share of guilt. Charles Schumer (D-NY), Maxine Waters (D-CA), and William Clay (D-MO) rank near the top of the list. [youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cMnSp4qEXNM&amp;amp;hl;=en&amp;amp;fs;=1] Please direct appropriate correspondence toward them. And if you&amp;rsquo;re having financial troubles, please ask them to pay your bills. They seem to think that paying other people&amp;rsquo;s bills is the patriotic thing to do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>