<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unemployment on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/unemployment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unemployment on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:55:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/unemployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>America Has a Job To Do</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</guid>
      <description>We believe that meaningful work dignifies and enriches human lives.
[olympus_highlight color=&amp;quot;yellow&amp;rdquo;]Every person who wants to work should find a choice of occupations to pursue. And every occupation improves the life of the person doing the work, the people the work is done for, and the family and community in which the worker lives.[/olympus_highlight]
The more workers engaged in meaningful work, the better our country becomes.
The opposite of work is not idleness but dependency, and dependency degrades human lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bakers Union Costs 300 St. Louisans Their Jobs  **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/bakers-union-costs-300-st-louisans-their-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 01:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/bakers-union-costs-300-st-louisans-their-jobs/</guid>
      <description>**UPDATE Union Declares Victory AsHostess Goes Out of Business. No more Ho Hos. ****
Unions destroy themselves like pathetic drunks, dragging down everyone around them.

In a fine example of anti-strategic thinking and un-game theory, the Bakers Union put 637 of its members out of work yesterday.
Hostess—makers of Twinkies—is bankrupt. Part of the bankruptcy involved rewriting union contracts to allow the company to stay in business.
Instead of taking one for the team and helping their company crawl out of its fiscal hole, the Bakers went on strike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why You Are Underemployed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</guid>
      <description>If you can’t find full-time work, blame Obamacare.

One reason the Middle Class has shriveled and wages shrunk over the the past four years is underemployment. People want full time work, but settle for anything. And anything is usually part time.
Most of the fantastic new jobs created since the 2009 have been part-time jobs.
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, 14.6% of Americans want a full-time job but settle for part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Insider Has No Idea Where Money Comes From</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/27/business-insider-has-no-idea-where-money-comes-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/27/business-insider-has-no-idea-where-money-comes-from/</guid>
      <description>I love some things about Business Insider. Mostly its great headlines.
Unfortunately, sometimes its writers show an ignorance of basic economics in their rush to catapult Obama to a second term. Joe Weisenthal is just the latest example.
Joe tries to claim that economic recovery in the US is retarded by loss of public sector jobs.

What Joe doesn’t seem to get is this: the private sector pays for those public sector jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday (Infographic)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</guid>
      <description>The world&amp;rsquo;s economy&amp;ndash;including BRICs&amp;ndash;is collapsing. The problem is debt, and the youth will set us free. Even if that&amp;rsquo;s a very painful liberation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Never Guess Who&#39;s About to Become Obama&#39;s Biggest Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/youll-never-guess-whos-about-to-become-obamas-biggest-nightmare/</guid>
      <description>In 2008, we heard all about the youth movement for Obama. We heard that the enormous Millennial Generation, born between 1982 and 2001, would destroy the GOP and everything America once stood for&amp;ndash;like jobs, family, faith, and hard work. And when Obama won, many believed the tales of the Obama Youth.
  
But many were wrong. Voters under 30 have had it with vague promises and glittering bullshit from that punk from Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Killed the American Job Machine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/who-killed-the-american-job-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/09/05/who-killed-the-american-job-machine/</guid>
      <description>Maureen Dowd’s having trouble slathering make-up on her favorite pigs these days. Her President—the man for whom she surrendered all pretense of intelligence, wisdom, and self-control—is flailing.
And Maureen Dowd is going all wobbly. Wobbly on Obama. Wobbly on America. Wobbly on life. Here’s an exceprt:
 On the razor’s edge of another recession; blocked at every turn by Republicans determined to slice him up at any cost; starting an unexpectedly daunting re-election bid; and puzzling over how to make a prime-time speech about infrastructure and payroll taxes soar, maybe President Obama is wishing that he had thrown the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Makes It Worse</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/06/03/obama-makes-it-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 14:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/06/03/obama-makes-it-worse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rdquo; could refer to anything. Anything at all.
In this case, though, I&amp;rsquo;m referring to unemployment. Well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;m referring to the economy overall.
Unemployment rate rises to 9.1%, 54K jobs added « Hot Air
Obama has increased regulation, seized entire industries (auto, student loans, commercial banking, medicine), and borrowed more money faster than all previous presidents combined.
Obama is a one-dictator disaster. And an incompetent one at that.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a job, Obama made it worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas Have Consequences—Even Stupid Ones</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/ideas-have-consequenceseven-stupid-ones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/ideas-have-consequenceseven-stupid-ones/</guid>
      <description>When Barack Obama became president in January 2009, he began a campaign to weaken America. I’m not talking about military cuts; I’m speaking of America’s stature. Barack Obama famously refused to acknowledge American Exceptionalism in 2009. He bowed to kings and princes, then denied doing so, then bowed again and again. His White House has driven down the dollar. Timothy Geithner, Obama’s Secretary of the Treasury, warns that the world economy must “rebalance” with less reliance on America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Signs of Economic Disaster</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/3-signs-of-economic-disaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/3-signs-of-economic-disaster/</guid>
      <description>Each day, more economists jump onto the Double-Dip bandwagon. Signs abound that the natural economic recovery that would normally follow a deep recession won’t happen. Instead, the economy is now saddled with so much debt, so many regulations, and such onerous new taxes that the Obama Administration tells us to be happy with 9.5 percent unemployment.

Barack Obama is an economic disaster of the first order.
So why all the pessimism?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed: Other Shoe About to Drop</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/fed-other-shoe-about-to-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 03:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/fed-other-shoe-about-to-drop/</guid>
      <description>The only two people in the world who believe the economy is healthy and vibrant are Barack Obama and Joe Biden.

Now, the Federal Reserve Board’s Open Market Committee (FOMC) is getting ready to announce that the economy is sicker than we thought.
 Although Fed policymakers still believe the basic trajectory of the economy remains one of moderate expansion, there may be more attention given to heightened dangers of a sharp slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White House Unveils Unemployment Strategy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/01/10/white-house-unveils-unemployment-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 19:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/01/10/white-house-unveils-unemployment-strategy/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, DC: The White House unveiled a new strategy to lower the nation’s unemployment rate, currently standing at 10 percent.
In his weekly radio address Saturday, the President announced that he will use remaining funds from the failed Stimulus bill to take advantage of little known variable in the unemployment rate factor: “discouraged workers.”
Pointing out that “discouraged” workers are excluded from the unemployment calculation, the President explained that the government will encourage the unemployed to simply give up hopes for finding work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Skeptical</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/18/i-am-skeptical/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 13:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/18/i-am-skeptical/</guid>
      <description>You should be, too.
 The tally of continuing claims, or benefits drawn by workers for more than one week, fell 148,000 to 6,687,000, the first weekly decline since the week ended Jan. 3 and largest since Nov. 24, 2001. (wsj.com)
 That would be good news, but only if a) it&amp;rsquo;s true, and b) 148,000 more people found jobs than lost them last month.
Frankly, I think the government&amp;rsquo;s lying to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed Report Hints At Depression--Markets Tank</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/19/fed-report-hints-at-depression-markets-tank/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 21:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/19/fed-report-hints-at-depression-markets-tank/</guid>
      <description>The Federal Reserve Board&amp;rsquo;s Open Market Committee released the minutes of its October 28-29 meeting, today, in which some members raise the specter of economic depression extending more than 4 consecutive quarters. The report calls the present financial mess the worst in more than half a century, carefully avoiding direct references to the Great Depression.
Stocks Tank
Wall Street responded with 427 point (5.16 percent) collapse, with Citigroup leading financial stocks to a 10 percent crash.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>