<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unemployment on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/unemployment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unemployment on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:55:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/unemployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>America Has a Job To Do</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 10:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/11/america-has-work-to-do/</guid>
      <description>We believe that meaningful work dignifies and enriches human lives.
[olympus_highlight color=&amp;quot;yellow&amp;rdquo;]Every person who wants to work should find a choice of occupations to pursue. And every occupation improves the life of the person doing the work, the people the work is done for, and the family and community in which the worker lives.[/olympus_highlight]
The more workers engaged in meaningful work, the better our country becomes.
The opposite of work is not idleness but dependency, and dependency degrades human lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bakers Union Costs 300 St. Louisans Their Jobs  **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/bakers-union-costs-300-st-louisans-their-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 01:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/13/bakers-union-costs-300-st-louisans-their-jobs/</guid>
      <description>**UPDATE Union Declares Victory AsHostess Goes Out of Business. No more Ho Hos. ****
Unions destroy themselves like pathetic drunks, dragging down everyone around them.

In a fine example of anti-strategic thinking and un-game theory, the Bakers Union put 637 of its members out of work yesterday.
Hostess—makers of Twinkies—is bankrupt. Part of the bankruptcy involved rewriting union contracts to allow the company to stay in business.
Instead of taking one for the team and helping their company crawl out of its fiscal hole, the Bakers went on strike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why You Are Underemployed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</guid>
      <description>If you can’t find full-time work, blame Obamacare.

One reason the Middle Class has shriveled and wages shrunk over the the past four years is underemployment. People want full time work, but settle for anything. And anything is usually part time.
Most of the fantastic new jobs created since the 2009 have been part-time jobs.
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, 14.6% of Americans want a full-time job but settle for part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Insider Has No Idea Where Money Comes From</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/27/business-insider-has-no-idea-where-money-comes-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/27/business-insider-has-no-idea-where-money-comes-from/</guid>
      <description>I love some things about Business Insider. Mostly its great headlines.
Unfortunately, sometimes its writers show an ignorance of basic economics in their rush to catapult Obama to a second term. Joe Weisenthal is just the latest example.
Joe tries to claim that economic recovery in the US is retarded by loss of public sector jobs.

What Joe doesn’t seem to get is this: the private sector pays for those public sector jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday (Infographic)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/03/black-friday/</guid>
      <description>The world&amp;rsquo;s economy&amp;ndash;including BRICs&amp;ndash;is collapsing. The problem is debt, and the youth will set us free. Even if that&amp;rsquo;s a very painful liberation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>