<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John McCain on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/john-mccain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in John McCain on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 18:17:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/john-mccain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>John McCain&#39;s Most Evil Sin</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/05/john-mccains-most-evil-sin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 18:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/05/john-mccains-most-evil-sin/</guid>
      <description>John McCain may have done some heroic things, but he is a hero no more.
Imagine how you&amp;rsquo;d feel.
A knock on your door.
Through the deadlights around your front door, you see a car with government stencils on the side. When you get close enough, you look out and see a man in uniform. An officer. You know. You know why he&amp;rsquo;s here. Your throat tightens. You want to turn around and walk away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give McCain a Break</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/19/give-mccain-a-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 17:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/19/give-mccain-a-break/</guid>
      <description>Hate John McCain if you want. Call McCain a traitor, even.
I look at John McCain and marvel at his strength. Many do.
Everyone knows about McCain being shot down over Vietnam and spending 5 years in a POW camp. But most people don&amp;rsquo;t know about the deep emotional scar McCain brought home with him. And that emotional scar undoubtedly drives him to his fits of anger and telling lies about people he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Libertarian Kids, Not Drones, Scare McCain and Graham</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/12/why-here-is-the-real-reason-mccain-and-graham-lost-their-minds-over-rand-pauls-filibuster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/12/why-here-is-the-real-reason-mccain-and-graham-lost-their-minds-over-rand-pauls-filibuster/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer Rubin—WaPo’s token conservative—said it perfectly:
 McCain lost his cool with Rand Paul and sounded like the old man down the street screaming to the new kids on the block, “Get off my lawn!”
 The real reason McCain and Lindsey Graham embarrassed themselves on the floor of Senate had nothing to do with what Rand Paul said. Rand Paul&amp;rsquo;s ideas terrify McCain, Graham, and most of the Republican establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why John McCain Wants the GOP To Go First</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/08/why-john-mccain-wants-gop-to-go-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 09:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/08/why-john-mccain-wants-gop-to-go-first/</guid>
      <description>John McCain doesn&amp;rsquo;t want the Republican Party to outlive him.
He&amp;rsquo;s afraid. Afraid that, after he&amp;rsquo;s gone, his political widow will remarry someone younger, sexier, more fun.
Thursday, March 7, 2013: Senate Office Building, Washington, DC In the dark cloisters of his Senate office, McCain leans back in his chair, tie loosened, jacket tossed casually over a guest chair, fingers interlaced behind his white head, and broods.
He sees those rascally young libertarians&amp;ndash;the ones who actually want to own their own lives&amp;ndash;plunging into the party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is The Infographic That The Whole Republican Party Is Freaking Out About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</guid>
      <description>The 3 million McCain voters who didn’t vote for Romney?
They’re dead.

[Click image to view full size. Please forward, download, and print. This is important.]
To survive, the GOP needs to stop being afraid of Millennials and tell them truth: they can move out of mom and dad’s house, they can drop out of school, they can quit their dead-end job with the idiot supervisor. But they can’t get away from government and debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Lloyd Smith and Jo Ann Emerson Plan This All Along?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/04/did-lloyd-smith-and-jo-ann-emerson-plan-this-all-along/</guid>
      <description>In an open Republican primary in Missouri’s 8th Congressional District, a solid conservative would beat an establishment &amp;ldquo;my turn&amp;rdquo; Republican, hands down. And the Missouri GOP would hate it.
That’s why I smell a rat. Would you be surprised to learn that Jo Ann Emerson and Lloyd Smith had this switcheroo planned months ago? You have to admit that the timing is suspicious:
 * Emerson wins a certain re-election * Smith announces he&#39;s stepping down as Missouri GOP Executive Director * Emerson announces she&#39;s resigning to become Queen of Lobbyists * Missouri&#39;s GOP Establishment breaks hips to tell reporters &amp;quot;Lloyd Smith&#39;s our man!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama the Reckless</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/08/obama-the-reckless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/08/obama-the-reckless/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, the United States suffered its highest human lost since the Afghanistan conflict began. At least 38 elite, brave American warriors died in combat.
Flasback to May 23 of this year. That’s when Barack Obama made the surprise announcement that he would begin accelerated troop withdrawals in July. That timetable meant beginning the withdrawal during the summer fighting season.
Current and former military experts advised the president against this reckless move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Tilley vs. Fiscal Responsibility</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/14/steve-tilley-vs-fiscal-responsibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2011 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/14/steve-tilley-vs-fiscal-responsibility/</guid>
      <description>Four men risked their political lives to help solve the problem of our lifetimes, but they forgot to massage Steve Tilley’s monstrous ego.
When John McCain (R-AZ) and Roy Blunt (R-MO) agree with Michele Bachmann and Rush Limbaugh, you can bet the issue is beyond debate.
In this case, the issue is the massive U.S. debt and what that debt is about to do to America.
McCain compared the U.S. situation to Greece and Spain, saying we should prepare for a “fiscal meltdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Post-Palin Electoral College Map</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/06/the-post-palin-electoral-college-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 18:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/06/the-post-palin-electoral-college-map/</guid>
      <description>Sarah Palin will push 9 toss-up states into McCain&amp;rsquo;s camp (from left to right):
 * Nevada * Colorado * New Mexico * [Michigan](https://www.politico.com/news/stories/0908/13198.html) * New Hampshire * Indiana * Ohio * Virginia * [Florida](https://www.surveyusa.com/client/PollReportEmail.aspx?g=e3a24829-6f3f-4928-b30f-cb21804091f0)  This will give McCain the Electoral College victory in November, 300 to 238. The Palin-Effect works two different ways: Rough Rider Admiration and Strong Woman Identification. This estimate and projection is based on analysis of detailed polling data from Gallup and Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Starkest of Contrasts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/04/the-starkest-of-contrasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 03:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/04/the-starkest-of-contrasts/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard John McCain&amp;rsquo;s horrible experience in Vietnam. I&amp;rsquo;ve never before heard him tell it.
What strikes me is the enormous contrast between him and Barack Obama. John McCain has lived a noble, heroic, remarkable life. Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s read about such things.
John McCain left it all on the battle field, then in a POW camp, then in hospitals where he gave his all for his country. Barack Obama took everything he could get his hands on: money from a convicted slum-lord felon, street cred from bigotted America-hating minister, political favor from a convicted anti-American terrorist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCain - Palin Rally in O&#39;Fallon, Missouri, Is Still On</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/31/mccain-palin-rally-in-ofallon-missouri-is-still-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 16:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/31/mccain-palin-rally-in-ofallon-missouri-is-still-on/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re getting ready to head out to the McCain Rally in O&amp;rsquo;Fallon, Missouri. I just checked with the campaign and the rally is still on. John McCain is stopping in New Orleans to check on hurricane preparations before the rally, so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be surprised if it starts late.
I&amp;rsquo;ll have photos and a report on the events this evening.
Technorati Tags: McCain-Palin Rally,O&amp;rsquo;Fallon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palin Pick Energizing the Right **Update**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/30/palin-pick-energizing-the-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2008 16:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/30/palin-pick-energizing-the-right/</guid>
      <description>Conservative spirits soared like roman candles three times in my life:
 * Ronald Reagan&#39;s emergence in 1980 * Newt Gingrich&#39;s Contract with America in 1994 * [Sarah Palin&#39;s selection](https://www.politico.com/blogs/jonathanmartin/0808/GOP_grassroots_on_fire.html) as McCain&#39;s vice president in 2008  Besides the math (each event exactly 14 years apart), Palin&amp;rsquo;s selection could change the face of politics in America for a long time.
Yesterday, I hurriedly outlined some of the instant wins from McCain&amp;rsquo;s brilliant move.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>