<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John McCain on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/john-mccain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in John McCain on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 18:17:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/john-mccain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>John McCain&#39;s Most Evil Sin</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/05/john-mccains-most-evil-sin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 18:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/03/05/john-mccains-most-evil-sin/</guid>
      <description>John McCain may have done some heroic things, but he is a hero no more.
Imagine how you&amp;rsquo;d feel.
A knock on your door.
Through the deadlights around your front door, you see a car with government stencils on the side. When you get close enough, you look out and see a man in uniform. An officer. You know. You know why he&amp;rsquo;s here. Your throat tightens. You want to turn around and walk away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give McCain a Break</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/19/give-mccain-a-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 17:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/02/19/give-mccain-a-break/</guid>
      <description>Hate John McCain if you want. Call McCain a traitor, even.
I look at John McCain and marvel at his strength. Many do.
Everyone knows about McCain being shot down over Vietnam and spending 5 years in a POW camp. But most people don&amp;rsquo;t know about the deep emotional scar McCain brought home with him. And that emotional scar undoubtedly drives him to his fits of anger and telling lies about people he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Libertarian Kids, Not Drones, Scare McCain and Graham</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/12/why-here-is-the-real-reason-mccain-and-graham-lost-their-minds-over-rand-pauls-filibuster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/12/why-here-is-the-real-reason-mccain-and-graham-lost-their-minds-over-rand-pauls-filibuster/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer Rubin—WaPo’s token conservative—said it perfectly:
 McCain lost his cool with Rand Paul and sounded like the old man down the street screaming to the new kids on the block, “Get off my lawn!”
 The real reason McCain and Lindsey Graham embarrassed themselves on the floor of Senate had nothing to do with what Rand Paul said. Rand Paul&amp;rsquo;s ideas terrify McCain, Graham, and most of the Republican establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why John McCain Wants the GOP To Go First</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/08/why-john-mccain-wants-gop-to-go-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 09:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/08/why-john-mccain-wants-gop-to-go-first/</guid>
      <description>John McCain doesn&amp;rsquo;t want the Republican Party to outlive him.
He&amp;rsquo;s afraid. Afraid that, after he&amp;rsquo;s gone, his political widow will remarry someone younger, sexier, more fun.
Thursday, March 7, 2013: Senate Office Building, Washington, DC In the dark cloisters of his Senate office, McCain leans back in his chair, tie loosened, jacket tossed casually over a guest chair, fingers interlaced behind his white head, and broods.
He sees those rascally young libertarians&amp;ndash;the ones who actually want to own their own lives&amp;ndash;plunging into the party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is The Infographic That The Whole Republican Party Is Freaking Out About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 04:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/06/this-is-the-infographic-that-the-whole-republican-party-is-freaking-out-about/</guid>
      <description>The 3 million McCain voters who didn’t vote for Romney?
They’re dead.

[Click image to view full size. Please forward, download, and print. This is important.]
To survive, the GOP needs to stop being afraid of Millennials and tell them truth: they can move out of mom and dad’s house, they can drop out of school, they can quit their dead-end job with the idiot supervisor. But they can’t get away from government and debt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>