<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Illinois on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/illinois/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Illinois on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:47:02 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/illinois/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Turn Nursing Homes Into Death Camps</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 16:47:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/democrats-turn-nursing-homes-into-death-camps/</guid>
      <description>When I wrote this post on May 6, I worried how it would be received. Accusing a governor of intentionally killing nursing home residents in order to save money is a serious charge. And, with only circumstantial evidence, difficult to prove.
Since then, Andrew Cuomo&amp;rsquo;s behavior has been consistent with guilt. The latest example is deflection. He&amp;rsquo;s trying, now, to blame federal guidelines for his order to force uninfected nursing homes to treat confirmed COVID-19 patients even if they lacked the facilities and skills to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Flynn for Congress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/25/mike-flynn-for-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 21:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/25/mike-flynn-for-congress/</guid>
      <description>I was hungover.
I sat in a booth at the Holiday Inn in Quincy, Illinois, with my wife and two friends from St. Louis. The day before was my wife&amp;rsquo;s birthday, which she graciously spent waiting for me to speak at a tea party in Quincy.
Angela and I sat with Jim Durbin and Ben Evans. About four feet away, sitting at the bar, were Andrew Breitbart and editor-in-chief of Andrew&amp;rsquo;s BigGovernment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why You Are Underemployed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</guid>
      <description>If you can’t find full-time work, blame Obamacare.

One reason the Middle Class has shriveled and wages shrunk over the the past four years is underemployment. People want full time work, but settle for anything. And anything is usually part time.
Most of the fantastic new jobs created since the 2009 have been part-time jobs.
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, 14.6% of Americans want a full-time job but settle for part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Vote in Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/19/go-vote-in-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 04:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/19/go-vote-in-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Go vote, please. Please. Vote now. Don’t Put It Off!!
Did you know that ObamaCare is my fault?
Of course, it is. Read my story below the clock.

**I didn’t vote in 2006. You know why? **
I put it off.
I decided not to stop on my way to work in the morning. Why? _I’ll have plenty of time tonight, _I thought. I’ll stop on my way home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rodger Cook Best Choice for Southern Illinois</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/17/rodger-cook-best-choice-for-southern-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/17/rodger-cook-best-choice-for-southern-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Rodger Cook fools no one into thinking he’s a member of the political class. He’s not. Rodger’s a human being, like the rest of us. That’s just one of the reasons that Rodger Cook has earned my personal endorsement in next Tuesday’s (March 20) Illinois primary.*

Actually, Rodger’s not so much like the rest of us. Rodger has served the people of Illinois all of his adult life. Rodger has been a police officer, a detective, a mayor, and private businessman.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>