<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pursuit of happiness on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/pursuit-of-happiness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pursuit of happiness on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 15:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/pursuit-of-happiness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Planning Is Killing the Economy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/26/government-planning-is-killing-the-economy/</guid>
      <description>Friedrich Hayek warned more than half a century ago that central planning doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. Here’s why:
 * Central Planners (government) makes a plan * The plan includes specific expectations * The expectations are never, ever, realized * A “crisis” ensues * So the planners demand more control * And create more plans * Ad hoc * Willy nilly * Capriciously * So you must wait for things to settle down to make your decision  Today’s Wall Street Journal article about the fiscal cliff demonstrates the futility of central planning:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is How To Spend Election Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/this-is-how-to-spend-election-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/06/this-is-how-to-spend-election-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives take great pride in working, and for good reason. Work gives shape to life. Work is the poles of a tent, the bones of a body, the beams in the ceiling.

But work isn’t why we live. We live to pursue happiness.
For some, the pursuit of happiness involves acquiring property. Land, clothes, cars, plastic surgery. All examples of the pursuit of happiness.
Voting is another pursuit. People vote for minor candidates representing strange parties who have no chance of winning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/24/the-ghost-of-christmas-yet-to-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 20:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/12/24/the-ghost-of-christmas-yet-to-come/</guid>
      <description>In the course of our lives, we sometimes lose our way. We wander off the good path. Or we fail to blaze the trail we should.

 THE Phantom slowly, gravely, silently, approached. When it came near him, Scrooge bent down upon his knee; for in the very air through which this Spirit moved it seemed to scatter gloom and mystery.
It was shrouded in a deep black garment, which concealed its head, its face, its form, and left nothing of it visible save one outstretched hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Extensive Interview with Missouri News Horizon</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/my-long-interview-with-missouri-news-horizon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/my-long-interview-with-missouri-news-horizon/</guid>
      <description>When I hear all the lies, slanders, and threats against the Tea Party movement from folks on the left, I wish I could counter with a fuller examination of my beliefs. Luckily, with the help of Missouri News Horizon, I can.
The Friday before the 9/12 Tea Party, I sat down with Rebecca Townsend to talk about the Tea Party.
Rebecca and I chatted for an hour. She led me through just about every aspect of the Tea Party’s history up to that point.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>