<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>American Tea Party on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/american-tea-party/</link>
    <description>Recent content in American Tea Party on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:31:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/american-tea-party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Consent of the Governed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/consent-of-the-governed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 04:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/09/consent-of-the-governed/</guid>
      <description>In the battle between conservatives and statists, a fundamental difference seems to lie in the meaning of a concept found in the Declaration of Independence:
 Governments are instituted among Men, deriving their just powers from the consent of the governed[.]
 The dispute is how men convey consensual powers to their government.
Conservatives believe that governmental power is conveyed exclusively through the Constitution; statists believe power is conveyed through elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow-Thru Afterglow</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/flow-thru-afterglow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/28/flow-thru-afterglow/</guid>
      <description>Dangerous Thoughts Standing in the Wings
_Why are you here? _I thought.
I was standing on the steps of the Arch fully aware that my fingers were painfully cold when the wrong thought crossed my mind. By &amp;ldquo;wrong thought,&amp;rdquo; I mean that one thought that will subconsciously sabotage the important or dangerous thing you are about to attempt. Like thinking, &amp;ldquo;what if the front wheel just fell off?&amp;rdquo; as you&amp;rsquo;re cruising down a winding road on a motorcycle, or &amp;ldquo;what if I forget my lines?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Tea Party Turnout Rocks!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-turnout-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 20:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-turnout-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the 1,000+ patriots who stood in the snow at the Arch, Dana &amp;ldquo;The Energizer&amp;rdquo; Loesch, Doug Saur, the speakers, Michelle Moore and Jeff who managed the fairgrounds, Desiree&amp;rsquo; the Poster Party Lady, and the true leaders at #TCOT who held my hand after I stumbled into this event. Today at the Arch in St. Louis was simple patriotic magic. I have to do some wrapping up of the event, but I&amp;rsquo;ll say this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis Tea Party Live Feed All Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-live-feed-all-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 14:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/27/st-louis-tea-party-live-feed-all-day/</guid>
      <description>Stay on Hennessy&amp;rsquo;s View for continous live coverage of the St. Louis Tea Party
https://www.ustream.tv/flash/live/1/528594Free TV : Ustream</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the World with Twitter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/25/how-to-change-the-world-with-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 02:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/02/25/how-to-change-the-world-with-twitter/</guid>
      <description>My light blogging owes to our efforts to change the world in a week. My role is, appropriately, miniscule.
When Congress listens, it will repeal the trillions of waste, fraud, and abuse it has produced over the past 4 months, it will stop proposed borrowing and bailouts, it will stop rewarding bad behavior in corporations and citizens, or it will retire. This time, there are no two ways.
 Using tools like Twitter, email, and Facebook, TCOT has provided at least 163 patriots a forum to voice its discontent on Friday, February 27 at 11:00 a.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>