<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academics on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academics on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:30:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>America&#39;s Business is Jobs, Not College</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/14/americas-business-is-jobs-not-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/14/americas-business-is-jobs-not-college/</guid>
      <description>Many of us are guilty. I am, too. You, probably.
In high school (and after) we mocked the kids who took shop. The &amp;ldquo;greasers&amp;rdquo; who got credit for wrenching on cars or welding or making cabinets. It was the 1980s and shop, along with home economics, became an elective in most schools.
Until the 80s, some practical life skill class was a requirement at most American public and parochial high schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mizzou Protests Were About Abortion All Along</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/mizzou-protests-abortion-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 12:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/mizzou-protests-abortion-along/</guid>
      <description>I hate to say &amp;ldquo;I told you so.&amp;rdquo;
But the St. Louis Post Dispatch has found that I may have been right on November 8. That&amp;rsquo;s when I made the outlandish comment that the whole race issue at Mizzou is actually an abortion issue. I suspected that Planned Parenthood&amp;rsquo;s vast lobbyist network is agitating leaders of left-leaning organizations trying to create general unrest.
**The manipulators would use campus racial unrest to demand restored privileges for Planned Parenthood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are abortionists manipulating Mizzou&#39;s black athletes?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/08/are-abortionists-manipulating-mizzous-black-athletes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 18:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/08/are-abortionists-manipulating-mizzous-black-athletes/</guid>
      <description>A few Mizzou football players announced they&amp;rsquo;re boycotting all sports activities until University of Missouri system president Tim Wolfe quits or is fired. Considering the football team&amp;rsquo;s dismal performance, the cynic in me wonders if sitting out might help the players&amp;rsquo; chances of getting an NFL draft.
The players and other African-American students at Mizzou believe they are victims of &amp;ldquo;systematic oppression&amp;rdquo; and they want Tim Wolfe to fix it simply by resigning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Don&#39;t Need More Technology--They Need Less</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</guid>
      <description>I was on my high school&amp;rsquo;s board of education for a year. It was quite an honor, honestly, but I screwed it up.
At the time, I was a software architect. They put me on the board as the technology guy. I was supposed to make the case for more funding for smart boards and other tech stuff.
But I said kids really don&amp;rsquo;t need more technology in school. Technology, I said, was like sex education: they&amp;rsquo;ll get more than they can handle on the streets or watching TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockwood School Board Quid Pro Quo?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/rockwood-school-board-quid-pro-quo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 21:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/04/13/rockwood-school-board-quid-pro-quo/</guid>
      <description>From the &amp;ldquo;see, I told ya so&amp;rdquo; file . . .
Rockwood NEA President Suzanne Dotta worked hard to influence the recent school board election. The candidates Ms. Dotta pushed won.
The new board hired Ms. Dotta as Director of Professional Learning within 72 hours of the election.
I expect Ms. Dotta to teach Rockwood&amp;rsquo;s professionals how to game the system for personal gain at taxpayer expense.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to question this apparent quid pro quo, the next Rockwood Board meeting is April 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eileen Tyrrell Is Only Rockwood Candidate In It For All Stakeholders</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/29/eileen-tyrrell-rockwood-candidate-stakeholders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/29/eileen-tyrrell-rockwood-candidate-stakeholders/</guid>
      <description>Eileen Tyrrell is the only candidate who represents ALL the stakeholders in Rockwood School District.
While other candidates focus on more money for the system, Eileen focuses on using Rockwood&amp;rsquo;s (embarrassingly) ample resources better.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to ask youself:
 Do you plan to fulfill your duty to vote on April 8? What time of day do you plan to vote? Where will be and what will you be doing immediately before you go to vote?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Million Reasons to Vote for Eileen Tyrrell on April 8</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/1-2-million-reasons-vote-eileen-tyrrell-april-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 18:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/17/1-2-million-reasons-vote-eileen-tyrrell-april-8/</guid>
      <description>Do you live in Rockwood School District?
I do. My kids all went to Rockwood schools. My wife taught in a Rockwood school for three years.
The teachers in Rockwood tend to think a lot like the people who live here. They&amp;rsquo;re not a bunch of wacked-out lefties. Not most of them.
Still, that good education has come with HUGE price tag. Rockwood is one of the most expensive districts in Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And the inspiring truth about teachers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/26/and-the-depressing-truth-about-teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 00:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/26/and-the-depressing-truth-about-teachers/</guid>
      <description>Samantha.
She&amp;rsquo;s the daughter every parent hopes for. Diligent. Dedicated. Kind to a fault. Smart. Hard working. Loyal. Prettier than she knows.
She gets it from her mother.
She&amp;rsquo;s about to graduate from college and become a teacher.
Like her mom.
She doesn&amp;rsquo;t need a union.
She is a union.
With her mom.
And a million others.
They care. And try. And teach. Or try.
Your kid would be blessed to walk into Sam&amp;rsquo;s classroom one day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Devastating Truth About Teachers&#39; Unions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/26/devastating-truth-teachers-unions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 22:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/08/26/devastating-truth-teachers-unions/</guid>
      <description>The stronger the union the weaker the learnin&amp;rsquo;. According to Harvard Business Review, students learn less in states with stronger teachers&amp;rsquo; unions.
 A 1-standard-deviation rise in teachers&amp;rsquo; union dues per teacher is associated with a 4% fall in student proficiency rates, according to a study of 721 U.S. school districts in 42 states by Johnathan Lott of the University of Chicago Law School and Lawrence W. Kenny of the University of Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Vote in Kirkwood School District, Listen Up</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/if-you-vote-in-kirkwood-school-district-listen-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/18/if-you-vote-in-kirkwood-school-district-listen-up/</guid>
      <description>In the past 15 years, Kirkwood School Districts operation costs have skyrocketed almost 100 percent. But the people paying the taxes for that district have seen a cost of living increase of only 44 percent.

Obviously, at some point, the system will crash. Unless you do something now.
On April 2, you can elect two fiscally responsible members to the board of education.
Eric Peterson and Amy Russell
Here’s what you should do:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s The Dirty Little Secret About Teachers Nobody Is Telling You About</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/15/heres-the-dirty-little-secret-about-teachers-nobody-is-telling-you-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 05:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/15/heres-the-dirty-little-secret-about-teachers-nobody-is-telling-you-about/</guid>
      <description>I know a teacher pretty well, and I know nasty little secrets she’s not telling.
She sneaks out of bed at 4:45 every morning. No one else is up. No one’s watching her. At that hour, she can do whatever she wants without consequence.
She sneaks downstairs and puts on her make-up in front of the TV. She also encrypts mysterious lesson plans into a little black book. Names and numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Schools Replace Great Fiction With Government propaganda</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</guid>
      <description>[Originally posted on Redstate.com]
English was my favorite subject in school, so much so that I can still recite from memory large passages of the books we read, like A Separate Peace:
 I went back to Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there 15 years before.
 And who doesn’t know this by heart:
 If you really want to hear about it, the first thing you’ll probably want to know is where I was born and what my lousy childhood was like and how my parents were occupied and all before they had me and all that David Copperfield kind of crap, but I don’t feel like going into it, if you want to know the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Suffocate Free Speech</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 15:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/16/colleges-suffocate-free-speech/</guid>
      <description>Colleges in the United States are systematically destroying free speech, free thought, and creative writing. Sixty-five percent of colleges and universities censor students, even in creative writing classes.
[youtube=https://youtu.be/Z3vgGqlZGGE] Hillsdale or nothing.
Related articles  * [GREG LUKIANOFF IN THE NEW YORK TIMES: Feigning Free Speech on Campus. &amp;quot;Colleges and universities a...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/155479/) (pjmedia.com) * [ONE WAY FREE SPEECH: The progressive vision of free speech is decidedly one-way, excluding any s...](https://pjmedia.com/instapundit/154514/) (pjmedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DESE: The original box of rocks that nothing is dumber than</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/24/dese-the-original-box-of-rocks-that-nothing-is-dumber-than/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/24/dese-the-original-box-of-rocks-that-nothing-is-dumber-than/</guid>
      <description>According to research from Missouri Education Watchdog, the Department of Elementary and Secondary Education (DESE) agreed to surrender Missouri&amp;rsquo;s education voice under Obama&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Race to the Top&amp;rdquo; scheme. Race to the Top was a contest in which states agreed to let the federal Department of Education, via two puppet organizations, run all of the state&amp;rsquo;s education systems. In exchange, some states were awarded money, but others were not.
Chris Nicastro, chief rock in the DESE box, applied for the grant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Lucky?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/14/whos-lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 23:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/14/whos-lucky/</guid>
      <description>There’s a “special” school in St. Louis County. Its seniors graduated on last Friday.

How sad it must be for those kids. They’re not graduating from the district’s “normal” schools with their peers. For various reasons, they’ve been relegated to a school for misfits.
Seeing the building makes the bad feelings worse. It’s a former grade school, crammed inconveniently behind a bank and a Taco Bell. Its Eisenhower era architecture stands out amidst its Mortgage Boom surroundings like a dandelion on golf course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMSL: Communist Recruiting With Taxpayer Dollars</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/09/umsl-communist-recruiting-with-taxpayer-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 02:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/05/09/umsl-communist-recruiting-with-taxpayer-dollars/</guid>
      <description>The University of Missouri St. Louis uses tax dollars to provide a recruiting station for the Communist Party USA—an organization whose purpose is to shred the United States Constitution.
UMSL Student Philip Christofanelli heroically chronicles the remarkable Marxist indoctrination known as “Introduction to Labor Studies” on BigGovernment.com. I’ll give you a taste:
 Prof. Giljum then introduced Tony Pecinovsky, a local organizer for the Communist Party, who proceeded to speak to us for two hours about the beliefs of the Communist Party and the benefits of membership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Question for Gail Hackett of UMKC</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/one-question-for-gail-hackett-of-umkc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 05:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/29/one-question-for-gail-hackett-of-umkc/</guid>
      <description>Gail Hackett, UMKC Provost, released a deceitful, false, and irresponsible defense of UMKC instructors who encouraged students to use violence, sabotage, and intimidation to their way.
But Gail Hackett refuses to answer hard questions.
I have one question for the UMKC Provost: ****
**Do you agree with Don Giljum’s statement “I believe in a violent overthrow of Bourgeois?” **
Before you answer, remember that Giljum’s use of the personal term “Bourgois” instead of the the class “bourguoisie” indicates that Giljim believes in violence against individual members of the middle class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Great Reasons to Send Your Kids to Vacation Liberty School</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/25/3-great-reasons-to-send-your-kids-to-vacation-liberty-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/03/25/3-great-reasons-to-send-your-kids-to-vacation-liberty-school/</guid>
      <description>Register today for Vacation Liberty School. Here&amp;rsquo;s 3 reasons why you should:
 Most school systems don&amp;rsquo;t care about liberty; they care about conformity. The only way kids will learn an appreciation for the blessings of libertyis if their parents send them to schools that put liberty at the center of the cirriculum. That&amp;rsquo;s what Vacation Liberty School does.
  Many teachers would love to teach more about the blessings of liberty to their skulls full of mush, but they can&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seducing the States</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/08/seducing-the-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/08/seducing-the-states/</guid>
      <description>You can’t call yourself a conservative and ask for education money from Washington.
Republicans dominate both houses of the Missouri legislature. You’d think they’d act like republicans (lower case). But when it comes to education bribes from Washington, many of our Republican legislators show little resistance to political seduction. We can help them.
On BigGovernment. com, Bob McCarty highlights the hypocrisy of blasting ObamaCare from one side of the mouth while begging for federal cash out of the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Has the Fear?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</guid>
      <description>For 100 years in America, government, business, and the education establishment built schools and laws about education. The purpose of these government schools and education laws was to produce compliant, unimaginative, order-taking automatons.
Don’t believe me? Here’s Woodrow Wilson, educator and president, speaking on the American plan for education:
 We want one class of persons to have a liberal education, and we want another class of persons, a very much larger class of necessity in every society, to forgo the privilege of a liberal education and fit themselves to perform specific difficult manual tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Explain the Uselessness of Teachers’ Unions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/03/how-to-explain-the-uselessness-of-teachers-unions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 04:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/03/how-to-explain-the-uselessness-of-teachers-unions/</guid>
      <description>America’s coolest governor explains it all:
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ksLlAi3iIc&amp;amp;color1;=0xb1b1b1&amp;amp;color2;=0xd0d0d0&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;feature;=player_embedded&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francis Howell Has a Sicko Teacher</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/24/francis-howell-has-a-sicko-teacher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 02:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/24/francis-howell-has-a-sicko-teacher/</guid>
      <description>Celeste is an eighteen-year-old student in the Francis Howell High School.
Celeste’s fellow students and, apparently, a teacher named Debra Blessman are bullying and abusing the girl. Celeste’s sin? Conservatism.
Bob McCarty tells the story better than I can. Dana Loesch has been all over this story. There’s a facebook page dedicated to supporting Celeste, which everyone should like, even those of us who hate facebook.
I should point out that, to date, the school’s administrators are standing behind the abusive teach, Blessman, who calls Celeste a “tea bagger” and encourages the students to mock the girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epiphany</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/epiphany/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 03:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/epiphany/</guid>
      <description>I can’t tell you the date of our last sandlot football game. We didn’t commemorate it or mark with a special ceremony. We probably didn’t even know it would be our last game together.

After school, the kids would come to my house. Our next door neighbors, the Nahers, had a double lot, and Mrs. Naher was a former professional women’s baseball player. She loved sports and kids and let us tear up the the lawn they manicured all summer by playing sandlot football in the fall and winter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>