<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>psychology on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/psychology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in psychology on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 10:40:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/psychology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Being the Oddball Sucks</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/how-leaders-decide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 10:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/20/how-leaders-decide/</guid>
      <description>Could you stand by a &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; answer?
Let&amp;rsquo;s pretend you&amp;rsquo;re in a room with 10 people about your age and background. You&amp;rsquo;ve been talking for a while, and you&amp;rsquo;ve gotten to know the others. Then the task begins. It&amp;rsquo;s straightforward.
On a large TV, you see a line drawing of a face. The instructor calls out people by name and asks if the face is a happy face, a sad face, or neutral face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s How the Ryan-Trump Meeting Ends</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/11/heres-how-the-ryan-trump-meeting-ends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 14:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/05/11/heres-how-the-ryan-trump-meeting-ends/</guid>
      <description>Nothing happens in politics by accident. Every move has an angle. Some players are better than others. Paul Ryan and Donald Trump are two of the best players alive, but one is better than the other. We&amp;rsquo;ll see that tomorrow.
House Speaker Paul Ryan has set aside Thursday for meetings with his party&amp;rsquo;s nominee for President. Every nominee for president meets with the senior members of his party&amp;rsquo;s Congressional caucus, so there&amp;rsquo;s nothing odd about the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use This One Word Because It Makes You More Influential</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/use-this-one-word-because-it-makes-you-more-influential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/27/use-this-one-word-because-it-makes-you-more-influential/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me to explain why the human brain works the way it does. And don&amp;rsquo;t ask me how scientists get the idea for some experiments.
Instead, take note of the most influential work in the English language, because I want you to be more influential.
What&amp;rsquo;s that one word?
It&amp;rsquo;s not &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;instantly&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;new.&amp;rdquo; They&amp;rsquo;re very powerful words, as every copywriter knows. But they&amp;rsquo;re not the most influential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss The Brain Study That Tells You How to Influence Democrats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/01/dont-miss-the-brain-study-that-tells-you-how-to-influence-democrats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/01/dont-miss-the-brain-study-that-tells-you-how-to-influence-democrats/</guid>
      <description>One of the most powerful tools of influence is fear.
Decades of research shows that fear of loss is about three times as motivating as hope for gain. (This changes under certain situations, like conditions of certain loss, but that’s for another time.)
So political message writers often use negative messages to influence voters to take a chance on a cause or a candidate.
This tactic works well with Republican voters, and less well with Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Depression Be Your Guide</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/02/let-depression-be-your-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/07/02/let-depression-be-your-guide/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I gave you a reason to celebrate the Supreme Court’s decision. But I never said to let go of your anger or depression. ** That’s because we need creativity, focus, and action, and you get those through emotional distress. **

In his new best-selling book, Jonah Lehrer discusses the link between depression and creativity:
 This helps explain why Forgas has found that states of sadness— he induces the downcast mood with a film about death and cancer— also correlate with better writing samples; subjects compose sentences that are clearer and more compelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Glenn Beck Helping?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/21/is-glenn-beck-helping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 01:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/21/is-glenn-beck-helping/</guid>
      <description>For (at least) the past two nights, Glenn Beck’s program has been spell-bindingly depressing and eye-gougingly infuriating. He’s chronicled the Obama administration’s anti-Constitutional transfer of power and wealth from private Americans to other countries. He’s shown that the administration has no concern over the 2010 election because it has no intention of obeying the laws passed by Congress.

For example, the newly appointed Consumer Protection Czar, a hard-line communist, Elizabeth Warren, is funded directly from the U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>