<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>common core standards on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/common-core-standards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in common core standards on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 04:13:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/common-core-standards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This Seems Like a Really Big Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/this-seems-like-a-really-big-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 04:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/02/25/this-seems-like-a-really-big-win/</guid>
      <description>I am so embarrassed.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know that Fred Sauer, Gretchen Logue, and Anne Gassel were suing Missouri over Common Core.
Did you know that?
(I probably knew it and forgot. Sorry.)
But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: THEY WON!!!!
Wait. YOU won. You won because Fred, Gretchen, and Anne stuck their necks out for you. And for me.
So Thank You! to Fred, Gretchen, and Anne. And this case seems really, really big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Schools Replace Great Fiction With Government propaganda</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/11/american-schools-replace-great-fiction-with-government-propaganda/</guid>
      <description>[Originally posted on Redstate.com]
English was my favorite subject in school, so much so that I can still recite from memory large passages of the books we read, like A Separate Peace:
 I went back to Devon School not long ago, and found it looking oddly newer than when I was a student there 15 years before.
 And who doesn’t know this by heart:
 If you really want to hear about it, the first thing you’ll probably want to know is where I was born and what my lousy childhood was like and how my parents were occupied and all before they had me and all that David Copperfield kind of crap, but I don’t feel like going into it, if you want to know the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>