<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Navy SEAL on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/navy-seal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Navy SEAL on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 01:35:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/navy-seal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Cried and Made My Bed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/22/cried-made-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 01:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/05/22/cried-made-bed/</guid>
      <description>I cried this morning. At work. Tears of shame.
Every day when I get to work, I go through a thirty-minute routine. I write down the 3 things I want to accomplish that day. I write down my appointments. I write down a one-sentence prayer. I copy a quote to guide me. With the time remaining, I learn one new thing.
Today that one thing I learned was humbling. Shameful, actually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When The Three O&#39;Clock Call Came, Barack Obama Froze</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</guid>
      <description>The fog of war is lifting from Benghazi, and what lies beneath should shame Obama’s most ardent supporters. Barack Obama choked, and Americans died.

When America came under attack, Obama panicked and froze.
When Americans under his direction pleaded for their lives, he was afraid to pull the trigger.
Here’s the emerging picture.
White House Ordered Military and CIA to Stand Down and Let Al Qaeda Kill Former Navy SEALs Ty Woods and Glen Doherty, so disgusted by the White House’s refusal to help Americans under attack, defied an order to stand down.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>