<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ferguson on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/ferguson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ferguson on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 23:37:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/ferguson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day of Hope, Prayer, and Clean-up in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/a-day-of-hope-prayer-and-clean-up-in-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 23:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/a-day-of-hope-prayer-and-clean-up-in-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Dellena Jones’s 911 Hair Salon was attacked at about 11:15 PM by a small band of young men. The break-in and robbery occurred close to the time of the first shooting. The hair salon is less than 100 yards from the scene of the shooting.
But that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop volunteers from St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and friends from helping.
[caption width=&amp;quot;300&amp;rdquo; id=&amp;quot;attachment_16631&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignright&amp;rdquo;]Volunteers pose for a picture after helping clean and repair 911 Hair Salon in Ferguson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overnight in Ferguson: &#34;A remarkable amount of gunfire out there&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/overnight-in-ferguson-a-remarkable-amount-of-gunfire-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 08:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/overnight-in-ferguson-a-remarkable-amount-of-gunfire-out-there/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis County Police Chief Jon Belmar told reporters &amp;ldquo;there was a remarkable amount of gunfire out there,&amp;rdquo; describing the scene on W. Florissant last night.
A shooter confronted plain-clothes officers and opened fire. Officers returned fire, striking the suspect. The suspect is in critical, unstable condition in a local hospital. One officer was treated, but the severity and cause of his injury is unknown.
The shooting and at least one break-in of a business marred what had been peaceful commemorations of the death of Michael Brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible video of shooting in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/incredible-video-of-shooting-in-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 07:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/10/incredible-video-of-shooting-in-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Watch. You can see the shooter in a white t-shirt.
https://youtu.be/fZmpmVdIfJU
We can make a difference.
If you want to make the world better, like this, then we have to change the way talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Emphasis on Race Hurts Efforts to Reform Municipal Courts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/08/how-race-hurts-efforts-to-reform-municipal-courts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 22:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/08/how-race-hurts-efforts-to-reform-municipal-courts/</guid>
      <description>My story on the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s Ferguson report addressed race early. .
So let&amp;rsquo;s have a little blunt talk about race from a West County white guy&amp;rsquo;s point of view (which is alway helpful).
Faction A and Faction B Whenever race comes up, two large factions shut down. They shut down intellectually because &amp;lsquo;race&amp;rsquo; touches an irrational, emotional nerve.
Faction A views every issue as a race problem. They see rain at a picnic as racist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Do With the DOJ Report on Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/what-to-do-with-the-doj-report-on-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 17:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/what-to-do-with-the-doj-report-on-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>The will of man is not shattered, but softened, bent, and guided; men are seldom forced by it to act, but they are constantly restrained from acting. Such a power does not destroy, but it prevents existence; it does not tyrannize, but it compresses, enervates, extinguishes, and stupefies a people, till each nation is reduced to nothing better than a flock of timid and industrious animals, of which the government is the shepherd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/02/doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 22:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/02/doing/</guid>
      <description>Ben Evans worked hard to host a joint event with St. Louis Tea Party Coalition and Heritage Foundation a couple years ago.
Because of Ben&amp;rsquo;s hard work, we met Dottie.
Then the trouble in Ferguson happened last August. Fearless Dottie joined our band of BUYcotters who went to Ferguson to shop while the city still smoldered.
We met Dellena.
Dottie cultivated a relationship with Dellena.
Saturday, February 28, Dellena hosted Level One training in Self-Governance at her 911 Beauty Salon on W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Police Officers Like Writing Tickets?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/14/police-officers-like-writing-tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 22:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/14/police-officers-like-writing-tickets/</guid>
      <description>[audio mp3=&amp;quot;https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/do-police-like-ticket-quotas.mp3&amp;rdquo;][/audio]
What do police officer think about traffic ticket quotas? Here&amp;rsquo;s one officer&amp;rsquo;s thoughts:
 In my agency, those of us in patrol had to keep a &amp;ldquo;Daily.&amp;rdquo; This would be a formal document that showed the times, addresses where we went, written in code, of what we had done.
 On the back were boxes for how many traffic citations, criminal citations, parking citations and felony and misdemeanor arrests we had made on that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What No One Tells You About Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/13/no-one-tells-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2014 22:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/13/no-one-tells-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s something happening here But what it is ain&amp;rsquo;t exactly clear There&amp;rsquo;s a man with a gun over there Telling me I got to beware &amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;For What It&amp;rsquo;s Worth&amp;rdquo; by The Buffalo Springfield
 &amp;ldquo;This isn&amp;rsquo;t about Michael Brown.&amp;rdquo;
Those words popped out of my mouth as I watched the Sunday evening news with my dad. It was August 10.
Full-scale rioting hadn&amp;rsquo;t erupted, but the battle lines were drawn: police on one side, people, mostly young people, on the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Evidence Never Mattered</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/01/evidence-never-mattered/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 04:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/12/01/evidence-never-mattered/</guid>
      <description>The danger of jumping to conclusions isn’t that you might be wrong. It’s that your brain will be unable to recognize its error.
We’ve all heard of the psychological (or just logical) fallacy of confirmation bias. It’s worth looking at three aspects of confirmation bias from Science Daily:
*1. In psychology and cognitive science, confirmation bias (or confirmatory bias) is a tendency to search for or interpret information in a way that confirms one&amp;rsquo;s preconceptions, leading to statistical errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Stop the Commies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/30/stop-commies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 04:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/30/stop-commies/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s all a lie.   It didn&amp;rsquo;t start that way. At first, the Mike Brown protesters were all about Mike Brown and people like him. But not anymore.
Even the New York Times admitted the protests in Mike Brown&amp;rsquo;s name are actually the Revolutionary Communist Party advancing Marxism. (The NYT pulled down the story on Sunday morning. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have linked it, anyway.)
I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of stomping on someone else&amp;rsquo;s parade, even if I disagree with their cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Ideas to Save Christmas in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 22:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/11/25/8-ideas-save-christmas-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>Nixon buck-passed while Ferguson burned. With the city’s main business district laid to rubble, buycotts won’t have much effect. And Christmas is around the corner.
Who got hurt last night?
*1. People who own businesses *2. People who work at businesses *3. People who rely on businesses
Time is short. The people affected by last night’s riots need help rebuilding and jobs right now. While I don’t have complete plans, I can throw out eight ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where I&#39;m Kicking Off My Ferguson BUYcott Saturday</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/29/im-kicking-ferguson-buycott-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 23:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/29/im-kicking-ferguson-buycott-saturday/</guid>
      <description>At 1:00 PM, I&amp;rsquo;ll be at 911 Beauty Salon: 9193 W Florissant Ave, St Louis, MO 63136, Cross Streets: Between Ferguson Ave and Canfield Dr. Let us knowyour story here. Upload photos, reciepts, and stories. People love stories.
You are welcome to join me there at 1:00, or shop and dine on your own.

This Ferguson BUYcott is getting massive national attention. Big thanks to everyone who took part last week and who&amp;rsquo;s joining in this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Ferguson and Dellwood This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 04:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/27/shop-ferguson-dellwood-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I&amp;rsquo;m so late on this. This sounds whiny, I know, but I have a really involved week at work this week. Sorry. Crap always seems to work out this way, though. When there&amp;rsquo;s a great need for Tea Party services, I&amp;rsquo;m tied up with work obligations. Something has to give, and it&amp;rsquo;s usually the thing that doesn&amp;rsquo;t generate revenue.
But we all have work to do. Ferguson businesses and families are still struggling with the effects of the riots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exposing the Race Hustlers in Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/25/exposing-race-hustlers-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 21:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/25/exposing-race-hustlers-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s an awesome YouTube video of Jesse Jackson getting skewered in Ferguson.
First, though, a little history.
One of the greatest books ever on race-based poverty and jobs programs is Tom Wolfe&amp;rsquo;s Mau-Mauing the Flak-Catchers. You won&amp;rsquo;t understand race politics in America without reading it. Twice. Four times, maybe.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve read it, you know why Jesse Jackson and Capt. Ron Johnson and all the other &amp;ldquo;black leaders&amp;rdquo; are impotent to stop riots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Jay Nixon Lost the Liberal Press</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/24/jay-nixon-lost-liberal-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 21:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/24/jay-nixon-lost-liberal-press/</guid>
      <description>“And then say what? say, ‘forget you’re hungry, forget you got shot inna back by some racist cop—Chuck was here? Chuck come up to Harlem—’ ”“No, I’ll tell you what—” “‘Chuck come up to Harlem and—’ ”“I’ll tell you what—” “Say,‘Chuck come up to Harlem and gonna take care a business for the black community’?” That does it. Heh-heggggggggggggggggghhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! It’s one of those ungodly contralto cackles somewhere out there in the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**DOH!** ACTION: Tell Missouri Legislature Jay Nixon to Pass Tax Holiday for Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 20:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/23/action-tell-missouri-legislature-pass-tax-holiday-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>****UPDATE
Tim Jones let me know that I&amp;rsquo;m giving the legislature more power than it actually has.
Veto sessions are limited to overriding vetos. Thus the name. BUT the governor can call a Special Session to vote on a Ferguson Tax Holiday. That session can run concurrent with the Veto Session, saving taxpayer dollars.
SO &amp;gt; &amp;gt; &amp;gt; New Action: Ask Jay Nixon (via Twitter and Facebook) to call a Special Session concurrent with the Veto Session to create a Tax Holiday for Ferguson/Dellwood.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>