<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Milton Friedman on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/milton-friedman/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Milton Friedman on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 10:55:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/milton-friedman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Buckley vs. Friedman on Service-Part 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 10:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</guid>
      <description>This is part 2 of a series on national service and the Franklin Project. Read part 1 here.
First, answer this for yourself: would you vote for William F. Buckley Jr?
Milton Friedman on National Service My friend Lloyd Sloan points out that Milton Friedman disagreed with Buckley’s call for national service. It seems appropriate, then, to view the idea of a service ethos through the eyes of two champions of conservatism of the 20th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Companies Should Adopt Conscious Capitalism Because It Pays</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/27/companies-adopt-conscious-capitalism-pays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 04:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/01/27/companies-adopt-conscious-capitalism-pays/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re going to hit me with the small sample size argument here, but that&amp;rsquo;s okay.
I firmly believe that the purpose of a company is to make life better, and if it does that well, it will make a profit. If, on the other hand, a company makes life worse, the market should let that company die.
Some companies try to improve life with insanely great technology products. Some make life better with fast, safe cars that are fun to drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conscious Capitalism:The One Book Every Conservative Must Read</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/26/heres-the-one-book-every-conservative-must-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/26/heres-the-one-book-every-conservative-must-read/</guid>
      <description>The motivating force behind the first tea party protests of February 27, 2009, was , in part, crony capitalism. Across the country and on the steps of the Arch in St. Louis, signs and speakers denounced bailouts for failed businesses.
Rasmussen found that 68 percent of Americans believe Big Business and Big Government work together against the rest of us.
I think they’re right.
Since then, crony capitalism has only grown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Learned from Milton Friedman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/26/what-we-learned-from-milton-friedman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/26/what-we-learned-from-milton-friedman/</guid>
      <description>I am a big fan of Milton Friedman. I’m also becoming a big fan of Creating Shared Value. Some believe the two values are inconsistent, but I disagree.
In 2005, Reason Magazine posted an online debate between Friedman and Whole Foods Market CEO John Mackey. The debate coincided with the 35th anniversary of Friedmans’ famous The New York Times Magazine article entitled: : &amp;ldquo;The Social Responsibility of Business Is to Increase Its Profits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>