<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AGW on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/agw/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AGW on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 17:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/agw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The UN Game</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/the-climate-agreement-from-game-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 17:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/13/the-climate-agreement-from-game-theory/</guid>
      <description>The UN is a game with many players.
The UN makes money by convincing member nations that the costs of funding the UN are less than the costs of not funding it.
The UN wants to grow as large as possible, like any organization or organism or rear end.
The UN is already very large. Its last budget was $5.4 billion, and that represented a 2.9 percent reduction from the previous two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Weinstein and His Call to Jail Global Warming Skeptics</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Yet, in holding scientific research and discovery in respect, as we should, we must also be alert to the equal and opposite danger that public policy could itself become the captive of a scientific-technological elite.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ndash;President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Farewell Address, 1961
A young man named Adam Weinstein recently called for incarceration of disbelievers in the cult of catastrophic anthropogenic global warming (CAGW). His argument mirrors the argument Goebbels used in 1930s to quash dissent from eugenics and to take immediate policy actions for the betterment of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Climate Scientists Aren’t Telling You About Global Warming</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/10/what-climate-scientists-arent-telling-you-about-global-warming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/10/what-climate-scientists-arent-telling-you-about-global-warming/</guid>
      <description>Allan Savory caused the slaughter of 40,000 elephants in a vain attempt to save the planet by stopping desertification.
It turns out that he succeeded only in turning lush grasslands into desert. And, of course, killing 40,000 elephants.
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;1134&amp;rdquo;] Biologist Allan Savory lobbied for the slaughter of 40,000 elephants in a vain attempt to save grasslands. Instead, the grasslands died even faster. Savory devoted his life to finding out why he and other scientists were so wrong about desertification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Hansen Lies and Defrauds Even More</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/29/james-hansen-lies-and-defrauds-even-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 14:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/29/james-hansen-lies-and-defrauds-even-more/</guid>
      <description>Watts Up With That has a graph illustrating the ridiculous extent to which James Hansen has gone to perpetuate his global warming myth. Hansen has rewritten US temperature data of the past 2 centuries&amp;ndash;as if he was there.
It&amp;rsquo;s time for NASA to fire Hansen. The DOJ should open a fraud investigation.
Link: https://wattsupwiththat.com/2009/06/28/nasa-giss-adjustments-galore-rewriting-climate-history/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As the World Cools</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/02/as-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/02/as-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Two quick global warming notes.
Arctic Sea Ice Extend Growing
Not too long ago, Al Gore told German school kids that the North Pole, Santa, Polar Bears, and puppies would all be dead and rotting hunks of diseased fleshed in barren, desserts that were once the Arctic Sea by the time they entered high school. Turns out that the Arctic Sea Ice Extent for 2007-08 and 2008-09 is pretty much in the average for entire history of measured sea ice extent (1979 to present).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooling Planet Escalates Global Warming Hysteria</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/27/cooling-planet-escalates-global-warming-hysteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 15:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/27/cooling-planet-escalates-global-warming-hysteria/</guid>
      <description>The increased urgency to legislate or judicially impose new, draconian burdens on society to &amp;ldquo;save the planet&amp;rdquo; is not your imagination. Neither is it a response to increasingly rising temperatures. Temperatures have been falling for 8 years now, and have not risen in more than 10. The reason the AGW alarmists need to impose restrictions is: credit. Remember the ozone holes? According to leftists, the holes were caused by chloroflourocarbons like refrigerant used in air conditioning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Superior Freezing Over</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/27/lake-superior-freezing-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 15:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/27/lake-superior-freezing-over/</guid>
      <description>Even as CO2 levels rise, western Lake Superior is freezing over for the first time years.
 The western tip of Lake Superior has frozen over in December for the first time in recent memory, and that could mean a long season of ice angling that hasn’t been seen in years.
 “We were just talking that it’s been something like 17 years since we had a good, long ice fishing season at this corner of Lake Superior,’’ said Russ Francisco, owner of Marine General sporting goods store in Duluth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Video of 2008</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/25/best-video-of-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 04:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/25/best-video-of-2008/</guid>
      <description>OMG, this is golden: [youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JmPSUMBrJoI&amp;amp;w;=425&amp;amp;h;=344]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>