<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foreign Relations on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/foreign-relations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foreign Relations on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 02:01:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/foreign-relations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UN Security Council Ignores Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/un-security-council-ignores-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 02:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/un-security-council-ignores-obama/</guid>
      <description>Jimmy Carter was the Rodney Dangerfield of international politics: he got no respect from the people who counted. The bad guys laughed at him. The bad guys must be rolling on the floor tonight.
Rogue Leaders Respect Nothing But Strength
Almost simultaneous with North Korea&amp;rsquo;s launching an ICBM in violation of international law and in defiance of US warnings, Barack Obama stood before the world and declared his intention to disarm the arsenal for democracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America’s Survival Is In Your Hands</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/25/americas-survival-is-in-your-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 23:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/25/americas-survival-is-in-your-hands/</guid>
      <description>Are you as amazed as I am at how quickly our country has descended into something resembling an oversized banana republic? Consider:
* [Gangs of thugs](https://michellemalkin.com/2009/03/25/the-rule-of-the-mob/) freely harass and intimidate AIG employees out of murderous envy** The Obama administration announced its willingness to [abandon the US dollar](https://www.bloomberg.com/apps/news?pid=20601087&amp;amp;sid=aqDuKEqQn39I&amp;amp;refer=home) as the international reserve currency** The administration shows no willingness to check [China’s menacing military](https://rds.yahoo.com/_ylt=A0WTTkuqvspJpXkAAwjQtDMD;_ylu=X3oDMTBjMHZkMjZyBHBvcwMxBHNlYwNzcg--/SIG=13lepic2b/EXP=1238110250/**http%3a//www.cnn.com/2009/WORLD/asiapcf/03/25/china.military.report/index.html%3fsection=cnn_latest) build-up, even though the Pentagon issued a warning just today** Secretary of State Clinton went to Mexico to [denounce the US](https://news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, Obama and his secretaries really are idiots</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/19/yes-obama-and-his-secretaries-really-are-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 03:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/19/yes-obama-and-his-secretaries-really-are-idiots/</guid>
      <description>The new Secretary of Homeland Security has replaced the word &amp;ldquo;terrorism&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;man-caused disasters.&amp;rdquo;
 I did not use the word &amp;ldquo;terrorism,&amp;rdquo; I referred to &amp;ldquo;man-caused&amp;rdquo; disasters. That is perhaps only a nuance, but it demonstrates that we want to move away from the politics of fear toward a policy of being prepared for all risks that can occur.
 I assume that appointing an idiot like Napolitano to the cabinet qualifies as a man-cause disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama invites enemies to our gates</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/15/obama-invites-enemies-to-our-gates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2009 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/15/obama-invites-enemies-to-our-gates/</guid>
      <description>Since Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s inauguration, America&amp;rsquo;s enemies have achieved gains that should frighten everyone: * Russia reportedly will deploy strategic bombers to Cuba and Venezuela. For the first time, Russia can strike American cities from advanced positions without a carrier battle group. * North Korea will soon test-fire a ballistic missile under the thin veil of &amp;ldquo;satellite&amp;rdquo; test * Iran has or will have 4 nuclear weapons with capabilities of hitting Israel from land and the US from sea * Pakistan is growing more violent * Pentagon facing 10 percent budget cut while admitting 2-war strategies isn&amp;rsquo;t enough wars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel Continues Assault on Terrorists</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/israel-continues-assault-on-terrorists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 13:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/israel-continues-assault-on-terrorists/</guid>
      <description>Israel&amp;rsquo;s assault on Hamas terrorists in Gaza continued for a second day. As if reading from a script, the UN Security Council called for an immediate stop to Israel&amp;rsquo;s self-defense. As the air strikes continued, Israel has moved more troops and tanks to the border, possibly in preparation for an incursion into the area now under terrorist control.
Some internation responses were less than predictable, though. France, for instance, demands first that the terrorists stop pitching rockets at Israeli school kids, then that Israel stop its air assault.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retaliation in Gaza</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/27/retaliation-in-gaza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 14:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/27/retaliation-in-gaza/</guid>
      <description>The most important fact in this story: retaliation.
Israel attacked dozens of terrorist targets in Gaza today, killing at least 145.
The Arab world (yawn) reacted predictably, condemning Israel (yawn) and staging street protests (yawn). I&amp;rsquo;m sure many a rifle was fired into the air.
The left&amp;ndash;and I suspect Barack Obama is included&amp;ndash;will decry Israel&amp;rsquo;s self-defense. They will call for Israel to show restraint. They will call on Israel to take another body blow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Get Feeling That Israel&#39;s Toast</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/03/you-get-feeling-that-israels-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 12:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/03/you-get-feeling-that-israels-toast/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama has a lot of friends who would like to see a Final Solution to the Middle East, if you get my drift. Samantha Power, for instance, told the Institute for Policy Studies (which was founded by the KGB during the Cold War) that the US should invade Israel and set up a puppet government to impose a suicidal deal with Hamas. Nice, huh?
Add to that a mounting certainty that Iran will deploy a nuclear weapon by the end of 2009&amp;ndash;a year Obama must devote almost solely to the economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mumbai Thoughts: Is This Prep for USA Siege?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/27/mumbai-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 02:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/27/mumbai-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Is Mumbai a test run for an attack on the United States?
 Al Qaeda is out of practice. The terror organization has been quite since 2001, pinned down inside in Iraq where our heroes destroyed their efforts to establish a beach head.
The coincidence of the horror in Mumbai with the FBI reports of a serious, legitimate threat to the NYC subway system seems coordinated to me.
Since 9-11, the US, UK, and Israel have trained and developed anti-terrorism techniques jointly with many nations, including India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mumbai Massacre Real-time on Twitter *UPDATES*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/27/mumbai-massacre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 02:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/27/mumbai-massacre/</guid>
      <description>Vietnam was the first televised war. Film from the morning was flown one-stop to California allowing Americans to witness action within 24 hours of its occurrence.
The Gulf War upped the ante with live, streaming video, 24 hours a day on CNN.
September 11 and the liberation of Iraq came with live blogging from people feet from the action.
But reading text messages on Twitter from people on the streets of Mumbai as events unfold is truly bizarre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Attacks Syria--About F&#39;ing Time</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/26/us-attacks-syria-about-fing-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/26/us-attacks-syria-about-fing-time/</guid>
      <description>The US launched an attack against terrorists inside Syria, killing at least eight deserving sons of bitches.
 Ninety percent of foreign fighters enter Iraq through Syria, according to U.S. intelligence estimates. Foreign fighters often enter Iraq in order to bring cash to Al Qaeda in Iraq&amp;rsquo;s chief. They also are deadly &amp;ndash; trained in bomb-making and willing to sacrifice themselves in suicide attacks.
 Syria has permitted terrorists to stage attacks against American in Iraq for five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia Vows Pullout as Troops Dig In - washingtonpost.com</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/17/russia-vows-pullout-as-troops-dig-in-washingtonpostcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 03:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/17/russia-vows-pullout-as-troops-dig-in-washingtonpostcom/</guid>
      <description>Maybe I didn&amp;rsquo;t overreact last week. According to the Washington Post on the scene in Gori, Republic of Georgia, Soviet Russian troops are &amp;ldquo;digging&amp;rdquo; for a long offensive or occupation:
 Russia pledged Sunday to begin removing its troops from Georgia on Monday, but the streets of this occupied city reflected a broadening, not a waning, of Russia&amp;rsquo;s military incursion.
 . . .
During a reporter&amp;rsquo;s 24-hour stay in the city this weekend, Russian soldiers roamed the streets in armored personnel carriers and waved Kalashnikov rifles to prevent entry to a captured Georgian military base that is now the Russian headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia v. Georgia:  McCain Was Right, Obama Was Everywhere</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/17/russia-v-georgia-mccain-was-right-obama-was-everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/17/russia-v-georgia-mccain-was-right-obama-was-everywhere/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve had a week to look at our two presidential candidates&amp;rsquo; handling of the largest foreign policy incident so far this campaign. In this crisis, we saw the difference between a strong man and an insecure boy.
John McCain, who warned us a long time ago that President Bush&amp;rsquo;s evaluation of Putin was naive, called the matter right from the start, according Jim Wooten in the Atlanta Journal-Constitution. McCain, who once said that he looked into Putin&amp;rsquo;s eyes and saw &amp;ldquo;a &amp;lsquo;K&amp;rsquo;, a &amp;lsquo;G&amp;rsquo;, and a &amp;lsquo;B&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rdquo; held one, single, defining position throughout the crisis:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brink of World War **UPDATES**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/11/brink-of-world-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 03:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/11/brink-of-world-war/</guid>
      <description>Am I the only person who sees that we are on the brink of world war thanks to those Russian sonsofbitches?
 Russian forces swept across Georgia on Monday, capturing the town of Gori and moving to within 35 miles of the capital city Tbilisi, FOX News confirmed.
 This is very serious stuff. Russia&amp;rsquo;s expansionist intentions are as obvious as they were in the Prague Spring and the Hungarian Revolt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s 180 on Troops in Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/27/obamas-180-on-troops-in-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 10:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/27/obamas-180-on-troops-in-iraq/</guid>
      <description>The boy-candidate has changed his mind again. For the second third fourth umpteenth time in a week, Barack Obama has shifted his view of how long American forces must stay in Iraq. His latest position &amp;ldquo;articulated&amp;rdquo; Saturday in an interview with Newsweek parrots the long-held positions of the Bush administration and of rival John McCain: forever.
 U.S. Democratic presidential candidate Barack Obama said in an interview published on Saturday the size of a residual U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Shipley Dispenses With Objectivity</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/21/david-shipley-dispenses-with-objectivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 02:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/21/david-shipley-dispenses-with-objectivity/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, the New York Times refused to publish an op-ed piece by Republican nominee John McCain (FoxNews.com). This might be the first time in American history that a newspaper turned down a column by a presidential candidate from a major party. According to Jonathan Martin of Politico, the Times demanded that McCain include &amp;ldquo;timetables&amp;rdquo; for withdrawal if he wants NYT inches. This also demonstrates why liberalism is incompatible with democracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch Iran&#39;s Navy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/01/03/watch-irans-navy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 03:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/01/03/watch-irans-navy/</guid>
      <description>Iran commissioned a stealth attack submarine on November 28, adding a dangerous and potentially destabilizing weapon to its aggressive arsenal. Built with Russian help, the Ghadir is capable of launching torpedoes and missiles simultaneously.
Perhaps Iran has suspended its nuke program. Perhaps not. An advanced sub patrolling the Med in the hands of Iranian nuts is bad news for that part of the world.
Makes me wish I was still in our submarine force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GOP Horse Race</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/29/the-gop-horse-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2007 17:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/29/the-gop-horse-race/</guid>
      <description>Mike Huckabee&amp;rsquo;s recent ascent through the polls is about to reverse itself. Looking through RealClearPolitics news stories and polls, I saw a pattern:
 * Huckabee says something stupid * Romney fires off attack ads on Huckabee * Huckabee makes something up that might not be true * Romney fires off attack ads on Huckabee * Huckabee attacks Romney&#39;s ads * Repeat until sick  Let&amp;rsquo;s assume that people in Iowa, New Hampshire, Michigan, and the Palmetto State are not sadists who pick a candidate based primarily upon his or her ability to insult and impugn opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huckabee Slammed By Senior Aide</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/28/huckabee-slammed-by-senior-aide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 23:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/28/huckabee-slammed-by-senior-aide/</guid>
      <description>From CNN:
 A senior aide to Republican presidential candidate Mike Huckabee admitted Friday that the former Arkansas governor had &amp;ldquo;no foreign policy credentials&amp;rdquo; after his comments reacting to the assassination of former Pakistani Prime Minister Benazir Bhutto raised questions.
 When a candidate&amp;rsquo;s senior aide admits the candidate knows nothing about the world beyond Arkansas, USA, the voters must take the aide seriously. A vote for Huckabee might be more un-American than a vote for a Democrat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Prove Incapable . . . Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/28/democrats-prove-incapable-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 18:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/28/democrats-prove-incapable-again/</guid>
      <description>The two leading Democrat contenders for president took time out from their campaigns, yesterday, using Benazir Bhutto&amp;rsquo;s assassination to demonstrate their utter incapability and unpreparedness to lead the world&amp;rsquo;s last remaining superpower.
Obama
Barrack Obama&amp;rsquo;s team blamed the United States, George Bush, and everyone who supported the Iraq War for Bhutto&amp;rsquo;s assassination. In other words, like the child he is, Obama blamed everyone but himself.
Clinton
Our friend Gateway Pundit points out that Hillary&amp;rsquo;s soliloquy on Bhutto centered on the Senators long, close, personal relationship with Bhutto that lasted a dozen years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Combat Surge With Propaganda Campaign</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/26/democrats-combat-surge-with-propaganda-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 11:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/26/democrats-combat-surge-with-propaganda-campaign/</guid>
      <description>Just a few days, other bloggers (Captain Ed) and I speculated on the ramifications on Democrat surrender strategies of the increasingly obvious improvements in Iraq since the surge began. Ever the WaPo worried about how the Dems would deal.
Now we know: propaganda.
Following the phony story that Gen. Pace would urge the President to cut troops in Iraq by half, the Red Crescent, today, released a report that a record number of Iraqis have fled their homes in fear of their lives since the surge began.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pace Pullout Talk Pack of Lies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/26/pace-pullout-talk-pack-of-lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 11:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/26/pace-pullout-talk-pack-of-lies/</guid>
      <description>For a couple of days, the wingnuts have been ecstatic over a story that Joint Chiefs of Staff Chairman Peter Pace would tell President Bush to cut Iraqi troop strength in half. I first heard the story on CBS Radio News Friday morning on my way to work. TheLA Times, quoting anonymous Pentagon and Administration officials, printed the the story in its Friday edition.
But the story was a fabrication, likely designed to quell the growing support for the war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Changing Tune on Iraq/Pullout</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/22/democrats-changing-tune-on-iraqpullout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 00:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/22/democrats-changing-tune-on-iraqpullout/</guid>
      <description>It started in July with polls showing Americans were increasingly supportive of the war in Iraq. Then, the President&amp;rsquo;s approval rating began to climb. Then Congress&amp;rsquo;s approval rating fell to an all-time low. In between, the odd Democrat Congressman or analyst returned from Iraq saying good things, not bad, about the effect of the troop surge.
With thanks to the California Conservative and Captain Ed for finding this story, we find that the Washington Post is reporting that the Democrats are forced to shift their policy on Iraq because of the undeniable success of the surge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinton on Iraq:  Victory is Not an Option</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/21/clinton-on-iraq-victory-is-not-an-option/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2007 04:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/21/clinton-on-iraq-victory-is-not-an-option/</guid>
      <description>St. Louis, MO&amp;ndash;Campaiging in Mooseknuckles, MO, today, Democrat Hillary Clinton gave supporters her strongest argument to date for an immediate, unconditional pull-out from Iraq.
&amp;ldquo;You read the news,&amp;rdquo; she shrilled to the largely silent crowd. &amp;ldquo;You read the reports the coming out of Iraq. You know what&amp;rsquo;s happened during George Bush&amp;rsquo;s war!&amp;rdquo;
The audience&amp;rsquo;s polite but blank silence indicated that they didn&amp;rsquo;t.
&amp;ldquo;You have seen Senator Durbin and several Brookings Institute scholars report from the field that the surge is pushing back the insurgents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to Take Down Iran</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/time-to-take-down-iran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2007 02:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/time-to-take-down-iran/</guid>
      <description>I was lying in the bathtub after a rare Sunday afternoon football practice when the Big Red post-game show was interrupted:
 We interrupt this program for a CBS Radio News special report.  I&amp;rsquo;m Morton Dean. The US State Department has announced that a group of students under control of the Ayatollah Khomeini of Iran have siezed the American Embassy in Tehran, taking more than 100 Americans hostage.
or something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where I stand on Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/where-i-stand-on-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2007 20:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/where-i-stand-on-iraq/</guid>
      <description>I stand for total victory in Iraq.
Background Some say that I blindly support President Bush and everything he does. I do not. Nor do I publicly lambaste his missteps the way others, like Peggy Noonan, do. This blog, I hope, will explain to my readers and friends how I can hold several seemingly incongruous positions on Bush and the War.
 * The United States, the free world, in fact, was justified in invading Iraq and overthrowing Saddam * The war in Iraq was not successful in its early days despite the perception of a rout * The administration&#39;s greatest failure was kowtowing to the left * The symptom of that kowtowing was establishing a defensive posture instead of continuing the attack * Donald Rumsfeld failed the President by refusing to return to an offensive strategy * The key to victory is ruthless aggression * Republicans should limit criticism of Bush to recommendations that will achieve victory  Justification Following 9/11, President Bush told Peggy Noonan in a private meeting that every night he goes to bed expecting to be woken and told that Saddam has unleashed a WMD in America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iranians in Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/iranians-in-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2007 17:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/19/iranians-in-iraq/</guid>
      <description>Apparently, an Iranian army special forces unit is in Iraq training Shiite militias on the more effective methods of killing Americans. You&amp;rsquo;ll be pleased to know that the US is &amp;ldquo;tracking&amp;rdquo; them.
My question is, Why aren&amp;rsquo;t we killing them? The Kurds are, according this story at Gateway Pundit.
They are enemy combatants in an American occupation zone. We need answer to no one for eliminating this problem.
This points to my whole problem with the way the Bush administration has handled Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haditha Marines Vindicated</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/10/haditha-marines-vindicated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2007 04:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/10/haditha-marines-vindicated/</guid>
      <description>The three Marines who were charged and cleared of murdering civilians in Iraq became the poster children for Jack Murtha&amp;rsquo;s attempts to destroy the U.S. Marine Corps. (I have no doubt that Murtha drank of Ho Chi Minh&amp;rsquo;s kool-aid in Viet Nam.) Murtha&amp;rsquo;s lies, smears, libels, and slanders launched an anti-American industry that just held its Yearly Kos nightmare in Chicago.
The Marines libeled by Murtha and others are free, now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Left&#39;s Foreign Policy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/10/the-lefts-foreign-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2007 13:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/10/the-lefts-foreign-policy/</guid>
      <description>The left&amp;rsquo;s foreign policy is both domestic and global.
John Hawkins, in Right Wing News&amp;rsquo;s Q&amp;amp;A, responds to a question posed by RtWingNutCase, to wit: should the US pull out of Iraq prematurely, would the left turn its activism toward influencing a withdrawal from Afghanistan?
Hawkins correctly says, &amp;ldquo;Yes,&amp;rdquo; but he stops short of speculating on motives. I won&amp;rsquo;t.
The left&amp;rsquo;s motive in withdrawing from the world is to weaken America and the West.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bush&#39;s Popularity Linked to War&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/09/bushs-popularity-linked-to-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2007 23:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/09/bushs-popularity-linked-to-wars/</guid>
      <description>Over the past two or three weeks, several polls have shown increased support for the war in Iraq. Now, we see that President Bush&amp;rsquo;s poll numbers are up.
 * AP/IPSOS poll shows Bush&#39;s favorability up to 31 percent in July from 28 in June	* CBS/NYT found that 42 percent now consider the war in Iraq &amp;quot;the right thing to do&amp;quot;[FoxNews.com ](https://www.foxnews.com/story/0,2933,292709,00.html)a longer list of the small victories President Bush and the Pentagon have achieved in Iraq and with the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mullah Cirac Leads Me To A Great Post</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/07/mullah-cirac-leads-me-to-a-great-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2007 06:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/07/mullah-cirac-leads-me-to-a-great-post/</guid>
      <description>Someone calling himself Mullah Cirac posted a comment to an earlier post on the growing popularity of the war in Iraq. I posted a long reply to the Mullah. Then I checked my comments meta to see if he left legit e-mail and website. I don&amp;rsquo;t know about the e-mail, but web url he claims as his belongs to a girl from Texas who might be able to kick Cirac&amp;rsquo;s unholy ass from Mecca to Odessa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Popularity Continues to Grow</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/06/war-popularity-continues-to-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2007 03:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/06/war-popularity-continues-to-grow/</guid>
      <description>The second poll in a week&amp;ndash;this one by USAToday/Gallup&amp;ndash;shows that support for the war in Iraq is growing. The latest poll shows that public perception of America&amp;rsquo;s success has increased substantially in the past month. The numbers coincide with the increasing effectiveness of the surge.
 In the latest USA TODAY/Gallup Poll, taken Friday through Sunday, the proportion of those who said the additional troops are &amp;ldquo;making the situation better&amp;rdquo; rose to 31% from 22% a month ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YearlyKos Review</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/05/yearlykos-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2007 16:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/05/yearlykos-review/</guid>
      <description>The YearlyKos could be the last hurrah of this new hard left, the way Woodstock was the final note of the song of the Sixties.
YearlyKos is a get-together of hard left bloggers organized by DailyKos founder Markos Moulitsas. DailyKos claimed, perhaps rightly, responsibility for the Democrat Congressional victory in 2006&amp;ndash;much the way Hammas might claim victory for blowing up an Israeli schoolhouse.
The Kos and Democratic Underground people who filled attendee list are the kind of folks who giggle at Dick Cheney&amp;rsquo;s heart problems, wish al Qaeda victory in its war against the West, and popped bottles of bubbly upon hearing of Chief Justice Roberts&amp;rsquo; seizure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ron Paul&#39;s Fifteen Minutes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/03/ron-pauls-fifteen-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2007 01:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/03/ron-pauls-fifteen-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Congressman Ron Paul (R-TX) generates more internet press than all the other candidates combined, it seems. His name has been on Technorati&amp;rsquo;s most-searched list for a couple weeks, rivaling Paris Hilton and YouTube for search popularity endurance. Whether or not his fledgling campaign for President will so endure is another matter.
Rummaging through the odd blog with a Ron Paul theme, I found some common characteristics among his supporters:
 * Young * Typically apolitical * Technology careers * Homosexual * Educated * Atheist * Decent writing skills * No particular axe to grind  I know many who fit the type, particularly working in the software industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Weird Chess Game</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/02/obamas-weird-chess-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2007 01:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/02/obamas-weird-chess-game/</guid>
      <description>Democrat candidate for president Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s bizarre chess game with foreign policy took another twist today.
In remarks to a report, Obama seemed to formulate his nuclear policy as he went along:
 &amp;ldquo;I think it would be a profound mistake for us to use nuclear weapons in any circumstance,&amp;rdquo; Obama said, with a pause, &amp;ldquo;involving civilians.&amp;rdquo; Then he quickly added, &amp;ldquo;Let me scratch that. There&amp;rsquo;s been no discussion of nuclear weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis-St. Paul Bridge Collapse</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/01/minneapolis-st-paul-bridge-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2007 03:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/01/minneapolis-st-paul-bridge-collapse/</guid>
      <description>_UPDATE and Bump: Predictably, the idiot left has begun blaming George W. Bush and the Iraq War on Terror for the bridge collapse (Gateway Pundit). They know they&amp;rsquo;re full of manure. Saturday, liberal Bob Beckel on FoxNews admitted that there was no connection, but he went to explain the liberal lies: &amp;ldquo;Those of us who are opposed to this war will anything to advance our point.&amp;rdquo; _
_It&amp;rsquo;s nice to hear a Democrat fess up to lying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Little Mind on Foreign Policy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/01/8099/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2007 22:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/01/8099/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama proves he would be a dangerous commander-in-chief.
Two weeks ago, he told us that the United States is obliged to stay out of wars, even to prevent genocide. He would not have fought Germany in World War II unless Germany attacked the United States. He would not stop the genocide in Darfur or Congo. He would not have gone to Somalia or Bosnia.
That, again, was two weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UN Approves Darfur Force</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/01/un-approves-darfur-force/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2007 07:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/01/un-approves-darfur-force/</guid>
      <description>The UN Security Council, today, finally got around to approving a 26,000-strong force to control the violence in Darfur (FoxNews.com).
I have a depressing suspicion that this means there are no Christians left for the Muslims to kill in Darfur. Expat Yank thinks the same:
 There are only two reasons a predator state engaged in fomenting widespread slaughter (the UN has not termed Darfur “genocide”) will voluntarily allow in a UN peacekeeping force: 1) that state has already accomplished most of its ”slaughter” goals (remember, this conflict began in February 2003), or 2) it doesn’t believe the UN force will be able to accomplish much of anything anyway, so its best to let it be deployed in order to get the “international community” off its back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Morning Hits</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/31/quick-morning-hits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2007 12:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/31/quick-morning-hits/</guid>
      <description>US Casualties in Iraq hit 8 month low (myway)
More Democrats say the surge is working (Captain&amp;rsquo;s Quarters)
So You Think You Can Dance an elaborate excuse for liberals to public hate the US Marine Corps (Michelle Malkin). I agree. Mia Michaels&amp;rsquo; apology was about as sincere as a toilet seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brookings Institute Says US Gaining in Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/30/brookings-institute-says-us-gaining-in-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2007 02:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/30/brookings-institute-says-us-gaining-in-iraq/</guid>
      <description>The headline would have read, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re Gaining in Iraq,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to confuse any liberals for whom the &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; in Iraq is al Qaeda.
The surge is working according two liberals from the Brookings Institute writing in the New York Times. And according to Dean Barnett blogging on HughHewitt.townhall.com, their former friends on the left are ready to do to them what it appears Chuck Schumer did to the Chief Justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New UK PM Praises, Thanks Bush</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/29/new-uk-pm-praises-thanks-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 06:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/29/new-uk-pm-praises-thanks-bush/</guid>
      <description>The Sun Online carries the story of new British Prime Minister Gordon Brown&amp;rsquo;s rather effusive praise of George W. Bush&amp;rsquo;s leadership.
In his speech, Brown referred to Winston Churchill:
   The Prime Minister vowed to take Winston Churchill’s lead and make Britain’s ties with America even stronger.
  Mr Brown stunned critics by THANKING President Bush for the fight against Islamic extremism, and insisted the UK-US relationship will be his No1 foreign policy priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bad Day for Democrats -- and Terrorists</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/a-bad-day-for-democrats-and-terrorists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2007 22:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/26/a-bad-day-for-democrats-and-terrorists/</guid>
      <description>Gateway Pundit provides this top-shelf story of a US F-16 taking out 30 or so al Qaeda terrorists in Iraq. It&amp;rsquo;s a thing of beauty, and it must make Democrats sick to see their well-trained comrades die under American attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Al Qaeda&#39;s Base is Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/24/al-qaedas-base-is-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 04:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/24/al-qaedas-base-is-iraq/</guid>
      <description>The ultimate argument for winning the war in Iraq came down from W today. The Discerning Texan has done a superlative job of breaking it down for you, so I won&amp;rsquo;t even try.
We will win this thing, damn it. And we won&amp;rsquo;t damage the republic or the Republican Party in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Support For War Grows</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/23/american-support-for-war-grows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 23:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/23/american-support-for-war-grows/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times, believe it or not, has this story in its campaign blog:
Poll: American Support for War Inches Up The story cites an NYT/CBS Poll that showed America support for war in Iraq rose to 41% in July from 35% in May. You will not see this story on the CBS Evening News or on the front page of America&amp;rsquo;s most un-American paper, though. The results do not fit either organization&amp;rsquo;s political agenda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Al Qaeda Impotent?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/23/is-al-qaeda-impotent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/23/is-al-qaeda-impotent/</guid>
      <description>Captain Ed raises an interesting point in response to al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s declaration of war on North Africa
 Despite their general inability to prevail in Iraq, successfully detonate explosives in Britain, and do anything else in the US, AQ warned Muslims to stay away from their own government buildings on the south side of the Mediterranean
 He writes a good piece&amp;ndash;which reminded me of this humor entry I posted in 2003 and agian in 2005:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Hysterium</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/20/hillary-hysterium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2007 05:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/20/hillary-hysterium/</guid>
      <description>Senator Clinton asked the Pentagon to describe its plans to withdraw from Iraq. The Pentagon—specifically, undersecretary of defense, Eric Edelman—replied in the most appropriate manner imaginable:
 Premature and public discussion of the withdrawal of U.S. forces from Iraq reinforces enemy propaganda that the United States will abandon its allies in Iraq, much as we are perceived to have done in Vietnam, Lebanon and Somalia
 In response, Ms. Clinton displayed the kind of hysterium one associates with under-medicated paranoid schizophrenics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peggy Noonan: Turning Coats Softly With Her Song</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/17/peggy-noonan-turning-coats-softly-with-her-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2007 04:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/17/peggy-noonan-turning-coats-softly-with-her-song/</guid>
      <description>Peggy Noonan is a great ally and a doubtful foe. She turned, mildly, on Reagan. She has turned on Bush. So what. Her human insights are wonderful, her writing , usually, excellent. She is setting up her pick for 2008 awkwardly.
Bush supporters and detractors, alike, have made much of Ms. Noonan&amp;rsquo;s Friday Opinion Journal column about President Bush. As a fan Peggy&amp;rsquo;s, I was disappointed. One of the hallmarks of conservatism—something that should distinguish us from them—is that we don&amp;rsquo;t eat our own in public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grass is Greener on the Other Side of the Aisle</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/09/grass-is-greener-on-the-other-side-of-the-aisle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2007 09:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/09/grass-is-greener-on-the-other-side-of-the-aisle/</guid>
      <description>Congressional Democrats are finding leadership isn&amp;rsquo;t as fun as they thought it would be. With pressure for radical action mounting on the left, this fall could get ugly for Pelosi and Reid.
The Democrats of 2006 ran against Bush in contrast to the Republics of 1994 who ran on the Pledge with America. The result is that the current Congress sees only one duty: damage the President. That duty, unfortunately, appears nowhere in Article I of the Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannibalism on the Left</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/08/cannibalism-on-the-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 23:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/08/cannibalism-on-the-left/</guid>
      <description>The problem with elevating dim-witted self promoters to some contrived position of power, as the Dems are learning, is that they are never satisfied with the seat you give them.Â They want the big seat.Â They want to call the shots.
Cindy Sheehan, the woman who turned her heroic son&amp;rsquo;s death in Iraq into a national campaign of ego, says she&amp;rsquo;ll run against Nancy Polosi unless the House Speaker introduces articles of impeachment against the President within two weeks:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>William M. Arkin, RIP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/01/31/william-m-arkin-rip-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2007 03:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/01/31/william-m-arkin-rip-2/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps it would be best if Mr. Arkin, wearing a dingy t-shirt and stained khakis, locked himself into a small room lighted by a lone, unsheathed incandescent bulb strung from a wire, supplied with a bottle of store label whiskey and a loaded Browning 9mm semi-automatic pistol, drank the whiskey, cried apologies to his absent mother, and discharged a single, lethal round into his angry and imbalanced head, ending a life whose pinnacle was to anger men and women smarter, braver, and stronger than he.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>William M. Arkin, RIP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/01/31/william-m-arkin-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2007 03:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/01/31/william-m-arkin-rip/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps it would be best if Mr. Arkin, wearing a dingy t-shirt and stained khakis, locked himself into a small room lighted by a lone, unsheathed incandescent bulb strung from a wire, supplied with a bottle of store label whiskey and a loaded Browning 9mm semi-automatic pistol, drank the whiskey, cried apologies to his absent mother, and discharged a single, lethal round into his angry and imbalanced head, ending a life whose pinnacle was to anger men and women smarter, braver, and stronger than he.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Cheers for Maliki</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/01/06/three-cheers-for-maliki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2007 22:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/01/06/three-cheers-for-maliki/</guid>
      <description>Iraqi Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki told the world that his army, with American support, would soon secure Baghdad.Â Unlike previous such promises, this time he seems to mean it.
Already the Iraqi army has killed at least 30 deserving scum, and they&amp;rsquo;re looking for more.
 We are fully aware that implementing the plan will lead to some harassment for all beloved Baghdad residents, but we are confident they fully understand the brutal terrorist assault we all face,&amp;rdquo; he said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Oppose American Victory in Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/01/05/democrats-oppose-american-victory-in-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2007 01:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/01/05/democrats-oppose-american-victory-in-iraq/</guid>
      <description>**UPDATE Mark Noonan posits several critical questions for Pelosi and Reid.
 Last September, a group of St. Louis Cardinals fans would call local sports talk shows and say they hoped the team wouldn’t make the playoffs. They commented similar sentiments on various Cardinals forums and blogs. When the Cardinals lost a game, they’d gloat, making fun of the “kool-aid guzzlers” who wanted the team to make the playoffs. Claiming that losing was in the team’s best interest, they cheered for any team the Cardinals played, including the Chicago Cubs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYT Discovers Iraqi Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/17/nyt-discovers-iraqi-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2005 15:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/17/nyt-discovers-iraqi-election/</guid>
      <description>The December 15 Parliamentary election in Iraq was so overwhelmingly successful that it took the New York Times editorial writers two full days to find something nasty to say about it. Not wanting to hold the bad news for the story, the headline writer did his best to explain that the recent election was a non-story, proclaiming:
Iraq Votes for a Third Time
As if Iraq voting is as commonplace as Howard Dean embarrassing himself in public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Iraqi Surprises for the Left</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/15/more-iraqi-surprises-for-the-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2005 20:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/15/more-iraqi-surprises-for-the-left/</guid>
      <description>On Monday I blogged about the ABC News poll of Iraqis that surprised the left by its upbeat results. Seventy percent of Iraqis are opimistic and better off than a year ago.
Today, Jason on Countercolumn notices that the media are, once again, surprised&amp;ndash;this time because of the success of Iraqi parliamentary elections.
Obviously, the press is reading its own press. We on the right like claim the liberal media intentionally distorts the news to conform to its world view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Have Nothing to Say</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/13/i-have-nothing-to-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 05:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/13/i-have-nothing-to-say/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We knew,&amp;rdquo; you&amp;rsquo;re thinking.
Well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t. Not until tonight. I just read through half a dozen blogs, scanned or read 20 articles on MyWay.com news, and checked out all of the major network news websites.
I considered writing about thesilliness coming from Tookie Williams supporters. None of the stories I read quoted anyone who is unswervingly pro-life. No, the stories quoted people who think murderers are cool, but state laws that punish murderers with a taste of their own medicine are evil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iraq Strategy:  Vindicated</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/12/iraq-stategy-vindicated-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 13:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/12/iraq-stategy-vindicated-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week, a colleague commented that he only put credence into international polls. As if the poll gods were listening, today ABC News released the most affirming poll for President Bush&amp;rsquo;s Iraq strategy ever conducted.
It must have pained the ABC News editors to write such a glowing headline:
Poll: Broad Optimism in Iraq
So pained, in fact, that they felt compelled to immediately qualify that statement:
But Also Deep Divisions Among Groups</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saddam&#39;s Dream Team</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/06/saddams-dream-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2005 17:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/06/saddams-dream-team/</guid>
      <description>When your dream team defense includes the pro-Soviet, anti-American Ramsey Clark, you&amp;rsquo;re in deep trouble. Yesterday, Clark stormed out of the court room in an effort to undermine the trial, US foreign policy, and God Almighty, whom Clark seems to consider an underling. Today, he apparently advised his Hitleresque client to refuse to return to court. Saddam also told the judge to &amp;ldquo;go to hell,&amp;rdquo; according to FoxNews.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure where the Constitution and case law stand on this, but it seems fitting that Clark be denied reentry into the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Hate Howard Dean</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/05/i-hate-howard-dean/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2005 04:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/05/i-hate-howard-dean/</guid>
      <description>I know, I know. I pray for graces to overcome this weakness. But, God help me, I hate him so.
Click to see Howard Dean posing for Michelle Malkin&amp;rsquo;s camera.
In other Dean news, Howard Dean announced thathe is betting on the terrorists and against the US Military.
&amp;ldquo;As an American, I&amp;rsquo;d love to see the Army win. As a betting man, though, I have go with my gut. I&amp;rsquo;m putting all my bets on Al Qaeda in Iraq to win and the Sunnis to place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Home for Senator Kerry</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/05/a-new-home-for-senator-kerry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2005 18:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/12/05/a-new-home-for-senator-kerry/</guid>
      <description>Today I saw two Veterans for Kerry bumperstickers on my way to work. I wonder if the people who emblazoned their cars with those stickers are really veterans. If so, do they consider themselves terrorists? Their choice for CINC &amp;lsquo;04 does.
Yesterday on CBS&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Face the Nation,&amp;rdquo; Senator Kerry said
 And there is no reason, Bob, that young American soldiers need to be going into the homes of Iraqis in the dead of night, terrorizing kids and children, you know, women, breaking sort of the customs of the&amp;ndash;of&amp;ndash;the historical customs, religious customs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Political Failure</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/09/01/total-political-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2005 03:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/09/01/total-political-failure/</guid>
      <description>I know many will disagree with me, but must agree with Ron Fournier of the AP:
 At every turn, political leaders failed Katrina&amp;rsquo;s victims. They didn&amp;rsquo;t strengthen the levees. They ceded the streets to marauding looters. They left dead bodies to rot or bloat. Thousands suffered or died for lack of water, food and hope. Who&amp;rsquo;s at fault?
 There&amp;rsquo;s plenty of blame to go around - the White House, Congress, federal agencies, local governments, police and even residents of the Gulf Coast who refused orders to evacuate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Jennings:  RIP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/08/07/peter-jennings-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2005 05:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/08/07/peter-jennings-rip/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that I was only two when Peter Jennings became the anchor of ABC&amp;rsquo;s Nightly News. It was 1965, before the 60s began. Timothy Leary was still at Harvard, and Viet Nam was still an opportunity to thwart communism&amp;rsquo;s uholy advance.
Jennings didn&amp;rsquo;t last long. Berated by critics as a pretty face, ABC demoted him to foreign correspondent in 1968. In London, Munich, Brussels, and other foreign capitals, Jennings paid his dues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Stupid School Tricks</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/05/06/more-stupid-school-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2005 23:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/05/06/more-stupid-school-tricks/</guid>
      <description>A high school in Columbus, GA suspended a 17-year-old student for taking a cell phone call from his mother who is serving our country in Iraq.
 The confrontation Wednesday began after the 17-year-old junior got a call at lunchtime from his mother, Sgt. 1st Class Monique Bates, who left in January for a one-year tour with the 203rd Forward Support Battalion. (USAToday)
 Spencer High School pats itself on the back for not having the kid arrested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Send in the Pigs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/05/04/send-in-the-pigs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2005 21:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/05/04/send-in-the-pigs/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s clear, based on documents recently seized in Iraq, that the terrorists are down to their final shots. Because of this, they carry out daring attacks, like the one yesterday that killed 60.
Now is the time to send pig skins to Iraq with the promise that any terrorist&amp;ndash;captured or killed&amp;ndash;will be sewn into the animal&amp;rsquo;s skin and buried. This will go for the remains of suicide bombers as well as those killed in combat or captured and executed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethanol, Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/04/18/ethanol-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2005 02:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/04/18/ethanol-now/</guid>
      <description>Several St. Louis area gas stations are selling high-ethanol gasoline for $0.85 a gallon. That&amp;rsquo;s eighty-five cents a gallon. How can they sell this alternative to Saudi Arabian oil so cheaply? According to the AP
 Ethanol prices have declined sharply in recent months, largely because of the rapid growth in supply and few new markets. Shaw maintains that refiners are ignoring ethanol and keeping the additive out of some markets where it is readily available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help Prevent a Murder</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/26/help-prevent-a-murder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2005 06:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/26/help-prevent-a-murder/</guid>
      <description>At the behest of BlogsForTerri, here&amp;rsquo;s my e-mail to major media outlets informing them that the story of Terri&amp;rsquo;s plea to live is not new&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s been reported for a week.
The media are claiming that the Schindlers&amp;rsquo; lawyer first came up with the story of Terri&amp;rsquo;s words, &amp;ldquo;Aaah&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Waaahn&amp;rdquo; tonight. In fact, that story has been reported for a week. Please make sure your readers, listeners, and viewers understand this is an old story that the MSM ignored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enough Killing Already</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/25/enough-killing-already/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2005 03:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/25/enough-killing-already/</guid>
      <description>Robert of Hip-Hop Politics shares a sick but touching experience.
 But, when I saw these guys carried away on a strecher and saw his peoples crying, that just stuck. When I got home, I just broke down. I&amp;rsquo;ll admit it. I cried.
 With little girls dying, Terri Schiavo dying, people in Iraq dying, can&amp;rsquo;t we stop killing each other for Easter weekend?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seattle High School Anti-Military Day Follow-up Letter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/24/seattle-high-school-anti-military-day-follow-up-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 21:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/24/seattle-high-school-anti-military-day-follow-up-letter/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE SIGN OUR PETITION: Click Here.
We have been active indemanding action from the Seattle School Board over a disgusting political ambush of American service members last week.
Upon further review of theletters and e-mails issued by the Seattle School Board and Susan Derse, principal of West Seattle High School, I am determined to garner a more substantive response. Specifically, I expect every adult involved to apologize directly to the ambushed service member and to all members, veterans, and their families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Seattle High School Anti-Military Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/24/update-seattle-high-school-anti-military-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/24/update-seattle-high-school-anti-military-day/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE: Kimberly was kind enough to link to this entry, but no trackback posted. So check out Kimberly&amp;rsquo;s comments.
UPDATE: Michelle Malkin has discovered that Susan Derse has a history of anti-Military attitudes. Read her post. (Corrected Link)
Also LGF has printed the letters from the Principal, but not the one I received from the school board.
UPDATE: March 24 letter to the Seattle School Board demanding additional information and apologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Atlanta Killer and His Savior</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/15/the-atlanta-killer-and-his-savior/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2005 00:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/15/the-atlanta-killer-and-his-savior/</guid>
      <description>Being Catholic, I&amp;rsquo;m not big on deistic revelations. (Ironic that the parish I grew up in was The Epiphany, huh?) Still, I admit that the story of the Atlanta courthouse shooter has touched me.
Until today, I was more interested in the Wisconsin church shooting.
Then something happened.
About 11:30 I went out to smoke. I walked to my car, where I leave my cigarettes, and turned on the aux to listen to Rush.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirit of America Update</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/09/spirit-of-america-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2005 03:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/09/spirit-of-america-update/</guid>
      <description>This is an e-mail from Spirit of America. Please help the cause.
**ROCKIN THE CORPS - MARINES WELCOME HOME
**A nonprofit organization headed by Joe Robert is putting together a great welcome home party at Camp Pendleton no April 1 for Marines now returning from Iraq. This will be a terrific event to thank the Marines (and their families) who have been stationed mainly in Al Anbar province since last summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Senate Hypocrite In Trouble</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/08/another-senate-hypocrite-in-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2005 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/08/another-senate-hypocrite-in-trouble/</guid>
      <description>via Drudge
Senator John McCain, the Keating Five escapee who put his name on a bill intended to destroy the First Amendment, has been caught with his hand in the till.
According to theAssociated Press, one of the few organizations that stands to gain politically under McCain-Feingold, the Senator and former POW pressed for pricing changes on behalf of Cablevision while soliciting $200,000 from Cablevision for one of McCain&amp;rsquo;s tax-exempt political action committees, The Reform Institute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winning One for Democracy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/08/winning-one-for-democracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2005 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/08/winning-one-for-democracy/</guid>
      <description>Blogs for Bush
   &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;What&amp;rsquo;s taken place in a number of those countries is enormously constructive,&amp;rdquo; the Massachusetts Democrat said on the ABC news program &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;This Week.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a reflection the president has been involved.&amp;rdquo;
  The Massachusetts Democrat Matt Margolis refers to is none other than Ted Kennedy singing the praises of Bushs foreign policy in the Middle East.
Here was the same Teddy Kennedy just last summer while campaigning for John Kerry:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Byrd:  A History of Abusing Power</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/06/robert-byrd-a-history-of-abusing-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2005 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/06/robert-byrd-a-history-of-abusing-power/</guid>
      <description>This week, the blogosphere buzzed with reaction to Senator Robert &amp;ldquo;Grand Wizard&amp;rdquo; Byrd&amp;rsquo;s comparison of the Republican Senate leaders to Nazis. His Washington Post op-ed contains some of the most partisan and hate-inspiring language penned by a sitting Senator in modern times.
Some of the shock over Byrd&amp;rsquo;s incendiary comments may arise from the carefully managed but false image of Byrd. The mainstream press, liberal academicians, and historians have, for decades, portrayed Byrd as a kindly, intellectual defender of the Senate&amp;rsquo;s history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC:  Iraqis Turning Against Insurgents</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/06/msnbc-iraqis-turning-against-insurgents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2005 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/06/msnbc-iraqis-turning-against-insurgents/</guid>
      <description>This AP story on MSNBC report details the increasing anger against insurgents in Iraq. Even prominent Sunnis are jumping into the fray. I can hear this editorial meeting:
   EDITOR: Johnson, wuddah you got?
  JOHNSON: Well, chief, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a story about the Iraqi people turning agianst the insurgents . . .
  EDITOR: You mean turning against the US troops?
  JOHNSON: No, sir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Admits Democrats Pulling for Terrorists</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/05/democrat-admits-democrats-pulling-for-terrorists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2005 17:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/05/democrat-admits-democrats-pulling-for-terrorists/</guid>
      <description>Former Clinton White House aide Nancy Soderberg admitted on The Daily Show that she and other Democrats want Bush&amp;rsquo;s war against terrorism to fail.
NewsMax.com: Inside Cover Story
_After noting that the U.S.&amp;lsquo;s stunning foreign policy success followed the toppling of one of the three members of the axis of evil, Soderberg suggested again that the more success America has in defeating global terrorism, the worse it is for her party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uday Plotted Coup?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/04/uday-plotted-coup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2005 13:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/04/uday-plotted-coup/</guid>
      <description>According to Saddam Hussein&amp;rsquo;s personal MSM reporter, Peter Arnett, Uday Hussein was only days away from toppling his father when the US invaded the country.
Given Uday&amp;rsquo;s history of masochism, murder, rape, and mayhem, the Iraqi people are damn lucky the US showed up when it did. Here&amp;rsquo;s Wikipedia&amp;rsquo;s brief rundown of some of Uday&amp;rsquo;s more famous attrocities against humanity:
 As head of the Iraqi Olympic Committee, Uday oversaw the imprisonment and torture of Iraqi athletes who were deemed not to have performed to expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsweek Buys the Bush Doctrine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/03/newsweek-buys-the-bush-doctrine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2005 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/03/newsweek-buys-the-bush-doctrine/</guid>
      <description>Well, at least one of its more, shall we say, &amp;ldquo;anti-Bush&amp;rdquo; writers, Christopher Dickey. He sees a permanent, structural shift word democracy in the Middle East. &amp;ldquo;So, say the despots, this wave of rising expectations about freedom and democracy will pass. Theyve seen it all before,&amp;rdquo; writes Dickey. But this time, he senses something different.
        Well, not this time. The whole political environment has changed in the Middle East.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court and Death Penalty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/01/the-supreme-court-and-death-penalty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2005 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/01/the-supreme-court-and-death-penalty/</guid>
      <description>So, theSupremes peered into the US Constitution and found an entry regarding the age of criminal defendants and what punishments states may imposed thereon. I wish they would release the version of the Constitution which they read so we citizens, subject to the document as we are, may read it. Clearly, the one published in text books isn&amp;rsquo;t the one given the Supreme Court. Either that, or it reads differently under the magnification of their crystal ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Steyn on the Suicide of the West</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/23/mark-steyn-on-the-suicide-of-the-west/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2005 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/23/mark-steyn-on-the-suicide-of-the-west/</guid>
      <description>Dean Esmay hooked us up tothis fine column. As I commented on Dean&amp;rsquo;s blog, it reminds me of reading James Burnham&amp;rsquo;s masterpiece, Suicide of the West, in 1980. In the prologue, Burnham writes about looking over political maps of the world from ancient Egypt to the 20th century. He paints stark images of the West&amp;rsquo;s advances, eventually engulfing more than half the world. (Please don&amp;rsquo;t lecture me on the math.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Monkey with Good News</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/23/dont-monkey-with-good-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2005 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/23/dont-monkey-with-good-news/</guid>
      <description>Steven Taylor rightly predicts that today&amp;rsquo;s top story will be the Washington Post report that the White House redacted the whole of the report on Iraq&amp;rsquo;s economy from last week&amp;rsquo;s economic report.
The story claims that the good news about Iraq&amp;rsquo;s economy would be inappropriate at a time when so many security problems exist. That rings hollow. The President could use some good news in his European trip, and the whole world could use some good news about Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the 9/11 Commission Actually Said</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/23/what-the-911-commission-actually-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2005 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/23/what-the-911-commission-actually-said/</guid>
      <description>An argument with a gentleman whose blog is called HairyFishNuts.com pointed out the need to remind people what the 9/11 Commission said about Saddam&amp;rsquo;s ties to terrorism. To wit:
   Iraq under Saddam supported international terrorist organizations to bolster Iraq&amp;rsquo;s revolutionary credentials, ensure his own role as Great Arab leader, and intimidate rival governments. In examining the history, methods, and patterns of behavior of Saddam Husayn in supporting international terrorism, some &amp;ldquo;truths&amp;rdquo; stand out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peaceniks in St. Louis:  Much Ado About Nothing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/22/peaceniks-in-st-louis-much-ado-about-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2005 02:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/22/peaceniks-in-st-louis-much-ado-about-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Four hundred people representing more than 1,000 anti-war groups met in St. Louis, Missouri, over the weekend. The aim was to define a strategy to get the US out of Iraq before it turns into a success. Among the &amp;ldquo;luminaries&amp;rdquo; present: Danny Glover and Tom Hayden.
Fortunately for the causes of freedom, liberty, justice, and common sense, the assembled lefties spend so much time decrying the vote count in Ohio and Michael Crichton&amp;rsquo;s book, they ran out of time to produce a strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bush Shows He&#39;s a Diplomat</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/21/bush-shows-hes-a-diplomat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2005 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/21/bush-shows-hes-a-diplomat/</guid>
      <description>Newsday.com: Bush Suggests Chirac Is &amp;lsquo;Good Cowboy&amp;rsquo;
In his first European trip since re-election, President Bush displays remarkable statemanship.
Balancing between firmness and friendliness, the President places American interest first, yet he undeniably wins friends on every stop.
Sometimes, timing is everything, and the President dares to admit such:
_&amp;ldquo;This is the first dinner since I&amp;rsquo;ve been re-elected on European soil, and it&amp;rsquo;s with Jacques Chirac. And that ought to say something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-War Movement Hates US</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/21/anti-war-movement-hates-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2005 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/21/anti-war-movement-hates-us/</guid>
      <description>A Little More To The Right: Humor AND Opinion
https://www.alittlemoretotheright.com/journal/00002143.html
Anti-War lefties hang American Soldier in effigy. Good job, folks. That convinced me: Im wrong. Lets pull all of the troops out of Afghanistan and Iraq. South Korea, too. Life was so much better for those people without us. Except for the South Koreans, who would be so much better off with Kim Jong ILL as their slavemaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard Right Republicans For African-American Woman President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/21/hard-right-republicans-for-african-american-woman-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2005 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/21/hard-right-republicans-for-african-american-woman-president/</guid>
      <description>The American Thinker
   I am as pleased as anyone with Condoleezza Rices initial performance as Secretary of State. Shes a smart, articulate, passionate defender of America and George W. Bushs foreign policy vision. But all the excited talk about Condi for President is wildly premature, and even dangerous to the conservative cause.
 writes Steven M. Warshawsky on The American Thinker, February 15. Mr. Warshawsky goes on to list some pretty predictable problems with Condoleezza Rices White House credentials:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunter S. Thompson:  RIP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/21/hunter-s-thompson-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2005 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/21/hunter-s-thompson-rip/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We were somewhere around Barstow, on the edge of the dessert, when the drugs began to take hold.&amp;rdquo;
 That&amp;rsquo;s how begins the book that drove me to misspend a significant portion of my youth. I first read Fear And Loathing in Las Vegas in 1982 after graduating from high school. If marijuana is a gateway drug, it&amp;rsquo;s literary equivalent is Catcher in the Rye. Fear and Loathing is literary adrenichrome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syria and Iran</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/16/syria-and-iran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2005 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/16/syria-and-iran/</guid>
      <description>From the AP:
   &amp;ldquo;In view of the special conditions faced by Syria, Iran will transfer its experience, especially concerning sanctions, to Syria,&amp;rdquo; Mohammad Reza Aref, Iran&amp;rsquo;s first vice president, was quoted as saying after meeting Syrian Prime Minister Mohammad Naji Otari.
 How surprising. Iraq&amp;rsquo;s neighbors joining forces to oppose the US, though they don&amp;rsquo;t mention us by name. It makes me wonder what their relationhip has been up until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More on the United Nations</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/14/more-on-the-united-nations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2005 01:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/14/more-on-the-united-nations/</guid>
      <description>Michelle Malkin has a nice roundup of blogs and MSM stories on the UN sex scandal. Thanks much, Michelle, for the plug.
Some stories hit me harder than others, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been anti-UN for about 20 years. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d post a few lines that wrote in my 1993 book, The Conservative Manifesto:
   Since there is little evidence to defend the United Nations as anything but a hindrance to the cause of democracy and the advance of American foreign policy, we will withdraw from the United Nations and expel it from our borders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Dean Thinks</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/12/how-dean-thinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2005 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/12/how-dean-thinks/</guid>
      <description>Want to know how Howard Dean thinks?
   I support allotting a certain percentage of seats in these elections for the Sunnis.
 Ponder that a moment.
The man who wanted to be chief executive of the modern world&amp;rsquo;s first democratic republic wrote on January 10, 2005, that he believes Iraqis deserve some sort of managed democracy in which votes are only marginally important.
Instead of letting the people, who can&amp;rsquo;t be trusted in Dean&amp;rsquo;s view, to decide affairs, Dean would have a team of fairness experts decide how to apportion seats in the Iraqi legislature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eason Jordon and  Alger Hiss</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/12/eason-jordon-and-alger-hiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2005 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/12/eason-jordon-and-alger-hiss/</guid>
      <description>I missed the Eason Jordan affair.
I heard about it, followed the stories, and read the blogs. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like commenting here. The reason was that the story was obvious. Senior executives in the mainstream media believe that conservatives are Bible-beating idiots, Republicans raped poor black women so they can later eat the off-spring, and soldiers are murderers who enlist so they can kill without repercusion. Sorry, folks, but that&amp;rsquo;s how MSM, most college professors, a good major of the population of New York City, and Eason Jordan view us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rafsanjani Seeks Common Ground with US</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/07/rafsanjani-seeks-common-ground-with-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2005 05:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/07/rafsanjani-seeks-common-ground-with-us/</guid>
      <description>In an interview with USA Today, Ali Akbar Hashemi Rafsanjani, the once and future president of Iran, said the US and Iran have more common ground than differences. Running for a return to the Iranian presidency, Rafsanjani was clearly speaking to the White House through the press.
If he&amp;rsquo;s sincere and he returns to power, this could be a major victory for Bush&amp;rsquo;s foreign policy in the Middle East. Bringing a moderate or liberal government to Iran is not Rafsanjani&amp;rsquo;s goal, for sure, but, like Gorbechev found in the Soviet Union, any reform could spin out of control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Janeane Garofalo:  One Human Being Too Many</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/07/janeane-garofalo-one-human-being-too-many/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2005 02:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/07/janeane-garofalo-one-human-being-too-many/</guid>
      <description>If there&amp;rsquo;s anyone on this planet whose presence depresses the hell out of me, it&amp;rsquo;s that brainless windbag Janeane Garofalo. Not that I needed more reasons to despise her, but A Little More to the Right found one. I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen this anywhere else, so take a read. Money quote:
   &amp;ldquo;The inked fingers and the position of them, which is gonna be a &amp;lsquo;Daily Show&amp;rsquo; photo already, of them signaling in this manner [Nazi salute], as if they have solidarity with the Iraqis who braved physical threats against their lives to vote as if somehow these inked-fingered Republicans have something to do with that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY DA Preparing Indictment in Oil-for-Terrorism Probe</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/07/ny-da-preparing-indictment-in-oil-for-terrorism-probe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2005 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/07/ny-da-preparing-indictment-in-oil-for-terrorism-probe/</guid>
      <description>According to Fox News,
   The Manhattan district attorney has launched a criminal probe into Benon Sevan , the U.N. Oil-for-Food chief who investigators said had &amp;ldquo;serious conflict of interest&amp;rdquo; while overseeing the program.
 I must say this is good news. An indictment by a US grand jury is one of only two ways to get to the bottom of the scam, and the only hope for putting the criminals behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Annan Go Down?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/06/will-annan-go-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2005 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/06/will-annan-go-down/</guid>
      <description>Looks like Paul Volcker&amp;rsquo;s investigation of the UN Oil-for-Terrorism scam is closing in on Kofi Annan.
   Investigators probing alleged corruption at the United Nations oil-for-food program are scrutinizing thousands of pages of U.N. Secretary-General Kofi Annan&amp;rsquo;s documents, including e-mail and phone records, to determine whether he exerted influence in securing a contract for a Swiss company that employed his son.
 Previously, Volcker&amp;rsquo;s team had cleared the elder Annan of wrong-doing in connection with the scam which diverted billlions of dollars intended to releive the suffering of poor Iraqis into the pockets of Saddam Hussein and his sons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rice:  Europe Ready to Move On</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/05/rice-europe-ready-to-move-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2005 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/05/rice-europe-ready-to-move-on/</guid>
      <description>Well, now that the Iraqi people have vindicated Bush&amp;rsquo;s policy through free and fair elections, the cheese-eating surrender monkeys want to be our friends again.
        &amp;ldquo;I think what we&amp;rsquo;re hearing from Europe is a desire to move on to the next chapter in this great alliance,&amp;rdquo; Rice said after meeting with Poland&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister, Adam Rotfeld.
  Of course. While Poland was on our side,Rice was likely referring to the French and Germans&amp;ndash;and possibly the wimpering new Spanish government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Must Be a Slow News Day</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/05/it-must-be-a-slow-news-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2005 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/05/it-must-be-a-slow-news-day/</guid>
      <description>But first must get Moose and Squirrel!
  All I can think about is Howard Dean! Poliblogger and Dean Esmay are talking about him, too.
Steven Taylor noticed my paranoia about Dean. Hey, I admit there&amp;rsquo;s no logical reason to conclude that Dean will revitalize the Democrat party. This blog frivilously documented Dr. Dean&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous run for the White House in 2003 (the wrong year).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zarqawi:  Sooner than Later</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/04/zarqawi-sooner-than-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2005 06:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/04/zarqawi-sooner-than-later/</guid>
      <description>Yes, this is too easy with the headlines that US and Iraqi troops have just missed him two or three times in the past two weeks. But I have a soft stop for gut things, and George Bush is on a roll.
 First, Condi and Gonzalez have been confirmed. The stock market continues to improve. The State of the Union address was the best he&amp;rsquo;s given so far. The Iraqi elections were an overwhelming success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrorists Kidnap American Soldier Doll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/02/terrorists-kidnap-american-soldier-doll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2005 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/02/terrorists-kidnap-american-soldier-doll/</guid>
      <description>Yes, folks, the end is obviously near for the terrorists in Iraq as evidenced bythis story of a video on a web site that frequently shows hostage tapes. Close inspection . . . what am I saying? . . . a casual glance reveals that the subject of photo is a GI Joe doll or some knock-off. The gun is obviously plastic.
A couple of years ago I wrote a satire piece about Al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s desparation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC Admits Lie . . . er, Error</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/01/bbc-admits-lie-er-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2005 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/01/bbc-admits-lie-er-error/</guid>
      <description>The BBC admits that it was wrong when it claimed coalition forces had killed more Iraqi civilians than had all other factors combined in the history of the country. Well, they didn&amp;rsquo;t claim that, exactly, but if the BBC can irresponsibly hyperbolize facts in order to promoted its twisted, anti-Western, pro-terrorist viewpoints, why can&amp;rsquo;t we?
Hat tip to Drudge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi Terrorists Use Disabled as Bombers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/31/iraqi-terrorists-use-disabled-as-bombers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2005 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/31/iraqi-terrorists-use-disabled-as-bombers/</guid>
      <description>Terrorists used a disabled child as a suicide bomber on election day, Iraqi interior minister Falah al-Naqib said today.
    In all, 44 people were killed in a total of 38 bomb attacks on polling stations. Police at the scene of one the Baghdad blasts said the bomber appeared to have Down&amp;rsquo;s syndrome.
    Mr Al-Naqib praised an Iraqi citizen who was killed while preventing one suicide bomber from reaching a crowd of people outside a polling station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Gotta Love Marines</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/30/you-gotta-love-marines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2005 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/30/you-gotta-love-marines/</guid>
      <description>Particularly, this one</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Left on Iraqi Elections</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/30/the-left-on-iraqi-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2005 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/30/the-left-on-iraqi-elections/</guid>
      <description>The hatred and anger of those still think Stalin a role model of good national governance earns its own blog entry. Again, I wish I could afford to buy these folks an old, polluting car and a good air-tight garage. They really seem to have exhausted the joy of living.
   Yea, this is going to be a great representative government,
  With a third of the counrty not voting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Than Expected</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/30/better-than-expected/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2005 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/30/better-than-expected/</guid>
      <description>The headline of Iraq&amp;rsquo;s first free elections. Better than expected. Less violence than feared. Higher turnout than anticipated&amp;ndash;over 60% nationwide.
Ah, lovers of freedom and self-determination, savor the moment. When the statues of Saddam fell, the world laughed. But when the people voted today, the gods smiled. This, like our own election in 1788, the election today is the first true exercise of freedom in Iraq.
Sure, John Kerry can only decry the lack of &amp;ldquo;international community&amp;rdquo; participation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dean vs. NYT</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/29/dean-vs-nyt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2005 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/29/dean-vs-nyt/</guid>
      <description>I get blasted for my occasional (okay, daily) venture into screaming at people. But the usually mellow Dean Esmay has had it with the New York Times, and it&amp;rsquo;s a beautiful thing to read.
Dean stopped reading too soon. Here is the entire list of NYT&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;complete&amp;rdquo; coverage of Iraq. Complete my Irish-white rear-end. Negative stories are in bold. (12 of 17)
 Flashback to the 60&amp;rsquo;s: A Sinking Sensation of Parallels Between Iraq and Vietnam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>48 Hours</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/29/48-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2005 04:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/29/48-hours/</guid>
      <description>`God save thee, ancient Mariner !
From the fiends, that plague thee thus !&amp;ndash;
Why look&amp;rsquo;st thou so ?&#39;&amp;ndash;With my cross-bow
I shot the ALBATROSS.
  Forty-eight hours from now, America and our allies will have brought democratic elections to a second former dictatorship in less than one year. While the media elite, acadmic snobs, and run of the mill liberal whiners want to pass this election off as a hoax, the historical significance cannot b overstated: the liberations of Aghanistand and Iraq begin the 21st century&amp;rsquo;s march of freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predictions 2005</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/01/predictions-2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2005 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/01/01/predictions-2005/</guid>
      <description>Last year, I hit about .500 on my predictions using my own, friendly measures. This year, though, is a bit tougher without an election to predict.
Tsunami
The disease outbreak won&amp;rsquo;t be as bad as the fearmongers at the UN hope. Still, the total human damage from the quakes will reach 200,000&amp;ndash;a massive loss of life.
The UN and the Bush Administration will have their final, irreparable falling-out over Bush&amp;rsquo;s coalition of aid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marc Rich FBI Target -- Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/13/marc-rich-fbi-target-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2004 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/13/marc-rich-fbi-target-again/</guid>
      <description>Regulars know that I rarely invoke the memory of William Jeffersonovich Clinton for the same reason I don&amp;rsquo;t I say &amp;ldquo;must win situation&amp;rdquo; when the Blues are down 3 - 1 in the Stanley Cup Finals. It&amp;rsquo;s a cliche.
Nonetheless, news in today&amp;rsquo;s New York Post that Marc Rich, the most controversial of Clinton&amp;rsquo;s Midnight Pardons, was a major player in the Oil for Food scam with Saddam.
        Rich, the fugitive Swiss-based commodities trader who received a controversial pardon from President Bill Clinton in January 2001, is a primary target of criminal probes under way in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Military Over-extended?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/11/military-over-extended/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2004 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/11/military-over-extended/</guid>
      <description>Professor Bainbridge quotes at length an essay by Andrew Bacevich in today&amp;rsquo;s Wall Street Journal which concludes a) we are over-extended in Iraq and Afghanistan, and b) Bush&amp;rsquo;s choices are &amp;ldquo;stark&amp;rdquo;. Those choice are: bring the troops home and use &amp;ldquo;other means&amp;rdquo; to battle terrorism, or grow the Army. Professor Bainbridge would be willing to raise taxes to build an 18 division Army.
If we are over-extended, and we might not be yet, I think there is a third option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pitts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/10/the-pitts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2004 02:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/10/the-pitts/</guid>
      <description>TOP OF PAGE UPDATE!
The editor of Pitts&amp;rsquo;s newspaper speaks:
&amp;ldquo;He is there to write stories, not make news himself,&amp;rdquo; Griscom said of Pitts. The editor added that the recipient of the e-mail, whom he would not identify, should not have passed it along.
The recipient should not have passed it along? Good God, Mr. Griscom. It&amp;rsquo;s called NEWS!!!!!!!!!! That&amp;rsquo;s how a lot of news gets made&amp;ndash;someone does something unethical and gets caught because their ego demands that they pound their chest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desperate Measures</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/07/desperate-measures/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2004 02:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/07/desperate-measures/</guid>
      <description>Howard Fineman hacked for Kerry when he said, in October, that President Bush sounded desperate. One can fairly say, though, that the insurgency in Iraq shows signs of desperation.
 Having lost a significant portion of its armaments in our attack on Fallujah and the corollary fight in Mosul, the terrorists sense an end game. They are going down in a blaze of glory. From the[ Associate Press via MSNBC](https://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/6577206/):       Brazen gunmen firing automatic weapons roamed Baghdads streets Monday within blocks of the countrys most fortified facilities, including the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words I Miss</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/06/words-i-miss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2004 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/06/words-i-miss/</guid>
      <description>I dont know what gets the blamepolitical correctness, pop culture, declining understanding of the subtleties of language, or just timebut I miss some words. I wish people used them more often.
Spatand the past of other verbs that end with -it. Instead of spat, I hear only spit used for any tense. He spat on me, lends an air of dignity that he spit on me lacks.
Spittleanother victim of the ubiquitous verb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Bin Laden&#39;s Trail</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/06/on-bin-ladens-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2004 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/06/on-bin-ladens-trail/</guid>
      <description>Outside the Beltway examines Michael Scheuer&amp;rsquo;s column in Los Angeles Times.
One point I&amp;rsquo;d add: The reason American people are outraged over Clinton&amp;rsquo;s failure to take out Bin Laden in 1998 and 1999 is that they don&amp;rsquo;t know. The press did a fine job of filtering out any criticism of the Clinton admin.
Remember Howard Fineman&amp;rsquo;s admission in October? That the MSM would report only bad news about Iraq until the end of the campaign?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2004 Predictions Report Card</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/06/my-2004-predictions-report-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2004 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/06/my-2004-predictions-report-card/</guid>
      <description>Back in December 2003, I blogged my predictions for 2004, Part I and Part II. Later, I added my 2004 resolutions. Lets see how I did. (My 20/20 hindsight is** in bold**.)
PREDICTIONS:
Economy
The US economy will continue to expand at the fast pace since the Reagan administration through the second quarter. While new home construction will slow, service and other sectors will more than take its place. Unemployment will improve in fits and starts, but it will be more than half a percentage point lower by the end of the second quarter as the economy creates 100,000 more jobs than existed at the peak in April 2000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Will Fight?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/06/who-will-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2004 03:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/06/who-will-fight/</guid>
      <description>_The DemocraticUnderground.org discussion forum _is full of vile and hatred toward everyone who voted for George W. Bush on November 2, 2004. One thread caught my attention more than others. It encourages conservatives to join the military.
        1-800-USA-ARMY. That is the number you can call to locate your local Army recruiter if you want to enlist or need information for your children or grandchildren or nephews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kofi Annan:  Abject Failure</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/05/kofi-annan-abject-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2004 23:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/12/05/kofi-annan-abject-failure/</guid>
      <description>Kofi Annan&amp;rsquo;s tenure as UN Secretary-General ranks as one of the most massive failings in modern leadership. Two American presidents and hundreds of thousands of American troops filled the void left by Annan&amp;rsquo;s abrogation of responsibility. In case you&amp;rsquo;ve missed the headlines, Kofi Annan presided over the slaughter of nearly one million people in Rwanda, the enslavement and systematic murders of millions in Sudan, the rise to emminence of Islamic terrorists, Saddam Hussein&amp;rsquo;s theft of billions, and the orchestrated attempt to eliminate Israel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colin Powell Resigns</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/15/colin-powell-resigns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2004 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/15/colin-powell-resigns/</guid>
      <description>According to MSNBC, Secretary of State Colin Powell has submitted his resignation.
Having served as SoS during the most critical time since World War II, Powell must be exhausted. I am not Powell&amp;rsquo;s biggest fan, having learned much about him from several of his lieutenants when he was still a general in the Army. But he did a remarkable job under very tough circumstances. He deserves our sincerest thanks for a life of service to his country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Reaction to Cheney&#39;s Hospitalization</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/13/democrat-reaction-to-cheneys-hospitalization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2004 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/13/democrat-reaction-to-cheneys-hospitalization/</guid>
      <description>Take a look. These are the Blue Staters. Is it any wonder that from these lands come the people listed below?
These are compassionate, loving, meek, intelligent liberals writing. Read the rampant ignorance. Read the abuse of the language. Read the hatred, the discontent, the vile wishes of pain and suffering. Read the desire to abandon the United States. Read their minds, which they merrily open to the world the way a dirty old man reveals his naked body to school children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review:  The Pentagon&#39;s New Map, by Thomas P. M. Barnett</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/12/book-review-the-pentagons-new-map-by-thomas-p-m-barnett/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2004 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/12/book-review-the-pentagons-new-map-by-thomas-p-m-barnett/</guid>
      <description>American military policy as most of us know it evolved in response to the Cold War. The Soviet Union represented a military commanders worst nightmare: equal or superior strength in numbers, technology, and intelligence, combined with a desire to conquer the world.
But, as we found in the 1990s, the Soviet Union was also a military commanders dream: a formidable adversary requiring American and NATO vigilance in the forms of large, new weapons systems, enormous training budgets, and hands-off intelligence programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerry Supports Blugeon Bush Supporter</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/10/kerry-supports-blugeon-bush-supporter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2004 18:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/10/kerry-supports-blugeon-bush-supporter/</guid>
      <description>According to posters to liberal forums, conservatives have a monopoly on violence. But some young Democrats, it seems, have learned their lessons from the union thugs who destroyed numerous Bush-Cheney and Republican offices prior to the election.
Three high school seniors who supported Kerry beat a Bush supporter with baseball bat and chains after school yesterday.
The SAINT PAUL PIONEER PRESS reported in morning editions: The argument began earlier in the day Thursday with a discussion about candidates the minors had supported for president, Backstrom said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Fodder from DemocraticUnderground</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/09/more-fodder-from-democraticunderground/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2004 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/09/more-fodder-from-democraticunderground/</guid>
      <description>Sorry. I know I should let them have their hissy fits in private, but when people who publicly claim to be intellectually, educationally, and morally superior to me spew nonsense, I have to point it out.
Please read this post on today&amp;rsquo;s du.org. This girl says that we conservatives can&amp;rsquo;t be reasoned with, then goes on to say she has cut ties with all of her friends who support Bush, because, like our troops in Iraq, all conservatives are evil (emphases mine):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Liberals Stop Supporting Troops?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/09/will-liberals-stop-supporting-troops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2004 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/09/will-liberals-stop-supporting-troops/</guid>
      <description>Arguing with Sign Posts reminds me that liberals continue to say things that seem, well, silly. But some liberals are teetering frightening close to the truth.
Someone posting to the democraticunderground.org forum ponders whether it&amp;rsquo;s time for liberals to stop supporting our troops. Her reasoning goes thusly: George Bush is a known evil; those who support Bush support evil; 72% of American service members in Iraq supported George Bush; therefore; 72% of American service member in Iraq are evil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God Bless our Troops</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/08/god-bless-our-troops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2004 03:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/08/god-bless-our-troops/</guid>
      <description>The assault on Fallujah has begun. 10,000 of the bravest Americans and Iraqis are about test their mettle. God bless them all. May each return to his family with all of his faculties.
How dare we forget the struggles of the few for the many. May those who must fall in fighting find fast, safe passage to eternal salvation, and may they one day welcome us, the beneficiaries of the their sacrifice, into God&amp;rsquo;s waiting arms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What The Election Portends</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/03/what-the-election-portends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2004 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/03/what-the-election-portends/</guid>
      <description>We know these things:
 The American people have re-elected President Bush The American people have given his party a stronger hand in the US Senate The American people have given his party a stronger hand in the US House of Representatives The American people have given his party a stronger hand in state governorships  Taken together, Election 2004 can be seen as nothing short of an endorsement of President Bush&amp;rsquo;s policies and the Republic view of our country and its place in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assuring His Fate</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/03/assuring-his-fate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2004 11:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/11/03/assuring-his-fate/</guid>
      <description>John Kerry has apparently decided to contest the presidential election in the courts by forcing Ohio, to count its 150,000 provisional ballots. Should that fail, perhaps he&amp;rsquo;ll sue everyone who voted for Bush. If John Kerry forces a prolonged fight in Ohio, he will have assured himself an ignoble, despised place in American history.
In 2000, Al Gore had several factors on his side that somewhat supported his challenges:
&amp;ndash;Gore won the popular vote</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Letter to Howard Fineman</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/10/09/open-letter-to-howard-fineman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/10/09/open-letter-to-howard-fineman/</guid>
      <description>You and the rest of the main stream have timed things well. Let the President rise a bit, then flood the airwaves and papers with bad news. Leave anything positive about the war on terrorism on deep, inside pages in 2-point print. Let Kerry make a great comeback.
No, Mr. Fineman, the President doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound desperate. He sounds like a candidate. He sounds full-throated and eager. His pathetic performance in debate one&amp;ndash;so reminiscent of his dad&amp;rsquo;s in debate 2 in 1992&amp;ndash;woke him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VP Debate</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/10/05/vp-debate-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/10/05/vp-debate-2/</guid>
      <description>Dick Cheney is really, really good. He should be on more often. He instills confidence.
John Edwards on Global Test: Yes, there is a global veto, but Senator Kerry said we will never give anyone a veto on American use of force. Another waffle.
John Kerry will never give control of the security of the United States of America to another country. What about the UN? Its not a country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy Beer for Soldiers--Not Andrew Sullivan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/24/buy-beer-for-soldiers-not-andrew-sullivan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/24/buy-beer-for-soldiers-not-andrew-sullivan/</guid>
      <description>National Review Online has a link to a story about soldiers in Iraq who&amp;rsquo;ve created a website that allows us back home to buy a beer for a soldier over the internet. What a great idea. I&amp;rsquo;ve added their site to my blogroll, or you can click this. I&amp;rsquo;ve already donated $20.00, because soldiers need beer.
On another front, I&amp;rsquo;ve removed Andrew Sullivan&amp;rsquo;s blog from the blogroll. I&amp;rsquo;m not happy about this, because Andrew offers superior writing and, until recently, superior thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Kerry Knows Iraq Better Than Iraqis?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/23/john-kerry-knows-iraq-better-than-iraqis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/23/john-kerry-knows-iraq-better-than-iraqis/</guid>
      <description>In the crassest act of political desparation since Richard Nixon waved the list of communist contributors in Helen Gehagen Douglas&amp;rsquo;s face, John Kerry today told the heroic interim PM of Iraq that the PM doesn&amp;rsquo;t know Iraq as well as Kerry does.
Well, consider the source. John Kerry believes that the world was a better place when the Taliban ruled Afghanistan. John Kerry believes that Iraq was a better place when Saddam was presiding over the murders of 300,000 people and the tortures of 5,000,000 and the enslavement of the nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules of War</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/22/rules-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/22/rules-of-war/</guid>
      <description>The Bush administration violated several of my rules of war in Iraq:
 Do not let politicians make military decisions; do not let generals make political decisions.  Tommy Franks has admitted that the declaration of the end of major combat operations was his idea. He hoped that by convincing President Bush to make that public declaration, our former &amp;ldquo;allies&amp;rdquo; would jump in to help rebuild Iraq. As a result, we stopped aggressive fighting before we had killed enough enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS News Ties to Kerry Campaign</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/21/cbs-news-ties-to-kerry-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/21/cbs-news-ties-to-kerry-campaign/</guid>
      <description>One thing we&amp;rsquo;ve learned from the CBS Memogate unraveling: if you need to get in touch with the Kerry Campaign, call CBS News.
CBS has admitted that its producer, Mary Mapes, arranged for a telephone conversation between Bill Burkett, source of the infamous memos, and Joe Lockhart, senior advisor to Senator Kerry and former Clinton press secretary.
According to USA Today new ethics experts, the contacts raise serious ethics questions, pointing to the possibility that CBS is using its power as a major television news network to influence the outcome of the Presidential election according to its liberal bias.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Sanctions Work</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/21/some-sanctions-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/21/some-sanctions-work/</guid>
      <description>I usually scoff at sanctions, like when the UN imposes sanctions against Iraq so that Kofi&amp;rsquo;s son can make millions violating them, but I propose two sanctions against CBS News that will have a desirable effect on the Tiffany network&amp;rsquo;s credibility:
 One year suspension of credentials to all federal government offices and events. Ban CBS from the presidential debates this fall.  These steps will ensure that the reorganized CBS News staff place objectivity and ethics before party politics and sensationalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerry Endorses Saddam</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/20/kerry-endorses-saddam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/20/kerry-endorses-saddam/</guid>
      <description>In his biggest break from his previous convictions, Sen. John Kerry today announced that Saddam Husssain should not have been removed from power in Iraq. If elected, the Mass. Senator will reinstate Saddam as president of the Middle East country, provided the Iraqis haven&amp;rsquo;t already executed the former despot.
&amp;ldquo;Democracy has gone too far,&amp;rdquo; Kerry told an audience of students in New York. &amp;ldquo;Some people, like most of the Middle East, do better under dictatorships and monarchies than under anything like a democratic-republic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reward Offered for 1,000th Killed American (satire)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/07/reward-offered-for-1000th-killed-american-satire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/09/07/reward-offered-for-1000th-killed-american-satire/</guid>
      <description>With the American military death toll since the beginning of the war in Iraq at 999, expectant news agencies have launched the &amp;ldquo;Million for A Thousand&amp;rdquo; reward program. CNN, NBC, CBS, ABC, New York Times, Washington Post, LA Times, AP, Reuters and the BBC are jointly sponsoring the program, which will pay $1,000,000 (US) to the Iraqi or foreign terrorist who kills the 1,000th American.
&amp;ldquo;This will be such a windfall for both news circulation [or viewership] and for the Kerry campaign that we all thought the person who delivers the story, so to speak, should share in the reward,&amp;rdquo; said a CNN spokesman on condition of anonymity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning in America II:  The Bush Era</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/30/morning-in-america-ii-the-bush-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/30/morning-in-america-ii-the-bush-era/</guid>
      <description>I agree with Richard Brookhiser that second terms are, more or less, pathetic disappointments. After four of the most tumultuous years of my life (and I lived through Kennedy&amp;rsquo;s assassination, Viet Nam, the horrid sixties, Nixon&amp;rsquo;s wage and price controls, Ford&amp;rsquo;s WIN buttons, Carter&amp;rsquo;s malaise, and Clinton&amp;rsquo;s intern training program, I think I&amp;rsquo;m ready for a dull four years of military victory, peace, and economic growth.
President Bush offers the best chance of those things coming true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Hostages:  How Does It Feel?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/29/french-hostages-how-does-it-feel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/29/french-hostages-how-does-it-feel/</guid>
      <description>Obviously, the taking of hostages is despicable, but we who have shouldered the responsibility of keeping the world safe for democracy for a century must think &amp;ldquo;how does it feel?&amp;rdquo; when we read this news.
The combination of rampant politically correct anit-religiosity with paranoid fear of self-defense has resulting in two French journalists in the hands of hostages who demand that France repeal its ban on Muslim headcovers.
Terrorism is the use of violence against non-combatants to advance a political cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerry On Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/25/kerry-on-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/25/kerry-on-iraq/</guid>
      <description>This is must-see TV
https://www.kerryoniraq.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Veterans Against Kerry</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/25/more-veterans-against-kerry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/25/more-veterans-against-kerry/</guid>
      <description>Letter to John Kerry
August 25, 2004
Senator John Kerry
304 Russell Senate Office Building
Washington, DC 20510
Dear Senator Kerry,
We are pleased to welcome your campaign representatives to Texas today. We honor all our veterans, all whom have worn the uniform and served our country. We also honor the military and National Guard troops serving in Iraq and Afghanistan today. We are very proud of all of them and believe they deserve our full support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Service Members Safer in Iraq</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/18/us-service-members-safer-in-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/18/us-service-members-safer-in-iraq/</guid>
      <description>Okay, this is simple enough for even John Kerry and Howard Dean supporters to understand: American service members are safer serving in Iraq than they are in the US.
The US mortality rate, according to the Centers for Disease Control, is 834 deaths per 100,000 of population per year. There have been 200,000 (average) US troops in Iraq for 18 months. The death rate for 200,000 Americans should be 1,668 per year, meaning that since the start of the war, statistically you&amp;rsquo;d expect 2,502 Americans to have died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kerry Must Want to Be Usama&#39;s Buddy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/02/kerry-must-want-to-be-usamas-buddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2004 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/08/02/kerry-must-want-to-be-usamas-buddy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The policies of this administration, I believe and others believe very deeply, have resulted in an increase of animosity and anger focused on the United States of America,&amp;rdquo; Kerry told reporters after a campaign meeting with first responders. &amp;ldquo;The people who are training terror are using our actions as a means of recruitment.&amp;rdquo;
Of course, they&amp;rsquo;re pissed at us, Senator. We drove them out of Afghanistan. We dried up their money supplies around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Up in Iraq?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/24/whats-up-in-iraq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/24/whats-up-in-iraq/</guid>
      <description>It would appear that the insurgency in Iraq heeded Southwest Airlines&amp;rsquo; marketing campaign: &amp;ldquo;You are now free to move about the country.&amp;rdquo; Having captured, in broad daylight, the head of an Iraqi construction company, the insurgents have sent the clear signal to the Iraqi people, &amp;ldquo;We are in charge.&amp;rdquo;
The United States had an opportunity to destroy the resistance in April, May, and June of 2003. Instead, we chose to let them take their AK-47s and RPGs home to regroup, plot, and recruit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Al Qaeda Threatens Europe</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/02/al-qaeda-threatens-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/02/al-qaeda-threatens-europe/</guid>
      <description>**&amp;ldquo;To the European people &amp;hellip; you only have a few more days to accept bin Laden&amp;rsquo;s truce or you will only have yourselves to blame.&amp;rdquo; **
Thus spake al Qaeda through two Arabic web sites. The date is July 15. The truce was to give European nations time to pull all troops out of Muslim countries, presumably Afghanistan included.
How will Europe respond? Why not America?
Al Qaeda should that it still has the capability to strike in Europe by the train in Spain bombing that changed that country&amp;rsquo;s government and policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sudan:  It&#39;s Not a Famine, Damnit!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/02/sudan-its-not-a-famine-damnit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/02/sudan-its-not-a-famine-damnit/</guid>
      <description>Newsweek, via MSNBC, has a story about the &amp;ldquo;famine&amp;rdquo; in Sudan. What the f*ck? When Muslim extremists murder scores, burn villages, block food relief, burn crops, and lay waste to an entire country, it&amp;rsquo;s not A GODDAMN FAMINE! It&amp;rsquo;s murder, genocide, evil-incarnate. It&amp;rsquo;s a spineless, greedy, UN chief taking money under the table to keep his mouth shut, as he did with Saddam. It&amp;rsquo;s a horror and disgrace to a world that considers itself &amp;ldquo;civlized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UN Oil For Food Scandal (reposted)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/02/un-oil-for-food-scandal-reposted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/02/un-oil-for-food-scandal-reposted/</guid>
      <description>The stories, the facts, the meat of the case, against the United Nations are beginning to leak out. Here is one such story from the New York Post.
Saddam used bribes to UN Officials to divert $10 billion from food and medicine for the Iraqi people to building palaces and killing people he didn&amp;rsquo;t like. The UN quietly endorsed this practice.
Giving money to UN relief agencies is more than a waste: it&amp;rsquo;s supporting corruption that kills innocent people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UN Oil for Food Scandal Tidbits</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/02/un-oil-for-food-scandal-tidbits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2004 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/02/un-oil-for-food-scandal-tidbits/</guid>
      <description>The stories, the facts, the meat of the case, against the United Nations are beginning to leak out. Here is one such story from the New York Post.
Saddam used bribes to UN Officials to divert $10 billion from food and medicine for the Iraqi people to building palaces and killing people he didn&amp;rsquo;t like. The UN quietly endorsed this practice.
Giving money to UN relief agencies is more than a waste: it&amp;rsquo;s supporting corruption that kills innocent people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over 10,000 Iraqi Deaths</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/01/over-10000-iraqi-deaths/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/01/over-10000-iraqi-deaths/</guid>
      <description>Iraq&amp;rsquo;s population is about 25 million. It&amp;rsquo;s 2004 death rate is 5.66 deaths per 1,000. The US population is more than 10 times that at just under 300 million. Our death rate is 8.34 per 1,000.
Before you go crying about all the people we are killing in Iraq, bear in mind that your chances of dying in 2004 are much, much greater here than there. Iraq is obviously safer than the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect Christmas Gift</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/01/the-perfect-christmas-gift/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/01/the-perfect-christmas-gift/</guid>
      <description>Iraqis are flocking to stores to buy a dancing Saddam doll.
Now I know what to get the kids for Christmas. Not too long ago, such a novelty would have earned torturous death for its owner. Today, stores can&amp;rsquo;t keep the things on the shelves.
This is the best proof in a long time that we were morally right to liberate Iraq.
On to Iran!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seething Hatred of Maureen Dowd</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/01/the-seething-hatred-of-maureen-dowd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/01/the-seething-hatred-of-maureen-dowd/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s New York Times, Maureen Dowd&amp;ndash;as rotten a human being as she is a writer&amp;ndash;rips George Bush for writing &amp;ldquo;Let Freedom Reign,&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;ring&amp;rdquo; on a note announcing the control of Iraq had been passed to Iraqi&amp;rsquo;s governing council.
Maureen Dowd must be a joy. I hope I never meet her. Virtually the whole her being now works toward displaying her visceral hatred for George Bush and for anyone who would vote for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMD Smoking Guns</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/01/wmd-smoking-guns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/07/01/wmd-smoking-guns/</guid>
      <description>Secretary of Defense Donald Rumsfeld revealed that coalition soldiers from Poland have discoverd WMDs in Iraq.
Bet you won&amp;rsquo;t hear it on television news, though. So read the source.
RUMSFELD:
   Now what&amp;rsquo;s actually happened? Right now you have the Iraqi Survey Group, which is a multinational group that&amp;rsquo;s out there reviewing documentation and looking at suspect WMD sites. I was with the Polish minister of defense this weekend in Istanbul, Turkey at the NATO Summit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something Big?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/29/something-big/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/29/something-big/</guid>
      <description>Do you get the feeling that something&amp;ndash;really big&amp;ndash;is about to happen?
I do. Something tells me it will be something good and big. Capture bin Laden? Maybe, but I think that would be anticlimactic at this point. As the 9/11 Commission reported June 6, the US war on terror has all but crippled Al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s abilitiy to do something big and bad. They are reduced to killing hapless innocents abroad one at a time with a knife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking News:  Al-Zarqawi Captured?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/28/breaking-news-al-zarqawi-captured/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/28/breaking-news-al-zarqawi-captured/</guid>
      <description>Econopundit  is reporting, from a source listening to Iraqi radio, that Iraqi intelligence has captured terrorist Al-Zarqawi. If so, mark June 27 as the turning point in the Iraqi operation: the second deadliest terrorist in the world captured, and a democracy in the Middle East. Not to mention NATO capitulation to Bush and Blair and limited victories for the administration handling of Gitmo detainees from the Supremes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iraq is a Nation Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/28/iraq-is-a-nation-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/28/iraq-is-a-nation-again/</guid>
      <description>In a move designed to shock the American press and Iraqi terrorists, the new Iraqi government took sovereign control of that country this morning in a low-key ceremony in Baghdad. The US, British, Polish, Turkish, Czech, South Korean, Japanese, and other troops are now guests of the interim government.
Just months ago, critics claimed that June 30 was a ridiculous date, that the Iraqis, being dark-skinned people who don&amp;rsquo;t speak English natively, would never be able to handle the responsibilities of self-governance with so little preparation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Restores Full Diplomatic Ties to Libya</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/28/us-restores-full-diplomatic-ties-to-libya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/28/us-restores-full-diplomatic-ties-to-libya/</guid>
      <description>According to CNN.com: 
The United States has formally resumed diplomatic ties with Libya after a 24-year break, the State Department says.
Oh, if only the al-Zarqawi story were true. Imagine, since taking office, George Bush&amp;rsquo;s State Department has overthrown Saddam and freed 25 million Iraqi prisoners, overthrown the Taliban and freed 25 million Afghan slaves, disarmed and normalized relations with Libya, and, so far, prevented a single act of terrorism on United States soil or against significant US interests since 9/11/01.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killing the Enemy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/20/killing-the-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2004 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/06/20/killing-the-enemy/</guid>
      <description>Struggling to find an answer to the problems of Al Qaeda, the Iraqi insurgents, and terrorists in general? Kill them. Kill them all. Kill them and those who aid and abet. I have no pity for the Iraqis killed by American bombers that took out a terrorist safe house. I pity the children whose criminal parents placed them in harms way, but no one else. (In case you believe the locals who said it was an innocent family home, weapons and bombs that were cached in the house exploded for 20 minutes after the US attack was over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off From New Hampshire</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/28/off-from-new-hampshire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2004 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/28/off-from-new-hampshire/</guid>
      <description>I must admit that I paid no attention the New Hampshire primary until about 15 minutes ago.
For those of you who are like me, Kerry won by more than 10 points over Dean. Edwards and Clark tied for third. (Is this Clark any relation to Ramsey Clark? And if not, why not?)
Howard Dean&amp;rsquo;s post coital speech sounded a lot like a farewell, according to the snippets I read. He named a lot of people who work(ed) on his campaign, thanking them for their long hours, [insert all the stock phrases here].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN/Time Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/07/cnntime-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2004 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/07/cnntime-poll/</guid>
      <description>For poll junkies, today&amp;rsquo;s CNN/Time poll is loaded with interesting tidbits: * Dean&amp;rsquo;s support is slipping, no doubt due to the doctor&amp;rsquo;s idiotic statements, Biblical errors, short temper, and whining * Several Democrats (Kerry, Clark, Lieberman, Gephardt) seem to be getting stronger, perhaps because they&amp;rsquo;re buying air time to compete with the hours of free time Dean has gotten since last June * Bush&amp;rsquo;s approvals keep going up:** 61% approve of his job in Iraq** 58% approve the president&amp;rsquo;s overal foreign policy** 54% approve the president&amp;rsquo;s handling of the economy * This graphic is the most revealing, though, on the Democrats:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life for Iraqis Better by the Second</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/07/life-for-iraqis-better-by-the-second/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2004 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/07/life-for-iraqis-better-by-the-second/</guid>
      <description>An Iraqi-American engineering professor appearing on KTRS 550 AM radio&amp;rsquo;s morning show today reports that life for the Iraqi people is</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decontructing Kerry, Part II</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/07/decontructing-kerry-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2004 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/07/decontructing-kerry-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>Even more bizarre, or so it must have seemed to Senator Kerry, was the effect of the war, for which he voted. The more successful our campaign in Iraq, the less his fellow Democrats liked him. Had we lost the war, one assumes that the rank-and-file Democrats would have supported a warmonger candidate. But as our victory became apparent, the Dems fled to the two candidates who opposed the war in the first place: Dean and Clark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickly</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/07/quickly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2004 00:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/07/quickly/</guid>
      <description>Hillary Clinton came to St. Louis today to make Gandhi jokes. First, I live in St. Louis and didn&amp;rsquo;t know she was coming. Second, she showed up in Iraq the day after the President, now she shows up in St. Louis the day after the President. Pattern?
Howard Dean potentially faces criminal charges for releasing secret security plans for the Yankee Nuclear Power plant after 9/11/01. He won&amp;rsquo;t release records of meetings from his 11 years as governor, but he&amp;rsquo;s pretty fast and loose with national security plans whose compromise could give terrorists the information they need to overcome that security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy and Durbin v. Democracy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/03/kennedy-amp-durbin-v-democracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2004 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/03/kennedy-amp-durbin-v-democracy/</guid>
      <description>AGHHH!!!!
I HATE computers!
750 words of analysis of the unfolding story about a Democrat senate conspiracy to subvert the federal judiciary, and my computer screwed you, dear reader, out of it.
I will rewrite it if I get the energy. This is all that remains&amp;ndash;a quote from Federalist No. 64 by John Jay:
 the President and senators so chosen will always be of the number of those who best understand our national interests, whether considered in relation to the several States or to foreign nations, who are best able to promote those interests, and whose reputation for integrity inspires and merits confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pope wants &#34;New World Order&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/03/pope-wants-ampquotnew-world-orderampquot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2004 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/03/pope-wants-ampquotnew-world-orderampquot/</guid>
      <description>His Holiness, John Paul II, has begun a crusade of his own. According to The Guardian, the pontiff wants to replace the United Nations with an organization capable of preventing things like the liberation of Iraq.
The pope made his speech flanked by none other than Cardinal Renato Martino, a devout America-hater who felt sorry for Saddam Hussein</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North Korea Allows US Inspectors</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/02/north-korea-allows-us-inspectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2004 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2004/01/02/north-korea-allows-us-inspectors/</guid>
      <description>When Town Hall was in its infancy on CompuServe, and I was writing three columns a week, Jimmy Carter&amp;rsquo;s illegal negotiations with North Korea that resulted in US assistance in building nuclear weapons to be aimed at Los Angeles and Chicago inspired my most vitriolic pieces. What bothered me, perhaps, more than anything was the fact that Carter&amp;rsquo;s meddling had me siding with Clinton. That was 1994.
Ten years later, we are still digging out from that mess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predictions Part I</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2003/12/31/predictions-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2003 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2003/12/31/predictions-part-i/</guid>
      <description>Everyone does it, so Ill join the fray. If you feel tempted to wager based on these predictions, please just send the money to me: I need, and your chances of getting a return are much better.
Economy
The US economy will continue to expand at the fast pace since the Reagan administration through the second quarter. While new home construction will slow, service and other sectors will more than take its place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Dividends</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2003/12/20/war-dividends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2003 01:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2003/12/20/war-dividends/</guid>
      <description>Back in 1989, the term Peace Dividend was all the rage. Peace Dividend referred to money Democrats could spend on welfare programs and pork as a result of the end of the Cold War. Today, Bush and Blair announced a new, better, and real dividend: the dividends of war.
After seeing the effectiveness of Bush&amp;rsquo;s policy in overthrowing Saddam, Libyan leader Moammar Gadhafi has admitted trying to develop weapons of mass destruction &amp;ndash; but now plans to dismantle all such programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kofi Annan &#34;Frustrated&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2003/12/19/kofi-annan-quotfrustratedquot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2003 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2003/12/19/kofi-annan-quotfrustratedquot/</guid>
      <description>The vassal of vascilationville, Kofi Annan, is frustrated that the US and the Iraqi Governing Council are not giveing him &amp;ldquo;specific answers&amp;rdquo; to his questions regarding the UN&amp;rsquo;s role in post-war Iraq. The ballsy son-of-a-*** is sounding pretty damn uppity about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markets Update</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2003/12/15/markets-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2003 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2003/12/15/markets-update/</guid>
      <description>Well, the President gets more positive coverage with a press conference, the Army announces the arrests of Iraqi resistence leaders based on information contained in documents found with Saddam, and the markets respond by turning down. The Dow, up by more tha 80 points earlier in the day, is at +60, while NASDAQ is just about flat at +2.
The American investor class knows nothing of patriotism. Sometimes, at seminal moments in history, it is right to subordinate your personal wealth to the national or world good.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>