<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foreign Relations on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/foreign-relations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foreign Relations on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 02:01:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/foreign-relations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UN Security Council Ignores Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/un-security-council-ignores-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 02:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/04/05/un-security-council-ignores-obama/</guid>
      <description>Jimmy Carter was the Rodney Dangerfield of international politics: he got no respect from the people who counted. The bad guys laughed at him. The bad guys must be rolling on the floor tonight.
Rogue Leaders Respect Nothing But Strength
Almost simultaneous with North Korea&amp;rsquo;s launching an ICBM in violation of international law and in defiance of US warnings, Barack Obama stood before the world and declared his intention to disarm the arsenal for democracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America’s Survival Is In Your Hands</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/25/americas-survival-is-in-your-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 23:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/25/americas-survival-is-in-your-hands/</guid>
      <description>Are you as amazed as I am at how quickly our country has descended into something resembling an oversized banana republic? Consider:
* [Gangs of thugs](https://michellemalkin.com/2009/03/25/the-rule-of-the-mob/) freely harass and intimidate AIG employees out of murderous envy** The Obama administration announced its willingness to [abandon the US dollar](https://www.bloomberg.com/apps/news?pid=20601087&amp;amp;sid=aqDuKEqQn39I&amp;amp;refer=home) as the international reserve currency** The administration shows no willingness to check [China’s menacing military](https://rds.yahoo.com/_ylt=A0WTTkuqvspJpXkAAwjQtDMD;_ylu=X3oDMTBjMHZkMjZyBHBvcwMxBHNlYwNzcg--/SIG=13lepic2b/EXP=1238110250/**http%3a//www.cnn.com/2009/WORLD/asiapcf/03/25/china.military.report/index.html%3fsection=cnn_latest) build-up, even though the Pentagon issued a warning just today** Secretary of State Clinton went to Mexico to [denounce the US](https://news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, Obama and his secretaries really are idiots</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/19/yes-obama-and-his-secretaries-really-are-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 03:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/19/yes-obama-and-his-secretaries-really-are-idiots/</guid>
      <description>The new Secretary of Homeland Security has replaced the word &amp;ldquo;terrorism&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;man-caused disasters.&amp;rdquo;
 I did not use the word &amp;ldquo;terrorism,&amp;rdquo; I referred to &amp;ldquo;man-caused&amp;rdquo; disasters. That is perhaps only a nuance, but it demonstrates that we want to move away from the politics of fear toward a policy of being prepared for all risks that can occur.
 I assume that appointing an idiot like Napolitano to the cabinet qualifies as a man-cause disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama invites enemies to our gates</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/15/obama-invites-enemies-to-our-gates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2009 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/03/15/obama-invites-enemies-to-our-gates/</guid>
      <description>Since Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s inauguration, America&amp;rsquo;s enemies have achieved gains that should frighten everyone: * Russia reportedly will deploy strategic bombers to Cuba and Venezuela. For the first time, Russia can strike American cities from advanced positions without a carrier battle group. * North Korea will soon test-fire a ballistic missile under the thin veil of &amp;ldquo;satellite&amp;rdquo; test * Iran has or will have 4 nuclear weapons with capabilities of hitting Israel from land and the US from sea * Pakistan is growing more violent * Pentagon facing 10 percent budget cut while admitting 2-war strategies isn&amp;rsquo;t enough wars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel Continues Assault on Terrorists</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/israel-continues-assault-on-terrorists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 13:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/28/israel-continues-assault-on-terrorists/</guid>
      <description>Israel&amp;rsquo;s assault on Hamas terrorists in Gaza continued for a second day. As if reading from a script, the UN Security Council called for an immediate stop to Israel&amp;rsquo;s self-defense. As the air strikes continued, Israel has moved more troops and tanks to the border, possibly in preparation for an incursion into the area now under terrorist control.
Some internation responses were less than predictable, though. France, for instance, demands first that the terrorists stop pitching rockets at Israeli school kids, then that Israel stop its air assault.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>