<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>export-import bank on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/export-import-bank/</link>
    <description>Recent content in export-import bank on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 23:46:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/export-import-bank/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Come to Export Import Speaking and Gathering This Saturday at Paddy O&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/27/come-to-export-import-speaking-and-gathering-this-saturday-at-paddy-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 23:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/27/come-to-export-import-speaking-and-gathering-this-saturday-at-paddy-os/</guid>
      <description>With Opportunity for All; With Favoritism Toward None Join Us Paddy O&amp;rsquo;s&amp;ndash;618 S. 7th Street, St. Louis, MO 4:15 PM Saturday, May 30 RSVP on Facebook
They say the Export Import Bank is a tiny agency that creates jobs for small business while producing a profit for the Treasury. And rescues baby rabbits from dangerous predators. And it’s gluten free.
Call us skeptics.
We saw the news that Goldman Sachs used the Export Import Bank to secure funding for a financially unstable buyer—after paying the Secretary of State’s husband $200,000 for a fifteen-minute speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lazy Person&#39;s Cure for Herpes Ex-Im</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/07/the-lazy-persons-cure-for-herpes-ex-im/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 22:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/07/the-lazy-persons-cure-for-herpes-ex-im/</guid>
      <description>Every six months.
Just when you can you least afford it.
It happens.
A breakout.
It&amp;rsquo;s Herpes Ex-Im, a cronyism disease that can make the prettiest economic system look sick.
Herpes Ex-Im is a virus that attacks your economy&amp;rsquo;s competitive system, resulting ugly blemishes. Even your lover won&amp;rsquo;t want to kiss you.
But there&amp;rsquo;s a cure.
**Left untreated by Congress, Herpes Ex-Im will die. **
The free-market system has built-in defenses against crony diseases like Herpes Ex-Im.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Will Not Vote for Ann Wagner in 2014</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/21/will-not-vote-for-wagner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/21/will-not-vote-for-wagner/</guid>
      <description>There is a tide in the affairs of men. Which, taken at the flood, leads on to fortune; Omitted, all the voyage of their life Is bound in shallows and in miseries. On such a full sea are we now afloat, And we must take the current when it serves, Or lose our ventures.
 Julius Caesar Act 4, scene 3, 218–224
 The problem the Republican Party has, too many people are sitting around, waiting for a wave to take them across the election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Are the Ex-Im Facts Ann Wagner and Claire McCaskill Don&#39;t Want You to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/10/heres-ex-im-facts-ann-wagner-claire-mccaskill-wont-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 23:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/09/10/heres-ex-im-facts-ann-wagner-claire-mccaskill-wont-tell/</guid>
      <description>Rep. Ann Wagner&amp;rsquo;s Heritage Action Score is a disappointing 59. It&amp;rsquo;s about to drop even lower.
Last week, the Republican from Missouri&amp;rsquo;s 2nd Congressional District came out strongly in support of cronyism by endorsing and vowing to fight for extending the Export-Import Bank.
From Wagner&amp;rsquo;s interview with National Public Radio:
 “There is some talk about a short-term reauthorization, perhaps six or seven months on Ex-Im,” she said. “I’d like it to be longer than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Fascinating Results In The Missouri Primary</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/10-curious-results-missouri-primary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/06/10-curious-results-missouri-primary/</guid>
      <description>CORRECTION: My sincerest apologies for an inexcusable error in this post earlier. I erroneously congratulated my friend Martin Baker in the US House 1st District primary. I understand that Martin was about 500 votes short. I failed to verify information I received on the race, and I apologize for my irresponsibility.
Well, this got people talking. (See the comments.)
Yesterday was the Missouri Primary. Congratulations to Rick Stream and Jay Ashcrofton their wins in contested races for St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>