<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NTX on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/ntx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NTX on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 21:13:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/ntx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Print Edition of Fight to Evolve Now Available on Amazon. Rush!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/23/print-edition-of-fight-to-evolve-now-available-on-amazon-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 21:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/23/print-edition-of-fight-to-evolve-now-available-on-amazon-rush/</guid>
      <description>Most of my readers asked for a print edition of my new book, Fight to Evolve: The Government&amp;rsquo;s Secret War on NTX.
Great news! Your book is waiting for you on Amazon. It&amp;rsquo;s just $17.99, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be happy to know that I don&amp;rsquo;t get a penny from the sales. All proceeds go to the Coalition for Safer Drinking and its fight to reduce alcohol&amp;rsquo;s negative effects on health.
If you, like me, prefer electronic books, you can get the Kindle version of Fight to Evolve for just $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe Sex for Alcohol and a Condom for Your Liver - Podcast</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/20/safe-sex-alcohol-condom-liver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 20:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/20/safe-sex-alcohol-condom-liver/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s regress in time to the 1980s.
Remember C. Everett Koop, the Surgeon-General who launched the Safe Sex movement? Koop wanted to curtail the spread of AIDS. The Safe Sex movement started slowly and originally focused on non-monogamous gay men. By 1987, though, everyone was doing it. (Or not doing &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rdquo; as the case may be.) A February 17, 1987 New York Times headline declared &amp;ldquo;Safe Sex Movement Gains Favor Among Heterosexuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ve Been Drinking Wrong All Along PODCAST</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/09/youve-drinking-wrong-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 17:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/09/youve-drinking-wrong-along/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a beautiful day in spring. The sky is radiant and wonderful blue. Birds singing, trees starting to bloom, grass an impossible shade of vibrant green. A cool and welcoming breeze licks your bare skin, your cheeks, and playfully ruffles your hair like a lover.
Your work is done, now, so you sit in your favorite outdoor chair and take in the relaxing, comfortable view. Smell the freshness of spring wildflowers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look for Print Version of Fight to Evolve on April 14</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/07/look-print-version-fight-evolve-april-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 00:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/07/look-print-version-fight-evolve-april-14/</guid>
      <description>Thank you, so much, for asking. (So many have asked.) Fight to Evolve: The Government&amp;rsquo;s Secret War on NTX will be available in print on April 14. Just go to amazon.com and search for Fight to Evolve.
    If you can&amp;rsquo;t wait (and there&amp;rsquo;s no reason to wait) you can buy the Kindle edition right now. It&amp;rsquo;s already #2 bestseller on censorship in the Kindle store.
Amazon offers FREE Kindle readers for just about every device: Mac, Windows, iPhone, iPad, Android phones and tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks for Overwhelming Book Launch!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/06/thanks-overwhelming-book-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 03:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/04/06/thanks-overwhelming-book-launch/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick note because I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the road all week.
Fight to Evolve: The Government&amp;rsquo;s Secret War on NTX just hit Number 2 in Censorship category on the Amazon Kindle store. (These numbers change a lot, so I&amp;rsquo;m posting this screenshot to prove it.)
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_19181&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;630&amp;rdquo;] Fight to Evolve by Willam T. Hennessy Number 2 on Amazon Kindle Store for Censorship.[/caption]
And it&amp;rsquo;s #1 on Hot New Releases!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>