<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2010 on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2010/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2010 on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 13:49:23 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/post/2010/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Longest Year</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/31/the-longest-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 20:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/31/the-longest-year/</guid>
      <description>The year that ends tonight didn’t begin a year a go tomorrow. Nor does it have a number.
I’m not sure when this year started or what to call it. And, as surprising as it may sound, I don’t think I’ll miss it.
Call it the year of the tea party. It lasted 22 months.
We accomplished only two things, really, in this massive human wave.
  We reminded ourselves that we, the people, can still roar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Things to Read in 2011</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/30/8-things-to-read-in-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 13:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/30/8-things-to-read-in-2011/</guid>
      <description>This week last year, I read The 5000 Year Leap. Good book. If you haven’t read it, do so. You might learn some interesting things.
But don’t expect The 5000 Year Leap to change you. Or history. It won’t.
Now, if 70 percent of the US population read it, it might make a difference. Or maybe not. I tend to doubt it, but that’s fodder for a different post.
When tea partiers read books like Glenn Beck’s Common Sense or The 5000 Year Leap, we’re not broadening ourselves—we’re narrowing ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Despots Use Money to Buy Power</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/29/despots-use-money-to-buy-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 17:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/29/despots-use-money-to-buy-power/</guid>
      <description>Politicians don’t seek money. They seek power. They use money to acquire power. Once they have the power, money becomes irrelevant.
Did you see how states behaved last summer? The “Race to the Top” is all you need to know about the relationship between government money, power, and degradation.
The Race to the Top education initiative dangled cash in front of states. Most states, including Missouri, bit. They competed against each other for the privilege of surrendering their sovereignty over education to a DoE overlord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Don’t We Do Something Else?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/27/why-dont-we-do-something-else/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/27/why-dont-we-do-something-else/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I read that. And I saw that. And somebody told me about that, too.
I see the ridiculous charges leveled by ignorant bigots against the Tea Party. I hear the slander on MSNBC and CNN. I know that Ben Jealous and Nancy Pelosi live on lies about you and me the way vampires live on human blood.
I get it.
My immediate urge when I read or hear this nonsense is anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Stories of 2010</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/26/top-10-stories-of-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2010 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/26/top-10-stories-of-2010/</guid>
      <description>This is my opinion, and it’s not all about politics. Nor are they necessarily in any particular order. Save for one. (You’ll see.)
* [Nancy Pelosi](https://www.cnsnews.com/node/55971), [Phil Hare](https://biggovernment.com/publius/2010/04/01/rep-phil-hare-d-il-i-dont-worry-about-the-constitution/), and other Democrats admit their contempt for the US Constitution.** Barack Obama continues [bowing](https://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2009/04/obama_bows_down_to_saudi_king.html) to tin-horn dictators . . . who really are his superiors.** Rep. Russ [Carnahan funnels millions of tax dollars](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;cd=13&amp;amp;ved=0CCsQFjACOAo&amp;amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fgatewaypundit.rightnetwork.com%2F2010%2F10%2Fthats-weird-state-run-media-reports-on-carnahan-wind-farm-scandal%2F&amp;amp;ei=pLwSTfyxAoXGlQfCxvH6Cw&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGqHk_kEl6bWinUxSTFv6rjDZ8M1g&amp;amp;sig2=OGLfK5UEIUZF1jZDypt1Uw) to his family business.** The business world discovers “[gamification](https://blogs.hbr.org/haque/2010/12/unlocking_the_mayor_badge_of_m.html?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed:+harvardbusiness+(HBR.org)),” an idea that will turn marketing upside in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chains of a Different Master</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/25/chains-of-a-different-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/25/chains-of-a-different-master/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the most famous of all of Karl Marx’s writings was the clause “you have nothing to lose but your chains.”
Many people still believe that human beings are chained to corporate masters. Writers like Seth Godin talk about an awakening in which workers refuse to remain cogs in someone else’s machine.
These well-meaning people (some are well-meaning, anyway) have no problem, though with giving more power to a handful of slave-masters in Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/24/merry-christmas-2/</guid>
      <description>Christmas is the holiday about humility.
The humility of the immortal and all powerful and all knowing stooping to become a mere human being.
The humility of God and king to live among the humblest and poorest&amp;ndash;a carpenter&amp;rsquo;s son.
The humility of belonging to a race so broken that our Creator sent his only Son to redeem us.
For me, the humblest part of this season is what I&amp;rsquo;m doing right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Kill the Tea Party</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/how-to-kill-the-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/how-to-kill-the-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>If the Tea Party—or ACORN or the Democratic National Committee or anyone or anything else, for that matter—stays in a perpetual state of heightened negative emotions nothing positive gets accomplished.
The gazelle that flees imaginary lions soon dies of exhaustion. As positive emotions researcher Barbara Frederickson puts it:
 when extreme, prolonged, or contextually inappropriate, negative emotions can trigger a wide array of problems for individuals and for society.
 Phobias develop out of unchecked fear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apologies to Seth Godin and His Readers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/apologies-to-seth-godin-and-his-readers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 19:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/apologies-to-seth-godin-and-his-readers/</guid>
      <description>I tried to manually trackback to Seth Godin’s post on TV from this post.
Between WordPress’s false negatives on reporting success of links, my laptop’s touchy touchpad, and Typepad’s weird trackback URL system, I managed to:
a. Link once to the wrong blog post
b. Link twice to the right blog post
I pride myself on being respectful of blogging etiquette. I hate trackback spam. I hate it even more when I’m the one creating it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not So Fast, Seth</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/not-so-fast-seth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 13:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/23/not-so-fast-seth/</guid>
      <description>I am a big fan of Seth Godin’s thinking. He clearly understands that people are rejecting steep hierarchies where an oligarchy makes all the decisions and the rest of us are expected to blindly follow instructions.
He wrote a wonderful book on the subject. Linchpin: Are You Indispensable?  holds some wisdom (and some fallacy) that will empower you to take control of your life if you listen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Thanks to American Majority</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/22/special-thanks-to-american-majority/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 02:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/22/special-thanks-to-american-majority/</guid>
      <description>American Majority Action deserves a huge dose of the credit for Ed Martin’s tight race for Missouri’s 3rd district in 2010. But their ground help in September and October was only the tip of the iceberg.
Dana Loesch and I met American Majority back in April. Ned Ryun, the founder and president, asked us to speak at the group’s Post-Party Summit in Kansas City. The weekend was fabulous, informative, and fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 reasons why young voters might make a right turn (and how we missed an opportunity with them)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/22/3-reasons-why-young-voters-might-make-a-right-turn-and-how-we-missed-an-opportunity-with-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 02:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/22/3-reasons-why-young-voters-might-make-a-right-turn-and-how-we-missed-an-opportunity-with-them/</guid>
      <description>How many new voters has the tea party movement created? There’s reason to hope that first time voters will begin shifting to the right in 2010. There’s also reason for us on the right to worry.
About 8 million people turned 18 since the 2008 election. While the left undoubtedly brainwashed   many of them before they reached voting age, many others avoided indoctrination through good parenting, good thinking, or simply not paying attention to the left’s message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/22/thank-you-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 23:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/22/thank-you-2/</guid>
      <description>Hennessy’s View is now 255 on Wikio’s Political Blog rankings. I know that’s nothing compared to Gateway Pundit. After 10 years of blogging, though, it’s nice to crack some list somewhere.
If you’d like to see me move higher on this list, please use the social buttons below.
Also, please tell me why you read Hennessy’s View in the comments.
Thanks, again, for a great Christmas present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes a Morris is Just a Morris</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/sometimes-a-morris-is-just-a-morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 05:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/sometimes-a-morris-is-just-a-morris/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch invited Dick Morris onto her radio show today. Dana expected to discuss START with Mr. Morris. But Dick has a mind of his own.
Morris decided, about a minute and a half into a five-minute segment, that he wanted to talk about the 2012 US Senate race in Missouri instead. Specifically, he wanted spend the segment campaigning for Sarah Steelman for the the Republican nomination.
Decide for yourself: here’s the link to Dana’s show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generational Change</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/generational-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/20/generational-change/</guid>
      <description>A man lost in thought is liable to say anything. Anything at all.
A guy sitting behind me at a restaurant in Lambert airport began singing along with the background music. “Burning down the house (do do).”
Perfect.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_5VRhmgUNtM&amp;amp;hl;=en&amp;amp;hd;=1]
November 2, American voters burned down the U.S. House. Before the vote, estimates ranged from 45 to 70 seats switching from Democrats to Republicans. Burning down the house, indeed. The final number was 63.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Good Candidates. Start Now.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/19/get-good-candidates-start-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/19/get-good-candidates-start-now/</guid>
      <description>Conservatives (tea party, et al) and Republicans better learn to get along. Quickly. Just as quickly, the two need to recruit, vet, and prep some A-list candidates. Candidates for offices from President down to school boards.
That’s because the winners in 2012 will either belong to a conservative coalition or the most radical elements of the Democrat Party. Here’s why.
Pollster Frank Luntz points out in today’s Washington Post that the largest ideological faction in the United States is the combination of GOP plus tea partiers:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All-American Alternative to Leftist Omaha Steaks</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/18/all-american-alternative-to-leftist-omaha-steaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 14:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/18/all-american-alternative-to-leftist-omaha-steaks/</guid>
      <description>Jim Hoft of Gateway Pundit exposed Omaha Steak’s leftism yesterday. Omaha pulled its ads from Glenn Beck for ideological reasons.
 We took your comments regarding the Glenn Beck Program to heart. After further review and careful consideration, we have decided to pull all advertising from Glenn Beck programming effective December 20th, 2010.
 Then the president of the company, Bruce Simon, tried to deny his political motives.
If you want to order top quality meats at great prices, you don’t have to put money in a lefty’s pocket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Remarkable Discussion</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/18/a-remarkable-discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 12:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/18/a-remarkable-discussion/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve never heard of The Discussion Club, listen up.
Since 1955, The Discussion Club has brought to St. Louis the heavyweights of the time.
* Milton Friedman** Dr. Erik von Kuehnelt-Leddihn** Henry Regner** M. Stanton Evans** Dr. George C. Roche** Dr. Friedrich A. Von Haye (are you freakin’ kidding me?)** Dr. Russell Kirk (the father of American conservatism)** Arthur Laffer And that’s just the 70s and 80s. The [list of past speakers](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are We the Last Americans?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/07/are-we-the-last-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/07/are-we-the-last-americans/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes nightmares end well.
Sometimes they don’t.
Salon carries a depressing story for the lower 48 of North America. Author Alfred McCoy writes:
 Despite the aura of omnipotence most empires project, a look at their history should remind us that they are fragile organisms. So delicate is their ecology of power that, when things start to go truly bad, empires regularly unravel with unholy speed: just a year for Portugal, two years for the Soviet Union, eight years for France, 11 years for the Ottomans, 17 years for Great Britain, and, in all likelihood, 22 years for the United States, counting from the crucial year 2003.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tea Party’s Real Purpose Is . . .</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/06/the-tea-partys-real-purpose-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/06/the-tea-partys-real-purpose-is/</guid>
      <description>We talk about liberty, limited government, freedom, Constitutional principles, and the like. Those are all relevant to the purposes of the conservative grassroots movement. But are they ends? Or are they just means?
I believe they are means. In the founders’ writings we find clues to the end, even they don’t state it explicitly. Jefferson did. Jay came close. And Adams implicitly understood that end.

Let me ask this: what’s the point of all the work we did in the past two years?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Ways to Make Christmas Season Happier</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/05/2-ways-to-make-christmas-season-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 19:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/05/2-ways-to-make-christmas-season-happier/</guid>
      <description>Is it better to give or to receive?
Before you answer, let’s look at some of the science behind giving. Then let’s look a little deeper.
Dr. Barbara Fredrickson studies the psychology of happiness. About a decade ago, Dr. Fredrickson announced a formula for creating an “upward spiral” of happiness. In other words, she identified what it takes to have happiness breed happiness. The formula applies to individuals, families, groups, and even companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man’s Waning Days?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/29/mans-waning-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 02:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/29/mans-waning-days/</guid>
      <description>It’s easy to wonder whether humanity has simply grown weary of life.
* Yesterday I noted the [inhumanity of Christmas shoppers](https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/28/our-disordered-society/) on Black Friday.** For the past 24 hours, the world has watched the slow release of hundreds of thousands of [classified US diplomatic cables](https://www.latimes.com/news/nationworld/nation/sc-dc-1130-wikileaks-20101129,0,2557036.story).** As I write, [a gunman holds hostages](https://www.cnn.com/2010/CRIME/11/29/wisconsin.hostage/?hpt=T2) at a rural Wisconsin high school.** The [European debt crisis](https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2010/11/29/europes_ominous_reckoning_108078.html) refuses to remain quiet beneath the rug under which it’s been swept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Disordered Society</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/28/our-disordered-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 02:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/28/our-disordered-society/</guid>
      <description>Drudge’s headlines about Black Friday 2010 raise disturbing questions about America’s purpose as a nation.

We degrade ourselves for deals on crap some puppet-master tells us we cannot live without. In the name of Christ’s birth, we reveal ourselves with headlines like “Craze shoppers stampede,” “Marine stabbed,” “Shopper arrested after packing gun,” “Mall food court placed on lockdown,” “Shopper arrested…raging,” “Police called after thousands rush,” “Woman busted.”
We rush Toys-R-Us doors&amp;ndash;angry, armed, and belligerent&amp;ndash;because our society is grossly disordered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Left?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/whats-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/whats-left/</guid>
      <description>Exit polling tells the story. About 60 percent of voters agree with the tea party core principles of government constrained by a constitution and government transparency. Well over half of voters agree with specific measures advanced in the Contract From America, including:
  Balanced budget amendment to the Constitution.
  Elimination of earmarks until the budget is balanced, and then requiring a 2/3 vote.
  Audit the entire damn government, including the Fed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas Have Consequences—Even Stupid Ones</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/ideas-have-consequenceseven-stupid-ones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/14/ideas-have-consequenceseven-stupid-ones/</guid>
      <description>When Barack Obama became president in January 2009, he began a campaign to weaken America. I’m not talking about military cuts; I’m speaking of America’s stature. Barack Obama famously refused to acknowledge American Exceptionalism in 2009. He bowed to kings and princes, then denied doing so, then bowed again and again. His White House has driven down the dollar. Timothy Geithner, Obama’s Secretary of the Treasury, warns that the world economy must “rebalance” with less reliance on America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Courage of Roy Blunt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/13/the-courage-of-roy-blunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 18:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/13/the-courage-of-roy-blunt/</guid>
      <description>When you vote for a candidate for high office, sometimes you do so with fingers crossed. You just don’t know how they’ll handle the new responsibilities. Will they succumb to pressure and influence? Or will they remain true?
Luckily for us, Senator-elect Roy Blunt showed his courage in a recent Wall Street Journal article about the Tea Party and the GOP.
In a year when voters overwhelming demanded changes to business as usual in Washington, Roy Blunt showed he has the rectitude to stand strong for the tried and true practices of obfuscation, political double-speak, and deflection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Election Night</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/03/election-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 06:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/03/election-night/</guid>
      <description>Election Night. Already know that Christine O’Donnell lost. Not surprised. Rubio won going away. Not surprised. Roy Blunt already projected winner in Missouri. No word on Ed Martin, the race I’m most interested in.
I’m usually glued to radio, TV, and internet on election nights. I’m usually In The Know. Sort of a cruel cosmic joke that I’m at 35,000 feet as returns come in for the most important election in a century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shady City Votes and Ego-Trip Riders</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/03/shady-city-votes-and-ego-trip-riders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 06:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/03/shady-city-votes-and-ego-trip-riders/</guid>
      <description>Three precincts in the city of St. Louis delivered 3,800 votes for Carnahan in the last hour of counting. Wahby’s district. Wahby’s wife works for Mayor Francis Slay. They waited until they knew how many votes they needed, then they manufactured them&amp;ndash;typical Dems, in my view.
Now I ask you: how many dead or non-existent people voted in Wahby’s precincts?
Ed Martin won, and everyone knows it. City Democrats have no qualms with committing felonies to steal elections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>614 Days</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/01/614-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 05:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/01/614-days/</guid>
      <description>Six hundred fourteen days from the first Tea Parties to Election Day. That’s 307 days in 2009 and 307 in 2010.
In that time, we’ve met so many people. We’ve made too many friends. (Psychologists and sociologists and anthropologists believe that a person can manage no more than 150 human relationships, so there is such a thing as too many friends.) Most of us, I’m afraid, have seen friendships end, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Party to Congress: Pack Up, Get Out</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/01/tea-party-to-congress-pack-up-get-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 16:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/01/tea-party-to-congress-pack-up-get-out/</guid>
      <description>The clock is ticking on dozens of Democrat congressional careers. And a band of activists in Missouri are helping the losers move.
Operation “Pack Up and Get Out” struck the offices of Rep. Russ Carnahan (D-MO) today. Carnahan is struggling to hold off Republican challenger Ed Martin, an original Tea Partier whose campaign has energized Missouri’s 3rd Congressional District.

“Pack Up and Get Out” delivered 300 moving boxes to the Congressman’s offices in Brentwood, Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make an Election Day Plan</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/01/how-to-make-an-election-day-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 15:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/11/01/how-to-make-an-election-day-plan/</guid>
      <description>“Winning isn’t everything—it’s the only thing.” &amp;ndash; Bud Wilkinson
  Think you can vote without a plan? Maybe you can. Or maybe you’ll get too busy, traffic will be a mess, the weather will turn bad, or your boss will send you on a wild goose chase at 5:30. Without a voting plan, there’s a chance that Missouri will be stuck with a clown like Russ Carnahan.
So let’s make a plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Hear The People Sing?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/31/do-you-hear-the-people-sing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 04:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/31/do-you-hear-the-people-sing/</guid>
      <description>[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u1iBjVlg6lw&amp;amp;w;=480&amp;amp;h;=385] It&amp;rsquo;s been almost two years since we met. At the time, I had no idea where this was going. Or what I was doing.
I still don&amp;rsquo;t know what I&amp;rsquo;m doing, but we all know where America is headed.
Beginning Tuesday, because of your passionate, tireless efforts, America is returning to the right course to meet the destiny our founders envisioned.
On Tuesday, your vote, joined with millions of others, will turn the country around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What If They Turned Off The Traffic Lights?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/16/what-if-they-turned-off-the-traffic-lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 01:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/16/what-if-they-turned-off-the-traffic-lights/</guid>
      <description>A town in England has reduced traffic congestion, pollution, and accidents. One year after the experiment began, the townspeople gushed over the change in the people and the way they drive. One woman’s commute went from twenty minutes to five.
How did this happen?
The town did the opposite of what had always been done. Instead of adding more traffic lights or signs or spy cameras, they went the other direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Decay in the Age of Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/human-decay-in-the-age-of-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/human-decay-in-the-age-of-obama/</guid>
      <description>In 47BC, Julius Caesar assumed dictatorial power in Rome. He instituted “reforms” that transformed the Republic into the Empire. In the process, he became a dictator. Rome’s decent into oblivion began. In 44BC, seeing the damage Caesar’s tyranny and reforms, three men removed Caesar from power by the method of the day.
History moves faster now than it did 2,000 years ago. A megalomaniacal leaders bent on fundamentally transforming a nation can do remarkable damage in the blink of an eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Candidate Who Doesn’t Want You to Know Her</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/the-candidate-who-doesnt-want-you-to-know-her/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/12/the-candidate-who-doesnt-want-you-to-know-her/</guid>
      <description>Political candidates want to meet everyone. “If people would just meet me,” they say, “they’ll realize I’m a regular . . .” guy/gal/tea partier/whatever. This seems a good thing—willing to stand before the voters and be judged.
Missouri’s State Auditor, Susan Montee might want to keep her name, her history, and her record out of the spotlight. That’s because Susan Montee is about as hard left as you get.
Here’ just a sample:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Journalism’s Big News</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/11/big-journalisms-big-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/11/big-journalisms-big-news/</guid>
      <description>It seems impossible that nearly nineteen months have passed since I met Dana Loesch for the first time.
 It was on the sidewalk on Leonor K. Sullivan Blvd, 27 February 2010. Snow flurries drifted and bounced like little kids playing around at a wedding reception. Two-hundred or so people had already arrived, and Dana brought the cutest little megaphone you’ve ever seen. With that megaphone, we announced the first St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victory Center Packed—But More Help Needed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/07/victory-center-packedbut-more-help-needed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 00:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/07/victory-center-packedbut-more-help-needed/</guid>
      <description>Tonight at Victory Center, the phones were packed with volunteers, and it made a difference. We made over 1,600 calls and canvassers visited over 200 homes. But it gets better.

Because of the energy and enthusiasm in the room, the quality of the calls was fantastic. Veteran callers said that the people they spoke to were more engaged and pleasant than on past nights. That’s because success and energy drives enthusiasm, which people respond to even over the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drowning Beauty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/06/drowning-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 03:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/06/drowning-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Someday I’ll write more – much more – on this. But it’s important to remember what’s at stake in America, in the world, this election: beauty.
Totalitarian regimes despise beauty. They bury it in palaces where the rulers roam, their cancerous eyes raking over someone’s masterpiece the way raw sewage pollutes a clear stream after a pipe’s failure.
Regimes, in their attempts to hoard beauty, bury it.
In free America (remember it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irrational History</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/06/irrational-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 18:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/06/irrational-history/</guid>
      <description>Symbols can change history. Sort of.
I was on patrol on the USS John C. Calhoun in January 1992. I sat in the Crew&amp;rsquo;s Lounge. Ed Lesage, a radioman, delivered the latest news from the wire—usually a few days old. I got the first copy. The first story told me that President George H. W. Bush would not be re-elected.
I was right.
This morning, I saw a story on RealClearPolitics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Some Things Go; Fight For Others</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/04/let-some-things-go-fight-for-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 01:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/10/04/let-some-things-go-fight-for-others/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a passage from a fine roman a clef:
 [I]f the worst were to happen and a local armed militia were to descend on me and drive me out as a Jewish alien, their offense mainly would be against the Jew, not against the landowner. And in such a case my concern would be for the U.S. Constitution, not for my investment. The rooms, the rocks, the vegetation had no hold on my vital organs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Different World</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/30/a-different-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/30/a-different-world/</guid>
      <description>While we’ve been building the tea party, the world has changed. Our world has changed.
* Consumers consume less** Inflation is limited to food, fuel, and gold** Experiences and human connections are more important than possessions and promotions** Debt shifted from people and businesses to government—which means to all of us** The government took out a $48,000 loan in your name** Both major parties looked bad when we examined them  When the 112th Congress convenes, the priorities of February 27, 2009, may be irrelevant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power and the Glory</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/29/the-power-and-the-glory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/29/the-power-and-the-glory/</guid>
      <description>_**&amp;ldquo;For over a thousand years Roman conquerors returning from the wars enjoyed the honor of triumph, a tumultuous parade. In the procession came trumpeteers, musicians and strange animals from conquered territories, together with carts laden with treasure and captured armaments. The conquerors rode in a triumphal chariot, the dazed prisoners walking in chains before him. Sometimes his children robed in white stood with him in the chariot or rode the trace horses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Debate’s End</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/27/the-debates-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 03:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/27/the-debates-end/</guid>
      <description>Thirty minutes after the debate’s official end, pods of people remained in the Arnold Rec Center Sunday night: a circle in the vestibule, a half-moon in the center aisle, two or three amorphous clumps up front, the one I belonged to, and the loud groups around Ed Martin.
“Why didn’t Russ Carnahan stay and talk to people,” a young woman asked, implying a contrast with Ed Martin’s happy conversation a few feet away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Has the Fear?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 01:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/who-has-the-fear/</guid>
      <description>For 100 years in America, government, business, and the education establishment built schools and laws about education. The purpose of these government schools and education laws was to produce compliant, unimaginative, order-taking automatons.
Don’t believe me? Here’s Woodrow Wilson, educator and president, speaking on the American plan for education:
 We want one class of persons to have a liberal education, and we want another class of persons, a very much larger class of necessity in every society, to forgo the privilege of a liberal education and fit themselves to perform specific difficult manual tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want to End the Obama Era?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/want-to-end-the-obama-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 00:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/want-to-end-the-obama-era/</guid>
      <description>Share this.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_YXqf_6ug54&amp;amp;hl;=en]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generation Conflicted</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/generation-conflicted/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/22/generation-conflicted/</guid>
      <description>In the tech world, I meet a lot of brilliant, ambitious, hardworking entrepreneurs. These folks are committed to their dreams, working 100+ hour weeks, and paying themselves as little as possible. They stretch investors’ dollars to the limit and hunt for more VC to make dreams come true. They want to create jobs and better lives for many.
Over drinks, these young capitalists talk about three things:
  Easier access to capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Glenn Beck Helping?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/21/is-glenn-beck-helping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 01:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/21/is-glenn-beck-helping/</guid>
      <description>For (at least) the past two nights, Glenn Beck’s program has been spell-bindingly depressing and eye-gougingly infuriating. He’s chronicled the Obama administration’s anti-Constitutional transfer of power and wealth from private Americans to other countries. He’s shown that the administration has no concern over the 2010 election because it has no intention of obeying the laws passed by Congress.

For example, the newly appointed Consumer Protection Czar, a hard-line communist, Elizabeth Warren, is funded directly from the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Afraid to Live</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/20/afraid-to-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 03:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/20/afraid-to-live/</guid>
      <description>Leftist philosophies lead to despotism. Despotism appeals to some people because:
  They don’t have to think.
  They won’t face consequences.
  Problems arise when the people who thought they didn’t want to think decide to think for themselves. Traditionally, the despots either kill or incarcerate the thinkers.
Eventually, too many people think, the prisons overflow, and the people kill or incarcerate the despot.
Instead of living through this cycle of violence again, why don’t we stop the despot now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Magical Moment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/17/a-magical-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 02:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/17/a-magical-moment/</guid>
      <description>On November 5, 1980, ABC News Nightline was devoted to the aftermath of the election. Ronald Reagan won 51-41 over incumbent Jimmy Carter. Republicans took the Senate and picked up 30+ seats in the house.
The YouTube clip below shows us only the beginning of the program. But it’s a great reminder of what lies ahead for movement conservatives. Well, what lies ahead IF we continue to focus on moving the conversation toward first principles and away from the class warfare and Balkanization that Democrats love so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That’s One Awesome Friggin’ Photograph</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/08/thats-one-awesome-friggin-photograph/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/08/thats-one-awesome-friggin-photograph/</guid>
      <description>The venerable Jim Hoft (aka, Gateway Pundit) snapped this shot of the new sign at St. Louis Tea Party Coalition HQ on Hampton.

One year ago this week, we’d just finished a summer of street protests. ObamaCare had been delayed . . . twice. Cap and Trade had been put on hold. Many of us were getting ready to drive up to Quincy, Illinois, for the Midwest’s 9-12 Tea Party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Come to St. Louis If You Can’t Drive to the Beach</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/05/why-you-should-come-to-st-louis-if-you-cant-drive-to-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 16:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/09/05/why-you-should-come-to-st-louis-if-you-cant-drive-to-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Yes, there are three major Tea Party events on 9-12: Washington, Sacramento, and St. Louis. But if you can’t see the Atlantic or the Pacific from your window, why don’t you make the trip to the middle of the country, to the “Gateway to November” Tea Party under the Arch?

I’m hearing from groups in Florida, Georgia, Indiana, Ohio, West Virginia, Texas, Oklahoma, Nebraska, Iowa, and many from Illinois and Kansas who CANNOT WAIT for the 9-12 &amp;ldquo;Gateway to November&amp;rdquo; Tea Party in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innocent Until Proven Conservative</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/innocent-until-proven-conservative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/innocent-until-proven-conservative/</guid>
      <description>Within hours of reports of a firebombing at Rep. Russ Carnahan’s (D-MO) campaign finance office last Tuesday, St. Louis’s leftist bloggers leapt to the cause. In what seems to have been a coordinated attack, Riverfront Times and several progressive blogs and web sites ascribed culpability for the crime to St. Louis Tea Partyers. At one point, Chad Garrison of RFT flatly stated that the suspect “fit the description” of a tea partyer, a statement he later attempted to soften by claiming that firebombing is “too sane” a crime for Tea Partyers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Signs of Economic Disaster</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/3-signs-of-economic-disaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/3-signs-of-economic-disaster/</guid>
      <description>Each day, more economists jump onto the Double-Dip bandwagon. Signs abound that the natural economic recovery that would normally follow a deep recession won’t happen. Instead, the economy is now saddled with so much debt, so many regulations, and such onerous new taxes that the Obama Administration tells us to be happy with 9.5 percent unemployment.

Barack Obama is an economic disaster of the first order.
So why all the pessimism?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barney Frank Comes Home to the Facts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/22/barney-frank-comes-home-to-the-facts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 17:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/22/barney-frank-comes-home-to-the-facts/</guid>
      <description>Barney Frank Comes Home to the Facts.
Remarkable. Is this is a true change in heart, a real wising-up, of one of Congress&amp;rsquo;s biggest Fannie and Freddie supporters? Or is Barney Frank playing some angle here.
Let&amp;rsquo;s hope it&amp;rsquo;s the former. The best thing for America would be an awakening among big government Democrats. Imagine if Frank became a deficit hawk and a Tenther!.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A View From the Back</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/16/a-view-from-the-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 02:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/16/a-view-from-the-back/</guid>
      <description>I approached the Rennick Park Pavilion with a heavy heart for three reasons. At least three.
First, it was yet another night that I would not be home. And tomorrow’s first day of school. The last first day of school for my son, Patrick. I can’t think of that without thinking about his first day of kindergarten—which seems like yesterday—when he insisted on riding the bus. With his little backpack overflowing with supplies listed on a green sheet of paper (Rockwood-Green Pines-K), he stepped onto that bus in August of 1998.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Down Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/12/falling-down-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/12/falling-down-again/</guid>
      <description>One of the most popular and most talked about movies of 1993 was Falling Down, starring Michael Douglas, Barbara Hershey, and Robert Duval.
Douglas played William “D-FENS” Foster, an engineer at a defense contractor who has a really bad day. Some described the movie as “an ordinary man at war with the everyday world.”
Foster became an iconic anti-hero for the people who (stealing Bill Clinton’s line)worked hard and played by the rules, yet found themselves at the bottom of the heap in the post-Cold War era of 1993.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2/3 Think Worst Is Yet to Come for USA</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/11/23-think-worst-is-yet-to-come-for-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 03:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/11/23-think-worst-is-yet-to-come-for-usa/</guid>
      <description>The Wall Street Journal headline is grim:
   Grim Voter Mood Turns Grimmer  Underpinning the gloom: Nearly two-thirds of Americans believe the economy has yet to hit bottom, a sharply higher percentage than the 53% who felt that way in January.
Wow. I think thebarrage of terrible economic news this week has people realizing that you can’t borrow your way out of a debt problem.
So far this fiscal year, the US has paid more in interest on its rapidly rising debt than it’s taken in from all corporate taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Much Damage Can They Do in 84 Days? *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/10/how-much-damage-can-they-do-in-84-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 01:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/10/how-much-damage-can-they-do-in-84-days/</guid>
      <description>A lot.
Today, Congress gave failing states and cities $26 billion in Chinese loans. More failed policies bolstered.
Today, the Federal Reserve Board reversed its plan to pay down the debt in order to put off economic downturn until after the election.
Today, the Fed announced that our future is bleak.
Today, we learned that the government probably overstated 2nd quarter economic growth—by almost double. (h/t Ed Morrissey)
Today, we learned that inventories increased because people and businesses aren’t buying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Freedom Pledge</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/10/healthcare-freedom-pledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 00:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/10/healthcare-freedom-pledge/</guid>
      <description>Ed Martin’s launched the HealthcareFreedomPledge.com site.

Here you can find candidates who committed to protecting your right to choose your own healthcare options.
Great idea. The site contains short statements from candidates for both state and federal office who pledge to defend our basic rights.
Ask candidates in your area to sign the pledge today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nightmarish Carnival of Democrat Mayhem Continues</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/10/nightmarish-carnival-of-democrat-mayhem-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 11:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/10/nightmarish-carnival-of-democrat-mayhem-continues/</guid>
      <description>Congressional Democrats plan to hold a special session in August to pass yet another $26 billion bailout for states. Specifically for states that have create welfare empires they can no longer sustain.
So responsible states now have to pay for irresponsible states at the point of a federal gun.
It looks like the Democrats want to completely bankrupt America before they lose power in January.
Of course, this also gives empty suits like Russ Carnahan an excuse not to debate their opponents, talk to constituents, or hold town halls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Your Why</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/09/live-your-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/09/live-your-why/</guid>
      <description>As we approach the anniversary of Martin Luther King’s “I have a dream” speech, it seems we should both honor Rev. King and learn from that speech.
I can think of no better way to accomplish both goals than to liberally borrow from Simon Sinek’s fantastic blog post about that speech and the importance of living your “why.”
 On August 28, 1963, 250,000 people from across the country descended on the Mall in Washington, D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Events Coming Up</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/09/3-events-coming-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/09/3-events-coming-up/</guid>
      <description>I am very honored by the invitations I get to speak to various clubs and organizations around Greater St. Louis, including Illinois. This August, I have the chance to meet two groups and to guest host a radio show.
On August 18, I’ll speak to the Meramec Township Republican Committee.
On August 26, I’ll be speaking at the North County Republican Club meeting at Yac’s Restaurant at 407 Dunn Rd. in Florissant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed: Other Shoe About to Drop</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/fed-other-shoe-about-to-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 03:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/fed-other-shoe-about-to-drop/</guid>
      <description>The only two people in the world who believe the economy is healthy and vibrant are Barack Obama and Joe Biden.

Now, the Federal Reserve Board’s Open Market Committee (FOMC) is getting ready to announce that the economy is sicker than we thought.
 Although Fed policymakers still believe the basic trajectory of the economy remains one of moderate expansion, there may be more attention given to heightened dangers of a sharp slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Return of Marcos</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/the-return-of-marcos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/08/the-return-of-marcos/</guid>
      <description>No,not Marie Antoinette. Too clichéd and too . . . ancient. Rather, Michelle Obama’s opulent life rekindles fond memories of Imelda Marcos.
Imelda Marcos was the wife of Philippines President Ferdinand Marcos. Marcos was more a dictator than a president. Another parallel. In 1986, the Filipinos and the world had enough. Marcos was deposed and Imelda’s extravagance exposed.
Imelda Marcos’s closet contained 2,700 pairs of shoes. That’s a different pair of shoes every day for 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd Time, No Regrets</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/3rd-time-no-regrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 01:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/3rd-time-no-regrets/</guid>
      <description>On September 12, we make our third trip to the Arch Steps to rally our spirits and inform our neighbors.
[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5j8-s_9-y2E&amp;amp;w;=425&amp;amp;h;=355]
On February 27, 2009, we met for the for first time. It started a revolution. It disrupted lives. It promises to change the course of history, the way the great New Madrid Earthquake forever altered the course of the Mississippi River.
Over the past 18 months, we’ve come a long way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On to November</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/on-to-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 17:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/on-to-november/</guid>
      <description>The primaries are over.
I honestly believe that in the St. Louis area, the rightward-most, viable candidate won each of the key votes. The people of Missouri are in a position to make historical shifts in our Washington representation. And those shifts are just the first step and restoring America’s First Principles.

View Full Album
Roy Blunt is a conservative. He will be a big step up for conservatism in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Priceless! Boy Scouts Boo Bo</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/priceless-boy-scouts-boo-bo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 16:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/07/priceless-boy-scouts-boo-bo/</guid>
      <description>I guess this is the Boy Scout Jamboree. It’s too wonderful to research.
On the big screen, we see The One, The Despot, Barack “Ass Kicker” Obama.
In the foreground, we see and hear Boy Scouts booing and mocking and jeering.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oAWsy7VV8oE&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]
Part of me wishes the Boy Scouts were more respectful of the President of the United States, no matter who occupies that office. But another part of me believes that Obama is such a disgraceful, un-American anomaly that to disrespect him is to honor the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Your Bill and Shove It, Mr. President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/04/take-your-bill-and-shove-it-mr-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 15:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/04/take-your-bill-and-shove-it-mr-president/</guid>
      <description>Missouri voters roundly rejected ObamaCare, all of its works, and all of its empty promises.
By an overwhelming, unmistakable 71 percent, we said to the Obama Regime, “Take this bill and shove it.”
The overwhelming passage was a slap in the face to the Missouri Hospital Association and to BJC President Steven Lipstein who spent nearly $500,000 trying to convince their employees that the hospital chain profits trump the Constitution. Pathetic worms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond The Dip</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/03/beyond-the-dip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/03/beyond-the-dip/</guid>
      <description>I received a couple of phone calls this morning. Maybe because of the primary election in Missouri. Or is the stifling, stale heat of August that drove the calls? Either way, I believe the calls represent very good news.
We survived The Dip (Godin, 2007).
  
Back in April, I sensed a dip in the burgeoning grassroots movement. By June 1, my suspicions were confirmed and I blogged about The Dip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Questions You Must Answer Right Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/01/3-questions-you-must-answer-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 16:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/01/3-questions-you-must-answer-right-now/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Missouri becomes the first state in the union to vote on ObamaCare. If being a Tea Partyer means anything, it means you vote Yes on Prop C on Tuesday. I urge not to wing it.
Most elections, I wake up and think “it’s election day.” Then I take a shower and go to work. I think about stopping to vote, but I don’t want to walk into the office at 9:00.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick! What do 1994 and 2010 have in common?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/30/quick-what-do-1994-and-2010-have-in-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 01:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/30/quick-what-do-1994-and-2010-have-in-common/</guid>
      <description>Besides . . . lots?
In 1994, Dan Rostenkowski, then Chairman of the House Ways and Means Committee, was convicted of felony fraud charges.
  https://abcnews.go.com/assets/player/walt2.6/flash/SFP_Walt.swf
In 2010, Charlie Rangel, Chairman of the House Ways and Means Committee, is found guilty of ethics violations. (And BO says it’s time for him to go.)
In 1994, Democrats were on the ropes after winning the House, the Senate, and the White House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJC’s Overlord</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/27/bjcs-overlord/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 23:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/27/bjcs-overlord/</guid>
      <description>Steven Lipstein is president of BJC Hospitals. He is part of well-funded, national campaign to deny Missourians the right to NOT purchase something they don’t want.
In a preposterous letter to his employees, Lipstein attempts to argue that human beings have no right to say “no” to health insurance. As self-anointed overlord of our spending, Lipstein questions the very foundations of America’s guiding philosophy when he writes:
 Can a citizen decide not to buy health care services, and with that decision, not be required to buy health insurance?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Ready to Tea Party?????????</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/26/are-you-ready-to-tea-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 03:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/26/are-you-ready-to-tea-party/</guid>
      <description>The weekend of September 12, 2010, will be The St. Louis Tea Party Weekend. We have the Arch steps.
We have the Overlook Stage.
We have the streets.
We have the people.
We have the hunger.
We have the voice.
We have the people.
We have the stars.
We have the plan.
We have the people.
We have the cause.
We have the dedication.
We have the people.
We have the sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shark-Jumping Anderson Cooper Style</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/over-exposed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 04:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/over-exposed/</guid>
      <description>Just before her beatification, Shirley Sherrod jumped the shark.

On Thursday, CNN’s Anderson Cooper let the embattled former USDA director talk for an hour. Bad idea. It was bad for CNN, bad for viewers, and really bad for Sherrod, who lost her mind on the air. This is what she said:
 I think he’d [Andrew Breitbart would] like to get us stuck back in the times of slavery, That’s where I think he’d like to see all black people end up again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/1-do-the-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 02:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/25/1-do-the-math/</guid>
      <description>Have you noticed few people call Barack Obama “The One” anymore? “The Golfer” or “The Vacationer” is more like it. Something less than One, by any measure.

Still, with each passing day and each new, permanent crisis, it seems like BO just ain’t up to the job of President. Nothing new. When Jimmy Carter’s incompetence became obvious, the lefty press developed a theory that the job had simply grown too complex for one man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Wronged Shirley Sherrod?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/22/who-wronged-shirley-sherrod/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 22:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/22/who-wronged-shirley-sherrod/</guid>
      <description>To no one’s surprise, leftist idiots and hate-mongers like David Frum, Keith Olbermann, and the staff of CNN point their crooked, hostile fingers toward Andrew Breitbart as the cause of Shirley Sherrod’s pain. That’s like blaming Ron Howard for the problems on board Apollo 13.
What Breitbart and Big Government did regarding Ms. Sherrod was identical to what every television news program does every day of the week. They produced a news story based on information reasonably available to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innocent Victims</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/20/innocent-victims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 04:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/20/innocent-victims/</guid>
      <description>When the NAACP’s Ben Jealous fired a reckless volley at the Tea Party, he missed his marked and struck an innocent woman.
One week ago tonight, the news cycle was alive with the excitement of a heavyweight fight. The NAACP’s Ben Jealous needed to raise money and restore a sagging membership. He decided to pick a fight with the Tea Party.
On Monday, the NAACP leaked a resolution to the Kansas City Star that stated:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I know where you’ll be on July 24</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/18/i-know-where-youll-be-on-july-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/18/i-know-where-youll-be-on-july-24/</guid>
      <description>You’ll be in Grove Park in Grafton, Illinois, for:
ALTON IL. T.E.A PARTY FIRST ANNIVERSARY
“1776 FREEDOM RALLY”
Saturday, July 24th 4pm-7pm
Think about it. You’ve Fast Eddie’s right there. You’ve got two of the most haunted towns in America with Grafton and Alton. Great history, including homes that were critical to the Underground Railroad.
[Map of Grafton]
In short, you get to help make history in a place where history was made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tea Party Is Intolerant . . . of Racism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/18/the-tea-party-is-intolerant-of-racism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/18/the-tea-party-is-intolerant-of-racism/</guid>
      <description>Between a touch of the flu and the flurry of activity over this very issue, I missed the best, most direct breakdown of Ben Jealous&amp;rsquo;s misguided and hypocritical attack on the Tea Party. Read this column by Michael Graham on BostonHerald.com dated Thursday, July 15.
Money quote:
 When you’re looking for bigots at a Tea Party rally, they’re on the fringe. When you’re looking for them at the NAACP, they’re on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Just Joined Conservative TV Online. Will You?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/17/i-just-joined-conservative-tv-online-will-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 21:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/17/i-just-joined-conservative-tv-online-will-you/</guid>
      <description>For the past seventeen months, Alex Rife has covered the conservative movement with the highest quality video available. His work even got me on The Daily Show with Jon Stewart.
For Alex to continue his video apostolate, he needs our help.
I just joined his network for $5 a month. I hope you will, too. Today.
Alex has invested thousands of dollars and thousands of hours of his time in our mission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Took a Stand Against the NAACP</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/16/why-we-took-a-stand-against-the-naacp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 00:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/16/why-we-took-a-stand-against-the-naacp/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it is personal.

Beginning with a simple blog post in February 2009, the St. Louis Tea Party Coalition has attracted over 40,000 people to dozens of events and online crusades. The vast majority of these folks represent America’s highest ideals in character and citizenship. We are educated, polite, and patriotic. We are stand-up people who fix our own problems and earn our own livings. We are not perfect, of course, but we understand that no one else can live our lives for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Crap! Gov’t Shuts Down 73k Blogs</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/16/holy-crap-govt-shuts-down-73k-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 21:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/16/holy-crap-govt-shuts-down-73k-blogs/</guid>
      <description>Claim is it’s a law enforcement issue. But under the Obama Regime, anything seems possible. Anything at all.
I will spend this weekend backing up and downloading my blogs.
Who know. This could revitalize the mimeograph machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fighting Back Against NAACP Defamation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/13/fighting-back-against-naacp-defamation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 12:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/13/fighting-back-against-naacp-defamation/</guid>
      <description>The NAACP has decided that it’s worth time to call 20 million American patriots “racists” for advancing liberty and economic opportunity.
At midnight, the St. Louis Tea Party Coalition sent a resolution condemning the NAACP’s bigotry and hatred to its Washington bureau.
The Tea Party’s principles are simple and clear:
* Smaller federal government** Lower taxes** Fiscal responsibility** National defense** Federalism  Those are precisely the tools to lift all Americans out of poverty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Partisan Consensus: We’re Screwed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/12/bi-partisan-consensus-were-screwed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 00:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/12/bi-partisan-consensus-were-screwed/</guid>
      <description>What if: In January, a new Republican Congress is sworn in. First up on the agenda? A bi-partisan report stating that Congress must enact the most draconian tax increases and entitlement cuts in history or face total economic collapse.

That’s the scenario developing.
President Obama appointed a bi-partisan commission to make recommendations about the US government’s debt. The commission will not report out until after the November 2010 elections, but the leaders—Republican Alan Simpson and Democrat Erskine Bowles&amp;ndash;have given some warning about what we can expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Plan to Punish Voters</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/democrats-plan-to-punish-voters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 22:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/democrats-plan-to-punish-voters/</guid>
      <description>Democrats are planning to punish the American people with draconian, destructive legislation during the lame duck session following November’s election, according the Wall Street Journal.
 That&amp;rsquo;s why there have been signs in recent weeks that party leaders are planning an ambitious, lame-duck session to muscle through bills in December they don&amp;rsquo;t want to defend before November. Retiring or defeated members of Congress would then be able to vote for sweeping legislation without any fear of voter retaliation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We&#39;ve Made a Difference</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2010 18:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/10/how-weve-made-a-difference/</guid>
      <description>When you give over most of your private time to a cause, you need some feedback. We got some from former Reagan speechwriter Peggy Noonan on Friday: The Summer of the Angry Mob
[caption id=&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;521&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Dana&amp;rsquo;s Famous &amp;lsquo;Meet the Mob&amp;rsquo; Blog&amp;rdquo;][/caption]
Ms. Noonan reflected on the Townhall Revolt which began in St. Louis one year ago. Writes Noonan:
 When Rep. Russ Carnahan held a town hall meeting at a community college in Missouri on July 20, he tried patiently to explain that ObamaCare not only would be deficit-neutral, it would save money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A lovely trip down memory lane</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/08/a-lovely-trip-down-memory-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 03:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/08/a-lovely-trip-down-memory-lane/</guid>
      <description>1980 [youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PsDe-8cOSYY&amp;amp;hl;=en]
Reagan didn’t transform America. You did. All Reagan supplied was the blueprint, the story that brought economics and history to life.
You will do it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please Forgive Late Comment Approvals</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/07/please-forgive-late-comment-approvals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 23:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/07/please-forgive-late-comment-approvals/</guid>
      <description>I have had very limited internet access since July 2. I just approved a batch. Not censoring&amp;ndash;just haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to see what&amp;rsquo;s out there.
Thanks for your patience.
Bill</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Missouri US Senate Race Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/02/latest-missouri-us-senate-race-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 21:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/07/02/latest-missouri-us-senate-race-poll/</guid>
      <description>Rasmussen Report has the latest numbers from the Missouri Senate race.
The poll does not include any mention of Republican candidate Chuck Purgason. Purgason seems to be enjoying something of a surge. He’s doffed his toupee and traded the Bolo tie for a regular one. And Purgason’s released a radio commercial in key areas around the state.
Rasmussen finds strong support for Roy Blunt among those who consider themselves tea partyers:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Have Hearings</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/30/why-we-have-hearings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 01:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/30/why-we-have-hearings/</guid>
      <description>Elena Kagan reminds me of Norm Peterson’s (Cheers) meltdown in front the brewery president just before he landed his dream job as a beer taster. Poor Elena can’t remember the simplest things—like her own handwriting.
 
Today, Democrat Arlen Specter warned that he may have to vote “no.”
She might not be the infanticidal maniac some claim. Instead, she seems to be devoid of any substantial legal thought whatsoever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Night at the Ball Park</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/30/a-night-at-the-ball-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 00:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/30/a-night-at-the-ball-park/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes things just happen.
As Jim Durbin points out, last night’s St. Louis Tea Party Night at the Ball Game was a total fluke. A mix-up left us with 46 tickets to last night’s Cardinal’s game against Arizona. (Long story.) But this tea party thing that started over a year ago seems to generate its own publicity.

But the real story, to me, is what happened last night. Three incidents vindicated the shift toward more community building work, even if that work comes at the expense of big, boisterous rallies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Achieve</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/29/how-to-achieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 12:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/29/how-to-achieve/</guid>
      <description>When a family’s children are small, the family has such unity of purpose. Mom, Dad, and all the kids climb into the mini-van or the SUV and head to the store. From there, they visit her parents. Then stop at McDonald’s on the way home. If one of the older kids is involved in an organized program, the whole family attends.

At bath time, the younger ones are bathed in batch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Tea Party on Kudlow</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/the-real-tea-party-on-kudlow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/the-real-tea-party-on-kudlow/</guid>
      <description>Thanks, again, to Larry Kudlow for asking me to talk about tea party things on Friday, June 25.
https://plus.cnbc.com/rssvideosearch/action/player/id/1530503565/code/cnbcplayershare
The Kudlow Rehttps://www.cnbc.com/id/15838446/port airs weeknights at 6:00 p.m. CT on CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Answer Chavez</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/how-to-answer-chavez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 23:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/how-to-answer-chavez/</guid>
      <description>Communist dictator Hugo Chavez has has stolen eleven oil rigs owned by the American company Helmerich and Payne. As Reuters points out, Chavez has now nationalized oil, telecommunications (including news), power, steel, and banking.
If you’re keeping score, Chavez leads Obama 5-3, as Obama so far has managed to seize only banking, automotive, and healthcare. But Obama has vowed a comeback.
Over the weekend, I had the pleasure of cutting and splitting some oak and hickory with a friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Insults Americans . . . Again</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/obama-insults-americans-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 23:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/obama-insults-americans-again/</guid>
      <description>An arrogant and distracted Barack Obama appeared at a press conference for the G20 Summit today. His purpose: to insult, threaten, and cajole the American people from an international stage.
 I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because I said I was going to do it and I think it&amp;rsquo;s the right thing to do. People should learn that lesson about me because next year when I start presenting some very difficult choices to the country, I hope some of these folks who are hollering about deficits and debt step-up because I&amp;rsquo;m calling their bluff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Blink (you’ll miss the recovery)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/22/dont-blink-youll-miss-the-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/22/dont-blink-youll-miss-the-recovery/</guid>
      <description>The stock market reacted mildly to some devastating economic news today. In fact, the stock market appears to be in denial about the state of America’s economy.
Existing home sales fell in May. As of this morning, economists expected a six percent increase.
Economists expect new home sales to be worse than existing home sales.
And economists expected home sales to fall off the table in July and for the remainder of 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Overconfidence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/21/how-to-avoid-overconfidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 00:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/21/how-to-avoid-overconfidence/</guid>
      <description>Do you worry that conservative grassroots might get overconfident and blow our chance to stop the advance of socialism in America?
I do. I am concerned that we keep repeating the same tactics to the same audiences until both the audience and the actors become . . . well, bored.
When I read stories like this one, that GOP sentiment is at an all-time high, I worry that some on our side might decide they can go back to their regularly scheduled programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>849 Reasons You’ll Never Succeed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/19/849-reasons-youll-never-succeed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 20:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/19/849-reasons-youll-never-succeed/</guid>
      <description>View Full Album
Major General Stephen Layfield, the reviewing officer at the Navy’s June 11 Boot Camp Graduation, introduced my son, AT Jack Hennessy, and 848 of Jack’s fellow sailors to America&amp;rsquo;s enemies. He mocked at our enemies’ plots to destroy America, pointing out that before him stood “eight hundred and forty-nine reasons why you’ll never succeed.”
The crowd of about 4,000 roared. The sailors, in ranks, could not even clap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Reason to Read Playboy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/16/top-reason-to-read-playboy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 02:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/16/top-reason-to-read-playboy/</guid>
      <description>The Tea Party phenomenon has been with us for almost a year and a half already. We finally made it to the pages of America’s most venerable . . . um, girly magazine.
_Rogues of K Street _is an anonymous Washington insider’s view of the most effective and expansive political movement in at least half a century.
While the author may have overstated my contributions to the cause, the expose is important for historical purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Oil Leak</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/16/the-washington-oil-leak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/16/the-washington-oil-leak/</guid>
      <description>You would think that the basement of the White House was gushing 60,000 barrels of oil a day, wouldn’t you? After all, President Obama’s entire response to the greatest ecological disaster of modern times has been empower Washington, DC.
The disasters are in the Gulf of Mexico, Mr. President, and in the latest Gallup and Rasmussen polls.
Politicians who worship at the alter of omnipotent government have no answers to problems outside of government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday Night Throwdown</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/15/thursday-night-throwdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 12:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/15/thursday-night-throwdown/</guid>
      <description>ST. LOUIS TEA PARTY HOSTS A PARTY
Register Here
AT SKY MUSIC LOUNGE IN BALLWIN
  
**Folks, we decided that we can&amp;rsquo;t be all serious all the time! We need to have some fun, too! Sky Music Lounge in Ballwin is a fabulous place to share some adult beverages and have a good time. **
Register Now
Come join Dana Loesch of 97.1 FM, Jim Hoft, our very ownGateway****Pundit, Bill Hennessy of the St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Feed the Democrats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/14/dont-feed-democrats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 03:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/14/dont-feed-democrats/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_10218&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;260&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Democrat Congressman attacks college student&amp;rdquo;]  [/caption]
In less than twenty-four hours, the left has demonstrated its incapacity for civilized living by physically assaulting a college student, then exclaiming the virtues of physical assaults on reporters.
Background
A Democrat member of Congress assaulted a college student. The assault, shown on two video angles, was unprovoked (unless asking a simple, closed question is now cause for violence) andcontinuing long past the point at which the victim said stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Israel</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/13/go-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 23:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/13/go-israel/</guid>
      <description>No, I’m not a war monger. But peace is not the absence of war. It’s the presence of peace.

If you live in Israel, you are not at peace. You are at war. War against a massive body of people who want to destroy you before they move on to destroy Christendom. If Christendom doesn’t destroy itself first.
So let’s all thank Israel for standing tall on the front lines of this epic battle between good and evil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Points on Tea Party Popularity Poll (times 2)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/08/7-points-on-tea-party-popularity-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 00:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/08/7-points-on-tea-party-popularity-poll/</guid>
      <description>A Washington Post/ABC News poll shows a major shift in sentiment toward (against?) the tea party movement.
I would not challenge the accuracy of the results which show the tea party’s popularity waning among Southerners and people 18 to 29. In fact, the poll shows that a full 50 percent of Americans now have a negative view of the tea party.
Sure, there may have been some chicanery with the questions to skew the results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Steps to Launch Conservative Revolution</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/08/4-steps-to-launch-conservative-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 22:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/08/4-steps-to-launch-conservative-revolution/</guid>
      <description>Thirty-two years ago this month, the modern conservative movement was born.
The movement began with a local issue in a single state. Howard Jarvis of California succeeded in rolling back that state’s property taxes. Voters ignored Governor Jerry Brown’s apocalyptic predictions and captured the imaginations of a nation. After decades of government growth, the people of America’s largest state said, “Enough!”

As economist Stephen Moore wrote on cato.org a dozen years ago:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing: United Church of Christ Advancing Islam?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/07/disturbing-united-church-of-christ-advancing-islam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 23:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/07/disturbing-united-church-of-christ-advancing-islam/</guid>
      <description>This is disturbing. A St. Louis area “Christian” church, Parkway United Church of Christ, on N. Ballas is promoting Islam on its sign.

This photo was snapped today, June 7, 2010 by Marcia Behr of St. Louis.
While it’s understandable that a Christian church would treat Muslims as children of God, we are obliged to do so in the context of their prayerful conversion to Christ. Tolerance does not require submission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ouch: Obama loses the Left: suddenly, it&#39;s cool to bash Barack</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/06/ouch-obama-loses-the-left-suddenly-its-cool-to-bash-barack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 01:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/06/ouch-obama-loses-the-left-suddenly-its-cool-to-bash-barack/</guid>
      <description>Supporting Obama now seen as . . . naive nostalgia.
     It is an irony of Obama&amp;rsquo;s presidency - which came into being because he was the unBush - that it shares some of the worst traits of his predecessor&amp;rsquo;s administration. Among these are insularity and a blinkered arrogance.
    Obama has never been wracked by self-doubt and he is unusually self-contained for a politician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Explain the Uselessness of Teachers’ Unions</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/03/how-to-explain-the-uselessness-of-teachers-unions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 04:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/03/how-to-explain-the-uselessness-of-teachers-unions/</guid>
      <description>America’s coolest governor explains it all:
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ksLlAi3iIc&amp;amp;color1;=0xb1b1b1&amp;amp;color2;=0xd0d0d0&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;feature;=player_embedded&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Ignore Critics</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/03/how-to-ignore-critics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 23:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/03/how-to-ignore-critics/</guid>
      <description>This fantastic quote comes from Nasim Taleb (author of The Black Swan) via Timothy Ferriss (author of _The Four-Hour Work WeekI). _
 Robustness is when you care more about the few who like your work than the multitude who hates it (artists); fragility is when you care more about the few who hate your work than the multitude who loves it (politicians).
 Dazzling, really. Imagine what we could accomplish by ignoring the haters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Solve Every Problem</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/02/how-to-solve-every-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 00:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/02/how-to-solve-every-problem/</guid>
      <description>A friend of mine explained an interesting theory to me the other day.
“The natural tendency of the universe is to level everything,” he said. “This entropic force leads us to just ‘go with the flow.’ But what makes us human—what built civilization and made man noble—was when we finally resisted entropy. When we built a levy to keep our village from flooding, or when we learned to lure and trap, then farm, animals instead of tracking them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Jo Ann Emerson’s a Conservative . . .</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/02/if-jo-ann-emersons-a-conservative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/02/if-jo-ann-emersons-a-conservative/</guid>
      <description>then I’m a Hottentot. (by Bob McCarty )
She’s supporting Bob Casey’s bill to take your money and give it to union fat cats.
And she provides many channels to contact her. Let her know if you’re against a bailout for union bosses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dip</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/01/the-dip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 01:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/01/the-dip/</guid>
      <description>Seth Godin is one of my favorite writers, thinkers, marketers, and presenters. Everything he writes is worth your time reading. Two of his books stand out for me. One is Tribes, because Tribes describes the whole Tea Party experience perfectly. And he wrote it a year before the Tea Party things started.
Right now, though, my other favorite Godin book serves as a question and a guide for the Tea Party movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Great Way to Relieve Stress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/one-great-way-to-relieve-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 22:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/one-great-way-to-relieve-stress/</guid>
      <description>A new poll shows American’s are stressed out. Almost half of Americans say they’re under moderate to severe financial stress.
I feel it, too. Financially, emotionally, and chronologically.
While my book Zen Conservatism won’t fix all your problems, it will help you deal with what’s going on in America a little better.
From now until Father’s Day, I’m giving you $4.95 off the cover price, so you can get the book for just $10 plus shipping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Memorial Day Penance</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/a-memorial-day-penance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 18:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/a-memorial-day-penance/</guid>
      <description>I ran to Walgreen’s at lunch. I needed some medication—maybe for a cold? I don’t remember for sure. While I was there, I picked up a Muscle Milk and a protein bar so I wouldn’t have to make another stop. I had only about 20 minutes to complete the circuit before my next meeting.
Returning to work, I hit a traffic jam in an unusual place. The outer road was backed up—something I’d never seen before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Are We For?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/what-are-we-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 17:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/what-are-we-for/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back, the Christian Science Monitor asked me to write an op-ed. The subject was, “If the Tea Party ran America, how would things change; and why do you think you’ll win?”
The call was my opportunity to break from the easy, unassailable position that things are bad and getting worse. It meant coming up with a solution or two. And solutions already find disagreement somewhere.
For over a year I’ve said that the Tea Party movement, begun out of anger, must shift its energy over time from anger to solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Incompetence Leaves Americans At Risk</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/obamas-incompetence-leaves-americans-at-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 08:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/30/obamas-incompetence-leaves-americans-at-risk/</guid>
      <description>It took almost three years of Jimmy Carter’s dangerously naive worldview before the world rushed in. By “rushed in,” I mean the Soviet Union rushed into Afghanistan, Iranian radicals rushed into the US Embassy in Tehran, and Cuban-backed communists rushed into every Central and South American country they could.
These aggressions resulted from a world perception that Jimmy Carter was unwilling to use America’s arsenal for good. Additionally, following Vietnam and observing American culture, the world surmised that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reason TV Destroys Hillary Clinton’s Tax Theories</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/reason-tv-destroys-hillary-clintons-tax-theories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 21:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/reason-tv-destroys-hillary-clintons-tax-theories/</guid>
      <description>Hillary Clinton opened her mouth this week—the same mouth that she insisted on opening during the campaign, resulting in our most corrupt and juvenile president ever.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wzg0dGrfP60&amp;amp;color1;=0xb1b1b1&amp;amp;color2;=0xd0d0d0&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;feature;=player_embedded&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Failure of Leadership *UPDATES*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/total-failure-of-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 17:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/29/total-failure-of-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama’s incompetent, confused, and contradictory handling of the Gulf oil spill reveals a man unfit for any position of authority.
As Peggy Noonan pointed out in a painfully honest Wall Street Journal column on May 28, we know now that Barack Obama is an empty suit, a child playing grown-up.
 I wonder if the president knows what a disaster this is not only for him but for his political assumptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Ways to Stop Democrat Sen. Bob Casey From Stealing Your Tax Money to Reimburse SEIU for Bribing Media Matters and Huffington Post</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/28/3-ways-to-stop-democrat-sen-bob-casey-from-stealing-your-tax-money-to-reimburse-seiu-for-bribing-media-matters-and-huffington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 01:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/28/3-ways-to-stop-democrat-sen-bob-casey-from-stealing-your-tax-money-to-reimburse-seiu-for-bribing-media-matters-and-huffington-post/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch and 24th State have revealed the ring of corruption that extends from St. Louis bloggers and local St. Louis leftist rag, through SEIU, to Media Matters and Huffington Post.
An additional crook in this den of thieves is Democrat Senator Bob Casey of Pennsylvania. Casey has introduced yet another bailout package. This time, the bailout is intended to repay corrupt unions like SEIU and AFL-CIO for bankrupting their members’ retirements by bribing the media and politicians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taxpayers to Bailout SEIU?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/24/taxpayers-to-bailout-seiu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 03:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/24/taxpayers-to-bailout-seiu/</guid>
      <description>Senator Bob Casey (D-PA) wants you to pay $165 billion to bail out organized crimeunions. Actually, the bill heading toward taxpayers is unlimited and could reach into the trillions:
 Although right now taxpayers could possibly be on the hook for $165 billion, the liability could essentially be unlimited because these pensions have to be paid out until the workers die.
 Remember why we took to the streets for the first Tea Party Protests in 2009?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francis Howell Has a Sicko Teacher</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/24/francis-howell-has-a-sicko-teacher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 02:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/24/francis-howell-has-a-sicko-teacher/</guid>
      <description>Celeste is an eighteen-year-old student in the Francis Howell High School.
Celeste’s fellow students and, apparently, a teacher named Debra Blessman are bullying and abusing the girl. Celeste’s sin? Conservatism.
Bob McCarty tells the story better than I can. Dana Loesch has been all over this story. There’s a facebook page dedicated to supporting Celeste, which everyone should like, even those of us who hate facebook.
I should point out that, to date, the school’s administrators are standing behind the abusive teach, Blessman, who calls Celeste a “tea bagger” and encourages the students to mock the girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Obama Using SEIU to Terrorize Citizens?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/22/is-obama-using-seiu-to-terrorize-citizens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/22/is-obama-using-seiu-to-terrorize-citizens/</guid>
      <description>Interesting. Mounting evidence suggests [the White House may have been complicit](If so, even Democrats in Congress would be forced to open impeachment investigations) in SEIU’s terrorism (as defined by U.S. Patriot Act) of a banker’s teenage son.

Quit the SEIU. No decent person would belong to an organization that openly, and with the federal government’s approval, uses terrorism to get its way.
Quit the DC Metro Police Force. The President is using you to promote domestic terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grading my prediction for 2009</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/grading-my-prediction-for-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 04:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/grading-my-prediction-for-2009/</guid>
      <description>On December 28, 2008, I published my predictions for 2009. I should have graded myself in January, but I was still on hiatus from Hennessy’s View. So let’s take a look.
The Dow: The Dow trades within a range of 1,000 points with a daily average closing of 8,500.
Grade: D. The average would be a pain to figure out, but it looks like it was closer 9800.
GDP and Economy: By July, everyone pretty much calls the situation &amp;ldquo;Great Depression II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8,000 Dow? *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/8000-dow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/8000-dow/</guid>
      <description>So says Yale economist Nouriel Roubini in an interview today on CNBC.
 &amp;ldquo;There are some parts of the global economy that are now at the risk of a double-dip recession,&amp;rdquo; said Roubini, head of Roubini Global Economics. &amp;ldquo;From here on I see things getting worse.&amp;rdquo;
 
Roubini’s comments came in response to a 376 point drop in the Dow Industrials. Nasdaq and S&amp;amp;P 500 were off significantly as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Must Suck to be an Incumbent</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/19/it-must-suck-to-be-an-incumbent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 12:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/19/it-must-suck-to-be-an-incumbent/</guid>
      <description>Whether you’re the party darling or the federal office holder, 2010 is shaping up to be your last year in politics.
In Kentucky, Tea Party Republican, Rand Paul, opened a can of whoop-ass on Republican party favorite, Trey Grayson. No single race proves the strength or impact of the Tea Party, but races like Paul’s demonstrate that the right candidate with the right campaign team with the strong backing of the Tea Party and 9-12 Project can blow away the party candidate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poll: Tim Burns Can Take Murtha’s Seat</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/poll-tim-burns-can-take-murthas-seat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 03:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/poll-tim-burns-can-take-murthas-seat/</guid>
      <description>The final poll before Tuesday’s special election to fill Jack Murtha’s unexpired seat in the U.S. House shows that Republican Tim Burns is neck and neck with Democrat and pork barrel specialist Mark Critz. (Yes, Critz’s campaign is funded by lobbyists and special interests.)

PPP has it 48 to 47 Burns.
That means GOTV will determine the winner.
If you want to make a difference, here’s the four step plan:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epiphany</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/epiphany/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 03:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/epiphany/</guid>
      <description>I can’t tell you the date of our last sandlot football game. We didn’t commemorate it or mark with a special ceremony. We probably didn’t even know it would be our last game together.

After school, the kids would come to my house. Our next door neighbors, the Nahers, had a double lot, and Mrs. Naher was a former professional women’s baseball player. She loved sports and kids and let us tear up the the lawn they manicured all summer by playing sandlot football in the fall and winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abortion and ObamaCare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/abortion-and-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 16:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/abortion-and-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>In Tennessee and Arizona, insurance exchanges created under ObamaCare are barred from covering abortions. Pro-life groups claim this trend will continue as more states realize that the bill passed earlier this year allows states to block abortion coverage by private exchanges. (Missouri’s legislature sent a similar measure to Gov. Jay Nixon.)

Pro-abortion members of Congress are incensed, according to the Associated Press and Fox News:
 &amp;ldquo;Implementation of this reform should be about increasing access to health care and increasing choices, not taking them away,&amp;rdquo; said Sen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonishing Science: Sun May Cause Global Warming</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/astonishing-science-sun-may-cause-global-warming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 10:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/astonishing-science-sun-may-cause-global-warming/</guid>
      <description>Unbelievable! Scientists have discovered that the huge, glowing fireball in the sky may affect Earth’s temperature.
The latest evidence comes from . . . the Moon.
Back when we used to send astronauts to the Moon, we placed some temperature sensors on the Moon’s surface. We still monitor those sensors.
Guess what they show. Yep, you’re right! As temperatures rose on Earth, temperatures rose on the Moon.

Watts Up With That has all the details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Policy Polling</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/public-policy-polling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 09:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/16/public-policy-polling/</guid>
      <description>I realize that most people aren&amp;rsquo;t reading political insider blogs at 4:30 in the morning. But something in this story bothers me:
 But there&amp;rsquo;s also one big reason why the Democrats may just pull it out- and why Republicans may not have as big an election year as we&amp;rsquo;re anticipating. And that&amp;rsquo;s because only 26% of voters in the district have a favorable opinion of Congressional Republicans, with 56% seeing them unfavorably.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing Battles</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/choosing-battles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 01:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/choosing-battles/</guid>
      <description>For the record, I do not apologize for focusing on the most important battles facing self-government since the American Revolution.

Earlier this week, McGraw Milhaven of 550 KTRS criticized Tea Partyers for not opposing Missouri legislation, introduced by and championed by Republicans, that will force insurance companies to cover treatment for children diagnosed with Autism and associated conditions. (I personally oppose this legislation, by the way.)
Before that, a few Tea Partyers criticized me and others on facebook for not doing “enough” to support the Missouri Healthcare Free Choice act, which recently passed both the House and the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Exodus Planned for May 31: Will You Quit?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/facebook-exodus-planned-for-may-31-will-you-quit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 16:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/facebook-exodus-planned-for-may-31-will-you-quit/</guid>
      <description>Facebook Exodus Planned for May 31: Will You Quit?.
 The delete-your-Facebook movement — scheduled for May 31 — has yet to attract too many pledges, but with anti-Facebook sentiment on the rise that could change in the near future. In fact, yesterday Danny Sullivan of Search Engine Land noticed that “how do i delete my facebook account” is now one of the top Googlesuggestions when typing “how do i …” in the search box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pimp My Platoon—Right Now at McArthur’s in Chesterfield</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/pimp-my-platoonright-now-at-mcarthurs-in-chesterfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 14:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/15/pimp-my-platoonright-now-at-mcarthurs-in-chesterfield/</guid>
      <description>H/T and stolen content from SpikeSTL:

Say “Thanks” to some heroes in Afghanistan.
McArthur’s Bakery in Chesterfield
13700 Olive Blvd [map link]
Come to McArthur’s in Chesterfield Sat. May 15,2010. Starting at 7:00 A.M. to say hi to Dr. Randy Tobler from 97.1 Talk radio and make a donation for Dave’s son Moose and his Marine comrades in Afghanistan.
Bring a care package for the troops
I heard this morning that Moose was recently injured?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geek out on this</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/geek-out-on-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2010 05:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/geek-out-on-this/</guid>
      <description>You’ll be glad you did.
https://video.ted.com/assets/player/swf/EmbedPlayer.swf
This eighteen minute presentation synthesizes almost everything I believe about leadership and inspiration.
We own Why
We believe that God&amp;rsquo;s law trumps Man&amp;rsquo;s, and that the Constitution trumps Congress. And the President. And the courts. We believe that each one of us has the will and the capacity to dream our own dreams, live our own lives, and die our own noble deaths without government assistance or government contraints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Liberty Congressional Town Hall</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/ensuring-liberty-congressional-town-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 23:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/ensuring-liberty-congressional-town-hall/</guid>
      <description>Over at Ensuring Liberty, we held our first Congressional Virtual Town Hall on Tuesday, May 11. In case you missed it, Reps Michele Bachmann and Steve King discussed Senator Dodd’s proposed financial takeover bill with thousands of Americans.
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y6AvG1HVcDE&amp;amp;color1;=0xb1b1b1&amp;amp;color2;=0xd0d0d0&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;feature;=player_embedded&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;hl;=en]
Segment 1 of May 11 Ensuring Liberty Town Hall
Ensuring Liberty plans to team up with Bachmann, King, and many other conservative House members throughout 2010 and beyond. We want to bring your voices to their ears—again, and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is Running Out</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/time-is-running-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 22:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/14/time-is-running-out/</guid>
      <description>Money Bomb for Tim Burns ends at 11:00 p.m. Central tonight!
 If you want the satisfaction of replacing pork-barreler and Marine-basher, John Murtha, with fiscal conservative Tim Burns, then contributing to the money bomb will help.
If you have friends or family in Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s 12th Congressional district, you might want to give them a call this weekend and ask them if they plan to vote in Tuesday’s election. (People who are asked if they intend to vote are 40 percent more likely to vote than those who are not asked (Cialdini).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Paths to Focus</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/13/2-paths-to-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 14:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/13/2-paths-to-focus/</guid>
      <description>I had a small revelation yesterday: there are two paths to focus.
One path requires constant vigilance against distraction. This path also demands great awareness of many things, knowledge, and outlandish tenacity. This is the path we recognize as heroic.
The other path gets less notice, less acclaim. Those how follow this other path to focus don’t seem to try hard. These are the “naturals.” Things seem to come easy for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Minute Town Hall with Michele Bachmann is Tuesday Night</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/10/30-minute-town-hall-with-michele-bachmann-is-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 02:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/10/30-minute-town-hall-with-michele-bachmann-is-tonight/</guid>
      <description>* Rep. Michele Bachmann (R-MN)
Please join Ensuring Liberty tonight (Tuesday) at 8:00 EDT (7:00 Central, 5 Pacific) for a virtual townhall with Congresswoman Michele Bachmann to discuss the disasterous implications of the Dodd Financial Reform Bill.
Tuesday, May 11, 2010 at 8:00 PM Eastern
  
URL and Logon details will be sent in a follow up email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Happiness Makes You Better</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/10/how-happiness-makes-you-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 23:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/10/how-happiness-makes-you-better/</guid>
      <description>Earlier, I wrote about a little trick for making your day a little happier than it otherwise would have been. Now, there are a lot of reasons why I should wish to make you happier. But I have to admit that there’s something in it for me.
No, I don’t get 3 cents every time someone registers on ThankfulFor.com. But as a member of several grassroots organizations trying to change America, I want my teammates to be in the best possible spirits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Be Happier</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/10/how-to-be-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 13:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/10/how-to-be-happier/</guid>
      <description>Happiness is a choice; anger is a tactic.
Anger will have to wait for a future post. This one is about happiness. So let me ask: would you do something that took less than a minute if that something would make you happier?
Martin Seligman at University of Pennsylvania’s school of Positive Psychology has broken down happiness in more scientifically measurable components:
* Positive Emotion** Engagement** Purpose  Other research has shown how to increase your happiness score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrific: U.S. Pumping $$ into European Economic Abyss</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/09/terrific-u-s-opens-pumping-into-european-economic-abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 01:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/09/terrific-u-s-opens-pumping-into-european-economic-abyss/</guid>
      <description>Break out the Depression Glasses to toast the Obama Administration’s latest foray into economic disaster. Just posted on WSJ.com:
 BREAKING: The Federal Reserve and other central banks open a credit line to send dollars to Europe to ease debt crisis.
 Yes, folks. Your taxes are going up, your kids are going deeper into debt, to bail out lazy, overpaid, spoiled Greek socialists. Thank your president.
The U.S. move follows a panicked decision by EU leaders to pump hundreds of billions of $$ into failing socialist economies in Europe to avert a global economic collapse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Great New Phase Unveiled at Post-Party Summit</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/09/a-great-new-phase-unveiled-at-post-party-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 00:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/09/a-great-new-phase-unveiled-at-post-party-summit/</guid>
      <description>Ned Ryun, President of American Majority, has opened a new chapter in America’s conservative grassroots movement.
On Saturday, a crowd of several hundred 9-12 Project and Tea Party organizers heard Ryun explain why it’s time to move beyond the rallies at the American Majority Post-Party Summit in Kansas City. I have mentioned this before, and it seems to bother many people. I understand why.

The rally was the animating function of the Tea Party movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come to Kansas City This Weekend</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/06/come-to-kansas-city-this-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 03:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/06/come-to-kansas-city-this-weekend/</guid>
      <description>The Cardinals are out of town. The day before Mother’s Day is always boring. (You don’t want to go into a Mother’s Day Brunch hangin’ like Saddam Hussein, right?) So spend Friday evening and/or Saturday with Dana Loesch, Bill Hennessy, and hundreds of grassroots conservative activists at;

It’s not too late to register and arrive, and everything happens at the Embassy Suites at KC International Airport:
Kansas City Summit May 7-8* Embassy Suites KC – Int.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring Liberty: Virtual Town Hall with Rep. Michele Bachmann</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/06/ensuring-liberty-virtual-town-hall-with-rep-michele-bachmann/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 01:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/06/ensuring-liberty-virtual-town-hall-with-rep-michele-bachmann/</guid>
      <description>House Conservative Rock Star, Michele Bachmann, will hold a virtual Town Hall on Tuesday, May 11, 2010, at 8 p.m. Eastern, 7 Central, and 5:00 Pacific.
REGISTER NOW!
Representative Bachmann will discuss the Dodd Financial Reform Bill currently in debate in the U. S. Senate.
 Today’s Wall Street rollercoaster ride should remind everyone of the disaster caused by government intervention in the housing market through Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Todd Akin: Putting Al-Qaeda Ahead of the CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/05/rep-todd-akin-putting-al-qaeda-ahead-of-the-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 03:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/05/rep-todd-akin-putting-al-qaeda-ahead-of-the-cia/</guid>
      <description>Hey, one of our favorite members of Congress, and a true gentleman, Todd Akin (R-MO), has made the front page of BigGovernment.com.
The Obama Justice Department is quietly investigating the lawyers associated with the John Adams Project who may have violated a number of laws in place to protect our covert operatives and their families. But so far, with few exceptions, the media and their friends on Capitol Hill haven’t found this case nearly as interesting as Valerie Plame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truer Words Were Never Spoken</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/04/truer-words-were-never-spoken/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 03:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/04/truer-words-were-never-spoken/</guid>
      <description>A truer leader never walked this land
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zqAgmrSimx4&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;&amp;amp;hl;=en]
In human relations, there is a fixed ratio between leaders and those they lead.
The people trust leaders as much as the leader trusts the people.
In my lifetime, no leader ever trusted me as much as Ronald Reagan.
And I have trusted no leader as much as I trusted him.
And we never even met.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Win</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/04/how-to-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 12:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/04/how-to-win/</guid>
      <description>Focus.
There. That was easy, wasn’t it?
Focus.
Of the thousands of possible activities and initiatives, choose one.
Our goal is affect the outcome of the 2010 elections. That has not changed since our first tea party in Febuary 2009 with it’s tag line “Repeal the pork . . . or retire!”
They didn’t fix the fiscal problems. We owe it to ourselves to retire them.
But how?
Let’s try this: let’s go out and meet our neighbors and family and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want to see the signing of the Declaration of Independence?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/want-to-see-the-signing-of-the-declaration-of-independence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 00:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/want-to-see-the-signing-of-the-declaration-of-independence/</guid>
      <description>Here’s your chance.
At the Farmington, MO, Centene Center on May 14 at 7:00 p.m. (click for map and directions)

No admission, but I’ll bet the organizers would appreciate a donation to help the cause.
Thanks and congratulations to We the People of Farmington, MO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Must Evangelize Liberty</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/why-we-must-evangelize-liberty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 20:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/why-we-must-evangelize-liberty/</guid>
      <description>Earlier I linked to Glenn Reynolds’s Examiner column about the hard work that lies ahead for Tea Partyers. If you haven’t read that piece, do so after reading this.
At Tea Party marches and rallies, we are surrounded by others who understand and cherish liberty. We know the horrors that occur when a government loses accountability to and, yes, fear of the people they govern. Such regimes become murderous, intolerant, and repressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation, Mother’s Day, Father’s Day  . . .</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/graduation-mothers-day-fathers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 18:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/graduation-mothers-day-fathers-day/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Harlan Reynolds: Tea Party movement likely to have unglamorous but effective future | Washington Examiner</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/glenn-harlan-reynolds-tea-party-movement-likely-to-have-unglamorous-but-effective-future-washington-examiner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 16:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/02/glenn-harlan-reynolds-tea-party-movement-likely-to-have-unglamorous-but-effective-future-washington-examiner/</guid>
      <description>Glenn Harlan Reynolds: Tea Party movement likely to have unglamorous but effective future | Washington Examiner.
Glenn is right, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been saying it for a while. Rallies and marches do NOT change history.
It&amp;rsquo;s time to hit the streets. It&amp;rsquo;s time to go door-to-door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edward Whitacre Jr. Lies **Update: NYT Agrees**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/01/edward-whitacre-jr-lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 01:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/01/edward-whitacre-jr-lies/</guid>
      <description>No, General Motors did not pay back its debt to taxpayers. Edward Whitacre is a liar. Instead, Whitacre paid the Visa bill with his MasterCard. But both cards were issued by the same bank. So you, the banker, are still on the hook for the full amount.
Now we know why Obama hand-picked Ed Whitacre to “lead” GM: Whitacre will do the president’s bidding.
[youtube=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SOaS2SymjQ4&amp;amp;w;=425&amp;amp;h;=355]
UPDATE From Hotair.com: New York Times agrees that Whitacre and White House ain&amp;rsquo;t tellin&amp;rsquo; the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Crisis: Greece, Portugal, Spain . . . ?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/28/debt-crisis-greece-portugal-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 15:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/28/debt-crisis-greece-portugal-spain/</guid>
      <description>WSJ.com Alert:
 S&amp;amp;P downgrades Spain to &amp;lsquo;AA&amp;rsquo; with a negative outlook, saying the country is likely to have an extended period of subdued economic growth.
 Markets react: DJIA plummets from +23 to –22 in seconds after S&amp;amp;P drops Spain’s debt rating. And the sovereign debt nightmare is only beginning. The UK is next. But the USA borrows more money faster than anyone, and Socio-History blog ain’t happy:
  As I pointed out yesterday, US debt threatens to end the economic stabilization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greece: America’s Future</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/27/greece-americas-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/27/greece-americas-future/</guid>
      <description>As I waited to appear on Larry Kudlow’s show last Friday, I heard Larry announce over and over again that he’s sick of hearing about Greece’s problems. Greece isn’t America. The U.S. economy is booming, and Greece can’t hurt it.
I didn’t tell Larry, but I think he was wrong.
Greece’s problems will hurt the American economy because Greece’s problems foreshadow a far more dangerous crash headed to America.
Markets are people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Called Home</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/25/jack-called-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 23:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/25/jack-called-home/</guid>
      <description>I heard from my son, Jack, tonight for the first time since he left for Navy boot camp on April 14.
He is doing well. He survived the first week. He’s been declared fit for full duty. He’s learned to fold things very compactly, to recite the General Orders to the Sentry on command, and to identify his Chain of Command through the President of the United States.
If boot camp hasn’t changed, week two is worse that week one, but I didn’t tell him that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Focus for Better Living</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/25/how-to-focus-for-better-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 23:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/25/how-to-focus-for-better-living/</guid>
      <description>I once thought that focus meant you never got distracted. I was wrong.
A person with a powerful focusing ability gets as distracted as the next guy. The difference is that the Focus Master has learned to recognize distraction and gently guide his thoughts or actions back to the intended task at hand.
That simple skill is rare and remarkably powerful. Pay attention to every word of this two-step process:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fair Winds and Following Seas, Son</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/13/fair-winds-and-following-seas-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 03:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/13/fair-winds-and-following-seas-son/</guid>
      <description>I spent the afternoon with my oldest son, Jack. It was his last day as a civilian. It was probably the last day that he and I will share a mailing address. In a few days, I’ll get a postcard containing a new address at RTC Great Lakes. It will be written in his own hand. He will miss home when he writes it.
I hope I’m not revealing too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Rock Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/05/how-to-rock-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 00:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/05/how-to-rock-freedom/</guid>
      <description>[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bgU7T2au2Wg&amp;amp;hl;=en_US&amp;amp;fs;=1&amp;amp;color1;=0x2b405b&amp;amp;color2;=0x6b8ab6&amp;amp;border;=1]
Wow. A former Ambassador and candidate for Missouri State Auditor. And a Stones fan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis County Votes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/05/st-louis-county-votes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 00:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/04/05/st-louis-county-votes/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow, Tuesday, April 6, is Election Day in St. Louis County. In some places, especially throughout South County, the only measure on the ballot is Proposition A: a sales tax increase.
Prop A’s backers—principally County Exec Charlie Dooley and Chesterfield Mayor John Nations—claim this tax increase of up to $650 per family will allow Metro to grow. You know otherwise.
* Dooley and Nations cannot point to a specific plan. They point to four.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Happy Ending</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/03/23/how-to-make-a-happy-ending/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 17:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/03/23/how-to-make-a-happy-ending/</guid>
      <description>**How to Make a Happy Ending
**
We sat at a hi-top table for four at John D. McGurk&amp;rsquo;s Irish (duh) Pub in South St. Louis. Cold filled my being down to the soul. I&amp;rsquo;d been outside in the rain for the better part of two days. My favorite sport coat, soaked, lay in the back seat of my Jeep. My shirts clung to my shivering skin. My penny loafers made the sound of swishing mouth-rinse with every step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White House Unveils Unemployment Strategy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/01/10/white-house-unveils-unemployment-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 19:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/01/10/white-house-unveils-unemployment-strategy/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, DC: The White House unveiled a new strategy to lower the nation’s unemployment rate, currently standing at 10 percent.
In his weekly radio address Saturday, the President announced that he will use remaining funds from the failed Stimulus bill to take advantage of little known variable in the unemployment rate factor: “discouraged workers.”
Pointing out that “discouraged” workers are excluded from the unemployment calculation, the President explained that the government will encourage the unemployed to simply give up hopes for finding work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama Accepts Reid’s Apology</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/01/10/obama-accepts-reids-apology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/01/10/obama-accepts-reids-apology/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON, DC &amp;ndash; Saying, “The Senate relies on dingy-skinned white men, especially ones without a cracker dialect,” President Barack Obama accepted Senator Harry Reid’s (D-NV) apology for words Reid used in private in 2008.
According to the forthcoming book, “Game Changing,” Reid described Obama a “light-skinned” black man “with no Negro dialect . . . unless he wanted to have one” during the 2008 presidential election.
In his apology, Reid said, “I deeply regret using such a poor choice of words, but it’s mighty white of the President to accept my sincere apology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>