<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gary Wiegert on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/gary-wiegert/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gary Wiegert on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 02:45:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/gary-wiegert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Francis Slay Destroys the Transportation Sales Tax Trying to Support It **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/15/francis-slay-destroys-transportation-sales-tax-trying-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 02:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/15/francis-slay-destroys-transportation-sales-tax-trying-support/</guid>
      <description>Doesn&amp;rsquo;t it suck when Jay Nixon and Francis Slay get on opposite sides of an issue?
Where do we go?
They&amp;rsquo;re on opposite sides of Amendment 7, the largest tax increase in Missouri history. And you need to choose a side before August 5, because the ball&amp;rsquo;s in the voters&amp;rsquo; court.
But there&amp;rsquo;s no need to fear; Hennessy is here. And I heard Francis the talking Mayor on KMOX this morning (or maybe it was yesterday) talking about how much he loves, Loves, LOVES the 3/4 cent sales tax increase theoretically for transportation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Louis City Fathers Freak Out Because Police Sergeant Gary Wiegert Lobbies For Sane Marijuana Reforms</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/08/st-louis-city-fathers-freak-out-because-police-sergeant-gary-wiegert-lobbies-for-sane-marijuana-reforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 03:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/08/st-louis-city-fathers-freak-out-because-police-sergeant-gary-wiegert-lobbies-for-sane-marijuana-reforms/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think people would listen when a career police officer says we need to reform marijuana laws. But n-o-o-o-o. Not in St. Louis, anyway.
Gary Wiegert is a 30+ year police officer who signed up to lobby Jefferson City on behalf of tea party issues a couple of years ago. Some people freaked out over that, but Gary was instrumental in advancing tea party issues for the past 2 years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>