<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reading on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reading on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 10:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Herbert Hoover Launched Cardinal Nation</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/24/how-herbert-hoover-launched-cardinal-nation/</guid>
      <description>The St. Louis Cardinals were the major league team farthest west and farthest south until the 1950s. But that’s not the only reason the Redbirds built a massive flock of fans from the Alleghenies to the Rockies, and from Canada to the Gulf of Mexico.
The St. Louis Cardinals owe big government statism and technological innovation a big thanks, in addition to geography and great teams. The technology was radio. The big government statist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the Perfect Ingredients of Great Book?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/10/15/what-are-the-perfect-ingredients-of-great-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 17:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/10/15/what-are-the-perfect-ingredients-of-great-book/</guid>
      <description>Writers are always looking for the perfect topic for a book. But there’s a problem.
What’s important to me may not be important to you. And what you to read about, I might not care about.
That’s why great books achieve a certain universality. They touch on the essence of life itself, of humanity itself, of existence.
Some say that the secret to perfectly spellbinding stories is a mixture of just three elements: sex, food, and spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Things to Read in 2011</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/30/8-things-to-read-in-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 13:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/30/8-things-to-read-in-2011/</guid>
      <description>This week last year, I read The 5000 Year Leap. Good book. If you haven’t read it, do so. You might learn some interesting things.
But don’t expect The 5000 Year Leap to change you. Or history. It won’t.
Now, if 70 percent of the US population read it, it might make a difference. Or maybe not. I tend to doubt it, but that’s fodder for a different post.
When tea partiers read books like Glenn Beck’s Common Sense or The 5000 Year Leap, we’re not broadening ourselves—we’re narrowing ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>