<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eric Greitens on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/eric-greitens/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eric Greitens on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 19:56:27 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/eric-greitens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri&#39;s Festering Wound</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/missouris-festering-wound/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 19:56:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/missouris-festering-wound/</guid>
      <description>They say that time heals all wounds. But some wounds don&amp;rsquo;t heal. They fester and metastasize until pain demands the intervention of a surgeon&amp;rsquo;s scalpel.
Two years have passed since Eric Greitens was carried from the Missouri Governor&amp;rsquo;s Mansion by a toxic cocktail of lies, false allegations, and prosecutorial misconduct.
For two years, Missouri&amp;rsquo;s media and establishment Republicans pretended it never happened. They never liked Greitens, and they wanted him to go away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine for Nothing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/fine-for-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 16:12:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/fine-for-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Last week, the Missouri Ethics Commission fined former Governor Eric Greitens for nothing. Literally, they fined him for doing nothing wrong.
Even CNN finds the Missour Ethics Commission unethical and repulsive:
 A Missouri panel &amp;ldquo;found no evidence of any wrongdoing&amp;rdquo; by former Gov. Eric Greitens following a nearly 18-month investigation into allegations of misconduct by his 2016 gubernatorial campaign, according to a report released Thursday (CNN)
 Political pressure from the current Missouri governor undoubtedly weighed on the MEC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Is Scott Faughn&#39;s Book?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/where-is-scott-faughns-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 15:10:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/where-is-scott-faughns-book/</guid>
      <description>Scott Faughn is the publisher of the lobbyist &amp;ldquo;newspaper&amp;rdquo; Missouri Times and bagman for the sponsors of the illegal prosecution of Eric Greitens.
When he was caught delivering a laundry bag of cash to attorney Al Watkins to pay off Greitens&amp;rsquo; accusers and others, the always-broke Faughn claimed the money was somehow related to his forthcoming book on the Greitens administration. He even told his audience that they could order the book at at his website, scottfaughn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Those Rent Seekers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/about-those-rent-seekers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 12:12:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/about-those-rent-seekers/</guid>
      <description>What is &amp;ldquo;rent-seeking?&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo; a brief description from David John Marotta, What Is Rent-Seeking Behavior in Forbes
 Rent-seeking doesn&amp;rsquo;t add any national value. It is coerced trade and benefits only one side. Rent-seeking can include piracy, lobbying the government or even just giving away money.
 There are two kinds of lobbyists.
One kind of lobbyist is necessary to keep legislators and executive-branch bureaucrats informed and on notice. These lobbyists protect the interests of special interest group, but often their special interest needs protection because it is at the mercy of the government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unfinished Business: Exodus and Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/unfinished-business-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 13:20:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/post/2020/unfinished-business-greitens/</guid>
      <description>Parson will sell everything that isn&amp;rsquo;t nailed down.
 When the media, crooked businessmen, and corrupt politicians were in the midst of their coup against Eric Greitens, a friend told me, &amp;ldquo;If they get rid of Greitens, Parson will sell everything that isn&amp;rsquo;t nailed down.&amp;rdquo;
My friend was wrong. Governor Mike Parson (who may or may not have been a conspirator in the coup) is selling everything in Missouri, but he isn&amp;rsquo;t stopping at the loose items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Deal With Events</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/06/03/how-to-deal-with-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 16:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/06/03/how-to-deal-with-events/</guid>
      <description>Governor Eric Greitens resigned. Friend of the lobbyists, Mike Parson, became Missouri&amp;rsquo;s governor. In the words of someone who knows the new governor well, Mike Parson will &amp;ldquo;sell everything that isn&amp;rsquo;t nailed down.&amp;rdquo;
For those of us who believe in limited government that doesn&amp;rsquo;t put its thumb on the scale of achievement, it&amp;rsquo;s time to panic and despair, right?
Wrong. It&amp;rsquo;s never time to panic or despair. And we know this from two of the greatest philosophers of all time, Epictetus and Seneca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Descend on Jefferson City</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/17/descend-on-jefferson-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 11:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/17/descend-on-jefferson-city/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time. Powerful and corrupt people want to undo the 2016 election. In Washington. In Missouri.
Win or lose, Americans deal with the results of elections. Our commitment to open, public government, of the people, by, the people, for people, has sustained this nation. And made it the greatest nation in the history of humanity.
But dark forces in Missouri want to turn your government into their private club. A club managed by corrupt business who rely on tax dollars to keep their failed enterprises afloat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poll Your Missouri State Rep Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/16/poll-your-missouri-state-rep-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 03:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/16/poll-your-missouri-state-rep-now/</guid>
      <description>Simple mission: poll your Missouri State Rep. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know your rep, I&amp;rsquo;ll give you a link a little later. But hurry. Poll closes Friday, May 18 at 6:00 p.m.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the single poll question:
   &amp;ldquo;As your constituent, I want to know: if a vote on impeachment of Governor Greitens were held today, would you vote Yay or Nay?&amp;rdquo;
 Then, return to this page to record your Rep&amp;rsquo;s answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glory Days for Missouri Republicans</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/06/glory-days-for-missouri-republicans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 12:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/05/06/glory-days-for-missouri-republicans/</guid>
      <description>I had a friend was a big baseball player
back in high school
He could throw that speedball by you
Make you look like a fool boy
Saw him the other night at this roadside bar
I was walking in, he was walking out
We went back inside sat down had a few drinks
but all he kept talking about was Glory Days
—Bruce Springsteen, Glory Days</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri Crimes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/30/missouri-crimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 04:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/30/missouri-crimes/</guid>
      <description>Scott Faughn&amp;rsquo;s name came up in conversation last week.
&amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s this Faughn guy&amp;rsquo;s role in the Greitens&amp;rsquo; investigation?&amp;rdquo; someone asked.
Faughn is the publisher of Missouri Times and a former mayor of Poplar Bluff, Missouri. Papers call him a &amp;ldquo;power broker.&amp;rdquo; Others call him the &amp;ldquo;Candy Man.&amp;rdquo;
I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand the question. &amp;ldquo;Not sure,&amp;rdquo; I said. &amp;ldquo;His paper hates Grietens, but that&amp;rsquo;s as much as know. And I&amp;rsquo;ve been to his weird, hidden party pad in Jefferson City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King David and Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/24/king-david-and-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 11:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/24/king-david-and-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>People have an innate sense of justice.   One evening David got up from his bed and walked around on the roof of the palace. From the roof he saw a woman bathing. The woman was very beautiful,3 and David sent someone to find out about her. The man said, “She is Bathsheba,the daughter of Eliam and the wife of Uriah the Hittite.” 4 Then David sent messengers to get her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric Greitens in His Own Words</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/23/eric-greitens-in-his-own-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 12:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/23/eric-greitens-in-his-own-words/</guid>
      <description>My blog includes links to related posts at the bottom of every individual post page. I usually don&amp;rsquo;t pay much attention, but today I noticed something. (BTW, this new theme looks great on phones.)
One of the old stories in the Eric Greitens category was my first comments on his book Resilience﻿. My old post talked about why it took me so long to finish the book. And it contained two short passages from the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Odyssey of Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/21/odyssey-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 14:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/21/odyssey-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>O Divine Poesy, goddess, daughter of Zeus, sustain for me this song of the various-minded man who, after he had plundered the innermost citadel of hallowed Troy, was made to stay grievously about the coasts of men, the sport of their customs, good and bad, while his heart, through all the sea-faring, ached with an agony to redeem himself and bring his company safe home. Vain hope – for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Josh &#34;Hee&#34; Hawley</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/20/yellow-josh-hee-hawley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/04/20/yellow-josh-hee-hawley/</guid>
      <description>We all thought it.
&amp;ldquo;This time, for sure, McCaskill goes down.&amp;rdquo;
We&amp;rsquo;ve thought it before and been disappointed. But this time is different, right? This time, we have that up-and-coming Attorney General who&amp;rsquo;s backed by conservatives and establishment Republicans alike. A guy equally at home at a Tea Party conference or a Jack Danforth backyard barbecue. This time, for sure.
But this time looks like another disappointment for Missouri Republicans hoping to send another Republican to the US Senate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Win Consistently</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/06/how-to-win-consistently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/06/how-to-win-consistently/</guid>
      <description>If your favorite player hits a home run or scores a goal, but your favorite team loses, what have you accomplished?
If an athlete you despise makes a horrible error but the hated team he plays for wins the championship, how do you feel?
In several races across Missouri, some people seem willing to lose the war if it means they can win their private battles. That’s pretty sad, isn’t it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be inconsistent</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/03/how-to-be-inconsistent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 11:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/11/03/how-to-be-inconsistent/</guid>
      <description>This post is about why you should vote for Eric Greitens. But first, let&amp;rsquo;s take a stroll down memory lane.
Remember August 2015? It was hot, of course, but everybody was talking about when Trump would fade. For example, here&amp;rsquo;s the RCP Afternoon Edition from August 7, the day after the first GOP debate:
 Whose Party Is It, Anyway? - Molly Ball, The Atlantic The Republican Debate Was Awesome - David Harsanyi, The Federalist You Cannot Embarrass Donald Trump - Ezra Klein, Vox The Beginning of the End for Trump - Ed Rogers, Washington Post Martin O&amp;rsquo;Malley, the Dems&amp;rsquo; Fallback?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Missouri Great Again—Greitens for Governor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/30/make-missouri-great-again-greitens-for-governor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/30/make-missouri-great-again-greitens-for-governor/</guid>
      <description>As I pointed out last Saturday, a tiny faction of Missouri conservatives prefers Missouri&amp;rsquo;s pathetic status quo to true leadership and positive change. Those people apparently approve of Missouri&amp;rsquo;s horrible economy, weak schools, and declining stature in the country. And nowhere does Missouri&amp;rsquo;s decline stand out like San Diego, California.
Last week, I spent a few days bumming around San Diego with my son. He is stationed there in the US Navy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Are Some Missouri Conservatives Putting Position Before Interest?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/22/why-are-some-missouri-conservatives-putting-position-before-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 22:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/22/why-are-some-missouri-conservatives-putting-position-before-interest/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s play a little thought experiment.
Suppose you read that a scientific study proved dark blue socks look best with a gray suit. Then someone known for his remarkable sense of style shows up wearing purple striped socks with a gray suit. What would you do?
Before you answer that, consider this.
You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard that a handful of conservative activists are supporting the Democrat running for governor. Those misguided conservatives think the GOP nominee isn&amp;rsquo;t conservative enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the NRA Picks Candidates</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/06/how-the-nra-picks-candidates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/06/how-the-nra-picks-candidates/</guid>
      <description>You might find yourself freaking out that NRA endorsed the Democrat for Missouri Governor instead of Republican Eric Greitens. If you think about it, though, the endorsement makes perfect sense from the NRA&amp;rsquo;s perspective.
You realize that the NRA is a lobbying firm, and lobbyists have an easier time working with an established asset like Koster than cultivating an outsider like Greitens. Recruiting and cultivating an asset is to a lobbyist as finding and selling a new customer is to a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greitens&#39;s Win Was Just a Moment in Time. But a Big Moment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/03/greitenss-win-was-just-a-moment-in-time-but-a-big-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 06:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/03/greitenss-win-was-just-a-moment-in-time-but-a-big-moment/</guid>
      <description>Navy SEAL Eric Greitens won the first political race of his life. Few first timers win a major party&amp;rsquo;s nomination for governor of a state. You&amp;rsquo;ll probably hear just how rare Greitens&amp;rsquo;s feat was. But not tonight. I want to tell some stories.
Eric Greitens gave up a morning of this campaign to talk to one of my kids. That kid is a man now. He&amp;rsquo;s in the Navy at a helo combat squadron in San Diego.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Voting for Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/01/why-im-voting-for-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 02:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/08/01/why-im-voting-for-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>This was supposed to be a longer post, so I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you why I&amp;rsquo;m voting for Eric Greitens in a minute. First, why I have to cut it short.
I got home from door knocking for Eric at about 6:30 and walked straight to my laptop to write. Just as I sat down, my wife called me to dinner. She&amp;rsquo;d already eaten, but she heated up my dinner, called to me, then walked into our living room and shrieked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Republican Primary Key Races</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/30/2016-republican-primary-key-races/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 22:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/30/2016-republican-primary-key-races/</guid>
      <description>Some people have a loud opinion on each and every Republican Primary race.
I have a lot of opinions, but I like to focus on a few key races. Here are my major concerns for the 2016 Republican Primary on August 2.
[os-widget path=&amp;rdquo;/billhennessy/2016-republican-primary-key-races1&amp;rdquo; of=&amp;quot;billhennessy&amp;rdquo; comments=&amp;quot;false&amp;rdquo;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Choice for President Just Endorsed Eric Greitens for Governor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/30/my-first-choice-for-president-just-endorsed-eric-greitens-for-governor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 18:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/30/my-first-choice-for-president-just-endorsed-eric-greitens-for-governor/</guid>
      <description>From Dr. Ben Carson:
   President Obama and his allies are trying to hijack the Republican primary in Missouri by attacking my good friend Eric Greitens.
    Like me, Eric is a conservative outsider, and that means the political establishment is terrified of him. Obama and his allies are now spending a million dollars falsely attacking Eric Greitens and trying to fool the people of Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Just Predicted Greitens Beats Koster</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/29/democrats-prove-greitens-is-a-conservative-republican/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/29/democrats-prove-greitens-is-a-conservative-republican/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to help Democrats win? You can, and the Democratic Governors Association just told you how.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a Republican and you follow the advice of the Democratic Governors Association, you won&amp;rsquo;t vote for Eric Greitens. The DGA wants Democrat Chris Koster to win, so Democrats are telling Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Republicans not to nominate Greitens. Democrats believe Greitens beats Koster in November.
Smart people know that you watch what people do, not what they say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did Paul Holzer Expose John Brunner? Part III</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/29/why-did-paul-holzer-out-john-brunner-part-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 10:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/29/why-did-paul-holzer-out-john-brunner-part-iii/</guid>
      <description>This is part III of a four-part series. Here&amp;rsquo;s partI and part II.
Why Now? Why did Holzer choose last week to out himself? Why show himself now, putting his old boss, John Brunner, in such a bad light? And right before the August 2 primary?
**Holzer has damaged Brunner&amp;rsquo;s reputation and credibility. **And Brunner spent a ton of his own money in the process, including paying $100,000 to the guy who made the video, then squealed about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Brunner&#39;s Charade, Part II</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/28/why-did-paul-holzer-out-john-brunner-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/28/why-did-paul-holzer-out-john-brunner-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>This is part II of a three-part series. Here&amp;rsquo;s part__I.
That Shadowy Paul Holzer Paul Holzer is a former Navy SEAL Lieutenant Commander and a medical student at Dartmouth in New Hampshire. (Oddly, his bio shows MD, MBA, even though is still in medical school and simultaneously working toward an MBA.) Holzer also runs a biotech 501c3 and a political consulting firm, Draper Sterling LLC. He did some work for Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign, and he was John Brunner&amp;rsquo;s chief of staff last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Brunner&#39;s Charade, part I</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/27/paul-holzer-john-brunner-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 10:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/27/paul-holzer-john-brunner-1/</guid>
      <description>Why in the world would a political operative who once worked for John Brunner out himself and expose Brunner as either a liar or a patsy two weeks before an election?
 Reggie Lampert: Of course, you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to lie on your back for a while but then you can lie from any position, can&amp;rsquo;t you? &amp;ndash;Charade, 1963
 Things just got weirder in Missouri. After the stunning revelation that people associated with John Brunner&amp;rsquo;s campaign did, in fact, produce a false, negative video attacking Eric Greitens, you might be wondering what&amp;rsquo;s going on?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Voting for Eric Greitens Governor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/15/why-im-voting-for-eric-greitens-governor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 09:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/15/why-im-voting-for-eric-greitens-governor/</guid>
      <description>I believe the greatest threat to human freedom and thriving is the political class. That smirking political class infects both Washington, DC, and Jefferson City, Missouri. And I believe only one candidate has the courage, the brains, and the commitment to destroy that political class in Missouri. That candidate is Eric Greitens.
Do you want to live as a slave to that smirking political class? Or do you want to live free and thrive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surface thinking, deep thinking</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/17/surface-thinking-deep-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 22:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/17/surface-thinking-deep-thinking/</guid>
      <description>How people responded to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post, Maybe he&amp;rsquo;s not a conservative, varied. But there were two dominant types.
Surface thinkers ignored most of the content. I warned you about this early on. I decided against a deep examination of conservatism because people don&amp;rsquo;t care. Instead, I wrote a rather tongue-in-cheek story about why definitions of conservatism don&amp;rsquo;t matter.
Deep thinkers got the tongue-in-cheek shtick. Maybe they rolled their eyes at my cheap attempt at being clever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe he&#39;s not a conservative</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/16/more-on-first-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/16/more-on-first-principles/</guid>
      <description>As far as I can tell, the number one reason a few conservatives give for hating Eric Greitens is that he might not be a conservative. He&amp;rsquo;s probably not. But that shouldn&amp;rsquo;t make any difference.
Figuring out whether Greitens is a conservative or not requires a lot of thinking, a lot of writing, and a lot of clear analysis from readers. I won&amp;rsquo;t waste time on the first two because I won&amp;rsquo;t get the last no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proud to stand with veterans supporting Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/15/proud-to-stand-with-veterans-supporting-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 20:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/15/proud-to-stand-with-veterans-supporting-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>Today I learned that I am not alone. I am not alone in my anger over a morally-bankrupt attempt to smear a great leader. And I learned that I am not alone in recognizing Eric Greitens&amp;rsquo;s singular ability to inspire and lead.
I also learned that Eric Greitens has some really stupid opponents. Cowardly, stupid weasels. Cowardly because Greitens&amp;rsquo;s opponents funded, produced, and promoted an anonymous video, packed with lies. Stupid because that video so infuriated Missouri&amp;rsquo;s 500,000 military veterans that Greitens is picking up new supporters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greitens breathes life into our first principles</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/09/evangelical-papists/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 06:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/09/evangelical-papists/</guid>
      <description>I am Catholic.
I believe in and trust the magisterium of the church.
Nothing distinguishes me from Protestants more profoundly than that concept: the magisterium, or the teaching authority, of the church.
For me, the church is like Locke and Jefferson and Madison. They were learned men who read Socrates, Plato, Aristotle, Seneca, Cato, Epictetus, Epicurus, and other Greek and Roman philosophers, often in the original languages.
Those philosophical and political founders interpreted and organized ancient philosophy for England and America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Did the Pritzkers Donate to Greitens?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/29/why-did-the-pritzkers-donate-to-greitens/</guid>
      <description>A couple weeks ago, the blog Progressives Today ran an attack piece on Eric Greitens for two of his donors (link). The piece generated of lot angst and fury on the right side of social media.
**Turns out the story was pretty shoddy journalism. **
Progressives Today didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to look at the Pritzkers&amp;rsquo; other donations or the military museum they founded. If they had, they&amp;rsquo;d know that Jennifer N. Pritzker (formerly James N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Conversion Odyssey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/01/the-conversion-odyssey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 05:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/12/01/the-conversion-odyssey/</guid>
      <description>John Dos Passos has a mesmerizing name.
The &amp;ldquo;John&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t fit the &amp;ldquo;Dos Passos,&amp;rdquo; does it? Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be Juan Dos Passos?
But John Dos Passos was one of the Four Horsemen of American literature in the first half of the 20th century. And all four horsemen were Nomads, according to generational historians Howe and Strauss.
The Nomads Wander Left to Right I&amp;rsquo;m a Nomad, too. Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m drawn to Hemingway, Faulkner, Fitzgerald, and Dos Passos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I know it was you, Fredo</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/29/fredo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 23:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/29/fredo/</guid>
      <description>Fredo Corleone: I&amp;rsquo;m your older brother, Mike, and I was stepped over! Michael Corleone: That&amp;rsquo;s the way Pop wanted it. Fredo Corleone: It ain&amp;rsquo;t the way I wanted it! I can handle things! I&amp;rsquo;m smart! Not like everybody says&amp;hellip; like dumb&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m smart and I want respect!
 —The Godfather: Part II
I&amp;rsquo;m sure John Brunner never saw himself as Fredo Corleone.
A Burning Question Did you ever ask yourself why John Brunner would release a surreptitious recording of a phone call with an opponent?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get to Westport Plaza on September 26 at 11:00 a.m.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/14/get-to-westport-plaza-on-september-26-at-1100-a-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 02:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/09/14/get-to-westport-plaza-on-september-26-at-1100-a-m/</guid>
      <description>If you read this blog, you have a mile-wide curiosity streak.
Many of you want to know more about Eric Greitens.
You have a great chance to learn more on Saturday, September 26 at 11:00 a.m.
Eric Greitens will have some things to say. Perhaps he won&amp;rsquo;t say everything you want to hear. (It&amp;rsquo;s still 11 months until the primary.) But he&amp;rsquo;ll say things you need to hear.
And that&amp;rsquo;s my favorite thing about Eric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fascinating Results from Leaders Eat Last Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/22/fascinating-results-from-leaders-eat-last-poll/</guid>
      <description>This is the story of hard choices and how people resist making them.
Last week&amp;rsquo;s poll asked you to watch a video by Simon Sinek before answering two, simple, two-part questions: which Republican candidate for President and Missouri Governor is most likely and least likely to eat last?
I intended the poll to be hard. Not complicated, not long, but emotionally challenging.
Why the Poll Was Emotionally Challenging For several weeks, I have built a case for the importance of leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Conservative Missouri Service Program--Part 5</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/a-conservative-missouri-service-program-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 10:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/24/a-conservative-missouri-service-program-part-5/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve reached the end.
On Monday, we corrected disinformation about The Franklin Project.
Next, we looked at the historical conservative framework for national service.
Wednesday was a dissection of The Franklin Project&amp;rsquo;s Plan of Action (as distinguished from the group&amp;rsquo;s vision.)
Yesterday, we examined the consequences of ignoring the call for national service.
Today, we offer an oversimplified proposal for Missouri&amp;rsquo;s version of a national-service program. While inadequate, it is a start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Wrong With The Franklin Project? – Part 3</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/22/whats-wrong-with-the-franklin-project-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 10:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/22/whats-wrong-with-the-franklin-project-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This is part three of a five-part series on national service. Part 1 introduced the controversy and corrected a major misconception. Part 2 looked at national service through the eyes of conservative giants, Milton Friedman, William F. Buckley, and Ronald Reagan.
So, what’s wrong with the Franklin Project? Plenty.
The Franklin Project promotes the idea of a renewed ethos of national service in America. It’s mission:
 The Franklin Project envisions a future in which a year of full-time national service—a service year—is a cultural expectation, a common opportunity, and a civic rite of passage for every young American.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buckley vs. Friedman on Service-Part 2</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 10:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/21/buckley-vs-friedman-on-service-part-2/</guid>
      <description>This is part 2 of a series on national service and the Franklin Project. Read part 1 here.
First, answer this for yourself: would you vote for William F. Buckley Jr?
Milton Friedman on National Service My friend Lloyd Sloan points out that Milton Friedman disagreed with Buckley’s call for national service. It seems appropriate, then, to view the idea of a service ethos through the eyes of two champions of conservatism of the 20th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republican Governor Poll</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/12/republican-governor-poll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 18:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/07/12/republican-governor-poll/</guid>
      <description>Read my analysis of the poll here.
[yop_poll id=&amp;quot;2&amp;rdquo;]
You may vote only once.
Poll closes at midnight on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I finally finished reading Resilience by Eric Greitens</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/19/i-finally-finished-reading-resilience-by-eric-greitens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 21:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/05/19/i-finally-finished-reading-resilience-by-eric-greitens/</guid>
      <description>I usually breeze through books.
I read Thinking, Fast and Slow by Daniel Kahneman in four days. And it has math.
I read Eric Greitens&amp;rsquo;s book The Heart and the Fist in two days.
Why did it take me over a month to finish Resilience?
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure, but here&amp;rsquo;s what I think.
First, the book compels action. How could I read this paragraph without writing a blog post?
  If we are trapped in a life where everything is provided for us, our minds fail to grow, our relationships atrophy, and our spirits deteriorate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approaching Excellence</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/21/approaching-excellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 21:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/21/approaching-excellence/</guid>
      <description>Could it be?
Am I reading this right?
Has anyone ever surprised you with a wish? A wish that defied logic?
Yesterday, a friend wrote of his concerns about Eric Greitens, the Navy SEAL, humanitarian, Rhodes Scholar, charity founder, and former boxer who’s considering a run for Missouri Governor.
His concern began: “Most all GOP candidates proudly trumpet their positions . . . “
He was right, of course. Almost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Know You&#39;re Doing the Right Thing</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/14/how-to-know-youre-doing-the-right-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 21:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/14/how-to-know-youre-doing-the-right-thing/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What if everything goes wrong?&amp;rdquo;
I remember asking myself that on the morning of Friday, February 27, 2009.
I was driving on I-44 headed to the Arch to host a Tea Party. My co-hosts were people I&amp;rsquo;d never met: Dana Loesch, Gina Loudon, Ed Martin, Michelle Moore. Those were the three to offered to help. Others offered to speak: Jim Lembke, Shamed Dogan, and a few others. Others helped organize sign-making, food, sign-in sheets, and music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The SEAL, the Race, and the CEO</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/10/the-seal-the-race-and-the-ceo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/10/the-seal-the-race-and-the-ceo/</guid>
      <description>In its entire history, who was the safest CEO for Apple?
In other words, if you were a corporate recruiter hired by Apple&amp;rsquo;s board to find a chief executive, whom would hire?
I&amp;rsquo;ll answer this later, but first here&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m asking.
Who Would You Recruit? In response to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post on Brunner vs. Greitens, someone asked me a similar question about Eric Greitens. The inquisitor seems to question my judgment for preferring Greitens over John Brunner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greater of Two Goods</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/09/the-greater-of-two-goods/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 21:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/09/the-greater-of-two-goods/</guid>
      <description>You know the feeling.
You support someone for office. Call this person Candidate A. You&amp;rsquo;re all in. You&amp;rsquo;ve told your friends about this great person.
Then another candidate jumps in to oppose your candidate. Let&amp;rsquo;s call this person Candidate B. This insurgent has great qualifications. You campaigned for Candidate B in another race a few years ago. You&amp;rsquo;ve talked him up. In the past, told your friends to vote for Candidate B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering One&#39;s Domain</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/04/mastering-ones-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 01:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/04/04/mastering-ones-domain/</guid>
      <description>I own a ton of domain names.
Most of them I&amp;rsquo;ll never use. I bought them&amp;ndash;and pay for them&amp;ndash;because I don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone else to have them. Many contain &amp;ldquo;teabaggers.&amp;rdquo; Many contain &amp;ldquo;teaparty.&amp;rdquo; Many contain &amp;ldquo;Hennessy,&amp;rdquo; although the cognac people had sucked up quite a few of those already.
Everyone should invest in domains containing their surname. Anyone who is even mildly famous should own the domains containing their full name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Guy Puts People to Work</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/31/eric-greitens-puts-people-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 05:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/31/eric-greitens-puts-people-to-work/</guid>
      <description>Brett wanted to know more about Eric Greitens.
Ben deferred to me to tell the Greitens story. I went through the usual, remarkable life of a man, eleven years my junior, a century my senior. I told him about Duke, boxing, Bosnia, Rwanda, Mother Teresa. I told him about boxing at Oxford and becoming a SEAL.
Nothing from Brett.
&amp;ldquo;Really,&amp;rdquo; I thought. &amp;ldquo;How stuck-up is this guy?&amp;rdquo;
But we didn&amp;rsquo;t give up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am a Coward (but I&#39;m trying to get better)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/26/i-am-coward/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 21:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/26/i-am-coward/</guid>
      <description>A critic is someone who enters the battlefield after the war is over and shoots the wounded.
 ― Murray Kempton
Great leaders inspire thought and action.
But their real value? Great leaders inspire action. Hard action. Uncomfortable action.
I&amp;rsquo;m reading Resilience by Eric Greitens. I have already bought six copies of the book, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll buy more. I want everyone to read it. The book changes people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Don&#39;t Need More Technology--They Need Less</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/23/schools-dont-need-more-technology-they-need-less/</guid>
      <description>I was on my high school&amp;rsquo;s board of education for a year. It was quite an honor, honestly, but I screwed it up.
At the time, I was a software architect. They put me on the board as the technology guy. I was supposed to make the case for more funding for smart boards and other tech stuff.
But I said kids really don&amp;rsquo;t need more technology in school. Technology, I said, was like sex education: they&amp;rsquo;ll get more than they can handle on the streets or watching TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GOP&#39;s Sad New Whisper Campaign **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/21/the-gops-sad-new-whisper-campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2015 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/21/the-gops-sad-new-whisper-campaign/</guid>
      <description>Note: Updated to remove reference to Jeff Roe
Poor Catherine Hanaway.
Her shadowy operatives worked so hard to defeat Tom Schweich, but a new threat to Hanaway&amp;rsquo;s coronation emerged: Eric Greitens. (You can read all about Eric Greitens, here.)
The GOP establishment&amp;rsquo;s inept, new whisper campaign against Greitens is so amateurish and sad it evokes the kind of sympathy one feels toward the ignorance of animals (to paraphrase William F. Buckley).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will the Left Fund a Campaign to &#34;Fix&#34; Missouri? **UPDATE**</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/19/will-the-left-fund-a-campaign-to-fix-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 01:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/19/will-the-left-fund-a-campaign-to-fix-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Updated with new information
Leftist donors flooded Texas with money for two years.
Wendy Davis was the poster-child in 2014, but she was only a candidate of convenience. Leftists know that turning Texas purple would mean leftist domination in America. In 2013 &amp;ldquo;purple Texas&amp;rdquo; was all the talk. From Huffington Post:
 Last week, Politico reported that national Democrats are creating a &amp;ldquo;large-scale independent group&amp;rdquo; aimed at turning Texas into a legitimate electoral battleground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Hope Beats Anger</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/why-hope-beats-anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 06:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/07/why-hope-beats-anger/</guid>
      <description>The human brain is three times as sensitive to pain as it is to gain.
That’s a gross over-simplification, but it’s basically true. In other words, you’ll work three-times harder to save a dollar you have than to earn one you don’t.
Put another way, you won’t bet a dollar with even odds unless you stand to gain three dollars for a win.
That’s not a flaw. It keeps you alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providence and Hope in Missouri</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/providence-and-hope-in-missouri/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 23:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/03/05/providence-and-hope-in-missouri/</guid>
      <description>Fate moves in mysterious ways.
Just days before State Auditor and Republican gubernatorial candidate Tom Schweich died, Eric Greitens announced an exploratory committee. Greitens wants to test the water of a possible run for Missouri Governor as a Republican.
Greitens would be, perhaps, the most remarkable human being ever to pursue the office of Governor of Missouri. Here’s a sampling of Greitens’s achievements:
 Humanitarian who’s worked in Rwanda, Bosnia, Central America, India and other disaster zones—usually man-made disaster zones Boxer who won championships in England Rhodes Scholar who completed the program at Oxford Navy SEAL who earned the Bronze Star among other accolades in four tours in Iraq Founder of The Mission Continues to give wounded veterans a mission and a purpose in life Time Magazine’s 100 most influential people in the world Forbes’ Magazine’s 50 greatest leaders in the world  Purpose Over Party Greitens is no ideologue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Crony Capitalism Spreads Bureaucracy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</guid>
      <description>St. Louisan Eric Greitens did more before graduating from college than most people do in a lifetime. And, as if to insult us all, after college, Eric became a Navy SEAL.
In his remarkable book, The Heart and the Fist: The education of a humanitarian, the making of a Navy SEAL  , Greitens tells the story of a man who seems too good to be true. Seriously. And the book left me with two big impressions&amp;ndash;probably the wrong ones, but that&amp;rsquo;s how I am.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>