<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scotus on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/scotus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scotus on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 09:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/scotus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SCOTUS Reality Tour</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/scotus-reality-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/28/scotus-reality-tour/</guid>
      <description>By now you’ve seen the sensational headlines:
* People Are Saying That Obama&#39;s Healthcare Law Got Massacred At The Supreme Court Today*  Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/politics#ixzz1qMjfnTtF** Here Is The Moment When Justice Alito Shredded Verrilli At The Obamacare Hearings* Read more: https://www.businessinsider.com/politics#ixzz1qMjjQXFM** Skeptical Kennedy signals trouble for Obama&amp;rsquo;s healthcare law** Supreme Court Health Care Law: Justices Come Down Hard On The Mandate
And so it goes.
Before we start dancing in the streets, let’s face a little reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why People Are Being Unfair to Donald Verrilli</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/why-people-are-being-unfair-to-donal-verrilli/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 04:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/why-people-are-being-unfair-to-donal-verrilli/</guid>
      <description>Everyone (including me) is cracking on Donald Verrilli, Obama’s Solicitor General. He figuratively died on the biggest legal stage in the world today. Here’s a sample of the left’s reaction to Verrilli’s performance:
Mother Jones:
 Solicitor General Donald B. Verrilli Jr. should be grateful to the Supreme Court for refusing to allow cameras in the courtroom, because his defense of Obamacare on Tuesday may go down as one of the most spectacular flameouts in the history of the court.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg’s Crappy Argument In Support of ObamaCare</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/ruth-bader-ginsbergs-crappy-argument-in-support-of-obamacare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 00:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/27/ruth-bader-ginsbergs-crappy-argument-in-support-of-obamacare/</guid>
      <description>I’m often amazed at the weakness of arguments before the Supreme Court. Today, Ruth Bader Ginsburg, attempting to help out the Obama Administration’s fumbling solicitor-general, made the weakest argument I’ve ever heard.
First,Ginsburg statement:
 Mr. Verrilli, I thought that your main point is that, unlike food or any other market, when you made the choice not to buy insurance, even though you have every intent in the world to self-insure, to save for it, when disaster strikes, you may not have the money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democracy Is Not Above the Law</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/29/democracy-is-not-above-the-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 14:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/06/29/democracy-is-not-above-the-law/</guid>
      <description>In Honduras, the military overthrew a democratically elected president who used his election to seize dictatorial powers. Good for the military, which acted on a Supreme Court order. Let&amp;rsquo;s hope the SCOTUS will have the berries to shut down TheOne&amp;rsquo;s continuing slide into despotism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>