<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anthem protest on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/anthem-protest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in anthem protest on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/anthem-protest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump Instigates NFL Labor Dispute</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/28/trump-initiates-nfl-labor-dispute/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/28/trump-initiates-nfl-labor-dispute/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I predicted the NFL would suffer a season-shortening labor dispute this season or next.
The reason: President Trump&amp;rsquo;s pressure on owners to crack down on anthem haters will stir up a fight between NFL Players Association and the owners.
As if on cue:
[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_24766&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;1285&amp;rdquo;]Fox News[/caption]
 President Trump, in an exclusive interview with &amp;ldquo;Fox &amp;amp; Friends,&amp;rdquo; said that NFL owners are “afraid” to act against their players protesting the national anthem at games across the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Kemp Stood for Civil Rights . . . And America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 11:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/26/jack-kemp-stood-for-civil-rights-and-america/</guid>
      <description>Jack Kemp is on the top of my wall of heroes. Literally. An autographed Kemp card sits on top of my bookshelf housing the works and images of my heroes.
As the NFL self-destructs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth reading about Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s work for civil rights. And for the Republican Party. And for conservatism.
Jack Kemp&amp;rsquo;s Activism Kemp did it all. And, thanks to Jeffrey Lord, we can remember Kemp&amp;rsquo;s finest moments of civil rights activism:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Trump Popped the NFL&#39;s Biggest Zit</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/25/president-trump-popped-the-nfls-biggest-zit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 01:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/25/president-trump-popped-the-nfls-biggest-zit/</guid>
      <description>Coming to a head.
President Trump seems pathologically opposed to festering problems. When he sees a festering problem, he pops it like a zit. For example, the North Korean nukes problem has festered since the Clinton administration. Trump is bringing Little Rocket Man to a head.
NAFTA has been festering since the Clinton administration. Trump is bringing NAFTA to a head.
The latest example: the NFL anthem-haters.
This anthem-hating is over a year old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Else Can You Do?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/24/what-else-can-you-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 16:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/24/what-else-can-you-do/</guid>
      <description>Brain damage. They all have brain damage. And they&amp;rsquo;ll likely die from it. Like Aaron Hernandez.
99 out of every 100 football players have serious brain damage.
Kneeling for CTE NFL players and owners decided to show their disrespect to the flag, law enforcement, and the USA by kneeling during the national anthem. In a foreign country.
The president responded by saying the NFL (and the TV networks) would be in big trouble if people stopped watching or attending games.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>