<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Constitution on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/constitution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Constitution on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 08:14:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/constitution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Do We Deserve Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/do-we-deserve-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 08:14:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/do-we-deserve-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Do We Deserve Freedom?
You probably know people who are concerned about a &amp;ldquo;surveillance state&amp;rdquo; developing. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re one of them. I know I am.
It&amp;rsquo;s a reasonable fear.
Some police departments are using drones to spy on people in their homes, peering into living rooms and bedrooms with digital cameras and fining or arresting people who have more than the imposed limit of guests. The justification the state gives for these intrusions is, of course, coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives Keep Losing Because They’re Reading The Wrong Books</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/09/conservatives-keep-losing-because-theyre-reading-the-wrong-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/12/09/conservatives-keep-losing-because-theyre-reading-the-wrong-books/</guid>
      <description>For the past four years. conservatives have worried more about being right while liberals worried about winning.
We all know how that worked out.
It doesn’t matter how right you are if you’re powerless.Right now we are.
Satisfied?
I didn’t think so.

After four years of 5,000 Leap and Constitution study groups, of Constitutional workshops, and rallies in the park, let’s make a vow to ourselves and to each other: We’re Done With Losing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studies Show Most Americans Are Too Stupid to Vote</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/29/studies-show-most-americans-are-too-stupid-to-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 21:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/29/studies-show-most-americans-are-too-stupid-to-vote/</guid>
      <description>The new fad among Democrats is to see how many illegal aliens they can pack into a voting booth. While we conservatives decry this illegal and anti-American grab at tyrannical power, we should take some solace in this sobering fact: those illegal aliens probably know as much about the American political system as most 13th generation Americans.

The fact is, most Americans are too stupid about politics to vote, which explains the 2008 election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covenant of Liberty Is Available Now</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/20/covenant-of-liberty-is-available-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 14:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/03/20/covenant-of-liberty-is-available-now/</guid>
      <description>Covenant of Liberty is the best American history I’ve read in years.
Michael Patrick Leahy, among a very small group of patriots who hatched the first round of Tea Parties in February 2009, documents the US Government’s 230 year history of Constitutional infidelity.
My full review will be finished soon, but don’t wait: buy Covenant of Liberty today.
https://rcm.amazon.com/e/cm?lt1=_blank&amp;amp;bc1=000000&amp;amp;IS2=1&amp;amp;bg1=FFFFFF&amp;amp;fc1=000000&amp;amp;lc1=0000FF&amp;amp;t=hennesssview-20&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;p=8&amp;amp;l=as4&amp;amp;m=amazon&amp;amp;f=ifr&amp;amp;ref=ss_til&amp;amp;asins=0062066331
Mike Leahy was the keynote speaker on day one of the 3rd Anniversary Tea Party in St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Were You When Obama Nullified the Constitution?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/01/16/where-were-you-when-obama-nullified-the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>Most Americans know more about forensic evidence in the Casey Anthony case than they do about the Constitution. That ignorance gave Barack Obama the hubris to end constitutional government in the United States. He did it, and you probably didn’t even notice.
Over the course of a week, Barack Obama made a series of so-called recess appointments. In the process, he and his henchmen in Eric Holder’s Justice Department effectively nullified the US Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Contempt for the Rule of Law</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/obamas-contempt-for-the-rule-of-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 10:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/obamas-contempt-for-the-rule-of-law/</guid>
      <description>When he identified the three branches of government as President, House, and Senate, Was Chuck Schumer confused, or did he accurately state the Obama administration’s intent to subjugate the Judicial Branch of government? It seems the White House no longer considers the Judicial Branch the equal of the Executive.
In two cases—the Gulf oil drilling ban and Obamacare—the White House refuses to obey ruling from federal judges. In New Orleans, federal judge Martin Feldman found the White House in contempt for its re-imposition of oil drilling bans after his previous ruling to the contrary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s the Constitutional Standing of a City?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/26/whats-the-constitutional-standing-of-a-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 04:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/26/whats-the-constitutional-standing-of-a-city/</guid>
      <description>Many of the people who support eliminating state oversight of the St. Louis Board of Police Commissioners are not conservatives. Decidedly not.
There are some good conservatives who disagree over the Board of Police Commissioners for the City of St. Louis. I’ve heard some of these conservative make some strong arguments for abolishing the board or relinquishing it to St. Louis Mayor Francis Slay.
Some of the arguments in favor of so-called “home rule” are flat out false.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezra Klein and the Dead Constitution</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/01/ezra-klein-and-the-dead-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/01/ezra-klein-and-the-dead-constitution/</guid>
      <description>Clearly a fan of understatement, Ezra Klein once ran a blog called “Not Geniuses.” Now, of course, he demonstrates his ignorance on MSNBC.
Last week, Klein unwittingly advanced the cause of dead constitutions. He did a better job than any proponent could. He said:
 The issue with the Constitution is that the text is confusing because it was written more than a hundred years ago.
 (William F. Buckley once described a statement like Klein’s as evoking of the sort of pity one feels for the ignorance of animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tea Party’s Real Purpose Is . . .</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/06/the-tea-partys-real-purpose-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/06/the-tea-partys-real-purpose-is/</guid>
      <description>We talk about liberty, limited government, freedom, Constitutional principles, and the like. Those are all relevant to the purposes of the conservative grassroots movement. But are they ends? Or are they just means?
I believe they are means. In the founders’ writings we find clues to the end, even they don’t state it explicitly. Jefferson did. Jay came close. And Adams implicitly understood that end.

Let me ask this: what’s the point of all the work we did in the past two years?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of the Tenth Amendment</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/28/the-story-of-the-tenth-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2007 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/07/28/the-story-of-the-tenth-amendment/</guid>
      <description>**Note: Please read the entire store by clicking on the title or the Continue Reading link below. **
Those of us whose conservative conversions occured in the late 1970s and early 1980s, I think, are particularly fascinated by the 10th Amendment to the Constitution. We also mourn over its senseless destruction by Congress, courts, and citizens.
 The powers not delegated to the United States by the Constitution, nor prohibited by it to the States, are reserved for the States respectively, or to the people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>