<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>libertarianism on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/libertarianism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in libertarianism on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 01:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/libertarianism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Crystal-Clear Images From The Republican Primary De-Cantor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/15/3-crystal-clear-images-from-the-republican-primary-de-cantor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 01:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/15/3-crystal-clear-images-from-the-republican-primary-de-cantor/</guid>
      <description>“Shellacked!”
That was the word that stuck out to me.
Eric Cantor, the Republican House Majority Leader led by 34 points according to his pollster. He lost by 10. That’s a shellacking.
Eric Cantor was the first sitting House Majority Leader ever knocked off in a primary. Cantor was also one of Wall Street’s best friends and the embodiment of crony capitalism—the disease eating the heart out of the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why GOP Pandering to Young Voters Backfires</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/25/why-gop-pandering-to-young-voters-backfires/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/25/why-gop-pandering-to-young-voters-backfires/</guid>
      <description>Marco Rubio gave the Republican response to the State of the Union address for two reasons.
First, Rubio’s Cuban, and the GOP wants to court Latinos.
Second, Rubio’s relatively young, and the GOP wants to stop the bleeding when it comes to young voters.
But there’s a fundamental problem with the Republican approach, and it stems from the GOP’s least favorite discipline: behavioral science.
Young People Are Naturally Skeptical You hear about scams that target older folks all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Republican Party Seems Bent On Self-Destruction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/the-republican-party-seems-bent-on-destruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 13:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/24/the-republican-party-seems-bent-on-destruction/</guid>
      <description>Every election cycle millions of reliable Republican voters die and even more millions of Democrat voters get the vote. Messaging and pandering won’t fix the problem. Reforming the party might.
Libertarian reforms offer the best hope, because all the other conservative factions – evangelicals, Second Amendment, home schoolers, fiscal &amp;ndash; have hit their high-water marks. We saw that in 2012. Liberty, however, sells with the kids. Or it might, if Republicans would try it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ron Paul&#39;s Fifteen Minutes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/03/ron-pauls-fifteen-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2007 01:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/03/ron-pauls-fifteen-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Congressman Ron Paul (R-TX) generates more internet press than all the other candidates combined, it seems. His name has been on Technorati&amp;rsquo;s most-searched list for a couple weeks, rivaling Paris Hilton and YouTube for search popularity endurance. Whether or not his fledgling campaign for President will so endure is another matter.
Rummaging through the odd blog with a Ron Paul theme, I found some common characteristics among his supporters:
 * Young * Typically apolitical * Technology careers * Homosexual * Educated * Atheist * Decent writing skills * No particular axe to grind  I know many who fit the type, particularly working in the software industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>