<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cannabis on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/cannabis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cannabis on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 13:18:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/cannabis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Is Rand Paul&#39;s Secret to Broadening the Republican Base</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/27/rand-pauls-secret-broadening-republican-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 13:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/07/27/rand-pauls-secret-broadening-republican-base/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever felt like tuning out, giving up, and just riding out whatever storm comes down the pipe next?
I have. Many times. Every week. Sometimes more than once a day.
I think we can both give ourselves a pass on that feeling. In fact, I think we can both give ourselves a pass on acting on that feeling. It&amp;rsquo;s okay to check out occasionally. Everyone needs a break now and then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Time To End War On Weed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/01/its-time-to-end-war-on-weed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/01/01/its-time-to-end-war-on-weed/</guid>
      <description>When in the course of human events it becomes necessary for conservatives to divorce themselves from superstitions they’ve embraced since the Progressive Movement of the 1920s and join the pantheon of reasonable people, a decent respect to the opinions of mankind requires that they should declare the causes which impel them to the separation.
I hold these truths to be totally friggin’ obvious, that all drugs are not created equal, that we’ve wasted billions of dollars and millions of lives pursuing a** demented “zero tolerance” temperance goal that was Never Going To Happen**, that the losses we’ve endured trying stamp out weed have cost American society more than they&amp;rsquo;ve gained, that among these losses are lives, money, and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>