<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>electoral college on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/electoral-college/</link>
    <description>Recent content in electoral college on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/electoral-college/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop The Crazy Talk: Vote Fraud Didn’t Cost Romney The Election</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/19/vote-fraud-didnt-cost-romney-the-election/</guid>
      <description>I wrote yesterday that if you need someone to blame, blame me. Don’t blame bogeymen.

Yes, vote fraud is real. Voter rolls in most states need to be cleaned up. Voter intimidation should be harshly prosecuted.
You can sign up at True the Vote or Missouri Precinct Project to take effective, useful action. These organizations do vital work, and they both need more volunteers.
Using vote fraud, however, as an excuse for secession or for blocking the Electoral College vote is neither effective nor useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Conservatives: We Are Already Losing 2016</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/18/dear-conservatives-we-are-already-losing-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/18/dear-conservatives-we-are-already-losing-2016/</guid>
      <description>If you need to blame someone for our election losses, blame me.

I Let You Down I could have done more. I could have spoken up sooner. I could have been more honest with you about the mistakes we made and the opportunities we ignored. I could have worked harder on what I saw as the most important work we could do.
I let you down. I focused on petty issues of the day, too, instead of working on a different future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If We Don’t Flip Some Toss-Up States, Romney, Ryan, and the USA Are Screwed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2012 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/08/12/if-we-dont-flip-some-toss-up-states-romney-ryan-and-the-usa-are-screwed/</guid>
      <description>Choosing Paul Ryan as his running mate was a great Romney move. Looking ahead, Romney sees movement conservatives working hard right up to the election—even if he or his advisors continues to say stupid things. That was necessary.
SCROLL DOWN FOR TWO IMPORTANT EVENTS THIS WEEK
But it wasn’t enough to win the election and unseat America’s first anti-American president. To do that, we must find a way to win over the selfish middle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Let Missouri Surrender Its Electoral Votes</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/18/dont-let-missouri-surrender-its-electoral-votes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 03:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/18/dont-let-missouri-surrender-its-electoral-votes/</guid>
      <description>Fill out this online witness form TONIGHT.
Read this if you have any questions. Follow the links.
Missouri is considering surrendering its electoral votes to the whims of national popular elections.
STOP IT NOW!!!!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Tilley vs. the Constitution</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/17/steve-tilley-vs-the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2011 18:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/17/steve-tilley-vs-the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>And, he’s back.
Missouri House Speaker Steve Tilley (R-Perryville) has signed onto legislation designed to circumvent the Electoral College in presidential elections. Like his position on embryonic stem cell research and the national debt, Tilley seems far out of step with Missouri’s Republican base on this. And this guy wants to be Lt. Governor? Please.
This might be old news to some.
I see that Big Government’s Josie Wales blogged about the national effort last August.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>