<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ISIS on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/isis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ISIS on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 21:13:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/isis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gullible Evil Losers at CNN Criticize London Cops for Using Too Many Bullets. UPDATE</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/04/gullible-evil-losers-at-cnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 21:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/04/gullible-evil-losers-at-cnn/</guid>
      <description>Maybe we should consider CNN employees enemy combatants.
CNN&amp;rsquo;s latest hate-crime: **CNN is criticizing London police for using too many bullets. **
That&amp;rsquo;s right. CNN will soon demand a UN war crimes tribunal to try, convict, and hang the London cops who put down the London Bridge terrorists.
This photo caption appeared below this critical headline.
CNN has not responded to my request for comments.
Specifically, I asked CNN to provide the exact number of rounds police are allowed to use to stop a terrorist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our military leaders are no Pattons</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/our-leaders-are-no-pattons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 23:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/our-leaders-are-no-pattons/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, Lee Presser made a great point in this guest post, The Only Rule of Engagement Will Be Victory. As one commenter noted:
 This is the best analysis of the war on terror that I have read. If we do not fight to win, we shouldn’t be in the fight. Winning the war on terror starts with 1) admitting there is a war on terror, 2) being willing to confront the enemy with force, 3) fighting to win the war rather than appease the enemy, and 4) do whatever it takes to protect Americans and their homeland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s time for Democrats to abandon Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/18/its-time-for-democrats-to-abandon-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/18/its-time-for-democrats-to-abandon-obama/</guid>
      <description>In the war on terror, you’re on our side or theirs.
Barack Obama announced that he will veto any attempt by Congress to require background checks of Syrian refugees in an attempt to weed out ISIS terrorists. The President&amp;rsquo;s allegiances are now clear.
I heard Senator Dick Durbin (D-IL) say that we must ensure proper screening in the wake of last Friday’s Islamic terrorist attack in Paris.
The House of Representatives is working on legislation to do just that: increase the likelihood that we will catch terrorist infiltraters before they reach American soil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>