<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bureaucracy on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/bureaucracy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bureaucracy on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:43:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/bureaucracy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Crony Capitalism Spreads Bureaucracy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/23/bureaucracy-become-national-pastime/</guid>
      <description>St. Louisan Eric Greitens did more before graduating from college than most people do in a lifetime. And, as if to insult us all, after college, Eric became a Navy SEAL.
In his remarkable book, The Heart and the Fist: The education of a humanitarian, the making of a Navy SEAL  , Greitens tells the story of a man who seems too good to be true. Seriously. And the book left me with two big impressions&amp;ndash;probably the wrong ones, but that&amp;rsquo;s how I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here&#39;s One Way the Government&#39;s Making Medicine Worse in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 02:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/06/20/heres-one-way-the-governments-making-medicine-worse-in-america/</guid>
      <description>I had to go to the doctor today. The reason&amp;rsquo;s not important. Here&amp;rsquo;s what is:
It took my doctor 10 minutes to describe my symptoms into a government-mandated voice recognition system.   
In the old days, the doctor took notes. Now, he has to recite his observations into a Mad Men-era dictaphone. &amp;ldquo;Male, age 48, blood pressure one-twenty-one over seventy-three . . . &amp;quot;
The damn machine (government medical technology) couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand half the doctor&amp;rsquo;s words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the GSA&#39;s 8th Grade Minds That Run Your Life</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/21/meet-the-gsas-8th-grade-minds-that-run-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 18:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/04/21/meet-the-gsas-8th-grade-minds-that-run-your-life/</guid>
      <description>There are two kinds of people in America: those who grow up to become productive adults, and those who become bureaucrats.
The GSA scandal lit up the 3 Stooges mentality of the &amp;ldquo;men and women&amp;rdquo; who would run every aspect of your life if Obama and his czars get their way.

Jeff Neely&amp;rsquo;s the guy Thomas Jefferson had in mind when wrote:
 He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harass our people, and eat out their substance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>