<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>climate-change on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/climate-change/</link>
    <description>Recent content in climate-change on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:42:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/climate-change/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Weinstein and His Call to Jail Global Warming Skeptics</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/03/31/adam-weinstein-neo-nazi-propaganda-machine/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Yet, in holding scientific research and discovery in respect, as we should, we must also be alert to the equal and opposite danger that public policy could itself become the captive of a scientific-technological elite.&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ndash;President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Farewell Address, 1961
A young man named Adam Weinstein recently called for incarceration of disbelievers in the cult of catastrophic anthropogenic global warming (CAGW). His argument mirrors the argument Goebbels used in 1930s to quash dissent from eugenics and to take immediate policy actions for the betterment of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grading my prediction for 2009</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/grading-my-prediction-for-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 04:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/20/grading-my-prediction-for-2009/</guid>
      <description>On December 28, 2008, I published my predictions for 2009. I should have graded myself in January, but I was still on hiatus from Hennessy’s View. So let’s take a look.
The Dow: The Dow trades within a range of 1,000 points with a daily average closing of 8,500.
Grade: D. The average would be a pain to figure out, but it looks like it was closer 9800.
GDP and Economy: By July, everyone pretty much calls the situation &amp;ldquo;Great Depression II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYC Storm:  Don&#39;t Blame Global Warming</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/12/nyc-storm-dont-blame-global-warming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2007 22:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/12/nyc-storm-dont-blame-global-warming/</guid>
      <description>A NASA Goddard scientist says that the massive thunderstorm&amp;ndash;complete with tornado&amp;ndash;that struck New York City on Wednesday was not the result of global warming.
In a FoxNews.com article, James Hansen explains that the storm cannot be blamed on climate change, but it can be attributed to human activity.
Cities, it seems, make storms worse. Tall buildings direct wind upward, intensifying the storms. City heat islands, like warm ocean water to a hurricane, fuel storms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>