<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>petraeus on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/petraeus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in petraeus on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 22:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/petraeus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When The Three O&#39;Clock Call Came, Barack Obama Froze</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2012 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/10/27/when-the-300-am-call-came-barack-obama-froze/</guid>
      <description>The fog of war is lifting from Benghazi, and what lies beneath should shame Obama’s most ardent supporters. Barack Obama choked, and Americans died.

When America came under attack, Obama panicked and froze.
When Americans under his direction pleaded for their lives, he was afraid to pull the trigger.
Here’s the emerging picture.
White House Ordered Military and CIA to Stand Down and Let Al Qaeda Kill Former Navy SEALs Ty Woods and Glen Doherty, so disgusted by the White House’s refusal to help Americans under attack, defied an order to stand down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama the Reckless</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/08/obama-the-reckless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/08/08/obama-the-reckless/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, the United States suffered its highest human lost since the Afghanistan conflict began. At least 38 elite, brave American warriors died in combat.
Flasback to May 23 of this year. That’s when Barack Obama made the surprise announcement that he would begin accelerated troop withdrawals in July. That timetable meant beginning the withdrawal during the summer fighting season.
Current and former military experts advised the president against this reckless move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the Offense, Stupid</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/30/its-the-offense-stupid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2007 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/30/its-the-offense-stupid/</guid>
      <description>Since July, I have been saying that the surge is working because America is on offense instead of hunkering down on defense. Captain&amp;rsquo;s Quarters found a Petraeus interview in which the HMFIC in Iraq confirms that it&amp;rsquo;s not just the numbers, it&amp;rsquo;s the attitude:
 How have things changed in Iraq? Petraeus compared the previous condition of Ramadi to Stalingrad. The general told the newspaper that having to stay on defense had taken its toll on American strength and had emboldened the enemy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>