<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>positive psychology on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/positive-psychology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in positive psychology on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 03:00:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/positive-psychology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How bad would Trump presidency be?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/24/why-so-many-conservatives-are-wrong-about-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/02/24/why-so-many-conservatives-are-wrong-about-trump/</guid>
      <description>The world is about to end.
Or civil war is about to break out in Dayton, Ohio.
Believe it?
Glenn Beck, Erick Erickson, and other Republicans have convinced a lot of people that we are doomed if Donald Trump wins the Republican nomination. I know some people who are nearly incapacitated with fear and grief after last night&amp;rsquo;s Nevada caucuses. Because they listen to Glenn Beck. Sad!
Here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: **nothing is as bad as you think it will be while you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Pissed That I’m Pissed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/im-pissed-that-im-pissed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/08/06/im-pissed-that-im-pissed/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of being angry?
Did you know that a lot of other people are tired of your anger?
Did you know that 70 percent of Americans don’t like politics?
Did you know that the 70 percent of Americans who don’t like politics won’t vote for anything an angry person tells them to vote for?
Go look it up. It’s totally true.
So many conservatives want another Reagan, but they want an angry, vengeful, belligerent Reagan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Get More Twitter Followers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/05/how-to-get-more-twitter-followers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/03/05/how-to-get-more-twitter-followers/</guid>
      <description>Unless you just want to vent, the reason you post things on Twitter is to influence people. But you can’t influence people who don’t see your tweets. **The more people who see your tweets, the more influential you are. **So you should increase your Twitter followers.

How can you increase your followers? Research at Georgia Tech gives you the answer.
Twitter Things To Do Be Positive. Positive tweets are more likely to be retweeted and people who use positive words have more followers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Ways to Make Christmas Season Happier</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/05/2-ways-to-make-christmas-season-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 19:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/12/05/2-ways-to-make-christmas-season-happier/</guid>
      <description>Is it better to give or to receive?
Before you answer, let’s look at some of the science behind giving. Then let’s look a little deeper.
Dr. Barbara Fredrickson studies the psychology of happiness. About a decade ago, Dr. Fredrickson announced a formula for creating an “upward spiral” of happiness. In other words, she identified what it takes to have happiness breed happiness. The formula applies to individuals, families, groups, and even companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Be Happier</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/10/how-to-be-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 13:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/10/how-to-be-happier/</guid>
      <description>Happiness is a choice; anger is a tactic.
Anger will have to wait for a future post. This one is about happiness. So let me ask: would you do something that took less than a minute if that something would make you happier?
Martin Seligman at University of Pennsylvania’s school of Positive Psychology has broken down happiness in more scientifically measurable components:
* Positive Emotion** Engagement** Purpose  Other research has shown how to increase your happiness score.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>