<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Obmacare on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/obmacare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Obmacare on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 16:28:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/obmacare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Prostitutes In Business Suits Cost Ed Martin A Place On The Rules Committee?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/23/did-prostitutes-in-business-suits-cost-ed-martin-a-place-on-the-rules-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 16:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/02/23/did-prostitutes-in-business-suits-cost-ed-martin-a-place-on-the-rules-committee/</guid>
      <description>You probably never heard of Lance Beshore of Joplin, MO. He’s been Missouri’s delegate to the Republican National Committee’s Rules Committee for 12 years. He runs the lobbying department of Leggett &amp;amp; Platt furniture company. He’s on the Missouri Chamber of Commerce, and he’s chairman of the board of Freeman Health Systems.

In his roles at Freeman and the Missouri Chamber, Beshore advocates for Obamacare Medicaid Expansion in Missouri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why You Are Underemployed</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/this-is-why-you-are-underemployed/</guid>
      <description>If you can’t find full-time work, blame Obamacare.

One reason the Middle Class has shriveled and wages shrunk over the the past four years is underemployment. People want full time work, but settle for anything. And anything is usually part time.
Most of the fantastic new jobs created since the 2009 have been part-time jobs.
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, 14.6% of Americans want a full-time job but settle for part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTION:  Steve Tilley and Kevin Engler Want to Implement Obamacare. Stop Them.</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/03/action-steve-tilley-and-kevin-engler-want-to-implement-obamacare-stop-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 02:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/05/03/action-steve-tilley-and-kevin-engler-want-to-implement-obamacare-stop-them/</guid>
      <description>Missouri House Speaker Steve Tilley and Senate Leader Kevin Engler never tire of implementing Obama’s totalitarian agenda.

This time, Tilley and Engler are shoving HB 1193 through to passage. This bill is designed to score brownie points with Sibelius and Obama by creating a prescription spy network that monitors the prescription drug purchases of every Missouri resident.
If Tilley and Engler get their way, every time your doctor writes a prescription, your pharmacist will be required to inform Jefferson City and Washington bureaucrats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Contempt for the Rule of Law</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/obamas-contempt-for-the-rule-of-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 10:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/04/obamas-contempt-for-the-rule-of-law/</guid>
      <description>When he identified the three branches of government as President, House, and Senate, Was Chuck Schumer confused, or did he accurately state the Obama administration’s intent to subjugate the Judicial Branch of government? It seems the White House no longer considers the Judicial Branch the equal of the Executive.
In two cases—the Gulf oil drilling ban and Obamacare—the White House refuses to obey ruling from federal judges. In New Orleans, federal judge Martin Feldman found the White House in contempt for its re-imposition of oil drilling bans after his previous ruling to the contrary.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>