<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crime on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crime on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:00:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret to a Better Life and Less Political Violence Is Here</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</guid>
      <description>If you read a lot of business and personal improvement blogs, you know they feed a lot of tips for living a better life. By &amp;ldquo;better&amp;rdquo; they mean making more money, getting a promotion, being more productive, whatever.
Are those things really what makes life better? If so, why do so many successful people burn out? John Belushi, River Phoenix, Amy Winehouse, Janice Joplin, Michael Jackson. Is it show business? Well, look what&amp;rsquo;s happening to Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Pope Francis and Vatican Sec State Admit Viganò&#39;s Testimony?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/03/did-pope-francis-and-vatican-sec-state-admit-viganos-testimony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 12:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/03/did-pope-francis-and-vatican-sec-state-admit-viganos-testimony/</guid>
      <description>One week after Archbishop Carlo Viganò released his bombshell letter, it looks obvious that Pope Francis admits the key allegation: Francis knew McCarrick to be a serial molester, and he returned McCarrick to public ministry anyway. As we&amp;rsquo;ll see later in this post, Pope Francis has a pattern of letting molesters and their protectors off the hook.
Speaks for Itself Did the pope admit to the horrendous allegations directly? Not directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Towey Is Confused</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/01/jim-towey-is-confused/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 18:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/01/jim-towey-is-confused/</guid>
      <description>God bless Jim Towey and the work of his school, Ave Maria University. I am confident that he is confused, and we should pray for clarity.
I&amp;rsquo;m talking about his recent series of letters and clarifications regarding how Catholics should express their obedience to the pope. Jim is partially right and partially off base.
What Jim Towey Gets Right Jim is right that that conservative Catholics need to be very gracious and obedient when they challenge the pope&amp;rsquo;s formal teaching on matters like the death penalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pope Emeritus Benedict Can Settle It All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/pope-emeritus-benedict-can-settle-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/pope-emeritus-benedict-can-settle-it-all/</guid>
      <description>One man can confirm or deny the central allegation against Pope Francis. The Catholic Church needs that man to step up now.
In an 11-page letter by former US Nuncio (ambassador) Archbishop Carlo Maria Viganò, Pope Francis is accused of ignoring warnings about Cardinal Timothy McCarrick. Viganò claims he personally delivered the warning to Pope Francis in 2013. The pope allegedly ignored the warning and the dossier on McCarrick in 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fisherman&#39;s Other Shoe Just Dropped</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/the-fishermans-other-shoe-just-dropped/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/the-fishermans-other-shoe-just-dropped/</guid>
      <description>God, come to our assistance O, Lord, make haste to help us
 Pope Francis ignored evidence of crimes and overturned punishment imposed by Pope Benedict on the wicked and disgraced Cardinal McCarrick. That&amp;rsquo;s according to a former papal nuncio and corroborated by a former first counselor to the nunciature to the United States speaking on the record. The two men have direct knowledge of the matter.
Pope Francis refused to comment on the allegations that he personally covered up McCarrick&amp;rsquo;s crimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking News: Multiple Deputies Down in Shooting South of Denver (Active)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/31/breaking-news-multiple-deputies-down-in-shooting-south-of-denver-active/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/31/breaking-news-multiple-deputies-down-in-shooting-south-of-denver-active/</guid>
      <description>Latest: Sheriff sets up emergency shelter for displaced residents:
   Due to the size and cope of this investigation an emergency shelter has been set up @ East Ridge Rec Center, located at 9568 University Blvd. in Highlands Ranch. If anyone has been displaced from their homes due to this event please feel free to head there.
 — DC Sheriff (@dcsheriff) December 31, 2017
Earlier: Domestic disturbance led to shots fired, via Douglas County Sheriff:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: State Department releases Huma Abedin emails found on Weiner&#39;s hard drive</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/breaking-state-department-releases-huma-abedin-emails-found-on-weiners-hard-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 20:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/12/29/breaking-state-department-releases-huma-abedin-emails-found-on-weiners-hard-drive/</guid>
      <description>The US Department of State released 2,800 emails involving Hillary aid Huma Abedin that were found on Anthony Weiner&amp;rsquo;s hard drive last year, Judicial Watch reports. You can read all the emails here: FOIA Abedin Emails
In a statement, Judicial Watch, which forced the release through lawsuits, said this:
 This is a major victory. After years of hard work in federal court, Judicial Watch has forced the State Department to finally allow Americans to see these public documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equifax Update: More Breaches, More Lies</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/equifax-update-more-breaches-more-lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 21:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/19/equifax-update-more-breaches-more-lies/</guid>
      <description>You will be mad.
You probably don&amp;rsquo;t have a contract with Equifax. Your creditors do.
When you apply for a loan, you give creditors permission to:
*1. Obtain your credit file. *2. Update your credit file.
You expect that creditors vet their vendors, don&amp;rsquo;t you? You assume banks and credit card companies test their vendors&amp;rsquo; security.
And you expect financial services companies like Equifax to be on the up and up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I still think James Comey is a felon, and the FBI is corrupt</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/01/i-still-think-james-comey-is-a-felon-and-the-fbi-is-corrupt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 01:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/09/01/i-still-think-james-comey-is-a-felon-and-the-fbi-is-corrupt/</guid>
      <description>James Comey exonerated Hillary Clinton three months before he interviewed her.
James Comey exonerated Hillary Clinton before interviewing 16 key witnesses.
James Comey exonerated Hillary Clinton before he gathered any significant evidence.
James Comey gave Hillary Clinton permission to destroy evidence in a felony investigation.
James Comey leaked classified information to the media.
These are all facts. No one disputes them.
They are all crimes of various degrees. Some felonies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Betting on an Indictment of Comey</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/10/why-im-betting-on-an-indictment-of-comey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 21:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/10/why-im-betting-on-an-indictment-of-comey/</guid>
      <description>I made a lot of money on the election. Most of that money I cashed out. But I left a small balance in case I saw another opportunity to bet against the prevailing wisdom.
I saw that opportunityt last night.
My PredictIt Success In January 2016, I bought three kinds of shares on PredictIt, the prediction market.
*1. Trump would win the Republican nomination. *2. Trump would win the White House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Obstruction. No Collusion. He&#39;s a Leaker. UPDATES</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/09/no-obstruction-no-collusion-hes-a-leaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 23:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/06/09/no-obstruction-no-collusion-hes-a-leaker/</guid>
      <description>Scott Adams pointed out the linguistic brilliance of Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s perfect summation of James Comey&amp;rsquo;s failed takedown attempt.
&amp;ldquo;No obstruction. No collusion. He&amp;rsquo;s a leaker.&amp;rdquo;
That&amp;rsquo;s how Trump summarized Comey&amp;rsquo;s testimony to the Senate&amp;rsquo;s Russian Conspiracy Hoax Committee.
Click to watch:
  
Scott is a genius in persuasion and psychology. Everything he just said about Trump&amp;rsquo;s linguistic kill-shot is dead-on accurate. Trump destroyed Comey without firing a shot. &amp;ldquo;No obstruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is the New York Times blackmailing FBI and CIA?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 01:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/25/is-the-new-york-times-blackmailing-fbi-and-cia/</guid>
      <description>Sounds ridiculous, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?
How could a reporter at New York Times blackmail an FBI or CIA agent?
Easily. And everyone who ever went through counter-espionage training knows it.
What Went Down This morning, British Prime Minister Theresa May chastised the US government. The UK freely shares anti-terrorism intelligence with the US. The US is expected to keep secrets secret.
But the US intel community is one gigantic sieve these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Rich Murder Case Closing In On Clinton Crime Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/20/seth-rich-murder-case-closing-in-on-clinton-crime-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 21:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/05/20/seth-rich-murder-case-closing-in-on-clinton-crime-family/</guid>
      <description>Was Seth Rich murdered as an example?
Seth Rich was murdered. Two gunshots to his back. Like you&amp;rsquo;d see on The Sopranos (video). The police called it a robbery. But nothing was stolen. Not his cell phone. Not his wallet. Not his watch. Not his cash.
Shortly after his murder, Wikileaks posted embarrassing emails. Emails from the Democratic National Committee&amp;rsquo;s email server. Wikileaks maintains that the theft of the emails was an inside job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Lives Don&#39;t Matter to American Liberals</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/24/black-lived-dont-matter-to-american-liberals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 03:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/24/black-lived-dont-matter-to-american-liberals/</guid>
      <description>President Trump (who, by the way, has accomplished more in two days than Obama did in eight years) saw Chicago&amp;rsquo;s horrific crime statistics and warned the mayor and the governor to get to work or he&amp;rsquo;ll fix it himself. Seventy-five percent of murder victims in Chicago are black.
Immediately, leftists, who apparently enjoy all the carnage in Chicago, attacked Trump&amp;rsquo;s call for fewer shootings and murders.
Think of that. LIBERALS WANT MORE MURDER!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking: San Antonio Mall Shooting: One Dead, Six Wounded, Armed Citizen Shot Murderer</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/22/breaking-san-antonio-mall-shooting-one-dead-six-wounded-armed-citizen-shot-murderer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 23:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2017/01/22/breaking-san-antonio-mall-shooting-one-dead-six-wounded-armed-citizen-shot-murderer/</guid>
      <description>A Good Samaritan was shot and killed and three shot in a &amp;ldquo;robbery gone very wrong&amp;rdquo; at Rolling Oaks Mall in San Antonio, Texas Sunday afternoon about 3:30 p.m. Two others transported to hospitals with other medical conditions. One suspect is still at large and assumed armed and dangerous.
The dead man was a shopper who attempted to stop two robbers after they robbed a Kay Jewelers store in the mall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killing Scalia: The Clinton Crime Family</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/13/killing-scalia-the-clinton-crime-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/10/13/killing-scalia-the-clinton-crime-family/</guid>
      <description>Do you think the Clinton Crime Family whacked Antonin Scalia? You will soon if you let yourself read this and all the links. But first, a strange call I had last week.
Something Unrelated At the end of our talk, the reporter said, &amp;ldquo;do you mind if I ask you about something else? It has nothing to do with my article, and I won&amp;rsquo;t write about it.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Uh, sure,&amp;rdquo; I said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shameless James Comey Is a Liar and Darrell Issa Is a Hero</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/28/shameless-james-comey-is-a-liar-and-darrell-issa-is-a-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 01:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/09/28/shameless-james-comey-is-a-liar-and-darrell-issa-is-a-hero/</guid>
      <description>No honest company would hire FBI Director James Comey. He might be loyal, but he&amp;rsquo;ll commit crimes of loyalty.
Comey would have fit right in at Enron. Or in Ceauşescu&amp;rsquo;s Romania.
Today we learned that Comey flat out lied about Cheryl Mills&amp;rsquo;s immunity agreement. Rep. Darrell Issa (R-CA) exposed Comey&amp;rsquo;s lies just minutes after Comey lied to Congress under oath about the extent of immunity granted to Mills, who was both a State Department employee and one of Hillary&amp;rsquo;s huge stable of personal attorneys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama &amp; Hillary Have Lost Control of Cop Killer Rhetoric</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/17/cop-killer-hillary-has-lost-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/17/cop-killer-hillary-has-lost-control/</guid>
      <description>Hillary, Obama, and much of the Democrat Party have fomented race hatred for years. They&amp;rsquo;ve ratcheted up their lies in recent months, hoping to turn race hatred into votes. They are that cynical and self-serving.
Now, Hillary and Obama have lost control of the fire they started. Crazed, racist murderers all across the country have declared war on police officers. From Dallas, Texas, to Ballwin, Missouri, to Baton Rouge, Louisianna, Hillary has sent a message that says it&amp;rsquo;s okay to kill a cop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convict Hillary</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/10/convict-hillary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 15:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/07/10/convict-hillary/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people are mad at FBI Director James Comey. Comey read a list of crimes committed by Hillary Clinton, then announced he couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend prosecution for those crimes. On its face, it sounds like Comey caved.
Let&amp;rsquo;s play the imagine game. Imagine Comey decided to refer Hillary Clinton&amp;rsquo;s crimes to the Department of Justice for prosecution. What would happen?
First, you&amp;rsquo;d never hear about it. The FBI and the DOJ don&amp;rsquo;t discuss active criminal investigations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Petraeus Paying Price for Hillary&#39;s Crimes?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/19/ponder-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 03:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2016/01/19/ponder-this/</guid>
      <description>Beyond Top Secret.
Hillary famously kept an email server in her private bedroom where it was safe from being used as Bill&amp;rsquo;s YouPorn hub. (I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure Bill Clinton hasn&amp;rsquo;t visited the inside of his wife&amp;rsquo;s sleeping chamber in the 21st century.)
Being plugged into the internet, though, and lacking even the most rudimentary security, Hillary&amp;rsquo;s server was exposed to the prying eyes of Chinese, North Korean, Russian, and Anonymous spies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Create Hate and Discontent in America</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/17/create-hate-discontent-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 18:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/08/17/create-hate-discontent-america/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t written about Ferguson because I&amp;rsquo;ve known too little to add value. But ignorance hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped others from stirring up hate and discontent. For example, Missouri&amp;rsquo;s shakedown artist, Lacy Clay.
Lacy Clay, speaking from a private island in the Carribean, told the St. Louis Post-Dispatch that Michael Brown was murdered. Clay knew or should have known the effect of his words: more violence. Either Clay meant to incite violence or he has a casual disregard for the effect of his irresponsible speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not All Lies Are Meant To Fool</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/26/lies-meant-fool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 01:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/26/lies-meant-fool/</guid>
      <description>What line of work was Tony Soprano in? 
Waste management.
Did Tony Soprano expect people to believe he was in waste management?
No. Tony Soprano expected people realize he was a wise guy and treat him with due respect&amp;ndash;or what you and I call fear.
Some lies are meant to make the liar seem more successful or more talented or better than he thinks he is. Trust me, I&amp;rsquo;ve done it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Changing My Mind About Impeaching Obama</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/03/im-changing-mind-impeaching-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 23:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/03/im-changing-mind-impeaching-obama/</guid>
      <description>A lot of good people I know grumble that the House Republicans don&amp;rsquo;t try to impeach Obama.
I usually don&amp;rsquo;t say much in response. After the disaster of the ill-conceived Clinton impeachment fiasco,** impeachment seems like a superstition**. Like a unicorn. I think impeachment is a dangerous tool and should never be used for political purposes.
Besides, Harry Reid&amp;rsquo;s Senate wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consider articles of impeachment if they included NSA video of Obama throwing adorable, drooling toddlers off the George Washington Bridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shout It Out: Renegade Arizona Sheriff Intimidating Citizens *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/05/shout-it-out-renegade-arizona-sheriff-intimidating-citizens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 00:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/02/05/shout-it-out-renegade-arizona-sheriff-intimidating-citizens/</guid>
      <description>The incompetent Sheriff Dupnik of Pima County Arizona has intimidated speakers in an attempt to shut down the Tucson Tea Party.
Now, Tucson’s asking for our help. Jennifer Humphries wrote to Gateway Pundit Jim Hoft. She asked Jim of his help defending the First Amendment rights of the people of Tucson. Those rights are under assault from an incompetent and irresponsible sheriff who has now turned to intimidation to silence dissent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Left Doubles Down on Threats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/18/left-doubles-down-on-threats/</guid>
      <description>What would you do?
Suppose you did something stupid. You blamed the wrong person, for instance, for a capital crime. Then supposed one of your comrades compounded your . . . error . . . by threatening to kill someone on national television?
If you’re an American leftist, you might double down by issuing even more death threats to even more people.
That’s what’ happening right now in America. Death threats are pouring into Trent Humphries, Tucson Tea Party organizer, Dana Loesch, Sarah Palin (who vows not to be silenced), Glenn Beck, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Bill Maher’s Vitriol Responsible for Arrest?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/16/is-bill-mahers-vitriol-responsible-for-arrest/</guid>
      <description>Last week, America’s sleaziest leftists—Bill Maher, Chris Matthews, Keith Olbermann, E. J. Dionne, Paul Krugman, others – have [executed a prepared propaganda war](https://hennessysview.com/crime/a-national-day-of-shame/) against anyone who disagrees with them. Their theorem is: vitriolic rhetoric inspires conservatives to act out in violence.
Unfortunately for the loony left, there was no evidence to support their theorem. The evidence they falsely pointed to—Jarod Lee Loughner’s deranged murder rampage in Tucson—was determined to be a lie only hours after the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff Dupnik’s Culpability</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/10/sheriff-dupniks-culpability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 01:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/10/sheriff-dupniks-culpability/</guid>
      <description>According to an internal Department of Homeland Security memo, Jarod Lee Loughner’s mother “works for Pima County Board of Supervisors.”
In the memo, obtained by Fox News and posted on Greta Van Susteren’s blog, the DHS agent openly speculates about undue internal influence. That’s because Loughner’s arrests don’t all end with reasonable closure, if you will.
Here’s exactly what the DHS report says:
 suspect’s mother works for the Pima County Board of Supervisors* the suspect has multiple arrests &amp;hellip; But no criminal record?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A National Day of Shame</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/a-national-day-of-shame/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/09/a-national-day-of-shame/</guid>
      <description>It’s bad enough that five people died, including a wonderful nine-year-old girl.
It’s bad enough that a dozen or more people were shot.
It’s bad enough that a deranged man attacked our American system.
But America’s liberal elite turned the tragedy into a national day of shame. They accomplished this by callously and capriciously blaming innocent political opponents for the violence. When confronted with facts to the contrary, liberals, including Paul Krugman, CBS News, the New York Times, CNN, MSNBC, Jane Fonda, Sheriff Dupnick of Pima County Arizona, and others, continued to lie, slander, and libel the tea party, Rush Limbaugh, Sarah Palin, Glenn Beck, and conservatives in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Giffords Shooter: Jared Loughner Leaves Video *UPDATES*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/alleged-giffords-shooter-jared-loughner-leaves-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 21:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/alleged-giffords-shooter-jared-loughner-leaves-video/</guid>
      <description>Update: Gateway Pundit has much more on the alleged shooter.
These appear to be the paranoid ramblings of the man in custody for shooting Rep. Gabrielle Giffords and 11 others, including a federal judge, in Tucson, AZ. Lots of hard left references in his favorite books, including Mein Kampf and The Communist Manifesto. Politico’s Ben Smith calls Laughner’s writings “socialist.”
[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nHoaZaLbqB4&amp;amp;hl;=en&amp;amp;hd;=1]
Another Video by alleged shooter in Arizona made 3 weeks before shooting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Go With Hope—reports that Gabrielle Giffords is still alive, needs our prayers</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/gabrielle-giffords-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 19:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/08/gabrielle-giffords-rip/</guid>
      <description>Like all decent people, I am disgusted to hear the sad news out of Tucson, AZ: Rep. Gabrielle Giffords (D-AZ) was shot and killed along with four others today. Twelve were shot altogether. The murderer was apprehended by heroic bystanders and is in custody.
Not sure of the young murderer’s motives. I’m sure they weren’t worth killing or dying for. Except to him.
Please prayer for the souls of the faithful departed, the well-being of their families, the quick recovery of the wounded, and the delivery of justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innocent Until Proven Conservative</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/innocent-until-proven-conservative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/08/25/innocent-until-proven-conservative/</guid>
      <description>Within hours of reports of a firebombing at Rep. Russ Carnahan’s (D-MO) campaign finance office last Tuesday, St. Louis’s leftist bloggers leapt to the cause. In what seems to have been a coordinated attack, Riverfront Times and several progressive blogs and web sites ascribed culpability for the crime to St. Louis Tea Partyers. At one point, Chad Garrison of RFT flatly stated that the suspect “fit the description” of a tea partyer, a statement he later attempted to soften by claiming that firebombing is “too sane” a crime for Tea Partyers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Answer Chavez</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/how-to-answer-chavez/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 23:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/27/how-to-answer-chavez/</guid>
      <description>Communist dictator Hugo Chavez has has stolen eleven oil rigs owned by the American company Helmerich and Payne. As Reuters points out, Chavez has now nationalized oil, telecommunications (including news), power, steel, and banking.
If you’re keeping score, Chavez leads Obama 5-3, as Obama so far has managed to seize only banking, automotive, and healthcare. But Obama has vowed a comeback.
Over the weekend, I had the pleasure of cutting and splitting some oak and hickory with a friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Feed the Democrats</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/14/dont-feed-democrats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 03:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/06/14/dont-feed-democrats/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;attachment_10218&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;quot;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;quot;260&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;quot;Democrat Congressman attacks college student&amp;rdquo;]  [/caption]
In less than twenty-four hours, the left has demonstrated its incapacity for civilized living by physically assaulting a college student, then exclaiming the virtues of physical assaults on reporters.
Background
A Democrat member of Congress assaulted a college student. The assault, shown on two video angles, was unprovoked (unless asking a simple, closed question is now cause for violence) andcontinuing long past the point at which the victim said stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Ways to Stop Democrat Sen. Bob Casey From Stealing Your Tax Money to Reimburse SEIU for Bribing Media Matters and Huffington Post</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/28/3-ways-to-stop-democrat-sen-bob-casey-from-stealing-your-tax-money-to-reimburse-seiu-for-bribing-media-matters-and-huffington-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 01:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/28/3-ways-to-stop-democrat-sen-bob-casey-from-stealing-your-tax-money-to-reimburse-seiu-for-bribing-media-matters-and-huffington-post/</guid>
      <description>Dana Loesch and 24th State have revealed the ring of corruption that extends from St. Louis bloggers and local St. Louis leftist rag, through SEIU, to Media Matters and Huffington Post.
An additional crook in this den of thieves is Democrat Senator Bob Casey of Pennsylvania. Casey has introduced yet another bailout package. This time, the bailout is intended to repay corrupt unions like SEIU and AFL-CIO for bankrupting their members’ retirements by bribing the media and politicians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Obama Using SEIU to Terrorize Citizens?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/22/is-obama-using-seiu-to-terrorize-citizens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2010/05/22/is-obama-using-seiu-to-terrorize-citizens/</guid>
      <description>Interesting. Mounting evidence suggests [the White House may have been complicit](If so, even Democrats in Congress would be forced to open impeachment investigations) in SEIU’s terrorism (as defined by U.S. Patriot Act) of a banker’s teenage son.

Quit the SEIU. No decent person would belong to an organization that openly, and with the federal government’s approval, uses terrorism to get its way.
Quit the DC Metro Police Force. The President is using you to promote domestic terrorism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gloriously Goring Gore</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/04/gloriously-goring-gore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 14:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/04/gloriously-goring-gore/</guid>
      <description>The Huffington Post (of all things) brings us a most cogent, concise, and accurate repudiation of Al Gore and the whole &amp;ldquo;climate change&amp;rdquo; Nazi crowd (h/t ICECAP). Harold Ambler deserves the Nobel Prize for truth stating. Some highlights.
Strike One: How Al Gore (and Hansen and the rest) lie to you about climate change:
 First, the expression &amp;ldquo;climate change&amp;rdquo; itself is a redundancy, and contains a lie. Climate has always changed, and always will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Addicted to Entitlement</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/03/addicted-to-entitlement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 14:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2009/01/03/addicted-to-entitlement/</guid>
      <description>Entitlement is the psychological abnormality in which a person believes that he is owed an enrichment or compensation earned by suffering or activity and that society or government is obligated to pay. It is a psychological condition. It is abnormal&amp;ndash;or should be.
When a team of governors demands that the federal government steal wages and profits of the citizens and transfer those monies to state governors to dispense as the governors see fit, one wonders whether or not the disease is now the norm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WSJ: Obama Lied About Blagojevich Contacts</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/15/wsj-obama-lied-about-blagojevich-contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 11:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/15/wsj-obama-lied-about-blagojevich-contacts/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s Wall Street Journal directly contradict&amp;rsquo;s Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s claim to have never discussed his Senate replacement:
 Barack Obama had begun thinking about his Senate successor even before the presidential election, and dispatched Rahm Emanuel days after the vote to contact aides of Illinois Gov. Rod Blagojevich to begin talking up Mr. Obama&amp;rsquo;s preferred candidates, associates of Mr. Emanuel said this weekend.
 Remember that Obama also claimed that no one on his staff or acting on his behalf discussed the seat with Blago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Mother F****er&#34;</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/09/mother-fer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 23:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/12/09/mother-fer/</guid>
      <description>Wow. Why does news like this always break when I&amp;rsquo;m at work?
Illinois Governor Rod Blagojevich did the perp walk for his Chicago neighbors this morning. Others have written plenty about the facts of the indictment (here, here, here, here, and here). You should know two things:
1. There&amp;rsquo;s a chance Obama will pardon Blagojevich before he goes to court. Why? Because Obama is too close not to. Blagojevich is NOT AN HONORABLE CROOK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Rubin&#39;s Days Are Numbered</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/29/robert-rubins-days-are-numbered/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 04:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/29/robert-rubins-days-are-numbered/</guid>
      <description>Robert Rubin was a key player in keeping Enron afloat while he and his cronies fleeced billions from employees and investors.
Robert Rubin abandoned the Clinton administration when a recession was unavoidable. His relief was his protege, Larry Summers.
Robert Rubin talked the Citigroup board into investing in extremely high-risk mortgage-backed securities. He also showed the bank how to carry those risks off the books&amp;ndash;exactly the way he showed Enron how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Kept Shopping</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/29/they-kept-shopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 13:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/29/they-kept-shopping/</guid>
      <description>Say you&amp;rsquo;re the CEO of Wal-Mart. You get a report from your store in Valley Stream, NJ, that one of your employees was trampled to death by your customers who broke down the doors to get at your Black Friday specials before anyone else. In the chaos, a customer, 8-months pregnant, suffered a miscarriage.
How would you respond?
Suppose you were the police who responded? How would you handle the situation in which the crowd, gripped by throes of a shopping frenzy refused to allow first responders to attempt to save the man&amp;rsquo;s life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/28/merry-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 05:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/11/28/merry-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Hundreds of people trampled others to death so that they could get to cheap retail goods the fastest &amp;ndash; presumably to celebrate the birth of Jesus Christ. . . .At some point, that horrible irony should cause people to pause and think about what motivates them in this holiday season.
 Amen to that, Ed. While I have no eagerness to live through an economic Great Depression, I think we need it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Liberal Liar</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/26/another-liberal-liar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/26/another-liberal-liar/</guid>
      <description>Black Five has the story of cowardly, pussy, scum who&amp;rsquo;s pretending to be a military hero. I know his kind of talk is frowned upon, but Charlie W. Williams should be taken out and shot. The best we can hope for in our wimpy society is for a Marine to beat the living hell out of him. The fact that he&amp;rsquo;s an old man makes no difference: you pretend to be a war hero for political purposes, you get whatever comes to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s $26 Million Fannie Mae Be-atch</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/05/obamas-26-million-fannie-mae-be-atch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 20:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/05/obamas-26-million-fannie-mae-be-atch/</guid>
      <description>Her name is Jamie Gorelick. She was the principal architect of Al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s ability to plan and execute the 9-11 attacks under US intel&amp;rsquo;s radar. She took $26 Million in six years from Fannie Mae by ordering accountants and internal auditors to falsify records and forge documents so ensure that she, Jim Johnson, Franklin Raines, and other Democrat executives at Fannie received maximum bonuses.
FoxNews.com:
 Lehman Brothers collapse is traced back to Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, the two big mortgage banks that got a federal bailout a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Aren&#39;t These Democrats In Prison?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/04/why-arent-these-democrats-in-prison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 20:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/04/why-arent-these-democrats-in-prison/</guid>
      <description>[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=exxVZTKq1vA&amp;amp;hl;=en&amp;amp;fs;=1]
Barney Frank (D-MA)
Chris Dodd (D-CT)
Maxine Waters (D-CA)
Lacy Clay (D-MO)
Gregory Meeks (D-GA)
Charles Rangel (D-NY)
These Democrats were the most vicious in attacking Republicans who tried to stop the abuses at Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac in 2003-2006. These criminal Congressmen accused anyone of challenging the soundness and safety of Fannie and Freddie of racism. &amp;ldquo;The political lynching of Franklin Raines,&amp;rdquo; was was Lacy Clay of Missouri called an auditor&amp;rsquo;s report on Fannie Mae.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read The Dems Race Card Attacks on Fannie Mae Regulators</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/01/read-the-dems-race-card-attacks-on-fannie-mae-regulators/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2008 05:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/10/01/read-the-dems-race-card-attacks-on-fannie-mae-regulators/</guid>
      <description>In 2004, John McCain cosponsored legislation to clean up the criminal fraud of Obama advisorFranklin Raines&amp;rsquo;s Fannie Mae. The WSJ has a round up of key Democrats defending Raines&amp;rsquo;s fraud, calling the regulators and auditors liars, and telling McCain to stuff his reforms where sun shineth not.
 [youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_MGT_cSi7Rs&amp;amp;hl;=en&amp;amp;fs;=1] Rep. Barney Frank (D., Mass.): I worry, frankly, that there&amp;rsquo;s a tension here. The more people, in my judgment, exaggerate a threat of safety and soundness, the more people conjure up the possibility of serious financial losses to the Treasury, which I do not see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thief Jim Johnson Still Obama&#39;s Economic Advisor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/24/thief-jim-johnson-still-obamas-economic-advisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2008 04:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/24/thief-jim-johnson-still-obamas-economic-advisor/</guid>
      <description>On the night that the President of the United States described America&amp;rsquo;s current economic condition in terms reminiscent of the Great Depression comes word from Ben Smith at Politico that one of the chief architects of the next depression, Countrywide and Fannie Mae thief James Johnson, is advising Barack Obama on how to proceed on this crisis.
Smith quotes former Senator Tom Daschle:
Jim Johnson and I have scheduled another informal breakfast discussion and update on the campaign early next month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hubris</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/21/hubris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 17:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/21/hubris/</guid>
      <description>From the
Mercury News:
 Barack Obama made the calamity on Wall Street the central theme of his case against John McCain on Saturday, invoking the crisis to pound his rival on Social Security, health care and government reform.
 Let me get this straight: The highest-paid Fannie Mae/Freddie Mac politician on the planet wants to blame the financial crisis on the only politician whom Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac were unable to bribe!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Guess I&#39;m a Racist</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/19/i-guess-im-a-racist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2008 00:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/19/i-guess-im-a-racist/</guid>
      <description>Time magazine&amp;rsquo;s Karen Tumulty says that criticizing Franklin Raines&amp;ndash;the heart and soul of our current economic near-meltdown&amp;ndash;is racism because . . . Raines is black.
Therefore, criticizing any black is racism.
I&amp;rsquo;ve criticized and accused Franklin Raines brutally in the past two weeks, so I must be a regular David Dukes. Perhaps Karen Tumulty needs to change her meds.
Readers may not believe this, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize Raines was black until after I&amp;rsquo;d posted the second of my blog posts linking to Obama to Raines and Johnson and others responsible for the housing bubble and meltdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franklin Raines&#39; Criminal Enterprise and Barack Obama, His Accomplice **UPDATE** Top Recipients By $/Yr in Congress</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/15/franklin-raines-criminal-enterprise-and-barack-obama-his-accomplice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 01:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/15/franklin-raines-criminal-enterprise-and-barack-obama-his-accomplice/</guid>
      <description>TOP OF PAGE UPDATE
This is an eye-opener. I&amp;rsquo;ve simply added Years in Congress and divided total Fraudie
Mae and Fraudie Mac donations by that number to rank the top 15 recipients by $ per Year. Obama is winner by a ton:
Download Spreadsheet FannieMaeEarningsByYearsInCongress

As an executive at Fannie Mae, Franklin Raines illegally coerced his employees to falsify accounting facts so he&amp;rsquo;d get a maximum bonus. The government-backed firm used Enron-like fraud, in part at Raines&amp;rsquo;s orders, to create the largest bail-out in US history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama The Property of Freddie/Fannie Crooks</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/08/obama-the-property-of-freddiefannie-crooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 02:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/08/obama-the-property-of-freddiefannie-crooks/</guid>
      <description>Surprise, surprise. It turns out that the criminals who used Freddie Mac and Frannie Mae as a slush fund for influence purchasing and pocket-lining own Barack Obama, part and parcel.
According to the Wall Street Journal:
 Sen. Obama has received $105,849 from donors tied to the companies since he ran for the senate four years ago, making him the **third-largest recipient in Congress **among the top 25 listed in a recent report by the Center for Responsive Politics, which examined contributions dating to 1989.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peace-Loving Libs Attempt to Kill Republicans in Minnesota *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/01/peace-loving-libs-attempt-to-kill-republicans-in-minnesota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 21:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/09/01/peace-loving-libs-attempt-to-kill-republicans-in-minnesota/</guid>
      <description>Not an exaggeration. Gateway Pundit was an intended target as leftist protestors hurled sacks of rocks and cement on speeding busses of GOP delegates, media, and participants. The leftards stood on overpasses above an interstate highway and dropped the sacks on passing busses.
A few years back in St. Louis, a woman&amp;ndash;recent emigrant from Russia&amp;ndash;was killed by a rock dropped from an overpass over I-64 as she returned home from work late one evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death Penalty for San Francisco Mayor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/30/death-penalty-for-san-francisco-mayor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2008 16:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/30/death-penalty-for-san-francisco-mayor/</guid>
      <description>Danielle Bologna&amp;rsquo;s trembles like an injured child&amp;rsquo;s when she approaches the word, &amp;ldquo;widow.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d used that word about myself,&amp;rdquo; she recently told an interviewer.
Bologna is a widow. She&amp;rsquo;s also the grieving mother of two sons. On June 22, 2008, a wild, crazed killer wiped out Mrs. Bologna&amp;rsquo;s family as they returned home from a family picnic. Tony, husband and father; Michael, 20 years, sone; Matthew, 16 years, son.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marine Jose Luis Nazario NOT GUILTY!</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/28/marine-jose-luis-nazario-not-guilty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 01:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/28/marine-jose-luis-nazario-not-guilty/</guid>
      <description>The Marine who was charged in civilian court with murder for doing his job on terrorists in Iraq was found NOT GUILTY (h/t wizbang) by a jury of his peers.
Congratulations to Jose Luis Nazario! Thank you, Marine, for you proud and noble service to me, my family, and our country. Thank you, jurors, for rejected the sick arguments of that jack-booted thug federal prosecutor. May this serve as a warning to anti-military prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comrade Obama&#39;s Thugs Go After Kurtz</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/28/comrade-obamas-thugs-go-after-kurtz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/28/comrade-obamas-thugs-go-after-kurtz/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;sassault on freedom of speech and of the press continued today as his minions attacke WGN radio in attempt to squelch journalist Stanley Kurtz. Kurtz is investigating Obama&amp;rsquo;s long and deep ties to terrorist William Ayers. Obama laundered money through a non-profit education foundation into Ayers&amp;rsquo; numerous corrupt organizations during the 1990s. When news broke of Obama&amp;rsquo;s connection to the convicted terrorist, Obama responded by attempting to incarcerate anyone investigating the connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama&#39;s Ties to Terrorism Tighten</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/26/obamas-ties-to-terrorism-tighten/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 04:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/26/obamas-ties-to-terrorism-tighten/</guid>
      <description>According to Stanley Kurtz, one of a handful of reports allowed to see the Ayers Papers at University of Illinois, Chicago, &amp;ldquo;Our worst fears were confirmed.&amp;rdquo; Radical terrorist William Ayers, founder of the Weathermen and the Woods Fund of Chicago, appointed Obama as one of three directors of the &amp;ldquo;education&amp;rdquo; project in 1995. In exchange for the appointment and the right use it as street cred in his first political campaign, Obama voted to siphon funds intended for public school education programs into Ayers&amp;rsquo;s radical political organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday&#39;s Top News</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/25/tuesdays-top-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 04:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/08/25/tuesdays-top-news/</guid>
      <description>The University of Illinois releases the Obama-Ayers papers tomorrow. Don&amp;rsquo;t expect the MSM to mention it&amp;ndash;unless it&amp;rsquo;s good news for Obama.
Meanwhile, Obama has asked the Department of Justice to block ads that link the Illinois Senator to domestic terrorist William Ayers. Pathetic.
 Obama’s campaign has written the Department of Justice demanding a criminal investigation of the “American Issues Project,” the vehicle through which Dallas investor Harold Simmons is financing the advertisements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Throwing It Away</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/03/08/throwing-it-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 17:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/03/08/throwing-it-away/</guid>
      <description>Roger Kreutz dashed to right a wrong. A tiny wrong, by modern standards, but a wrong nonetheless. &amp;ldquo;Dammit,&amp;rdquo; Roger might have thought, &amp;ldquo;you can&amp;rsquo;t even enjoy a quiet cup of coffee anymore.&amp;rdquo; Then he sprang into action.
Aaron Poisson has a girlfriend and a car. And he&amp;rsquo;s out of high school. That&amp;rsquo;s a liberating combination to a young man. The boundaries of his youth&amp;ndash;walls to many young men aching to break the chains of childhood&amp;ndash;are far behind him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberalism = Terrorism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/03/06/liberalism-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 02:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/03/06/liberalism-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>Now that we&amp;rsquo;re winning the war, the left is ratcheting up its anti-military hatemongering&amp;ndash;all the way to terrorism. If the Congressmen who received the letters knew what was coming, they should taken out and shot, along the perp who did it. Today, leftist terrorists bombed a U. S. Armed Forces recruitment center in New York. This domestic terrorism should be met with lethal force. California Senator Diane Fienstein, in an e-mail, reported that members of the House of Representatives received letters with a photo of the perp and a copy of his political manifesto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crappily Evernafta</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/03/03/crappily-evernafta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 04:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/03/03/crappily-evernafta/</guid>
      <description>Technorati Tags: Rezko,Obama,Fraud,NAFTA,Goolsbee
Something happened on the way to the coronation: the truth hit Barack Obama square in the face.
Noam Scheiber of The New Republic previously dismissed the NAFTA-Canuk story, now admits the story has legs:
 Two things make it problematic for the Obama campaign: 1.) The sudden appearance of this lurid-sounding memo written by a Canadian consular official. I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s particularly revealing&amp;ndash;as I said this morning, it reflects what the Canadians thought they heard from Goolsbee; there are, significantly, no direct quotes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belichick Bad  *UPDATE*</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/02/03/belichick-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 05:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/02/03/belichick-bad/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE 2/4/2008 12:01 a.m.
Yahoo! calls Belichick a &amp;ldquo;sore loser.&amp;rdquo; 
 Because Bill Belichick wanted to go hide when he lost, the field ended up being flooded with people, and the officials had to clear the area before the Giants could take their final snap and make it official. When you lose, you take your loss. You don&amp;rsquo;t leave early because it makes you feel sad inside. Your opponent deserves more respect than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jay Grodner Guilty As Charged</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/01/18/jay-grodner-guilty-as-charged/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2008 03:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/01/18/jay-grodner-guilty-as-charged/</guid>
      <description>This is a heart-warming, uplifting story written eloquently. Jay Grodner, the Chicago lawyer and convicted vote fraud conspirator, was sentenced to probation and to donate to the Semper Fi fund for keying a Marine&amp;rsquo;s car. He keyed the car only because its owner was a Marine. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marine Murder Suspect Spotted</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/01/13/marine-murder-suspect-spotted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 16:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/01/13/marine-murder-suspect-spotted/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE 1:44 PM 1/13/08
Authorities say double murder suspect Cesar Armando Laurean was spotted heading through Louisiana toward Texas. Police are less than 2 hours behind the suspect. From FoxNews.com:
 Marine Cpl. Cesar Armando Laurean was seen getting on or off a Greyhound bus in Shreveport, La., Saturday night, said Shreveport police Chief Henry Whitehorn Sr.
 &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re working with the U.S. Marshal&amp;rsquo;s Service and other law enforcement agencies trying to locate him,&amp;rdquo; Whitehorn told The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**UPDATED 1/12** Help Find Missing Marine</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/01/11/help-find-missing-marine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 00:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/01/11/help-find-missing-marine/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE 1/12/08*
This story is now both depressing and disgusting and disturbing. According to FoxNews, Laurean, the Marine accused of raping Maria Lauterbach, violently killed her and burned her body in his back yard. He crafted a noted claiming Laurean had slit her own throat&amp;ndash;a scenario quickly dismissed by crime scene investigators.
 You&amp;rsquo;ll have to read the rest here. I&amp;rsquo;m too disgusted to keep writing.
 UPDATE 1/11/08*
Lance Cpl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jay Grodner&#39;s Voter Fraud Discipline</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/31/jay-grodners-voter-fraud-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/12/31/jay-grodners-voter-fraud-discipline/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED
Here&amp;rsquo;s the ISC document in PDF:Illinois Supreme Court Document
According to the Illinois Supreme Court web site, Jay R. Grodner, the scumbag who keyed a deploying Marine&amp;rsquo;s car, committed vote fraud resulting in the suspension of his law license in 1984:
Here&amp;rsquo;s highlights from the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s findings:
 The Administrator charged Petersen with forging voter signatures and with actively recruiting Grodner, Presbrey, Weir, and Truemper to assist in this effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Couey, Welcome to Hell</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/24/mr-couey-welcome-to-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2007 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/24/mr-couey-welcome-to-hell/</guid>
      <description>If you were with me in the winter of 2005, you may have read these posts about Jessica Lunsford, a beautiful Florida girl was missing for two weeks before investigators found her body.
3.19.05 Grant Her Peace  3.17.05 Person of Interest in Custody 3.5.05 Update on Missing Florida 9-Year-Old  2.28.05 Jessica Lunsford 
She was sexually assaulted for a week, then buried alive by this evil son of a bitch:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Long, Hot Day in St. Louis</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/16/a-long-hot-day-in-st-louis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2007 02:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/16/a-long-hot-day-in-st-louis/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I heard the news of the murder of a young police officer.
  Officer Norvelle Brown, only 22 years old and a rookie cop, made St. Louis headlines for the second time in his short career&amp;ndash;his short, honorable life. In April, Officer Brown responded to a hostage situation during a barber shop robber, defusing the situation and apprehending the armed robbers. He and another officer received citations for that action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruining Lives For Fun and Profit</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/13/ruining-lives-for-fun-and-profit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 01:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/13/ruining-lives-for-fun-and-profit/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know why this story depresses me so much, but it does. It makes me sad for a lot of people.
FoxNews.com relays a Times of London story of a company that offers to financially, socially, and otherwise ruin people&amp;rsquo;s lives for a meager $20 USD. I won&amp;rsquo;t provide a link to the dreadful site.
 A service offering a complete &amp;ldquo;revenge package&amp;rdquo; in which people can destroy the financial status and relationships of their enemies at the click of a mouse is being offered over the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illegals and Heinous Crime</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/12/illegals-and-heinous-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2007 01:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/08/12/illegals-and-heinous-crime/</guid>
      <description>Everyone who pays attention knows that the most spectacular and sickening murders of late were perpetrated by illegal aliens&amp;ndash;the kind of people to whom Ted Kennedy wishes to give unfettered access to our schools and hospitals.
Mel at aniMel describes two of the crimes, ending with a wonderful summary of the problem of illegal immigration:
 I want to be free. I want my country to be safe. I want to stop reading these sad stories of tragedy that the alien invaders hand us every day while they laugh and say, &amp;ldquo;now give me my civil rights or I&amp;rsquo;ll sue you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grant Her Peace</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/19/grant-her-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2005 01:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/19/grant-her-peace/</guid>
      <description>From FoxNews.com 
 Authorities said that John Evander Couey (search) admitted that he abducted Jessica from her bedroom more than three weeks ago. He also told them the general area where the young girl&amp;rsquo;s body could be found, according to police.
 What could sound more trite than to say, &amp;ldquo;At least they know?&amp;rdquo; As with Laci Peterson&amp;rsquo;s parents and Ron Goldman&amp;rsquo;s father, it&amp;rsquo;s now up to this sweet little girl&amp;rsquo;s daddy and grandparents whether evil prevails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Person of Interest in Custody</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/17/person-of-interest-in-custody/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2005 15:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/17/person-of-interest-in-custody/</guid>
      <description>Fox News reports that the man sought as a &amp;ldquo;person of interest&amp;rdquo; in Jessica Lunsford&amp;rsquo;s disappearance has been taken into custody. He was at the Savannah, Georgia, St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day Parade&amp;ndash;the largest parade in the Southeast. But where is that darling little girl?   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on Missing Florida 9-Year-Old</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/05/update-on-missing-florida-9-year-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2005 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/03/05/update-on-missing-florida-9-year-old/</guid>
      <description>Jessica Lunsford&amp;rsquo;s grandfather, with whom she and her father lived, was arrested 3 times in the 1950s for rape and kidnapping. He told police he was never convicted, but police say that the age of the arrests make it difficult to verify. Here&amp;rsquo;s the story and MSNBC</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessica Lunsford</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/28/jessica-lunsford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2005 04:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2005/02/28/jessica-lunsford/</guid>
      <description>](https://hennessysview.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/08/0_22_lunsford_jessica.jpg)[](https://www.foxnews.com/story/0,2933,148867,00.html)
Anyway, I pray that she is unharmed&amp;ndash;physically and psychologically. Logically, I know the odds are really, really low, but, God, I pray for most naive hope.
And if she&amp;rsquo;s not, I hope the horrible freak who would stoop to visit any harm to such a beautiful little girl meets a fate worse than any psychopathic torture junky could dream up. UPDATE: from FoxNews
 Despite heavy rain and a tornado watch, nearly 540 volunteers turned out to comb the rural community of 2,300 people, about 60 miles north of Tampa (search).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>