<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crime on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/categories/crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crime on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:00:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/categories/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret to a Better Life and Less Political Violence Is Here</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/10/29/this-will-make-your-life-better-no-matter-how-the-elections-turn-out/</guid>
      <description>If you read a lot of business and personal improvement blogs, you know they feed a lot of tips for living a better life. By &amp;ldquo;better&amp;rdquo; they mean making more money, getting a promotion, being more productive, whatever.
Are those things really what makes life better? If so, why do so many successful people burn out? John Belushi, River Phoenix, Amy Winehouse, Janice Joplin, Michael Jackson. Is it show business? Well, look what&amp;rsquo;s happening to Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Pope Francis and Vatican Sec State Admit Viganò&#39;s Testimony?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/03/did-pope-francis-and-vatican-sec-state-admit-viganos-testimony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 12:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/03/did-pope-francis-and-vatican-sec-state-admit-viganos-testimony/</guid>
      <description>One week after Archbishop Carlo Viganò released his bombshell letter, it looks obvious that Pope Francis admits the key allegation: Francis knew McCarrick to be a serial molester, and he returned McCarrick to public ministry anyway. As we&amp;rsquo;ll see later in this post, Pope Francis has a pattern of letting molesters and their protectors off the hook.
Speaks for Itself Did the pope admit to the horrendous allegations directly? Not directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Towey Is Confused</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/01/jim-towey-is-confused/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 18:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/01/jim-towey-is-confused/</guid>
      <description>God bless Jim Towey and the work of his school, Ave Maria University. I am confident that he is confused, and we should pray for clarity.
I&amp;rsquo;m talking about his recent series of letters and clarifications regarding how Catholics should express their obedience to the pope. Jim is partially right and partially off base.
What Jim Towey Gets Right Jim is right that that conservative Catholics need to be very gracious and obedient when they challenge the pope&amp;rsquo;s formal teaching on matters like the death penalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pope Emeritus Benedict Can Settle It All</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/pope-emeritus-benedict-can-settle-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/pope-emeritus-benedict-can-settle-it-all/</guid>
      <description>One man can confirm or deny the central allegation against Pope Francis. The Catholic Church needs that man to step up now.
In an 11-page letter by former US Nuncio (ambassador) Archbishop Carlo Maria Viganò, Pope Francis is accused of ignoring warnings about Cardinal Timothy McCarrick. Viganò claims he personally delivered the warning to Pope Francis in 2013. The pope allegedly ignored the warning and the dossier on McCarrick in 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fisherman&#39;s Other Shoe Just Dropped</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/the-fishermans-other-shoe-just-dropped/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/31/the-fishermans-other-shoe-just-dropped/</guid>
      <description>God, come to our assistance O, Lord, make haste to help us
 Pope Francis ignored evidence of crimes and overturned punishment imposed by Pope Benedict on the wicked and disgraced Cardinal McCarrick. That&amp;rsquo;s according to a former papal nuncio and corroborated by a former first counselor to the nunciature to the United States speaking on the record. The two men have direct knowledge of the matter.
Pope Francis refused to comment on the allegations that he personally covered up McCarrick&amp;rsquo;s crimes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>