<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eric cantor on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/eric-cantor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eric cantor on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 01:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/eric-cantor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Crystal-Clear Images From The Republican Primary De-Cantor</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/15/3-crystal-clear-images-from-the-republican-primary-de-cantor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 01:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2014/06/15/3-crystal-clear-images-from-the-republican-primary-de-cantor/</guid>
      <description>“Shellacked!”
That was the word that stuck out to me.
Eric Cantor, the Republican House Majority Leader led by 34 points according to his pollster. He lost by 10. That’s a shellacking.
Eric Cantor was the first sitting House Majority Leader ever knocked off in a primary. Cantor was also one of Wall Street’s best friends and the embodiment of crony capitalism—the disease eating the heart out of the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric Cantor and the Trojan Rabbit</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/10/eric-cantor-and-the-trojan-rabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 22:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2013/09/10/eric-cantor-and-the-trojan-rabbit/</guid>
      <description>Eric Cantor’s latest tactic in the battle to defund Obamacare reminds me of the Trojan Rabbit in Monty Python and the Holy Grail.
According to Business Insider’s Josh Barro:
 It&amp;rsquo;s a strategy predicated on the idea that Republican activists are stupid. Many of them are stupid. But they&amp;rsquo;re not stupid enough to fall for this.
 (Barro is hard-left, btw.)
From what I can gather, Cantor intends to pass two continuing resolutions out of the House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOP: Knock Off the Symbolic Crap</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/15/gop-knock-off-the-symbolic-crap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/01/15/gop-knock-off-the-symbolic-crap/</guid>
      <description>Just as in 2001, some Republicans are falling for Democrat mind games. In 2001, it was the shared leadership arrangement in the Senate, even thought the GOP had the majority because of the VP tie-break. This year, it’s beginning with “bi-partisan” seating at the State of the Union address.
I have one message for Republicans: Knock it the hell off.
When a Democrat offers to reach across the aisle, with very few exceptions, it’s to poison a Republican.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>