<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>candidates on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/candidates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in candidates on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 21:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/candidates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What You Think You Know About Establishment Candidates Is Probably Wrong</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-you-know-about-establishment-candidates-is-probably-wrong-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/21/what-you-know-about-establishment-candidates-is-probably-wrong-2/</guid>
      <description>I see is all the time. Supporters of Establishment candidates complain that their opponents are establishment, too.
We saw it in the Missouri 2nd District. We see in the GOP Presidential primary. The last refuge of the Establishment’s candidates is to spread the pain of the Establishment label.
What many people don’t get is what the Establishment label actually means. It’s time everyone understood this.
**The Establishment’s candidate is the candidate the Establishment chooses for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obama’s Surging in the Polls; Here’s Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/obamas-surging-in-the-polls-heres-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/20/obamas-surging-in-the-polls-heres-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</guid>
      <description>Don’t bother blaming it on poll questions designed to lead respondents. Never mind that it’s a long way until the election. And stop whining about the White House fudging the numbers on unemployment.
The fact is that Obama’s surging at just the right time. His re-election chances are now above 50 percent. His intrade.com chances of winning are near 60 percent. And he’s raising more money than al of the Republican candidates combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apathy</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/18/apathy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/02/18/apathy-2/</guid>
      <description>The world is a dangerous place to live; not because of the people who are evil, but because of the people who don&amp;rsquo;t do anything about it.
&amp;ndash;Albert Einstein
 It’s easy to blame the subject for our apathy. The candidates are uninspiring; the colors are dull; the task is boring.
Blaming the subject is easy because it relieves us, the objects, of any responsibility. “I can’t make Romney less WASPy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>