<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mizzou on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/mizzou/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mizzou on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 12:44:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/mizzou/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mizzou Protests Were About Abortion All Along</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/mizzou-protests-abortion-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 12:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/23/mizzou-protests-abortion-along/</guid>
      <description>I hate to say &amp;ldquo;I told you so.&amp;rdquo;
But the St. Louis Post Dispatch has found that I may have been right on November 8. That&amp;rsquo;s when I made the outlandish comment that the whole race issue at Mizzou is actually an abortion issue. I suspected that Planned Parenthood&amp;rsquo;s vast lobbyist network is agitating leaders of left-leaning organizations trying to create general unrest.
**The manipulators would use campus racial unrest to demand restored privileges for Planned Parenthood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week: November 15, 2015</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/15/the-week-november-15-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/15/the-week-november-15-2015/</guid>
      <description>Viva la France This week, let&amp;rsquo;s say a special prayer for the people of France. And the whole world.
Mayor Slay About to Change Tune on Refugees On September 11, St. Louis Mayor Francis Slay announced plans to accept 10,000 non-Christian Syrian refugees to St. Louis. After the coordinated attacks by ISIS terrorists in Paris on Friday, expect the mayor come under intense pressure to change plans. News that at least one of the Paris attackers entered France from Serbia as a Syrian war refugee will only intensify the pressure on Slay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paris Attacks Expose The Narcissists of Mizzou</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/14/paris-attacks-expose-the-narcissists-of-mizzou/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 14:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/14/paris-attacks-expose-the-narcissists-of-mizzou/</guid>
      <description>People tell us who they are, but we ignore it. Because we want them to be what we want them to be.
 &amp;ndash;Mad Men
You can&amp;rsquo;t make this stuff up.
Concerned Student 1950, the group that seized public ground for private use at the University of Missouri has a new concern today. It seems the kiddos are upset that ISIS deigned to steal the headlines by killing 120 to 150 people in Paris, wounding 200 others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are abortionists manipulating Mizzou&#39;s black athletes?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/08/are-abortionists-manipulating-mizzous-black-athletes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 18:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2015/11/08/are-abortionists-manipulating-mizzous-black-athletes/</guid>
      <description>A few Mizzou football players announced they&amp;rsquo;re boycotting all sports activities until University of Missouri system president Tim Wolfe quits or is fired. Considering the football team&amp;rsquo;s dismal performance, the cynic in me wonders if sitting out might help the players&amp;rsquo; chances of getting an NFL draft.
The players and other African-American students at Mizzou believe they are victims of &amp;ldquo;systematic oppression&amp;rdquo; and they want Tim Wolfe to fix it simply by resigning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shut Down Labor Studies Now, Governor Nixon</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/26/shut-down-labor-studies-now-governor-nixon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 02:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2011/04/26/shut-down-labor-studies-now-governor-nixon/</guid>
      <description>Governor Nixon:
What does it take to get your attention? What does it take to get you to act?
Your University of Missouri System humiliates this state, and you refuse to act.
Under your nose, the UofM teaches or encourages:
* **[Politically motivated](https://biggovernment.com/publius/2011/04/25/union-official-professor-teach-college-course-in-violent-union-tactics/) violence**** **Politically motivated [industrial sabotage](https://biggovernment.com/publius/2011/04/25/how-to-college-course-on-violent-union-tactics-part-ii-case-studies-edition/)**** **Politically motivated threats of violence and sabotage**** **Supporting and aiding [the enemy in Iraq and Afghanistan](https://biggovernment.com/driehl/2011/04/26/college-course-us-flag-is-racist-how-to-defeat-america-in-iraq-and-afghanistan/)**  You have permit these travesties. You, Jay Nixon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>