<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rosary on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/rosary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rosary on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 08:36:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/rosary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My First St Louis Forever Rosary (Videos)</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-forever-rosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 08:36:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/st-louis-forever-rosary/</guid>
      <description>I kept crying. And the t-shirt I wore was utterly inappropriate.
Last night (July 12), I finally made it to the nightly Rosary by the statue of St. Louis in Forest Park. It was the most fantastic experience. Most amazing.
When I arrived, Fr. Stephen Schumacher was leading about fifty people in chanting Vespers in Latin. Right there in the middle of Forest Park. That uniquely and unmistakably Catholic rite of daily prayer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Prayed at the Statue of St. Louis IX, King of France</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/why-we-prayed-at-statue-of-st-louis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 15:04:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/why-we-prayed-at-statue-of-st-louis/</guid>
      <description>Our purpose in holding this Rosary event at the statue of St. Louis was to satisfy the two greatest commandments: to love God and to love our neighbor as ourselves. To that end, we prayed equally for everyone present at the event:
 For those who attacked us and called us names For those who falsely accused us of being in the KKK For those on both sides of the issues who came to provoke the other side For those police officers who donned riot gear on a hot, humid day to keep us all safe For those who came out to pray  For all of them, we prayed to God that He softens our hearts and fills our souls with gifts of the Holy Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>