<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newsweek on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/newsweek/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newsweek on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/newsweek/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Here’s My Electoral Map Prediction</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2012/11/05/heres-my-electoral-map-prediction/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I’m feeling a wave toward Romney.

My gut tells me this year is a lot like 1980.
1980 Was A Dead Heat
The final Gallup poll that year had a dead heat. Time Magazine’s November 3, 1980, called the race a dead heat. So did Newsweek.
The press was hoping John B. Anderson, a former Republican Congressman running for president as an independent, would siphon votes from Reagan. He did siphon votes from Reagan, but not nearly enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsweek:  Obama Fading</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/12/newsweek-obama-fading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 00:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2008/07/12/newsweek-obama-fading/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s poll lead over John McCain has plummeted from 51-35 to a statistical dead-heat in less than a month.
Obama&amp;rsquo;s downward spiral has Newsweek&amp;rsquo;s headline writers asking if his glow is fading. The polls finds that more than half of voters consider Obama lying opportunist who will take any position for votes.
 Obama&amp;rsquo;s rapid drop comes at a strategically challenging moment for the Democratic candidate. Having vanquished Hillary Clinton in early June, Obama quickly went about repositioning himself for a general-election audience&amp;ndash;an unpleasant task for any nominee emerging from the pander-heavy primary contests and particularly for a candidate who&amp;rsquo;d slogged through a vigorous primary challenge in most every contest from January until June.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe We Need a Lazy President</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2007/09/03/maybe-we-need-a-lazy-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2007 13:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2007/09/03/maybe-we-need-a-lazy-president/</guid>
      <description>The MSM are tripping over themselves to publish stories about Fred Thompson&amp;rsquo;s supposed laziness. Newsweek decided to make the accusation head on (from CNN.com):
 [A]s he prepares to formally begin his campaign for the White House this week, after months of &amp;ldquo;testing the waters,&amp;rdquo; the conventional wisdom in Washington is that Thompson doesn&amp;rsquo;t want it badly enough, isn&amp;rsquo;t willing to work hard enough-put bluntly, that he is lazy. Newsweek: Grin and Bear It</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>