<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faith on Hennessy&#39;s View</title>
    <link>https://hennessysview.com/tags/faith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faith on Hennessy&#39;s View</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2000-2020, Bill Hennessy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 13:28:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hennessysview.com/tags/faith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;ve Never Been Closer to Totalitarianism</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/30/weve-never-been-closer-to-totalitarianism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 13:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/09/30/weve-never-been-closer-to-totalitarianism/</guid>
      <description>Very scary thought: If the Democrats take over the House and Senate in January, they could impeach both Trump and Pence and try them in the Senate at the same time making Nancy Pelosi president.
You&amp;rsquo;ve Never Lived in a Time Like This One I&amp;rsquo;m almost old enough to remember the Democrat National Convention of 1968. Almost. What a show. Hippies and Yippies marching, tear gas, Mayor Daley, Buckley threatening to punch Gore Vidal on live TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Do You Stay?</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/26/why-do-you-stay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 17:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/26/why-do-you-stay/</guid>
      <description>Why do you stay a Catholic?
Today&amp;rsquo;s Gospel reading comes from John 6. John chapter 6 is all about the bread of life. In it, Jesus shocks his Jewish followers by announcing that they must eat his flesh and drink his blood to achieve eternal life.
When some of his disciples challenged this formula for immortality, Jesus doubled down, saying:
 Truly, truly, I say to you, unless you eat the flesh of the Son of man and drink his blood, you have no life in you; he who eats my flesh and drinks my blood has eternal life, and I will raise him up at the last day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bishop Does the Right Thing and the Post-Dispatch Deceives You</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/24/a-bishop-does-the-right-thing-and-the-post-dispatch-deceives-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 14:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/24/a-bishop-does-the-right-thing-and-the-post-dispatch-deceives-you/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Friday, and our archbishop in St. Louis has done a great thing. (Maybe today would be a good time to thank a priest. Give him encouragement.) But the town blog used deception to report the story.
Archbishop Robert Carlson of St. Louis asked Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Attorney General, Josh Hawley, to review all of the archdiocese&amp;rsquo;s records regarding abuse cases. Hawley agreed to the Archbishop&amp;rsquo;s request.
Archbishop Carlson deserves our praise and respect for his openness and honesty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crawling Back to Happiness and Freedom</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/08/crawling-back-to-happiness-and-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 04:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/08/08/crawling-back-to-happiness-and-freedom/</guid>
      <description>Happiness Did you know that the word &amp;ldquo;happiness&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;blessed?&amp;rdquo;
Neither did I. But when I heard this on EWTN Radio the other day, I remembered there are two translations of the Beatitudes. One version goes with &amp;ldquo;Blessed are . . .&amp;rdquo; and the other with &amp;ldquo;Happy are . . . .&amp;rdquo; So, I guess it&amp;rsquo;s true. The words are interchangeable.
Happiness, then, doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean walking around in some lithium-induced state of bliss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Know a Saint</title>
      <link>https://hennessysview.com/2018/06/02/i-know-a-saint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 14:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hennessysview.com/2018/06/02/i-know-a-saint/</guid>
      <description>My mom and dad have two anniversaries. One anniversary celebrates the day my uncle Bob drove them to Hot Springs, Arkansas to elope. The other celebrates the day about a week later when, having learned of their civil nuptials, my grandfather ordered them to go see Father English and set themselves right with the church.
Like father, like son, I guess. Except, the kid&amp;rsquo;s a lot slower. Fifteen years slower.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>